<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Mmm, gentlemen, I put it to you, the worst tapioca pudding is better than the best pudding of any other flavour.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>First off, that is axiomatically wrong, because the best pudding is chocolate. Secondly, the organic structure of tapioca makes it a jiggling bowl of potential death. It is extracted from the plant…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Hey, I’m thinking of growing a mustache.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Ah, no kidding! A Fu Man Chu? A handlebar pencil?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It is extracted from the plant…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’m not sure yet. You know, George Clooney has one now!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Really? I once saw him shopping at Ralph’s. He was buying tequila.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, you’d think a guy like that would have some kind of booze lackey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Alright this is cruel, we better let him finish before his head explodes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Alright Sheldon, why is tapioca…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Tapioca is extracted from the root of the plant Manihot Esculenta. Due to a high concentration of cyanide it is poisonous in its raw form and lethal if prepared improperly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Feel better now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It is also indigenous to Brazil, as is the Cocoa Bean, from which we get chocolate, the best pudding. And you promised you wouldn’t do that anymore!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Kripke (arriving)</speaker><content>Hey Hofstadter!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey Kripke.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>Heard about your watest pwoton decay expewiment, twenty thousand data wuns and no statistically significant wesults. Vewy impwessive!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What a jerk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Don’t feel bad Leonard, negative results are still results.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Even twenty thousand of ’em.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Alright, please don’t cheer me up anymore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-21"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>C’mon, don’t let him get to you. It’s Kripke.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-22"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yeah, he’s a ginormous knob.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-23"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>That’s why he eats by himself, instead of sitting here at the cool table.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-24"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Fo’ shizzle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-25"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hey it’s true, Kripke lacks the basic social skills that we take for granted, but he also controls the new open science grid computer that I need to use to run some simulations of structure formation in the early universe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-26"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Good luck getting time on it. The only people he lets use it are his friends.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-27"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well then, the solution is simple. I shall befriend him. Kripke!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-28"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>Yeah?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-29"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What’d you say of the idea of you and I becoming friends?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-30"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>I would say, I have no intewest in becoming your fwiend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-31"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Really? That seems rather short sighted, coming from someone who is generally considered altogether unlikable. Why don’t you take some time to reconsider?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-32"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>Yeah, I’ll do that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-33"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well I think we’re off to a terrific start.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>There you go. Now any e-mail from Wolowitz will go right into your spam folder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Thanks! I mean the e-mail doesn’t bother me as much as the vacation pictures of him in a bathing suit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, I got the same one. And that’s not a bathing suit, it’s a tan line.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Sheldon (on phone)</speaker><content>Hello. This is Sheldon Cooper. I’m leaving a message for Barry Kripke. Barry, It was pleasant seeing you today in the cafeteria. I saw that you purchased the chef’s salad. Apparently, you did not know that the chef’s salad is kitchen trickery, to utilize scrap meat. Nevertheless, I hope you enjoyed it. I’m following up on our pending friendship, and I look forward to hearing from you regarding its status. Sheldon Cooper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What’s up with Ichabod?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh he’s trying to make a new friend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh really? Well, good for him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, unless he’s makes one out of wood like Gepetto, I don’t think it’s gonna happen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, how did you guys become friends?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>There was a flier on the bulletin board at the university. Roommate wanted. Whistlers need not apply.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>And you moved in anyway?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I assumed he was joking. You’d be surprised how many particle physicists have a whimsical side.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, what about Howard and Raj, I mean how did you become friends with them?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t know, how do carbon atoms form a benzene ring? Proximity and valence electrons.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well yeah, sure. When you put it that way. But it all worked out, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I suppose. I do miss whistling though.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh come on, really? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>First warning.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Sheldon (Knock, knock, knock) </speaker><content>Penny   Penny   Penny.This is for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hello Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What is this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It’s a questionnaire I devised. I’m having some difficulty bonding with a colleague at work, so I’m doing a little research to better understand why my current friends like me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yes. Well, that is a good question. But is this really the best way to figure it out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, I agree, the social sciences are largely hokum. But, short of putting electrodes in your brain and monitoring your response to my companionship, this is the best I can do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, question 1. Rank the following aspects of Sheldon Cooper in order of appeal. Intelligence. Ruthless attention to hygiene. Playfulness. Java applet writing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I know, I may have started off with a fairly obvious one. You did an aspect of my most appealing trait, playfulness. Why don’t you just go ahead and write that number 1. I’m afraid you’re on your own for the rest. It should take you no more than 3 hours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Wait! How many questions are on this thing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Only 211. Don’t worry, in deference to you, I’ve kept them on a high school graduate reading level.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Thanks pal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You got it, buddy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sheldon honey, did you ever consider making friends by being, I don’t know, pleasant?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well that’s certainly a thought-provoking hypothesis. May I suggest it as the topic for your essay.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Your questionnaire, very disappointing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I answered every question Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You answered the multiple choice questions in a pattern. A B B A C. A B B A C.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Aw, you picked up on that huh?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>How could I not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Come on! There’s over 200 questions. And look at some of these things. Sheldon is to camaraderie, as the space shuttle is to blank?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>There are a number of acceptable answers, for example, C: near earth transport, but certainly not B: avocado rancher. And your essay, suggesting that I’d have better luck making friends if I wait ’til the Cylons take over? Please.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hold on. I put some real work into that!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes, well it’s better than what Wolowitz did. He drew a raccoon with what appears to be, a distended scrotum.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It’s kinda cute, until you get to the scrotum.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What hope do I have for establishing new relationships given that my current friends apparently cannot take a few hours out of their lives to help me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, I’m not going to defend a big-balled raccoon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I don’t see how you could.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What I’m trying to say is that, maybe you can’t approach this as a purely intellectual exercise.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What do you mean!?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, remember when you tried to learn how to swim using the internet?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I did learn how to swim.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>On the floor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>The skills are transferrable. I just have no interest in going in the water.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Then why learn how to swim?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>The ice caps are melting Leonard. In the future, swimming isn’t going to be optional. But you do bring up an interesting point. I don’t have to break new ground here, I’m sure much of the research already exists.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-22"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No! no, my point is, if you want to learn how to make friends, then just go out to a coffee shop or a museum. Meet people. Talk to them. Take an interest in their lives.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s insane on the face of it. Come on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-24"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Where are we going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-25"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You’re driving me to the mall. I’m going to acquire a book that summarizes the current theories in the field of friendmaking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-26"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Why don’t you just lie down on the floor and swim there?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Coping with the death of a loved one. My condolences.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Woman in queue</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Family or friend?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Woman</speaker><content>Family.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Too bad. If it’d been a friend, I’m available to fill the void.  It’s just as well, she smelled like moth balls.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, if you’re gonna start sniffing people, I’m gonna go get a hot pretzel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Excuse me. Do you have any books about making friends?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Bookstore employee</speaker><content>Um, yeah but they’re all for little kids.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I assume the skills can be extrapolated and transferred.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Employee</speaker><content>Uh, I guess. They’re right over there by the wooden train set.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh! I love trains!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Employee</speaker><content>I bet you do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Sheldon (picks up train)</speaker><content>Oh my! That’s awfully sticky. Alright, let’s see. Bernie Bunny has Two Daddies Now. It’s probably about homosexual rabbits. Jerry the Gerbil and the Bullies on the Bus. Read it, not helpful. Oh! Here we go. Stu the Cockatoo is New at the Zoo. Author Sarah Carpenter lives in Fort Wayne, Indiana, with her husband and best friend Mark, and their cockatoos too. Hardly makes her an expert in making friends, wouldn’t you agree?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Little girl</speaker><content>I don’t like birds, they scare me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Me too! Most people don’t see it. What are you reading?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>Girl</speaker><content>Curious George.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh I do like monkeys!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-18"><speaker>Girl</speaker><content>Curious George is a monkey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Somewhat anthropomorphized but yes. Say, maybe sometime you and I can go see monkeys together. Would you like that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-20"><speaker>Girl</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, what are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m making friends with this little girl. What’s your name?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-23"><speaker>Girl</speaker><content>Rebecca.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-24"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hi Rebecca, I’m your new friend, Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-25"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No you’re not, let’s go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-26"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>We were really hitting it off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-27"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Don’t look up, there’s cameras.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I’m curious. In the “How Well Do You Know Sheldon” section, what do you put for his favourite amino acid?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Leonard and Howard</speaker><content>Lysine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Damn it. I had Lysine and changed it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh good! You’re just in time. I believe I’ve isolated the algorithm for making friends.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, there is no algorithm for making friends!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Hear him out. If he’s really on to something, we can open a booth at Comic-Con, make a fortune.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>See, my initial approach to Kripke, had the same deficiencies as those that plagued Stu the Cockatoo, when he was new at the zoo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Stu the cockatoo?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yes, he’s new at the zoo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It’s a terrific book. I’ve distilled its essence into a simple flowchart that would guide me through the process.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Have you thought about putting him in a crate while you’re out of the apartment?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Sheldon (on phone)</speaker><content>Hello, Kripke. Yes, Sheldon Cooper here. It occurred to me you hadn’t returned any of my calls because I hadn’t offered any concrete suggestions for pursuing our friendship. Perhaps the two of us might share a meal together… I see. Well then perhaps you’d have time for a hot beverage. Popular choices include tea, coffee, cocoa… I see. No, no, no, wait. Don’t hang up yet. What about a recreational activity? I bet we share some common interests. Tell me an interest of yours. Really? On actual horses? Tell me another interest of yours. Oh no, I’m sorry, I have no desire to get in the water until I absolutely have to. Tell me another interest of yours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh-oh, he’s stuck in an infinite loop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I can fix it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Mmhmm. Mmhmm. It’s interesting. But isn’t ventriloquism, by definition, a solo activity? Yeah? Tell me another interest of yours. Hmmm. Is there any chance you like monkeys? What is wrong with you? Everybody likes monkeys. Hang on, Kripke.  A loop counter? And an escape to the least objectionable activity! Howard, that’s brilliant! I’m surprised you saw that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Gee. Why can’t Sheldon make friends?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Alright Kripke, that last interest strikes me as the least objectionable and I would like to propose that we do that together. Tomorrow. Yes, I’ll pay. Alright, goodbye. Alright! Time to learn rock climbing.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You know, I am a fan of ventriloquism. Maybe you, me and your dummy could go get a hot beverage. He could talk while you drink.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>Nope, I wanna climb some wocks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>This appears significantly more monolithic than it did on my laptop. No, one expects to see Hominids learning to use bones as weapeons.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>You afwaid of heights, Cooper?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hardly. Fear of heights is illogical. Fear of falling, on the other hand, is prudent and evolutionary. What would you say is the minimum altitude I need to achieve to cement our new-found friendship?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>Come on, they have birthday parties here. Wittle kids climb this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Little kid Hominids, perhaps.  Is this your entire job? Your parents must be so proud.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>Let’s go, Cooper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Coming, Kripke. Okay. Harness seems to be secure. Small amount of incontinence just now, but the website said that’s to be expected. Hey, this isn’t so bad. A bit like vertical swimming.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>Hey, look at you, Cooper. You’re almost halfway to the top.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I am? I was wrong. It IS a fear of heights.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Not really. I feel somewhat like an inverse tangent function that’s approaching an asymptote.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>Are you saying you’re stuck?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What part of an inverse tangent function approaching an asymptote did you not understand?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>Understood all that. I’m not a mowon. Just keep going.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, I don’t think I can.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>Well, then. Cwimb back down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, that doesn’t seem any more likely.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>So what’s the pwan, Cooper?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, it’s not exactly a plan but I think I’m going to pass out.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m sorry. Can we please just do it one more time?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Okay. 1, 2, 1, 2, 3 and… </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It’s a little thing but you really do miss it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hello, everyone. I brought my new friend, Barry Kripke, home for dinner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Together</speaker><content>Oh…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>Hewo to you, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>How was rock climbing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>He passed out. Just hung there like a big sawami.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>D-d-d! That’s where I sit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>Ooh, you have a special spot. What kind of wacko are you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>How much time you got?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Want some Chinese food?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>Tewific. Got any dental fwoss?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>In the bathroom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>Be right back. I gotta fwoss the Indian food out of my teeth if I’m gonna eat Chinese.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sheldon, are you okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh yes, I pass out all the time. But, it was worth it. I’ve made substantial progress in bonding with Kripke, which brings me to an awkward moment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What’s that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Maintaining five friendships promises to be a Herculean task. So, I’m going to have to let one of you go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-20"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Me, me. Let it be me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Leonard, you are my roommate, my source of transportation and you help me fold my sheets when they come out of the dryer. You are safe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-22"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Can I whistle?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Don’t be silly. Howard, you do not have a PhD, your cologne is an assault on the senses and you’re not available for video games during the Jewish high holidays.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-24"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Guilty as charged. I’m out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-25"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No. You, too, are safe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-26"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh come on. What do I have to do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-27"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay. You know what? I see where this is going. I’m not one of you guys. I’m not a scientist. So just…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-28"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Penny, Penny, Penny. Everything you’re saying is true, but please allow me to continue. Raj, you’re out. The good question, while you do provide a certain cultural diversity to an otherwise homogenous group, your responses to the questionnaire were truly disturbing. How could you, for a moment, think that my favourite amino acid is Glutamine?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-29"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>He had Lysine but changed it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-30"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah. Shoulda, woulda coulda, Raj.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-31"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>I like to fwoss before I eat, so my gum pockets are open for new food.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-32"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Eww.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-33"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>Hewo. How did I walk past you? I’m Bawy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-34"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Penny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-35"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>Yeah, it’s not a vewy hot name. I’m gonna call your Woxanne. Ooh, pot stickers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-36"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Suddenly I’m looking pretty good, huh?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-37"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>So uh, Kripke, I was wondering if there’s any chance you could get me some time on the open science grid computer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-38"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-39"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No? But we’re friends!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-40"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>I’m sowy. No, my fwiend?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-41"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m confused. I was given an understanding that you allow your friends time on the machine?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-42"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>No, that’s wong. There’s an official schedule. I have no contwol over it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-43"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh. This entire endeavour seems to have been an exercise in futility. Raj, you’re back in. He likes monkeys.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You gotta give him credit for sticking with it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I didn’t think he had it in him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>He almost made it to the top this time.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>