<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Wow, Sheldon, I cannot believe you made up your own game.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, Research Lab is more than a game. It’s like the slogan says, the physics is theoretical, but the fun is real.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>We must not be playing it right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>All right, five. One, two, three, four, five. Oh, wow, look at that, my Department of Defence research grant is renewed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh! Great roll! Now you can demolish your Soviet-style cyclotron and build the large Hadron Collider.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You’re a natural at this, Penny. And as the first beta testers, you two’ll have quite the edge when we play with Wolowitz and Koothrappali on Sunday.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, gee, Sheldon, I don’t think we can play on Sunday.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Why not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Because of the reasons that Penny will now tell you. Penny?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Actually, I have to pick up my friend Justin from the airport.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>There you go, she has to pick up her friend Justin at the airport, aAnd I can’t play ’cause I’m going with her, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Um, yeah, if you want. I mean, there may not be room. He’s got a lot of stuff, like guitars and amplifiers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Wait. What are you talking about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>My friend, Justin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Pay attention, Leonard. That’s why she can’t play on Sunday.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Who is this Justin?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Your turn, Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I told you about him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, you didn’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Roll the dice, Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-22"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, my friend from Omaha, plays the guitar. Anyway, he’s coming to L.A. looking for some session work, so I told him he could just crash on my couch for a few weeks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Come on, Leonard, if you roll a six, Penny dies horribly in a nuclear meltdown. See what I mean when I say the fun is real?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-24"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hang on. Some guy is going to be sleeping on your couch?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-25"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>He’s not some guy. He’s my friend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-26"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>So by friend, do you mean friend friend, gay friend, or ex boyfriend who you’re now platonic with but still might have a thing for you friend”?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-27"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, he’s definitely not gay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-28"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, a definitely not gay musician sleeping on my girlfriend’s couch. Yippee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-29"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, we went out a little bit, a long time ago, but we were never like going out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-30"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, not to be pedantic, but the last I checked went out was in fact the past tense of going out, which I think we all know is a popular euphemism for saw each other naked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-31"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’ll just roll for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-32"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Do you have a problem with Justin staying with me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-33"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What was your first clue?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-34"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Uh-oh! Industrial accident.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-35"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You know what? Don’t talk to me like I’m an idiot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-36"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m not talking to you like you’re an idiot! I’m saying the whole idea is idiotic!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-37"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You accidentally stare at a helium-argon laser. Lose one turn and a retina.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-38"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>How is that not talking to me like I’m an idiot? It’s my friend, it’s my couch, and it’s my freakin’ life!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-39"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It’s also your roll.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-40"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You know what? It is your life. If you want to have some stupid guitarist stay on your couch, then fine. Why don’t you just rent some bunk beds and invite The Black Eyed Peas?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-41"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey, if I want to invite the entire line up of Lollapalooza to sleep in my apartment, I will, and it’s none of your business!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-42"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Are you listening to yourself? Do you know how childish you sound right now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-43"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, now I’m a child? Well, at least I’m not an idiot anymore!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-44"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>The two aren’t mutually exclusive!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-45"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, you are such a…  What the hell is he doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-46"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>He’s drowning us out. He doesn’t like fighting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-47"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sheldon, just stop, look, the fight is over. Oh, and FYI, you never even heard of The Black Eyed Peas until you met me!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-48"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I heard of ’em. Didn’t know they were a band. Sheldon, she’s gone. You can turn off the blender.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-49"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Has your relationship reached its inevitable ugly end?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-50"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, we just had a little spat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-51"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Look on the bright side. As the result of Penny’s forfeit, you have become the world’s first winner of Research Lab. Would you like a commemorative snow cone?</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t get how she can just announce that an old boyfriend is going to be sleeping on her couch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hey, I thought of a game we can play in the car.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t want to play a game, Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It’s called Scientists. Now, I will name three scientists, then you will put them in order of the size of their contribution to their respective fields. To make this game even more compelling, you must consider only the contribution of the man to the field, not the validity of the field itself. For example, Abu Musa Jabir ibn Hayn made a greater contribution to the discredited field of alchemy than Halbert Vanderplatt made to neurobiology. Okay, ready to have some fun?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>An old boyfriend who’s definitely not gay. That’s what a guy likes to hear, definitely.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right, I’ll start with an easy one, um, Isaac Newton, Madame Curie and Niels Bohr.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>And then I say one little thing and I end up being the bad guy!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hint, Madame Curie had her husband to help her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What am I supposed to say? Sure, Penny, I’m cool with your old boyfriend sleeping in your apartment. Well, Leonard, it doesn’t matter if you’re cool or not because I’m Penny and I’m pretty and I can do whatever the hell I want! Oh, I get it! You think you’re doing me a favour just by being in a relationship with me! No, no, Leonard! I’m doing you a favour just by being in the same room as you!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Leonard! Stop the car!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I can’t listen to the two of you fight anymore.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Come on, come on, we’re late.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Calm down, we’ll make the movie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I believe my alarm is appropriate, given the situation. The movie starts in 17 minutes, which means we’ll need to make all the lights on Colorado Boulevard, plus skip the concession stand, and preshow urination.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, dude, I wish you had said something before I pounded that last Red Bull.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Go, go, Power Rangers, go!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey. We’re, uh, going to the movies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, we’re not. We’re standing in the hallway, suffering through an awkward encounter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hang on. They’re showing a new digital print of Time Bandits, you wouldn’t want to come, would you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Not really, no.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right, invitation pointlessly offered, invitation declined as expected, everyone’s civil, nobody’s fighting. Have a nice evening.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Just give us a minute.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, take all the time you need.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>So, are we going to talk about last night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Are you ready to apologize?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>E-e-e-e-eh! Wrong answer, but thank you for playing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, come on. This is stupid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, there it is again! You think I’m stupid!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, there’s a difference between being stupid and acting stupid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-21"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, yeah? well, there’s a difference between being a jerk and being an ass!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-22"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, there isn’t! They’re synonyms!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-23"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Well, that was rather unpleasant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-24"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, I don’t think I need my preshow urination anymore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-25"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Leonard, when that woman moved in three years ago I told you not to talk to her, and now look, we’re going to be late for the movies.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Hey! Look! Amazing Spider-Man 183.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Got it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Remember this one? Spider-Man loses a big fight and then his girlfriend breaks up with him. Want me to get it for you? It’ll help take your mind off things.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Hey, guys. What’s going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, we need to kill a couple hours till the next showing of Time Bandits.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Oh, well, no problem. I was thinking of closing early and going home, but let’s face it, that’s just a slightly smaller lonely room filled with comic books.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Thanks, Stuart. Let me ask you something. Do you think it’s okay for Penny to have an ex-boyfriend sleep on her couch?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No, I mean, she’s obviously way out of line.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Thank you!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>But if she dumps you, she’ll have a new boyfriend by tomorrow morning and you’ll have a new girlfriend when you figure out how to build one. So the only question is, how long until you fold?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I am not going to fold.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Well, excuse me, I don’t think Penny’s out of line at all. You don’t own her. It’s like my girl, Beyonce says, if you like it, you shoulda put a ring on it.”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Come on. At the very least, when she found out Leonard was upset about it, she should’ve backed off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You mean like when a guy’s upset because his friend agreed to take a cooking class with him and then doesn’t show up because he’s doing a juice fast with his mother?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I didn’t know you were upset about that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Really! Did you miss all the subtle indicators, like me saying, Howard, I am upset.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Okay, sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Maybe it means something different in this country. Back in India, it means you’re upset with a guy named Howard!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I said I’m sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-20"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Sorry doesn’t make up for the fact that I had to make chicken and rice with this vegan guy. Do you know what vegan chicken and rice is? Rice!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-21"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, well, you think I was having fun, sitting around all night listening to my mother say “Have you ever peed so much in your life?”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-22"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, my God, you are such a mama’s boy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-23"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Hey, don’t bring my mother into this!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-24"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You brought your mother into this!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-25"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Stop it, both of you. All this fighting, I might as well be back with my parents! Damn it, George, I told you if you didn’t quit drinkin’ I’d leave you! Well, I guess that makes you a liar, ’cause I’m drunk as hell and you’re still here! Stop yelling! You’re making Sheldon cry! I’ll tell you what’s making Sheldon cry! That I let you name him Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-26"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Boy, what got him so upset?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-27"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, sure, you can tell when Sheldon’s upset.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, thank you very much. Come back soon. With the other half of my tip. Hey, Sheldon, what are you doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>This is a restaurant. It’s lunchtime. I would think, as a waitress, you’d be familiar with the paradigm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Is Leonard coming?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, I believe Leonard is waiting for you to come crawling back to him and apologize.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, that’s not gonna happen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I assumed that would be your attitude. Hence, my true purpose in coming here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Which is?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I want you to crawl back to him and apologize.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I’m busy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Excuse me, miss. I’d like to order lunch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Fine. What do you want?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I have a few questions. First, I notice that you offer soup and a half-sandwich?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Where exactly does the half-sandwich come from? Are you giving me half of someone else’s sandwich, or do I have to wait for someone else in the restaurant to order the other half?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, no, Sheldon, they just make a half-sandwich.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You can’t make a half-sandwich. If it’s not half of a whole sandwich, it’s just a small sandwich.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, fine, it’s soup and a small sandwich. Is that what you want?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Of course not. I’ll have my usual.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-19"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Aren’t you going to ask me if I want a beverage?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-21"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Don’t you usually get lemonade?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-23"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Do you want lemonade?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-24"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-25"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Anything else?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-26"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes, I want you to apologize to Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-27"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I am not going to apologize. I’ve done nothing wrong. He is completely overreacting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-28"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Irrelevant. The disruption in your relationship is making my life intolerable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-29"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, I’m sorry, Sheldon, but this really isn’t about you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-30"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I don’t follow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-31"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, yeah, I’ll be right there. Look, Sheldon, I have to go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-32"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right, let’s assume, ad argumentum, that in this case, Leonard is wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-33"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Leonard is wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-34"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Considering the number of transgressions you’ve committed that he’s overlooked, don’t you think that, just this once, you could return the favour?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-35"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I’m coming. Goodbye, Sheldon. What do you mean, transgressions I’ve committed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-36"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Were you under the impression that Leonard has no complaints about you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-37"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Like what? Yeah, yeah, I see you, you’re making a little cheque sign in the air, I got it, just hold your horses. What does Leonard complain about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-38"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Your driving, the plethora of stuffed animals on your bed that stare at him during your amorous activities, your constant tardiness, your singing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-39"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>My singing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-40"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s actually from my list, but Leonard would be a fool if he didn’t agree with it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-41"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, if Leonard has so many problems with me, why hasn’t he just said so?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-42"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Because, according to him, you’re oversensitive and have a temper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-43"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, really? Well, then, do me a favour and tell Leonard that he can drop dead!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-44"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And she wonders why she’s constantly undertipped.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, good, you’re home. I need you to do me a favour.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Go apologize to Penny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Right now would be good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Penny (knocking)</speaker><content>Leonard!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Although, a few minutes ago would have been better.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I hear you don’t like my stuffed animals, my driving or my punctuality.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What? Who would tell you something like that? Why would you tell her something like that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>It doesn’t matter why he told me. It’s true, isn’t it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, yeah, it’s true, but I can live with that stuff. What I can’t live with is you casually informing me that some guy’s going to be staying in your apartment without even asking me first!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>That isn’t even your problem, the problem is you don’t trust me!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, come on. Sheldon, have you ever once heard me say that I don’t trust Penny? Sheldon? Where did he go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, your yelling must have freaked him out again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Where are you going? You just walk away in the middle of an argument?!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, I’m going to go find your damn roommate before he hurts himself trying to cross the street or something!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Why didn’t you say so?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-19"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, now I need your permission for that, too?!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, I can’t read your mind, Penny!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-21"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Really? Why not? You’re so smart, and I’m so dumb!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content> Raj.  Raj.  Raj.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Stop knocking! It’s open! Please tell my parents that our dark matter research is at a critical juncture, and I can’t come home for my cousin Sanjay’s wedding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Mrs Koothrappali</speaker><content>Sheldon, ask our son what we’re supposed to say to Mr. and Mrs. Choudhry, whose daughter, Lakshmi is flying in from London, for the sole purpose of meeting him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I didn’t ask you to set me up with Lakshmi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Mrs Koothrappali</speaker><content>You should be thanking us!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Dr Koothrappali</speaker><content>Yes, Lakshmi just got her stomach stapled. You have an opportunity to get in good with her before she loses weight, and her self-esteem goes up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I don’t care! And why don’t you think I can find a woman for myself?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Mrs Koothrappali</speaker><content>Because you’re 27, and the closest thing we have to a daughter-in-law is that Jewish boy Howard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, that is completely below the belt. Sheldon, tell my parents that Howard and I are just friends. Sheldon? Howard and I are just friends! Fine. I’ll come home for Sanjay’s wedding.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Penny (out of the window)</speaker><content>Sheldon! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What are you doing? He’s not a lost dog.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey, why don’t you just let me find him while you sit there hitting your imaginary brake?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>The brake might be imaginary, but that stop sign you just ran wasn’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What stop sign?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Eyes on the road. Eyes on the road!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Howard’s Mother</speaker><content>Howard, answer the door! I’m busy!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’m busy too, you answer it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Howard’s Mother</speaker><content>I can’t! I’m on the toilet!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>For God’s sake, I don’t need to hear that! Can’t you just say, I’m busy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Howard’s Mother</speaker><content>I said I’m busy, but that wasn’t good enough for you!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You know what? I hope it’s one of those home invasion deals, and they shoot me in the head.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Howard’s Mother</speaker><content>Well, if it’s a home invader, don’t tell them I’m on the toilet!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>There’s no one there. You’re hearing things, you crazy old lady!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey, Stuart, have you seen Sheldon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Yeah, he’s, uh, over in the graphic novel section. Built himself a little nest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Uh, Penny?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Is everything okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What do you mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Uh, Sheldon told me you and Leonard were having a fight?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, yeah, kind of. It’s, it’s no big thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Oh, good, good.  I love you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m not leaving until you talk to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>All right, what’s going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It’s a little hard to explain. He does this thing where he pretends he’s in an alternate dimension that occupies the same physical space we’re in, but he can’t perceive us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Don’t flatter yourself. I’m just ignoring you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Come on, Sheldon, let’s go home. Look, we’re done fighting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’ve heard that before, but then, the next thing you know I’m hiding in my bedroom, blaring a Richard Feinman lecture while my mom is shouting that Jesus would forgive her if she put ground glass in my dad’s meatloaf, and my dad’s on the roof skeet-shooting her Franklin Mint collectible plates.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, there’s going to no more shouting and no skeet-shooting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Really? Where’s your friend Justin going to sleep?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, where’s he gonna sleep?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-20"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, my God, would you let this go?!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-21"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>I’d let it go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-22"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Why should I let it go? Why don’t you just tell the guy to find another place to sleep?  Oh, for God’s sakes. So, you have childhood issues, we all have childhood issues, at some point, you just need to grow up and get past them. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-23"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Leonard, will you just let me handle this, please? Look, let’s just… Sheldon, please,</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-24"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Always is a long time. Sure. Always.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-25"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You know, how about we buy you this robot, and then we all go home?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-26"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I want that one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-27"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, you can have that one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-28"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, come on, he’s just going to play with it twice, and then it’ll end up in his closet with all the other junk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-29"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Buy him the robot, Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-30"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Can I get this comic book, too?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-31"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yes, you can.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-32"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>We meet again.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>So what did Justin say when you told him he couldn’t sleep on your couch?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>He’s a musician. He’ll sleep in his own vomit, if he has to.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I should have asked for much more than a comic book and a robot.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>