<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Will you please turn your shirt off?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>What? I’m giving myself dramatic entrance music. People will know I’m awesome and to be feared.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, right, there’s nothing more awesome and frightening than a man who’s got music blasting from between his nipples.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey, Stuart, what’s going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Well, you might want to mark your Google calendars. Stan Lee is coming to do a signing on Thursday.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Did he finally write a sequel to his autobiography? I’m sure ages 79 through 87 were just action-packed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>No, just a regular comic signing. My uncle is his dermatologist and Stan’s doing him a favour.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, I don’t want to know that! How can I possibly discuss with Stan Lee the scientific foundations for interstellar flight on a silver surfboard when part of my brain will be scanning his face for signs of contagious skin disease?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Stan Lee does not have a contagious skin disease.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, look who thinks he’s Stuart’s uncle now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Can’t believe it. We’re going to meet Stan Lee! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’m sad to say I taught him those moves.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I can’t decide whether I want Stan Lee to autograph my Journey into Mystery 83, first appearance of Thor or my Fantastic Four number five, first appearance of Dr. Doom.  Alex, I’m going to go with what is… you’re a dumbass? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’ve decided I’m going to have Mr. Lee sign my copy of this month’s Batman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>That’s crazy. Stan Lee had nothing to do with Batman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes, which is why no one else will ask him to sign one, and I will be the possessor of a unique, albeit confusing, artifact, which will set me apart from the hoi polloi of comic book fandom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>That’s a great idea, I’m going to get him to sign a Batman as well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What is it about the word unique you don’t understand?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Ow! Damn, paper cut. Nothing worse than a paper cut.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Well, obviously you don’t remember your circumcision.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>There’s Neosporin and Band-Aids in my top desk drawer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Why don’t you keep that stuff in the bathroom?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>He does. And in the kitchen. And in the car. And in his pocket.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, but the ones in my pocket are mine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hi!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey. Guess who’s going to be at the comic bookstore on Thursday?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Um, can you give me a hint?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Stan Lee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Um, Stanley, Stanley, Stanley Tucci?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, no, Stan Lee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, oh, Stan Lee! Cool!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You have no idea who he is, do you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Of course I do. You’re an important part of my life and I pay attention to the things you are interested in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-22"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Good, good, so, who’s Stan Lee?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-23"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Um, he was on Star Trek.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-24"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Nope.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-25"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Star Wars?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-26"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-27"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Um, uh, Stan Lee, oh, he was in those goofy kung fu movies you love so much?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-28"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That’s Bruce Lee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-29"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh. So, is this Bruce Lee’s nerdy brother, Stan?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-30"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Sheldon, why do you have all these unopened paychecks in your desk?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-31"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Because most of the things I’m planning to buy haven’t been invented yet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-32"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>But there must be thousands of dollars here. Why don’t you put it in the bank?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-33"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I don’t trust banks. I believe that when the robots rise up, ATMs will lead the charge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-34"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You’ve also got something from the Pasadena Municipal Court.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-35"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Undoubtedly yet another snide response to my repeated letters complaining that the flags in front of the courthouse are flying in the wrong order. From left to right, it’s supposed to be federal, state, and then city of Pasadena.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-36"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I’m sorry. You sent more than one letter about that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-37"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It bothers me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-38"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Sheldon, this is a summons.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-39"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>A summons for what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-40"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Looks like you ran a red light on Marengo Avenue at 9:30 p.m. on November 16. They got you on a traffic camera. Nice picture.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-41"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>November 16? Penny, that’s the evening you fell in your bathtub and I had to drive you to the emergency room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-42"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, it isn’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-43"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes, it is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-44"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, it isn’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-45"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Penny, I have an eidetic memory. Also, that’s a picture of you in the passenger seat holding your dislocated shoulder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-46"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Mmm, no, it isn’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-47"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Okay, then why is a summons for a traffic violation committed in your car, bearing your license plates, coming to me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-48"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, look, they sent me the ticket. I told them I wasn’t driving and they were all, if it wasn’t you, who was it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-49"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>So you betrayed me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-50"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No! It wasn’t a betrayal. It was more of a can’t afford any more points on my license. I already have to buy my insurance from this place in the Cayman Islands.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-51"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>But the only reason I was driving your car was because you were in distress and I was rescuing you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-52"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yes, yes, look, and now you have a photo to remember that heroic day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-53"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It’s not that big a deal. You just go down to the court on Thursday and you pay the fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-54"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m not going to pay a fine. That would imply I’m guilty.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-55"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You are guilty.  That one I liked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-56"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I am not guilty. I only have a learner’s permit, Penny was the teacher. When the light turned yellow she said go, go, go, so I went, went, went.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-57"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sheldon, I’m sorry. I’ll be happy to reimburse you for the fine. You know, as soon as I get a part in a movie or my own TV series.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-58"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You don’t need to reimburse me because I’m not paying. On Thursday, I will have my day in court and justice will be done. In fact, I’m going to begin preparing my defence right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-59"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Okay, he’s going to jail.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-60"><speaker>Leonard (after Raj whispers to him)</speaker><content>Oh, that’s right. Thursday is Stan Lee Day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-61"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Now you see what you’ve done? Because of you, we’re all going to miss Stan Lee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-62"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Whoa! What do you mean all?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-63"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, you’re my friends. You’ll be standing by my side, supporting me, feeding me legal precedents, and if you had the upper body strength, carrying me out on your shoulders when I’m victorious.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-64"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, okay. No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-65"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Are you saying that you will not stand beside me as I plead my case?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-66"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That’s what I’m saying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-67"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Howard?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-68"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Wow. Uh, Stan Lee, or you in court? Uh, if this was Sophie’s Choice it would’ve been a much shorter movie. No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-69"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Raj? You’ll be there, won’t you?  All right, then, my so-called friends have forsaken me. So, I guess it’ll just be me and my eyewitness.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-70"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, balls.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-71"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Please try to wear something appropriate. It won’t help my case if the judge is busy trying to read the word Juicy scrawled across your buttocks.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content> Penny.  Penny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Penny (opening door)</speaker><content> Penny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s just wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>All right, let’s go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Wait, hold on. Before we get to the courthouse, I’d like to call on your skills as an actress.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What is this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’ve taken the liberty of scripting your appearance on the witness stand because, let’s face it, you’re somewhat of a loose cannon. Now, don’t worry, it’s written in your vernacular. So shall we rehearse?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Do I have a choice?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, of course you have a choice. Although we live in a deterministic universe, each individual has free will. Now, sit down. I call your attention to the events of November 16. Do you remember that date?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Penny (reading)</speaker><content>Darn tootin’, I do, if the court will excuse my homespun, corn-fed Nebraskan turn of phrase.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Excellent. Go on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>The reason that date is, like, so totally fixed in my memory is that I had the privilege to be witness to one of the most heroic acts I’ve ever seen in, like, ever.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And who performed that heroic act?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Why, you did, sir. You. Dr. Sheldon Cooper, and may I add, it is a privilege to know you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>There’s no need for compliments, this court is only interested in the facts.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>But it is a fact that it’s a privilege to know you. Totally. A teardrop rolls down my cheek?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Only a suggestion. A catch in your throat would work just as well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>Penny (pretending to be close to tears)</speaker><content>But it is a fact that it’s a privilege to know you. Totally.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Maybe you should put on your Juicy pants again.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Judge</speaker><content>Pay the cashier. Sheldon Cooper?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Good morning, Your Honour. Dr. Sheldon Cooper appearing in pro se. That is to say, representing himself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Judge</speaker><content>I know what it means. I went to law school.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And yet you wound up in traffic court. Anyway, if it would please the court, I’d like to begin with an opening statement.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Judge</speaker><content>The court would advise you to make it quick, as the court had a dicey-looking breakfast burrito this morning and just took an Imodium.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Very well, a quick opening statement. Like a milking stool, my case rests on three legs. I will demonstrate that I was improperly instructed in driving by a woman whose lack of respect for society borders on the sociopathic. I will argue that the emergency met the legal doctrine of quod est necessarium est licitum, that which is necessary is legal. But first, I will raise a Sixth Amendment issue. I’m unable to confront my accuser, a non-human entity, to wit, a camera. So, to sum up, improper instruction, quod est necessarium est licitum, Sixth Amendment. My milk stool is complete.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Judge</speaker><content>Impressive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Judge</speaker><content>Guilty. Pay the cashier.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I object. You’re completely ignoring the law.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Judge</speaker><content>No, I’m following the law. I’m ignoring you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Really? I would point out that I am at the top of my profession, while you preside over the kiddy table of yours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Judge</speaker><content>Dr. Cooper, before I find you in contempt and throw you in jail, I’m going to give you a chance to apologize for that last remark.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I am a scientist. I never apologize for the truth.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s my spot.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I can’t wait to ask Stan Lee why he insists on giving all his characters first and last names that start with the same letter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, come on, why would you do that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Bruce Banner, Reed Richards, Sue Storm, Stephen Strange, Otto Octavius, Silver Surfer, Peter Parker, oh, and worst of all, J. Jonah Jameson, Jr.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Okay, I’m cutting. I’m not gonna talk to Stan Lee after you cheese him off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Leonard (phone rings.)</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sheldon’s in jail.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon’s in jail?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You called it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>For what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What do you think? For doing the same crap he always does, except to a judge. He has to stay in there until he apologizes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>So tell him to apologize.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, gee, thanks, Leonard. That didn’t occur to me. If he doesn’t apologize by 5 o’clock he is going to spend the night in jail.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, no, that’s terrible. Ooh, the line’s moving. Got to go. Bye.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Excuse me? Excuse me, jailor?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Guard</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I need to use the restroom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Guard</speaker><content>Knock yourself out. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s the toilet?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Guard</speaker><content>Well, it ain’t a wishing well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Please tell the judge I’m ready to apologize.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Look at that. To my friend, Leonard, from Stan Lee, Excelsior!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Awesome. Mine says, To my friend, Howard, from Stan Lee, Excelsior!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Mine says, To Raj, from Stan Lee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>That’s ’cause you pissed him off about his character names.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Hey, I didn’t even mention Dum Dum Dugan or Green Goblin, Matt Murdock, Pepper Potts, Victor Von Doom, oh, and worst of all, Millie the Model.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>We’re home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, hey, buddy. How’d it go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You know very well how it went.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, but we all want to hear it from you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I was found guilty and fined $533.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I’m going to write you a cheque for that. As long as you promise to put it in your drawer and never cash it, like the others.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I also now have three points on a driver’s licence I do not yet possess, and I was forced to issue an undeserved apology, simply because I refuse to urinate in a stainless steel bowl in front of criminals.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Plus, you didn’t get to meet Stan Lee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, that’s enough, Howard. The poor guy’s had a tough time. He had to spend the entire afternoon in jail wearing that suit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You’re right, so it would be cruel to mention that after he finished signing autographs, Stan Lee took Stuart and us out for gelato.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You had gelato with Stan Lee?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>He said we could call him Stan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Except for Raj.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, I hope you’re satisfied, Penny. You are responsible for all the evil that has befallen me today.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-20"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, I realize that…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Not finished. It is because of you that I now have a criminal record, and it is because of you that I missed out on having gelato with Stan Lee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-22"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, maybe you’ll have another chance to have…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, no. I will never have another chance to have gelato with Stan Lee because opportunities to have gelato with Stan Lee come but once in a lifetime. The moving finger writes, and having writ, moves on!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-24"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Did he just somehow give me the finger?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-25"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Not just the finger. The moving finger.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey, Stuart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Oh, hey, Penny. Wow. Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What’s going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Nothing. I’m just getting ready to close up and head out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Ah. Cool. Got any fun plans?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Oh, yeah. Big night tonight. Gonna share a can of tuna with the cat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, nice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Not even my cat. I just feed it. Some nights it doesn’t even show up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, okay. Well, I was hoping, um, you could do me a favour.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Sure, yeah, name it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, I’m kind of responsible for Sheldon missing Stan Lee, and I really want to make it up to him. So I was hoping you could give me his phone number so maybe I can arrange for them to meet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Oh, I’m sorry, I don’t have his phone number.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hmm. Damn. All right. Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Mm-hmm. Wait. I have his address.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Really? Great!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>But I can’t give it to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Then why did you tell me you had it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>I don’t know. Just chatting. You’re looking at a guy who could very well get stood up by a stray cat tonight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-19"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I’m sorry, Stuart. Thanks anyway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-20"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Mm-hmm. Wait.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-21"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-22"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Maybe we can make a deal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-23"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What kind of deal?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-24"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>I will give you the address if you go to my cousin’s wedding with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-25"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You’re extorting a date out of me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-26"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>I kind of have to. The cousin who’s getting married is the cousin I usually go to weddings with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-27"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Can I bring Leonard?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-28"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Sure. What the hell.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-29"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Deal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-30"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>We’ll tell people he’s your cousin.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>This is Stan Lee’s front door. We were on Stan Lee’s curb, then we were on Stan Lee’s walk, and now we’re at Stan Lee’s front door.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yup.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, Lord, you just rang Stan Lee’s doorbell. At Stan Lee’s house. We’re about to go in and have milk and cookies with Stan Lee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, sweetie, I don’t know if we’re gonna have cookies, or he’s just gonna say hi, or really what’s gonna happen, so just let me talk, and we’ll…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Stan Lee (opening door)</speaker><content>Yeah?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Are you Stan Lee?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Stan Lee</speaker><content>Oh, damn.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hi. I’m Penny. This is my friend, Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>We’re not friends at the moment. Depends on how this goes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Right, right. Anyway, Sheldon here is a huge fan of yours, and he was supposed to meet you the other day at the comic book store, but he kind of ended up in jail.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Stan Lee</speaker><content>I see. And you thought you’d just come over to my house uninvited?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You said we were invited.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, no, no, I said I’m inviting you to come with me to Stan Lee’s house.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>Stan Lee</speaker><content>You know, you fan boys are unbelievable. Do you think you can just ring my doorbell any time you want? I mean, why don’t you just come on in and watch the Lakers game with me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, I’m not much of a sports fan, but thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I’m sorry. He doesn’t really understand sarcasm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-17"><speaker>Stan Lee</speaker><content>Well, I’ll give him something he’ll understand. Joanie, call the police!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-18"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Nice to meet you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Fantastic Four, Daredevil, Invincible Iron Man, Happy Hogan, Curt Connors…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Would you just let it go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>And worst of all, Fin Fang Foom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Leonard (as Sheldon enters)</speaker><content>Hey, where’ve you been?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’ll tell you where I’ve been. You boys may have had gelato with Stan Lee and gotten autographed comics, but I saw the inside of his house and got an autographed application for a restraining order.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Sweet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Plus, I get to hang out with him again at the hearing. This is going to look great hanging next to my restraining order from Leonard Nimoy.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>