<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Okay in Avatar when they have sex in Pandora they hook up their ponytails, so we know their ponytails are like their junk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, so?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>So, when they ride horses and fly on the birds, they also use their ponytails.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What’s your point?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>My point is, if I were a horse or a bird, I’d be very nervous around James Cameron.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It amazes me how you constantly obsess over fictional details when there are more important things in the real world to worry about. For example, why wasn’t William Shatner in the new Star Trek movie?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey, Sheldon, I was up in the administration office, and I happened to overhear the name of the winner of this year’s Chancellor’s Award for Science.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And you want to rub my nose in the fact that my contributions are being overlooked again? I am the William Shatner of theoretical physics. All right, I’ll play. What self-important, preening fraud are they honouring this year?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, I’m so glad you asked it like that. You.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I won?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You won.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I won! This is astonishing. Not that I won the award, no one deserves it more. Actually, I guess I misspoke. It’s not astonishing, more like inevitable. I’m not sure what to do first. Maybe I should call my mother. Wait! I know, I’m going to conduct an interview with myself and post it online.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Well, good for him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, the one thing the William Shatner of theoretical physics needed was an ego boost.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Didn’t it look like that spear was going to go right through your skull?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey, you didn’t want a Slurpee at 7-Eleven, you don’t get glasses.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Sheldon (phone rings)</speaker><content>Oh, that will be another congratulatory call for me. Uh, mute, please.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Uh, hang on, flaming arrow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hello? Oh, Chancellor Morton, how are you, sir? Yes, I was expecting your call  three years ago. I see. Wait. What happens if I choose not to give a speech? Uh-huh. And if I don’t want to forfeit the award? Well, you’ve got that tied up in a neat little bow. All right. Thank you.  Problem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>They expect me to give a speech at the banquet. I can’t give a speech.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Well, no, you’re mistaken. You give speeches all the time. What you can’t do is shut up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yeah, before the movie, you did 20 minutes on why guacamole turns brown. It turned brown while you were talking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I am perfectly comfortable speaking to small groups. I cannot speak to large crowds.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What, to you, is a large crowd?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Any group big enough to trample me to death. General rule of thumb is 36 adults or 70 children.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sheldon, congratulations. Brought you cheesecake from work. You know, ’cause of your award, not because a busboy sneezed on it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m not accepting the award.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Why not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Turns out the great Sheldon Cooper has stage fright.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>That’s no reason to back out. You know, I once got a pretty big honour in high school, and I was terrified about appearing in front of a big crowd, but I went through with it, and you know what? The world looked pretty darn good sitting on a haystack in the back of a Ford F-150 as a member of the Corn Queen’s court.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Thank you. Yeah, I’ll bear that in mind if I’m ever nominated for the Hillbilly Peace Prize.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, you’re being ridiculous.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Am I? Let me tell you a story.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-22"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Where’s 70 children when you need ‘em?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I was 14 and graduating summa cum laude from college. Summa cum laude is Latin for with highest honours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-24"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I just love how you always skip over the part where no one asks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-25"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I was valedictorian and expected to give an address. Even now, I can remember that moment when I walked up to the podium and looked out at the crowd. There must have been thousands of people. My heart started pounding in my chest. I began to hyperventilate. My vision became blurry, and before I knew it… oh, dear. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-26"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, my God.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-27"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon? Sheldon, are you okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-28"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Don’t trample me.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Come on, Mother, you know why I can’t accept the award. With all due respect, I don’t think praying will help. No, I have not heard the song, Jesus, Take the Wheel. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, you don’t need to start singing it. Yes, I’ll buy it on the iTunes, Mother. Good-bye, Mother.  Hello.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sit down, we want to talk to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Am I in trouble? Did my mother call you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Just sit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>We think we can help you with your stage fright.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, I doubt that. I haven’t figured out a way, and I’m much smarter than all of you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yes, but you’re not smarter than all of us put together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, I’m sorry, that is what I meant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, your problem is, you’re trying to do this all by yourself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>We can help you. We can be your team. Like, uh, Professor Xavier and his X-Men.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I do like the X-Men.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Did I see X-Men?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, we watched it last week. You said you liked it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh. I say a lot of things, sweetie. So, how about it, Sheldon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I don’t know. If you’re my X-Men, what are your powers?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay. Well, I am going to take you shopping, get you a nice suit. Might give you more confidence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s not exactly a mutation that would get you into Xavier’s School for Gifted Youngsters, but go on. Leonard?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I thought I could try to analyze you and get to the root of your anxiety.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What qualifies you to attempt to understand my mind?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>My mother is a highly regarded psychiatrist, and I’ve been in therapy ever since she accused me of breast-feeding co-dependently.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-21"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Raj says he can teach you, what did you call it? I don’t know, some Indian meditation crap.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I see. Well, I assume, since the rest of you have set the bar so low, you’re saving the most impressive contribution for last. Go ahead, Howard. Dazzle me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-23"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>My power is the ability to pretend like I give a damn about your piddly-ass problems. And that’s 24-7, buddy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-24"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And I appreciate the pretence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-25"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>So, what do you say, Sheldon? Are we your X-Men?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-26"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No. The X-Men were named for the X in Charles Xavier. Since I am Sheldon Cooper, you will be my C-Men.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-27"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, that’s not a good name.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Okay, Sheldon. I’m going to be leading you through a series of meditation exercises. These methods come from the ancient gurus of India and have helped me overcome my own fears.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And yet, you can’t speak to women.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>True, but thanks to meditation, I am able to stay in the same room with them without urinating. Now, close your eyes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Okay, but don’t punch me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>When I was little, my sister would say to me, close your eyes, you’ll get a surprise, and then she’d punch me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I’m not going to punch you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s what my sister used to say.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Do you want to do this or not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m sorry. Proceed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>All right. Imagine yourself in the one place you feel most at home. Where is that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Sim City. More specifically, the Sim City I designed, Sheldonopolis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Okay, you’re in Sheldonopolis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Where exactly? Sheldon Square? Sheldon Towers? Sheldon Stadium, home of the Fighting Sheldons?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Whatever you like.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I thought this was supposed to be a guided meditation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Fine. You’re in Sheldon Square.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Really? This time of year? It’s a bit nippy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Then, put on a sweater.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Suppose I could run downtown and pick up something at Shel-Mart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-21"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yeah, whatever. Just go buy a sweater.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You know, the nice thing about Shel-Mart is I own it, so I get a 15% discount.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-23"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You own the damn thing. Just take a freaking sweater!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-24"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Look, I didn’t turn a profit last quarter by taking product off the shelves willy-nilly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-25"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>All right. You’ve paid for a sweater, and you’re in Sheldon Square.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-26"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hang on. It’s a cardigan. I have to button it. Oh, no.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-27"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>What now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-28"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>A Godzilla-like monster is approaching the city. I have to get my people to safety. People of Sheldonopolis, this is your mayor. Follow me. If the children can’t run, leave them behind. Oh, the simulated horror!  Raj? Just as I suspected. Meditation is nothing but hokum.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I question your premise. How is a new suit going to prevent me from passing out in front of a ballroom full of people?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>It’ll give you confidence. You know, sometimes when I’m feeling all stressed out about something, I go out and buy a cute top or a fun skirt and I have a whole new outlook on life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Don’t you eventually realize you’re just the same stressed out person in a cute top or a fun skirt?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, that’s when I buy shoes. Now, let’s see what we’ve got. Ooh! This is nice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It’s only one colour.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, so?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s a lot of money for only one colour.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Fine. Why don’t you pick out what you like.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, you’re wrong.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Where the hell d’you find that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>In the prom department.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>It’s ridiculous.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Says the former member of the Corn Queen’s Court.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Please just try this one on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Okay. But anything I put on now is only going to suffer in comparison.  This is absurd. I look like a clown.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>So, Sheldon, how you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s how you start a psychotherapy session? How am I doing? I was promised a riverboat journey into the jungles of my subconscious. Instead, I get the same question I hear from the lady who slices my bologna at Ralph’s.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m sorry, I’ll start again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Would it be helpful to you if I told you about my dreams?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Um, I don’t know, maybe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I recently had a dream that I was a giant. But everything around me was to scale, so it all looked normal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>How did you know you were a giant if everything was to scale?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I was wearing size a million pants.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Why don’t we just talk?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Ah, the talking cure. Classical Freudian, good choice. If it will help speed things along, uh, my answers to the standard Rorschach ink blot test are A, a bat, B, a bat, C, a bat, and D, my father killing my mother with a hypodermic needle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Why don’t I just start? Sometimes people have trouble accepting accolades if, on a subconscious level, they don’t feel they deserve them. Do you think maybe that’s what’s happening here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Really, Leonard? You’re just going to try to recycle Adler’s doctrine of the inferiority complex? I could probably get that from the woman at Ralph’s. And she’d let me taste some pieces of cheese for free.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>But it could be part of your problem. Let me give you an example. When I was eight, I won a ribbon at the science fair for my project, “Do Lima Beans Grow Better to Classical Music.” But my mother pointed out that it was just a rehash of my brother’s earlier “Do Lima Beans Grow Worse to Rock ‘n’ Roll.” I felt so guilty, I gave the ribbon back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And how did that make you feel?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Terrible. I worked really hard on that project. I stayed up all night singing the clown’s aria from Pagliacci to a lima bean sprout.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Go on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It wasn’t my fault. I had never seen my brother’s project. And my mother could’ve told me before instead of at the ceremony in front of everyone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>So, I hear you saying you’re angry with your mother.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Damn right, I’m angry with my mother. For God’s sake, I was eight years old. She humiliated me. That’s when the bed-wetting started again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Thank you, Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>For what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>If someone as damaged as you can find his way to crawl out of bed each morning, I think I can face a simple award ceremony.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-23"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Wait, that’s it? I thought we had a whole hour!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Good evening, ladies and gentlemen. My name is Dr. Leonard Hofstadter, and it is my very great honour to introduce the winner of this year’s Chancellor’s award for Science and my good friend, Dr. Sheldon Cooper. But before I do, I’d like to share with you a letter from Sheldon’s mother, who couldn’t be here tonight. Isn’t that nice? His mother sent him a letter. She’s proud of him. I wonder what that feels like. Dear Shelly. That’s what she calls him. Shelly, it’s a pet name. You know what my mother’s pet name for me is? Leonard. But I digress. Dear Shelly. I am so proud of… </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, dear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What’s the matter?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m getting dizzy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Don’t worry. You’re surrounded by your C-Men.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I can’t do this. I’m going to faint.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Here, drink this. It’ll relax you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Alcohol? I don’t drink alcohol.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Fine, faint.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I don’t feel different, this alcohol’s defective.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Here, see if this one works.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Leonard (still talking)</speaker><content>First of all, the projects were totally different. I was showing that classical music nurtures lima beans and makes them grow, but my mother didn’t hear me. If you’d like to look at the relationship between nurturing and growth, I’d like to point out that my brother is eight inches taller than me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m ready.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, right. Ladies and gentlemen, our guest of honour, Dr. Sheldon Cooper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Thanks, shorty,I’ll take it from here. All right, you people ready to have some fun? You have a basic understanding of differential calculus and at least one year of algebraic topology? Well, then here come the jokes. Why did the chicken cross the Mobius strip? To get to the same side, bazinga! All right, a neutron walks into a bar and asks, how much for a drink? The bartender says, for you, no charge. Hello? I know you’re out there. I can hear you metabolizing oxygen and expelling carbon dioxide. Looks like we have some academic dignitaries in the audience. Dr. Randall from the geology department, only man who’s happy when they take his work for granite. Ba-da cha! I kid the geologists, of course, but it’s only ’cause I have no respect for the field. Let’s get serious for a moment. Why are we all here? ‘Cause we’re scientists. And what do scientists study? The universe. And what’s the universe made of? I am so glad you asked.  There’s antimony, arsenic, aluminium, selenium, and hydrogen and oxygen and nitrogen and rhenium, and nickel, neodymium,</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Penny, Leonard. Would you be able to answer some questions I’m having about the events of last night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Question one, where are my pants?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You might want to check YouTube.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What do I search?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It’s already loaded. Just hit play.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>On-screen Sheldon</speaker><content>All right, people, let’s get down to the math. It is only three dimensional thinking that limits our imagination. Can I take my pants off over my head? Of course not. My body’s in the way. But if we had access to higher dimensions, we could move our pants around our bodies through the fourth dimension and our days of dropping trousers would be over.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, Lord, this couldn’t be any more humiliating.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh-uh, give it a minute.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>On-screen Sheldon</speaker><content>Now, for the astronomers in the audience, get ready to see the dark side of the moon. And here’s Uranus.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>