<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hold.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Explain your sneeze.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I’m sorry?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Do you have allergies?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Is there too much pepper on your salad?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I don’t put pepper on salads.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’ve heard enough. Sit over there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, come on. I don’t want to sit by myself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s what Typhoid Mary said, and clearly, her friends buckled.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Guys, help me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Sheldon, come on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, it’s just one sneeze.  You’re on your own.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>See you, buddy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, Leonard, I have something for you. Per our roommate agreement, this is your 24-hour notice that I will be having a non-related female spending two nights in our apartment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>When you say non-related female, you still mean human, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Of course. Pets are banned under the roommate agreement, with the exception of service animals, such as seeing eye dogs and, one day, cybernetically-enhanced helper monkeys.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Are you planning on kidnapping a woman?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Sarcasm?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-21"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yes, but mixed with genuine concern.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>For your information, I’ll be playing host to Dr. Elizabeth Plimpton.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-23"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>The cosmological physicist from Princeton?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-24"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes. And until you acquire a surgical mask, please address your comments to me through a napkin. We’ve been corresponding for years about our mutual interest in gravitational wave signatures of inflatons in the early universe. And now she’s under consideration for a position at our university.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-25"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Why didn’t you tell me you knew Elizabeth Plimpton? I am a huge fan of hers!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-26"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I didn’t realize I was obligated to share my connection with things you’re a fan of, but very well. You enjoy Canadian bacon. I’ve been to Toronto.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-27"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, fine. Where is she going to sleep?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-28"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>My room, of course.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-29"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Holy crap!  Holy crap!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-30"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, um, I have a two-part question.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-31"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Go ahead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-32"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>A, are you kidding me? And B, seriously, are you freaking kidding me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-33"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>A, I rarely kid. And B, when I do kid, you will know it by my use of the word bazinga.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-34"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>So you’re saying the two of you are going to be sleeping in the same bed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-35"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes. Bazinga. Leonard?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-36"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Thank you. Why is a world-renowned scientist staying in our apartment instead of a hotel?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-37"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, she doesn’t care for hotels. And who can blame her? Windows that don’t open, multi-user linens, keys shaped like credit cards, as if one walks around with unassigned slots in one’s wallet. All right, I believe I have time for one more question. Yes, Raj?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-38"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>When can I sit with you again?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-39"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>When I’ve seen two consecutive negative throat cultures spaced 12 hours apart. You know the drill. All right, if you’ll excuse me, I am off to start a prophylactic course of antibiotics.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-40"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I can’t believe he’s friends with Elizabeth Plimpton.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-41"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I can’t believe they let him into Canada.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-42"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Whoa, whoa, whoa. You heard the man. Where’s your throat cultures? Kidding. Sit down.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey, Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, Penny, excellent. I have a question about these maxi pads. Are the wings truly functional or have I fallen victim to marketing hype?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What? What are you doing with, what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>The stock boy at Walgreens was frustratingly uninformed on the subject.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sheldon, what are you doing with maxi pads?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I have a lady friend who will be staying with me for a few days.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh. What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I want her to feel at home. I also bought scented soaps, pantyhose, Midol, calcium chews and what is apparently a yogurt specifically designed to regulate the female bowel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Wait, wait, hold on, back up. You’re having a woman stay with you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes. Why does that seem to flabbergast everybody?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, no, no, no, no. I’m not flabbergasted. I’m puzzled. Yeah, let’s go with puzzled.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>A word of warning. My guest is a noted physicist and the leading expert on quantum cosmology, so please try to avoid wasting her time with female jibber jabber.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Female jibber jabber?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Shoe sales, hair styles, mud masks, gossip about your friends Brad and Angelina.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, they’re not my friends.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m not surprised, considering the way you talk about them behind their backs.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>She’s here, she’s here. How do I look? Do I look smart?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, good grief. This isn’t about you. Coming! Now listen, one of the great minds of the 21st century is about to play host to one of the other great minds of the 21st century. So pay attention. Years from now, my biographer might ask you about this event.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, I have so many things to tell your biographer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>Ah, Dr. Cooper, thank goodness. I completely forgot your address. But then I remembered that I’d written it on my hand. Lucky for me, I didn’t confuse it with what I’d written on my other hand, which are the coordinates for a newly discovered neutron star. ‘Cause if I tried to go there, I’d be crushed by hypergravity. Anyway, hello.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hello.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>Nice to finally meet you in person.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I would imagine it is. This is my friend and roommate, Dr. Leonard Hofstadter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hi-lo. Oops. I started to say hi, and then I switched to hello in the middle. It came out hi-lo. Duh. Uh, it’s nice to meet you. I’ve read both your books and most of your papers. I’m Leonard, I live</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I apologize. He’s only an experimental physicist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>No need to apologize. Some of my best friends are experimental physicists. Well, not my best friends, but I know them. My best friend is a molecular chemist named Wendy. I’m sorry, I’m rambling. Hi-lo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Are you hungry, thirsty? Can I offer you anything?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, she’s my guest. If anyone should offer her anything, it should be me. Elizabeth, can I get you something? Perhaps a feminine hygiene product or a bowel-regulating yogurt?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>Interesting choices. Based on my current needs, I guess I’d pick the yogurt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Excellent. If the yogurt works, I bought some delightful scented candles.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Look, it’s you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>Thank you so much for opening up your home to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, who wants to stay in a hotel? With windows that don’t open, those crazy card-shaped keys.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>I’m so glad you understand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, he doesn’t understand. I understand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, I understand, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You’re just misappropriating my understanding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, . I think any university would want you. Except, of course, any university that had already had you. Because they would’ve already wanted you before they, you know, got you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>From the mind that brought you hi-lo. Let me show you to your room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>All right. I guess I am tired. Good night, Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh, sleep night. I mean, obviously, good night. I started to say sleep tight, then I changed my mind in the middle. I swear to God, I’m smart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Get it together, man.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right, let me show you some of the features of the room. First, windows. Conventional. Open, closed, open, closed, halfway open, or halfway closed, depending on your philosophical bent. Over here is my comic book collection. Feel free to browse. There’s a box of disposable reading gloves on the night stand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>Good to know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>In here, you’ll find emergency provisions. An eight-day supply of food and water, a crossbow, season two of Star Trek: The Original Series on a high-density flash drive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>What if there’s a disaster that destroys all the USB ports?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Then there’s really no reason to live, is there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>Can I ask a question about your roommate?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>He’s an odd duck, isn’t he?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>What’s his relationship status?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, there was a misbegotten adventure with a waitress who lives across the hall. It ended as inexplicably as it began. They had very little in common, except for carnal activity. That’s why I acquired these noise-cancelling headphones. If you decide to use them, please clean the ear pieces afterwards with the Wet Wipes you’ll find in the bathroom. They’re in the drawer labelled Wet Wipes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Good. I’ll leave you to your night time ablutions. I’ve e-mailed you the morning bathroom schedule. You’ll also find a laminated copy in your welcome packet. It’s on the back of the emergency escape route diagram.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>How thoughtful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Sleep well, my friend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>You, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, let me just get one thing. It’s my backup emergency supply kit. The living room escape route doesn’t pass through here. Now, good night. And if there’s an apocalypse, good luck.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>I saw your light on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Is everything all right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>Yeah, I just couldn’t sleep.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Me neither. Oh, look what I’m reading. It’s you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>I thought you already read it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I did, but it’s been a while, and I wanted to sound smart over breakfast.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>Aw, you’re smart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, good. Wasn’t sure it was coming across.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>What chapter are you on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh, six.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>Oh, the extragalactic distance ladder. Want to know a little secret?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>I wrote the section on the Wilson-Bappu Effect completely naked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Really? Uh, sure doesn’t read that way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>Here, let me show you. When we consider the brightness of pulsating variable stars, we start to see  a possible explanation for some of the discrepancies found in Hubble’s constant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Wow. You really make science come alive.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Vocal test. Morning vocal test. Second vocal test. Second morning vocal test.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Morning, Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>Morning, Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Morning. I trust you had a pleasant night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>More than pleasant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Excuse me, I’m going to relieve myself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>How do you take your coffee?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>Black.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okeydoke.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Sheldon (in bathroom)</speaker><content>Pee for Houston, pee for Austin, pee for the state my heart got lost in. And shake twice for Texas.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Something his mother taught him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right, Elizabeth, the bathroom is yours. The seat is down, and has been sanitized for your protection.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>That’s very thoughtful, but I think I’ll finish my coffee first.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Ah, so the yogurt didn’t work. I’ll fire off a critical e-mail to the manufacturer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, good, you’re up. Look, my car won’t start. I need a ride to work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Did you once again ignore your check engine light?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, Mr. smarty-pants. I ignored the fill gas tank light.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Leonard, Penny wants to exploit any residual feelings you have for her in order to get a ride to work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, yeah, sure, let me just put this in a travel mug.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-21"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hello.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-22"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-23"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, Penny, this is Dr. Plimpton, a leading expert on quantum cosmology. Dr. Plimpton, Penny is a waitress who doesn’t understand the role gasoline plays in the internal combustion engine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-24"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>Nice to meet you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-25"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Nice to meet you, too. Are you enjoying your stay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-26"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>Yes, very much.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-27"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-28"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Wonderful. Meaningless pleasantries accomplished. Elizabeth, Leonard’s bathroom time is coming up, and believe me, you do not want to follow him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-29"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>Excuse me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-30"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, well, I guess I should get dressed so I can take everyone to work. You and Sheldon and Sheldon’s friend, Dr. Plimpton, who you just met. It’ll be fun. Like a clown car.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-31"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hang on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-32"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hmm? Yeah? What? Huh?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-33"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>We just broke up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-34"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What, uh, you and me? Yeah, we did. Not too long ago. How are you doing with it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-35"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Not as good as you apparently.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-36"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I, um, I don’t follow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-37"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You know what? It’s, it’s none of my business. If you want to sleep with Sheldon’s doctor buddy right after we stopped seeing each other, go for it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-38"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, now…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-39"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Excuse me. I’m uncomfortable with you recommending that Leonard pursue having intercourse with Dr. Plimpton, who I assure you has better things to do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-40"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I’m not recommending it. I’m saying it already happened.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-41"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s preposterous. Tell her, Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-42"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-43"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-44"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Come on. It wasn’t my fault.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-45"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>The implication being that you somehow tripped and fell into her lady parts?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-46"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You know what? I’m just gonna take the bus to work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-47"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Penny, I can still drive you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-48"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, no, no, it’s okay. You might slip on a banana peel and get me pregnant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-49"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I must say, I’m shocked by this betrayal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-50"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I didn’t betray Penny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-51"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Not Penny, me!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-52"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>How am I betraying you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-53"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Elizabeth’s my friend, and you’re playing with her!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-54"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, I guess I did.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What the hell are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Relax, it’s Nyquil.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You still have a cold?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Maybe, but I don’t care. That’s the great thing about Nyquil, it’s like ten-percent booze. I call it the nighttime sniffling, sneezing, coughing, so you can talk to girls medicine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Are you having trouble sleeping? ‘Cause, boy, I was up all night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Did you get a cold, too?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, but I was awake all night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>If you want, I can give you some of my mom’s sleeping pills.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>She won’t notice they’re missing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>She doesn’t know she takes them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, that’s okay. It was something else keeping me up last night. And again this morning. And, I didn’t mind. I was up last night. I was up this morning. I didn’t mind. Those are your clues.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Ooh, ooh. Did the pigeon on your windowsill have more babies?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Were you up making another stop-motion Lego movie?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>‘Cause let me tell you, it’s not enough to make the Legos move, they also have to capture your heart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, I’ll give you one more clue. It involved another person.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Did you get a Japanese love pillow?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>How is a Japanese love pillow another person?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-20"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>It is if you love her and give her a name.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Dr. Plimpton, I’d like you to meet my colleagues, Dr. Rajesh Koothrappali</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-22"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And not-a-doctor Howard Wolowitz.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-24"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-25"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I’m a big fan of your work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-26"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-27"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And of course, you’ve already introduced yourself to Dr. Hofstadter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-28"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey, you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-29"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>Hey, you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-30"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Boy, I’m kind of tuckered out. How are you feeling, Elizabeth?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-31"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>You know what? I am a little tired. Would you be a dear and get me a cup of coffee?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-32"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sure. Black, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-33"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>Actually, now I think I want it hot, brown and sweet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-34"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Coming right up.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What do you mean what? It’s Halo night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I can’t. I’m too sick. Go away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>That’s why we moved Halo night here. Look, I brought my mom’s chicken soup.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I’m not hungry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>Don’t send him away. Let him in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Who’s that</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I bought a parrot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, right. Dr. Plimpton?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>Hi. Howard, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Uh, yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>Can I ask you a question, Howard? Do you like role-playing games?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, sure. In fact, I’m a dungeon master.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>Not tonight. Tonight you are a delivery man. You brought soup, but uh-oh, Raj and I don’t have enough money to pay you. So we’ll have to come to some other kind of arrangement.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Beg pardon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>You two figure out the details, I’m going to go change into something I don’t mind getting ripped off my milky flesh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What the frak?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Go away. She wants New Delhi, not Kosher deli. Besides, you have a girlfriend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-19"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>We broke up weeks ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-20"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Why didn’t you say anything?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-21"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I was waiting for the right time. This is the right time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-22"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey, who’s ready for Halo?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-23"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, this is like a nightmare. Get lost!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-24"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>He’s right. The numbers are shaky enough as it is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-25"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t understand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-26"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>Oh, good. Leonard’s here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-27"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Good?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-28"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Elizabeth? What’s going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-29"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>What’s going on is you and Howard are my moving men and Raj is my new landlord and I don’t have enough money to pay any of you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-30"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Is she suggesting what I think she’s suggesting?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-31"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yep. Welcome to the Penthouse Forum.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-32"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Okay, show of hands. Who’s up for this? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-33"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>We’ll all be naked in front of each other.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-34"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’m out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-35"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>Everybody ready?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-36"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Follow my lead. Almost. We’re, we’re going to go out into the hallway and, uh, make a dramatic entrance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-37"><speaker>Elizabeth</speaker><content>Oh, good. It’s so much better when everyone commits.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-38"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Run. Run, run, run. Don’t look back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-39"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I thought we had something special.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-40"><speaker>Raj (locks door)</speaker><content>So, you say you can’t pay your rent?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, Leonard?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I found these in the dryer. I’m assuming they belong to Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Thanks. It’s really hard to find these in his size. So, listen. I’ve been meaning to talk to you about the other morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You mean you and Dr. Slutbunny?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, I wanted to explain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, you don’t owe me an explanation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, you don’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>So you’re not judging me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, I’m judging you nine ways to Sunday, but you don’t owe me an explanation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Nevertheless, I’d like to get one on the record so you can understand why I did what I did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I’m listening.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>She let me.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>