<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, thank God we’re home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I can’t believe we spent three months in that frozen hell.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>It was like a snowy nightmare from which there was no awakening.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I don’t know what Arctic expedition you guys were on, but I thought it was a hoot and a half.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, hi mom. No, I told you I’d call you when I got home, I’m not home yet.  Alright, I’m home. The Arctic expedition was a remarkable success, I’m all but certain there’s a Nobel Prize in my future. Actually, I shouldn’t say that. I’m entirely certain. No, mother, I could not feel your church group praying for my safety. The fact that I’m home safe is not proof that it worked, that logic is Post Hoc Ergo Propter Hoc. No, I’m not sassing you in Eskimo talk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m going to go let Penny know we’re back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Mother, I have to go. Yeah, love you. Bye.  Hello, old friend.  Daddy’s home.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Leonard, you’re back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, I just stopped by to say…  Yeah, so, hi!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hi! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Dammit, I should have gone over and told her we were back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yeah, it was first come, first served.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I just want you both to know, when I publish my findings, I won’t forget your contributions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Thanks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Of course, I can’t mention you in my Nobel acceptance speech, but when I get round to writing my memoirs you can expect a very effusive footnote, and perhaps a signed copy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>We have to tell him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Tell me what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Damn his Vulcan hearing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You fellows are planning a party for me, aren’t you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Okay, Sheldon, sit down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>If there’s going to be a theme, I should let you know that I don’t care for luau, toga or under the sea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, we’ll keep that in mind, look, we need to talk to you about something that happened at the North Pole.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>If this is about the night the heat went out, there’s nothing to be embarrassed about.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>It’s not about that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>And we agreed to never speak of it again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>So we slept together naked. It was only to keep our core body temperatures from plummeting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>He’s speaking about it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>For me, it was a bonding moment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Sheldon, you remember the first few weeks we were looking for magnetic monopoles and not finding anything and you were acting like an obnoxious, giant dictator?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I thought we were going to be gentle with him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-20"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>That’s why I added the tator. And then when we found our first positive data, you were so happy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, yes. In the world of emoticons, I was colon, capital D.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-22"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Well, in actuality, what your equipment detected wasn’t so much evidence of paradigm-shifting monopoles as it was… static from the electric can opener we were turning on and off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-23"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>He just went colon, capital O.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-24"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You tampered with my experiment?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-25"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>We had to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-26"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>It was the only way to keep you from being such a huge Dickensian. You see that? I added the ensian.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-27"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Did Leonard know about this? Leonard’s my best friend in the world. Surely Leonard didn’t know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-28"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Actually, it was his idea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-29"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Of course it was. The whole plan reeks of Leonard.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I missed you so much.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I missed you, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I couldn’t even think of anyone else while you were gone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Me, neither. Except for one night when the heat went out. Long story, it’s… don’t ask.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content> Leonard.  Leonard.  Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Leonard (whispering)</speaker><content>Do not make a sound.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Whispering do not make a sound is a sound.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Damn his Vulcan hearing. Not a good time, Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content> Penny.  Penny.  Penny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, this is ridiculous. What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hello, Penny. I realize you’re currently at the mercy of your primitive biological urges, but as you have an entire lifetime of poor decisions ahead of you, may I interrupt this one?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>It’s great to see you too. Come on in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Wolowitz has informed me of your grand deception. Do you have anything to say for yourself?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yes, I feel terrible about it. I will never forgive myself, I don’t expect you to either, and I would really appreciate it if you would leave me with Penny for a session of self-criticism and repentance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, can someone please tell me what’s going on here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What’s going on is I was led to believe I was making groundbreaking strides in science, when in fact, I was being fed false data at the hands of Wolowitz, Koothrappali and your furry little boy toy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Is that true?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It was the only way to make him happy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-19"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Why did you have to make him happy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Because when he wasn’t happy, we wanted to kill him. There was even a plan. We were going to throw his Kindle outside, and when he went to get it, lock the door and let him freeze to death.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That seems like a bit of an overreaction.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-22"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, the overreaction was the plan to tie your limbs to four different sled dog teams and yell mush. Look, we kept the original data. You can still publish the actual results.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes, but the actual results are unsuccessful and I’ve already sent an e-mail to everyone at the university explaining that I have confirmed string theory and forever changed man’s understanding of the universe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-24"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Aw, see, yeah, you probably shouldn’t have done that. So write another e-mail, set the record straight, it’s no big deal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-25"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You’re right, Leonard, it’s not a big deal. All you did was lie to me destroy my dream and humiliate me in front of the whole university. That, FYI, was sarcasm. I, in fact, believe it is a big deal</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-26"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, the poor thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-27"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, I feel terrible.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-28"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Wait, wait. Aren’t you going to go talk to him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-29"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What? Uh, he’ll be fine, the guy’s a trouper, come here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-30"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, you’re right, you shouldn’t talk to him. I will.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-31"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Man, I cannot catch a break.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey. Do you want to talk?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>About what? Being betrayed by my friends? Spending three months at the North Pole for nothing? And I didn’t even get to go to Comic-Con!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, hon… Uh…   Soft kitty, warm kitty…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s for when I’m sick. Sad is not sick.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh. Sorry. I don’t know your sad song.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I don’t have a sad song. I’m not a child.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, you know, I do understand what you’re going through.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Really? Did you just have the Nobel Prize in waitressing stolen from you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, no, but when I was a senior in high school, one of my friends heard I was going to be named head cheerleader. Oh, I was so excited. My mom even made me a celebration pie. Then they named stupid Valerie Mossbacher head cheerleader. Big ol’ slutbag.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Are you saying that you think a celebration pie is even remotely comparable to a Nobel Prize?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, they’re pretty tasty.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And on a different, but not unrelated topic, based on your current efforts to buoy my spirits, do you truly believe that you were ever fit to be a cheer leader?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Look, Sheldon, I just don’t think that the guys and Leonard really meant to hurt you. You know? They just told an unfortunate lie to deal with a difficult situation. Okay, you know what it’s like? Remember that scene in the new Star Trek movie when Kirk has to take over the ship, so he tells Spock all that stuff he knew wasn’t true, like saying Spock didn’t care his mom died?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I missed Comic-Con and the new Star Trek movie!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I like the new look.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Thanks. I call it the Clooney.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I call it the Mario and Luigi, but whatever. Hey, how’s Sheldon doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, he came out of his room this morning wearing his Darth Vader helmet and tried to choke me to death with the Force, so I’d say, a little better.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>If I may abruptly change the subject, did you and Penny finally… you know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Howard…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Personally, I don’t care, but my genitals wanted me to ask.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, tell your genitals what I do with Penny is none of their business.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Howard (to his genitals)</speaker><content>He says they didn’t do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Leonard (to Sheldon, entering)</speaker><content>Sheldon, over here. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I feel bad for the guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, why are you sitting by yourself?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Because I am without friends. Like the proverbial cheese, I stand alone. Even while seated.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Come on. We said we were sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It’s going to take more than I’m sorry and a store-bought apology pie from Penny to make up for what you’ve done to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>Kripke (arriving)</speaker><content>Hey, Cooper. Wead your wetwaction e-mail. Way to destroy your weputation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You see? People have been pointing and laughing at me all morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>That’s not twue. People have been pointing and waughing at you your whole wife.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right, I’ve had enough. Attention, everyone. I’ m Dr. Sheldon Cooper. As many of you in the physics department might know, my career trajectory has taken a minor detour.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-21"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>Off a cwiff.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>My credibility may have been damaged…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-23"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>Compwetely wecked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-24"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>But I would like to remind you that in science, there’s no such thing as failure. There once was a man who referred to his prediction of a cosmological constant as the single biggest blunder of his career. That man’s name was, surprise, surprise, Albert Einstein.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-25"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>Yeah, but wesearch into Dark Energy pwoved that Einstein’s cosmowogical constant was actually wight all along, so you’re still, surpwise, surpwise, a woser.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-26"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, you think you’re so clever. Well, let me just tell you, while I do not currently have a scathing retort, you check your e-mail periodically for a doozy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-27"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>So much for our friendship with Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-28"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Well, we’ll always have the night the heat went out.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey. Listen, since we got, you know, interrupted last night, I didn’t have a chance to give you this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, Leonard, you shouldn’t have. Oh, boy! What is it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It’s a snowflake. From the North Pole.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Are you serious?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh-huh. It’ll last forever. I preserved it in a one percent solution of polyvinyl acetal resin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, my God. That’s the most romantic thing anyone’s ever said to me that I didn’t understand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It’s actually a pretty simple process. You see, cyanoacrylate are monomers which polymerize on… </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Howard (arriving)</speaker><content>Red alert, Leonard. Sheldon ran away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Man, I can not catch a break.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>So, how do you know he ran away?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Well, he’s not answering his phone, he handed in his resignation at the university and he sent me a text that said, I’m running away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, well, thanks for letting me know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, Leonard, aren’t you going to do something?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Of course I’m going to do something. Uh, Howard, you check the comic book store. Raj, go to the Thai restaurant. I’ll stay here with Penny in her apartment.  Oh, damn it. It’s Sheldon’s mother. A break cannot be caught. Hi, Mrs. Cooper. He is? Sheldon went home to Texas. Yeah, no, I know he resigned. Yes, I guess it kind of is our fault. No, no, no, you, you’re right, someone needs to come talk to him. Don’t worry, I’ll take care of it. Yeah. All right. New plan. Howard, you and Raj go to Texas. I’ll stay here with Penny in her apartment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, you’re not gonna go with them?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, you know, I gave you the snowflake and we were kissing and… Oh, come on, I don’t want to go to Texas!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, right, and I do? My people already crossed a desert once, we’re done.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Trust me, you’ll be fine. See ya.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-20"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, wait a second, Leonard, come on, how can you not go? He’s your best friend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, but I already saw him naked. Just come here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-22"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No. I promise I will be here when you get back. Just go help Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-23"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Really?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-24"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah. We waited a few months. We can wait a few more days.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-25"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Maybe you can.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-26"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-27"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Boy, you cannot catch a break, can you?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Here you go, Shelly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Thanks, Mom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Hold your horses, young man. Here in Texas, we pray before we eat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Aw, Mom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>This is not California, land of the heathen. Gimme. By His hand we are all…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Fed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Give us, Lord, our daily…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Bread.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Please know that we are truly…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Grateful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>For every cup and every…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Plateful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Amen. Now, that wasn’t so hard, was it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>My objection was based on considerations other than difficulty.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Whatever. Jesus still loves you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Thank you for carving a smiley face in my grilled cheese sandwich.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Oh, I know how to take care of my baby. His eyes came out a little thin, but you can just pretend he’s Chinese. So, do you want to talk about what happened with you and your little friends?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>They’re not my friends.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-19"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>All right. If you recall, when you were little, we sat right here at this very spot and we talked about some of the problems you had getting along with the neighbour kids.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That was different. They were threatened by my intelligence and too stupid to know that’s why they hated me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-21"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Oh baby, they knew very well why they hated you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I can’t believe you bought a red cowboy hat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Hello? I’m wearing a red turtleneck. Plus, it was the only boys’ large they had.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I’m sorry, this does not look like Texas. Where’s the tumbleweeds? Where’s the saloons?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Saloons?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yeah, like in the movies I saw growing up in India. You know, uh, Four for Texas, Yellow Rose of Texas.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>This neighbourhood is more Texas Chainsaw Massacre.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I was really hoping to see a cattle drive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What can I tell you? They probably have steaks on sale at that big-ass Costco over there.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Will you please take that stupid hat off?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No, I want to blend in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>To what? Toy Story?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Hi, boys.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Howdy, ma’am.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Howdy to you, too. You got here quick.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>– We took the red-eye.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Well, come on in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Thank you kindly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Can I… Can I get you something to drink?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh, no, thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>If y’all don’t mind, I got a hankerin’ for a Lone Star beer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>There’s no alcohol in this household. Stop talking like that and lose the hat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Sorry. I’ll take a diet Yoo-Hoo if you have it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>You’ll take a Cola.* What about you? Radge, isn’t it? Oh, you still having trouble talking to the ladies? Because, you know, at our church we have a woman who’s an amazing healer. Mostly she does, uh, crutch and wheelchair people, but I bet she’d be willing to take a shot at whatever Third World demon is running around inside of you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh, if you don’t mind, Mrs. Cooper, there’s a 3:05 nonstop back to Los Angeles, and you have no idea how much I want to be on it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-17"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>A girl?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh, yes, ma’am.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-19"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Oh, good. I’ve been praying for you. Oh, Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What are they doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>We came to apologize.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-22"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-23"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>And bring you home. So, why don’t you pack up your stuff and we’ll head back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-24"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, this is my home now. Thanks to you, my career is over and I will spend the rest of my life here in Texas trying to teach evolution to creationists.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-25"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>You watch your mouth, Shelly. Everyone’s entitled to their opinion.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-26"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Evolution isn’t an opinion, it’s fact.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-27"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>And that is your opinion.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-28"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I forgive you. Let’s go home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-29"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Don’t tell me prayer doesn’t work.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>How about that? I finally caught a break.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Uh-huh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You know how they say when friends have sex it can get weird?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Why does it have to get weird?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I don’t know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I mean, we were friends, and now we’re more than friends. We’re whatever this is. But why label it, right? I mean, it is what it is and…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Leonard?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>It’s weird.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Totally.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>