<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Howard (on the phone)</speaker><content>Yeah, I miss you, too, sweetie. Listen, I got to go, but I’ll see you tonight? Okay. Bye-bye. Yeah, bye-bye. No, you hang up first. Hello?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Dude, I’m glad you finally got a girlfriend, but do you have to do all that lovey-dovey stuff in front of those of us who don’t?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Actually, he might have to. There’s an economic concept known as a positional good in which an object is only valued by the possessor because it’s not possessed by others. The term was coined in 1976 by economist Fred Hirsch to replace the more colloquial, but less precise neener-neener.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>That’s not true. My happiness is not dependent on my best friend being miserable and alone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Although, I’d be lying if I said it wasn’t a little bit of a perk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Who’s miserable and alone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh. I used to be like that. Then I got a girlfriend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>In pre-1976 terms, neener-neener.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey, what are you and Bernadette doing for your first Valentine’s Day?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, I am pulling out all the stops. There’s a $39.95 lover’s special at P.F. Chang’s. Egg rolls, dumplings, bottomless wok, and you get your picture taken on the big marble horse out front.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Given that Saint Valentine was a third century Roman priest who was stoned and beheaded, wouldn’t a more appropriate celebration of the evening be taking one’s steady gal to witness a brutal murder?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I understand your point, but given a choice, Jews always go with Chinese food.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Well, if anyone’s interested, I’ll be spending this Valentine’s Day the same way I spend every Valentine’s Day. Buying a rotisserie chicken from the supermarket, taking it home, standing over the sink and eating it out of the package with my bare hands like an animal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, so to sum up: one giant marble horse, one asinine comment, one lonely man and his chicken. And let’s see, who’s left? Oh, that’s right. My plans. Isn’t anyone going to ask?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Fine, tell us you’re going to have sex with Penny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That’s not what I was going to tell you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>It’s okay. I don’t mind hearing about your sex life. It’s his that bugs me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Guess who the university is sending to Switzerland to attend a conference and see the CERN supercollider on February 14?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Professor Norton, although, God knows why. He hasn’t published anything of note since he won that Nobel Prize.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-22"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Actually, Professor Norton can’t make it. He threw his back out rock climbing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-23"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I heard he threw his back out climbing on his new girlfriend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-24"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>The big-boobed weather girl on Channel 2?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-25"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>That’s the one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-26"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>In any case, they’re asking me to fill in for him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-27"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>In Switzerland or with the big-boobed weather girl?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-28"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Switzerland. And I get to bring a guest!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-29"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, man!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-30"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No way, dude!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-31"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>This is incredible! I’m so happy, I’m not even going to question their judgment in picking you. I’m just going to run home and start packing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-32"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Why wouldn’t you take Penny?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-33"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I am taking Penny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-34"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh. Well, then I anticipate an awkward situation when you get home.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, you got a minute?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Of course, my good friend. Come in. Help me out, which ski hat says après supercollider?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, I’m not taking you to Switzerland.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, of course you are. Who else would you take?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Penny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What? That’s absurd. Penny has no interest in subatomic particle research.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yes, but it’ll be Valentine’s Day. We can go sightseeing and skiing and make love in front of a roaring fire in the shadow of the snowcapped Alps.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>But Penny has no interest in subatomic particle research.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m sorry, Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Sorry? I’ve been dreaming about going to the Large Hadron Collider since I was nine years old.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, well, I’ve been dreaming about spending Valentine’s Day with a girl since I was six.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Shame on you! That’s no dream for a scientist!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, what’s the big surprise?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Just a minute. This tray contains clues as to what you and I are going to be doing on Valentine’s Day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh. Wow. Okay. Let’s see. We’ve got, uh, milk chocolate, Swiss cheese, fondue. My lactose-intolerant boyfriend is going to eat all this, then I’m going to climb on his back and rocket to the moon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No. But it does involve air travel. Okay, um, let me slice this Swiss cheese with my Swiss army knife, and then you can wash it down with a cup of Swiss Miss instant cocoa.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, I’m starting to think Swiss is key here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh-huh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>We’re going to Disneyland and ride the Matterhorn?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>How does that involve air travel?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>We’re going to Disney World and ride the Matterhorn?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, sweetie, this started out fun, but I’m over it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>We’re going to Switzerland to see the CERN supercollider! And ski. We’ll also go skiing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>We’re going skiing in Switzerland?!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, you’ll ski, I’ll fall, but, yeah, we will be in Switzerland for Valentine’s Day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, my God, Leonard! That’s incredible!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Not so fast. You might want to hold off on lighting your rabeliechtli, Penny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>My Rabe-what-ly?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Rabeliechtli. It means turnip light and refers to a traditional lantern hand-carved from a root vegetable and used to celebrate certain Swiss festivals. Which you will not be celebrating because, A, these festivals occur in the fall, and B, you will not be going to Switzerland.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, we’ve been through this. I’m taking Penny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Afraid not. Do you recognize this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Not the roommate agreement.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Indeed, the roommate agreement. I call your attention to the Friendship Rider in Appendix C, Future Commitments. Number 37, in the event one friend is ever invited to visit the Large Hadron Collider, now under construction in Switzerland, he shall invite the other friend to accompany him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-23"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, for God’s sakes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-24"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You actually put that in an agreement?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-25"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah. We also put in what happens if one of us wins a MacArthur Grant, or if one of us gets superpowers, or if one of us is bitten by a zombie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-26"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>He can’t kill me, even if I turn.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-27"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Is there anything in there about if one of you gets a girlfriend?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-28"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, that seemed a little farfetched.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-29"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, do you really expect to enforce this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-30"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’ve lived up to all my commitments under the agreement. At least once a day I ask how you are, even though I simply don’t care. I no longer stage spontaneous biohazard drills after 10 pm And I abandoned my goal to master Tuvan throat singing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-31"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, I know I shouldn’t ask, but what is…?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-32"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-33"><speaker>Sheldon (after demonstrating)</speaker><content>I’d be much further along if I’d been allowed to practice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-34"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Look, Sheldon, I know it’s in the agreement, and if you turn into a zombie, I promise I will not kill you. In fact, I’ll even let you eat my brains. But I am taking Penny to Switzerland.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-35"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Is that your final decision?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-36"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-37"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Very well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-38"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>It’s not over, is it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-39"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What do you think? </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Got a bit of traffic this morning, huh? Think it’s gonna rain? Instead of underpants, I covered my crotch with potato salad this morning. Thoughts? Okay, I know what’ll cheer you up, let’s play one of your driving games.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right. This game is called Traitors. I will name three historical figures, you put them in order of the heinousness of their betrayal. Benedict Arnold, Judas, Dr. Leonard Hofstadter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You really think I belong with Benedict Arnold and Judas?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You’re right. Judas had the decency to hang himself after what he did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Come on, Sheldon. Can’t you at least try to understand how much this means to me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Round two, Leonard Hofstadter, Darth Vader, Rupert Murdoch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Rupert Murdoch?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>He owns Fox, and they cancelled Firefly. Hint, he and Darth Vader are tied for number 2.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’m sorry I couldn’t hang with you last night. I had a date with Bernadette.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I know. I saw the Tweet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>So, what did you end up doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Not much. Nuked a burrito. Prayed to the Hindu god Urvashi that your bowels would loosen and your penis would droop like a willow tree.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You seen Sheldon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No. Is he still mad about the supercollider?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah. He thinks I betrayed him. I mean, come on, what would you guys do if you were me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’d take Sheldon to Switzerland.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Seriously?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Absolutely. And I’d leave him there. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>What the hell is that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh, let’s see. Yup, 30 pieces of silverware.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Morning, old chum.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What’s going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’ve made you breakfast. Juice, coffee, and pancakes in the shape of some of your favorite fictional characters. See, here’s Frodo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You made Frodo pancakes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, I used coconut shavings to do the hair on his feet. If you need to void your bladder before eating, I can keep them warm with this beret that I thoroughly laundered and pressed into service as a pancake cosy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Why are you doing this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It’s by way of an apology for my recent behaviour. I’ve had some time to reflect and I’ve come to realize that friendship is not an aggregation of written agreements. It’s a result of two people respecting and caring for each other. Butterscotch scone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Thanks. It’s good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What you’re tasting is respect and affection. And about a pound of Crisco. After you’ve finished breakfast, I thought we could spend the day watching the final season of Babylon 5 with director commentary.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You hate Babylon 5.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I do. It fails as drama, science fiction, and it’s hopelessly derivative. But you like it, and you’re my friend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, great. Still not taking you to Switzerland.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Drat. No Frodo for you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hello.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hello.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Alright, let’s dispense with the friendly banter, I believe you know why I’m here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, I always figured it was to study us, discover our weaknesses, and report back to your alien overlords.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes, amusing. Extraordinary intelligence might well appear extraterrestrial to you, but let me be more specific. I believe you know why I’m here in the laundry room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Better acoustics for your throat singing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Sheldon (trying it)</speaker><content>It’s actually not bad. But my true purpose in being here will be revealed in this brief PowerPoint presentation. Lights. Why Sheldon Cooper, PhD, should go to Switzerland to see the CERN supercollider. A PowerPoint presentation by Sheldon Cooper, PhD.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, for God’s sakes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Here we have a highly gifted researcher in the field of particle physics whose work has brought him to the precipice of forever changing mankind’s understanding of the universe. AKA me. And here we have a waitress brushing her teeth with her finger. AKA you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I’m sorry. Is this supposed to be buttering me up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Please hold all questions to the end of the presentation. This is the Large Hadron Collider at CERN in Switzerland, the product of decades of planning and construction. It is a Mecca for physicists the world over. This is Bath and Body Works on Colorado Boulevard. They sell scented soaps and lotions, some of which contain glitter. Now, let’s see if we can match the individual to the appropriate destination.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, show’s over.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, it’s not. I’ve got five more slides.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sheldon, this is Leonard’s decision. He invited me to Switzerland, and I intend to go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Very well. Enjoy yourself. You’re going to be in the presence of something that I’ve dreamed of seeing for decades. I just hope you’ll be able to appreciate the magnitude of where you are and what it represents.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I’ll talk to Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You will?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yes. If it means that much to you, you should go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>Sheldon (Hugging her)</speaker><content>Oh, Penny, thank you!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-20"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You’re welcome.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Since I rarely hug, I’m relying on your expertise regarding duration.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-22"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I think we’re there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, good. Bye-bye.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You know what? Even though I don’t have a girlfriend, I can still have a good time on Valentine’s Day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Trust me, you can’t. I’ve tried.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No, no, no, I’m going to have a me day. First I’m going to go to one of those spas in Koreatown, take a steam and get a massage. Then I’m going to stop at a pet store and get licked by puppies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, I need to talk to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right, my friend. Would you like some cholermus?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Some what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Cholermus. It’s a traditional Swiss breakfast dish. I’m preparing my gastrointestinal system for the exotic cuisine of Switzerland.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You’re not going to Switzerland!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, but I am. Didn’t Penny tell you the good news?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>She told me that you went behind my back to guilt her into letting you go instead of her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes, that good news.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, forget it. I was the one who was invited, I get to decide who goes with me, and it’s Penny, not you!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Howard, could you lower the lights? I have a short PowerPoint presentation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t need to see your presentation. This discussion is over!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s a somewhat ambiguous response. Am I going or not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, at this point, I would go by myself before I would take you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Really?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, really.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well then, you leave me no alternative. From this moment forward, we can be roommates, but we will no longer be friends.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m sorry you feel that way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I don’t think you’re fully aware of the ramifications here, Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-22"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Why don’t you enlighten me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>With the friendship clause of our roommate agreement nullified you are no longer entitled to accompany me to go swimming at Bill Gates’ house should I be invited.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-24"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Ooh, that’s gotta sting.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Just think, this time tomorrow we’ll be in Geneva, Switzerland for our first Valentine’s Day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I know! I went shopping today and bought special undies for the occasion.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Thermal? ‘Cause it’s gonna be cold.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Think it through, Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Leonard (Penny sneezes)</speaker><content>Gesundheit. Or as they say in Switzerland, gesundheit. You getting a cold?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, no, it’s probably just allergies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Do you want an allergy pill? ‘Cause I have ’em all. Prescription, nonprescription, foreign, domestic, experimental.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Do any of them work?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Not really, I’m just an enthusiast.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Penny? You okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Did that sound okay to you? Do not come in here!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What’s going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I’m having a tea party. What do you think’s going on? I think I might have the flu. Or the plague.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, our plane leaves at 9 a.m. Do you think you’ll feel better by then?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yep. ‘Cause I’m gonna be dead.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey, Sheldon? Listen, Penny is pretty sick and she’s not going to be able to go to Switzerland. So if you’re still interested, you’re welcome to come. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Great. I’ll start packing. In a minute.  Oh, look, it’s the cholermus.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Here’s your soup.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Chicken?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>With the little stars?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Heated to 180 degrees?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Why don’t I pour it in your lap, and you can tell me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You don’t have to be mean. I’m sick.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, well, I’m sick, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Not my problem. I just don’t understand how this happened to me. I’m scrupulous about my hygiene. I regularly disinfect my hands, and I avoid contact with other people on general principle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I don’t know what to tell you, Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>Sheldon (remembering the hug)</speaker><content>It’s you! I touched you!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Happy Valentine’s Day.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, my goodness, look at this room! Champagne! Roses! Oh, and little chocolates! This is going to be the best Valentine’s Day ever.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, I forgot about all this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>But I never will.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>