<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>So two years later, there’s a knock on the door, guy opens it, and there on his porch is the snail, who says, “What the heck was all that about?”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I don’t really get it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Well, see, it took two years for the snail to…  not important.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Can I ask you a question?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Where do you think this is going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>To be honest, I was hoping at least second base.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>You’re so funny. You’re like a stand-up comedian.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>A Jewish stand-up comedian, that’d be new.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Actually, I think a lot of them are Jewish.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No, I was just… never mind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Look, Howard, this is our third date and we both know what that means.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>We do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Sex.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You’re kidding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>But I need to know whether you’re looking for a relationship or a one-night stand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Okay, just to be clear, there’s only one correct answer, right? It’s not like chicken or fish on an airplane?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Maybe you need to think about it a little.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You know, it’s not unheard of for a one-night stand to turn into a relationship.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-20"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Call me when you figure it out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-21"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Three dates means sex? Who knew?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Greetings, homies, homette.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Why are you back from your date so early?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>In romance, as in show business, always leave them wanting more.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What exactly does that mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>He struck out.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Hey, did either of you guys know that three dates with the same woman is the threshold for sex?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Actually, I’ve never had three dates with the same woman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>With Penny and me, it took two years. Now that I think about it, that was three dates.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Okay, well, before you and Penny hooked up, did she ask for any kind of commitment?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, she was pretty clear about wanting to keep her options open.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Sheldon (arriving)</speaker><content>I have something to announce, but out of respect for convention, I will wait for you to finish your current conversation. What are you talking about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>The cultural paradigm in which people have sex after three dates.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I see. Now, are we talking date, the social interaction, or date, the dried fruit?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Never mind, what’s your announcement?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, good, my turn. Well, this is very exciting and I wanted you to be among the first to know…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>Hey, Cooper, I hear you’re going to be on the wadio with Ira Fwatow from Science Fwiday next week.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Thank you, Kripke, for depriving me of the opportunity to share my news with my friends.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>My pweasure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>My thank you was not sincere.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>But my pweasure is. Let me ask you a question, at what point did National Public Wadio have to start scwaping the bottom of the bawwel for its guests? Eh, don’t answer, it’s wetowical.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Why are you such a stupid head? That is also rhetorical. I’m sorry you had to hear that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Are you really going to be on NPR?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes, they’re interviewing me by phone from my office, regarding the recent so-called discovery of magnetic monopoles in spin-ices. It’s pledge week and they’re trying to goose the ratings with a little controversy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Very cool, congratulations.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Thank you. My mother is very excited. She’s convening her Bible study group to listen in, and then pray for my soul.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-21"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I was on the radio once. I called in to Fever 104 FM New Delhi and was the fourth person to say the phrase that pays, “Fever 104, आज के नये अच्छे संगीत का घर.” That means: “Fever 104, home of the really good current music.” It’s much catchier in Hindi.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right. These are the talking points for my NPR interview tomorrow. I need to make sure that they’re simple enough for the less educated in the audience to understand. Howard, look this over and tell me what’s unclear to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Excuse me, I have a master’s degree in engineering from the Massachusetts Institute of Technology. It required the completion of 144 units of grad work and an original thesis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes. Look this over and tell me what’s unclear to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You know, when Sheldon gives you homework, you don’t have to do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>In fact, it’s better if you don’t, otherwise it makes the rest of us look bad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hi, guys.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hello.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yo, Raj, talk to me. I’m sorry, just screwing with you. Hey, Howard, why haven’t you called Bernadette?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Did she say something?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, she said she hasn’t heard from you in a week. I thought you liked her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I do, yeah, but she wants a commitment and I’m not sure she’s my type.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>She agreed to go out with you for free. What more do you need?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Look, Bernadette is really nice. I just always thought when I finally settle down into a relationship, it would be with someone, you know, different.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Different how?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Well, you know, more like Megan Fox from Transformers, or Katee Sackhoff from Battlestar Galactica.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Are you high?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You’d have a better shot with the three-breasted Martian hooker from Total Recall.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Okay, now you’re just being unrealistic. Anyway, that movie was like 20 years ago, imagine how saggy those things would be.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-20"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Howard, you’re going to throw away a great girl like Bernadette because you’re holding out for some ridiculous fantasy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-21"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Hey, just because you settled doesn’t mean I have to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-22"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Excuse me, I’m sitting here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-23"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey, I did not settle for Leonard. I mean, obviously, he isn’t the kind of guy I usually go out with, you know, physically.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-24"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Again, I’m right here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-25"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>My point is, I do not judge a book by its cover. I am interested in the person underneath.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-26"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I am here, right? You see me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-27"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Hey, I’m interested in what’s inside people, too, but why is it wrong to want those insides wrapped up in, say, the delicious caramel that is Halle Berry?  Yes, you’re delicious caramel, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-28"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>All right, you know what, I will tell you why it’s wrong…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-29"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Excuse me, may I interject?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-30"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-31"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Biologically speaking, Howard is perfectly justified in seeking out the optimum mate for the propagation of his genetic line.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-32"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Thank you, Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-33"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Now, whether that propagation is in the interest of humanity is, of course, an entirely different question.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Radio</speaker><content>This is Ira Flatow and you’re listening to NPR’s Science Friday. Joining us today by phone from his office in Pasadena, California is Dr. Sheldon Cooper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>Oh, this is going to be a wiot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Radio</speaker><content>Thanks for being with us today, Dr. Cooper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>My pleasure, Ira.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Ira</speaker><content>Now, let’s talk about magnetic monopoles. Can you explain to our audience just what a monopole is?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Of course. First, consider an ordinary magnet which has,  as even the most uneducated in your audience must know, two poles,  a north and south pole. If you cut that in half, you have two smaller magnets, each with its own north and south pole.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Ira</speaker><content>Uh, Dr. Cooper, I think there might be something wrong with our connection.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Sheldon (even higher pitch)</speaker><content>No, I hear you fine. As I was saying, an ordinary magnet has two poles. The primary characteristic of a monopole is that it has only one pole, hence, monopole.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>A requirement for string theory, or M-theory, if you will, is the existence of such monopoles. I, myself, led an expedition to the Arctic Circle in search of said particles. Kripke, I found the nozzle! I’m going to kill you!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>So nice you could join me this evening. You’re looking lovely as always.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Katee Sackhoff</speaker><content>Thanks, Howard. Always nice to be part of your masturbatory fantasies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Come on, Katee, don’t make it sound so cheap.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Katee</speaker><content>I’m sorry, fiddling with yourself in the bathtub is a real class act.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Thank you. So, shall we get started?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Katee</speaker><content>Sure. But can I ask you a question first?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You want to play Cylon and colonist?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Katee</speaker><content>No. I want to know why you’re playing make-believe with me when you could be out with a real woman tonight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You mean, Bernadette?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Katee</speaker><content>No, I mean Princess Leia. Of course I mean Bernadette. She’s a wonderful girl and she really likes you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I know, but she’s not you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Katee</speaker><content>I’m not me. The real me is in Beverly Hills going out with a tall, handsome, rich guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Really? Tall?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Katee</speaker><content>Six-four.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Ouch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>Katee</speaker><content>The point is, you’ve got a wonderful girl in your life, and you’re ignoring her in order to spend your nights in the bathtub with a mental image and a wash cloth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>Howard’s Mother</speaker><content>Howard! What are you doing in there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-18"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’m taking a bath!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-19"><speaker>Howard’s Mother</speaker><content>I hope that’s all you’re doing! We share that tub!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-20"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Don’t remind me!  Oh, man. All soaped up and no place to go.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>How ya doin’, buddy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I was humiliated on national radio. How do you think I’m doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Come on, it wasn’t that bad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What do you want?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Raj (in a munchkin voice)</speaker><content>We represent the Lollipop Guild, and we want you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, so Kripke played a joke on you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It wasn’t funny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I thought it was funny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Raj.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You laughed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Did you laugh?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I fell on the floor. All right, he got you, you can get him back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I refuse to sink to his level.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You can’t sink. With all that helium in you, you’re lucky you don’t float away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Are you really admitting defeat?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I never admit defeat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>However, on an unrelated topic, I am never getting out of this bed again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What if you could make Kripke look even sillier than he made you look?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-20"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I don’t think that’s possible, dude.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You’re not helping.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-22"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I didn’t come to help, I came to mock.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-23"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, what you need to do is figure out a way to exact vengeance on Kripke, like, uh, like, how the Joker got back at Batman for putting him in the Arkham Asylum for the Criminally Insane.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-24"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>That’s true. He didn’t just stay there and talk about his feelings with the other psychotic villains. He, he broke out and poisoned Gotham’s water supply.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-25"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, I suppose I could poison Kripke.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-26"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, no.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-27"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It’s a simple matter. There are several toxic chemicals that’d be untraceable in an autopsy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-28"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, uh, that’s the spirit, but, um, let’s dial it back to a non-lethal form of vengeance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-29"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh! How about we put awhoopee cushion on his office chair? He’ll sit down, it’ll sound like he’s flatulent, even though he’s not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-30"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Let’s keep thinking.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, gee, you’re too late. Scarlett Johansson and Wonder Woman were just in here trolling around for neurotic, little weasels.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, I came to talk to Bernadette. She’s working today, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yes, but I don’t think she wants to see you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Why not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Come on, Howard. You hurt her feelings by not calling her all week. Plus, I’ve kind of been talkin’ some smack about ya.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Hello, Howard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Wait, Bernadette, I need to talk to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I can’t now, I’m working.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>This will only take a second. You asked me to think about where our relationship was going, and I did. Bernadette? Will you marry me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Is this more comedy that I don’t understand?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No. I’m serious. I’m never going to find another girl like you who likes me and is, you know, real.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>So, this isn’t a joke?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Then you’re insane.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I prefer to think of myself as quirky.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Howard, we’ve only been on three dates. We haven’t even had sex yet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Fair enough. When’s your break?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Wow. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Don’t you just hate when this happens?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-20"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Wow.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right, how’s this for revenge? A solution of hydrogen peroxide, and one of saturated potassium iodide.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>What’s this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Mountain Dew. Ah, refreshing. Now, we’re going to combine these chemicals with ordinary dish soap, creating a little exothermic release of oxygen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Foamy vengeance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes, exactly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>This is brilliant, Sheldon. How are we going to deploy it in Kripke’s office?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Already taken care of. Observe. This is a live shot of Kripke’s lab via a mini webcam I was able to install, thanks to a dollar bill discreetly placed in the night janitor’s shirt pocket. At the same time, I also secured large quantities of these chemicals above the tiles in the drop ceiling.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, Sheldon, you remind me of a young Lex Luthor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You flatter me, sir.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Let me guess, motion sensors?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>The reaction will be triggered when Kripke reaches the center of the room. Mwah, ha, ha.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I gotta say, I am really impressed. This is truly the Sheldon Cooper way to get even. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It may be low-tech, but I still maintain the whoopee cushion has comic validity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Here comes Kripke!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Who is that with him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I believe that’s the president of the university.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>And the board of directors. Abort! Abort!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>There is no abort.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-19"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Well, how could you not put in an abort?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I made a boo-boo, all right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-21"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>I think the board will weally appweciate how well we’re using that NSA gwant, Pwesident Seibert. Wight here we have a micwo-contwolled pwasma… </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-22"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Wow. Looks like the Ganges on laundry day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-23"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>At least they don’t know it was you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-24"><speaker>Sheldon (on Kripke’s computer in the lab)</speaker><content>Hello, Kripke. This classic prank comes to you from the malevolent mind of Sheldon Cooper. If you’d like to see the look on your stupid face, this video is being instantly uploaded to YouTube. Oh, and a hat tip to Leonard Hofstadter and Raj Koothrappali for their support and encouragement in this enterprise.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-25"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Well, I’m going back to India. What’s your plan?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey, here’s your tip from table seven.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Oh, thanks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Mm-hmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Howard (on the stage, into a microphone)</speaker><content>Testing. Check. Check two.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Oh, now what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You want me to throw him out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>No, that’s okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Are you sure? He’s small. I bet I can get a nice, tight spiral on him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I want to dedicate this number to a great gal who I’ve done wrong.   Bernadette, I am so sorry for trying to propose to you, Bernadette, you found it creepy but that’s just the kind of thing I do. I know now it was too soon to talk of love. It was just a crazy idea that came to me in my tub. But, Bernadette, give me one more chance, sweet Bernadette, I’ll get the hang of this thing they call romance, sweet Bernadette, I dream to once again kiss your lips, sweet Bernadette. Sincerely yours, Howard Wolowitz, Bernadette…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, I am so sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Are you kidding? That’s the most romantic thing anyone’s ever done for me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Howard (still singing)</speaker><content>…Bernadette! Thank you, Cheesecake Factory!</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>