<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Ma, Ma, calm down. Listen to me. I know it says click with the mouse, but on a laptop, the trackpad is the mouse. Now, put your finger on it. Doesn’t matter which finger. Good choice. Now move it down to your e-mail icon. Yeah, the little envelope. What do you mean, what does it look like? It looks like an envelope! Fine, you don’t like the computer, don’t use it! Sure, we can exchange it for a salad spinner. Good-bye!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>That’s a Hanukkah present you’re regretting, huh?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I won’t say that all senior citizens who can’t master technology should be publicly flogged, but if we made an example of one or two, it might give the others incentive to try harder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I had a great idea. You know how we’re always having to stop and solve differential equations, like when you’re doing Fourier analysis, or using the Schrodinger equation?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Howard doesn’t. He’s only an engineer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I was thinking, we could write a little app that would use handwriting recognition, and then run it through a symbolic evaluation engine. You just use your smartphone, take a picture of the equation and bam!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You know what’s a great app? The one that makes fart noises.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You know, Leonard, that’s actually a valid idea. Very good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Can you say that and not make it sound like I’m a cat who learned how to use the toilet?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No. The two achievements are equally surprising and equally admirable, though if pressed, I’d have to give a slight edge to the cat. I’ll save you the pain and nervousness of waiting for the answer. I agree to be part of your project. Congratulations.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, yay for me. What about you guys? I can’t promise anything, but people do make money off stuff like this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>A few extra bucks would be nice. I could finally move out of my mother’s house.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Where would you go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I always dreamed about building a little place of my own over the garage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You know, if I made more money, I could take time off from work and give pretty girls submarine rides.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What’s that? Some weird sex thing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No. You take pretty girls underwater in your private submarine, and you show them fish. Why does everything have to be dirty with you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I was thinking we could work on this at night, and then maybe in a couple of weeks, we’ll have ourselves an app to sell.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Sounds like we’re in business.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-20"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I think we should take a picture to capture this moment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-23"><speaker>Raj (pressing button on camera phone. Camera makes a fart noise)</speaker><content>Was that the best 99 cents I ever spent, or what?</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I checked the App Store. No one is doing handwriting-recognition differential equation solving.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, dear Lord, shush.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You have so few good ideas, Leonard. And you’re just going to spill the beans in front of an outsider?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Who, me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Sheldon, I don’t think Penny cares about handwriting-recognition based differential…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Sheldon (singing)</speaker><content>The stars at night are big and bright, deep in the heart of Texas.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>She’s not going to steal our idea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What idea?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>We’re gonna write an application…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Sheldon (singing)</speaker><content>The prairie sky is wide and high, deep in the heart…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, stop, stop!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Of Texas.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Whatever your secret is, I’m sure it’s boring, so I’m not interested.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It’s not boring at all. You see, in higher order mathematics, there are certain sets of equations that…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Bored.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Satisfied?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hardly. Consider this unlikely but very plausible scenario. A young woman alone in the big city. Her ridiculous dream of becoming an actress lies shattered about her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey, wait a minute.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Well, hang on. Let’s see where he’s going.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Then it hits her. How is she going to survive? I mean, she has no prospects, no marketable skills. And then one day, she meets a group of geniuses and their friend Howard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-22"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Hey, I…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-23"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hang on. Let’s see where he’s going.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-24"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>She befriends them, and then lies in wait until they reveal a marketable idea, which she steals and sells to the highest bidder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-25"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That is ridiculous.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-26"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, is it? Well let’s see you come up with an explanation as to why this woman hangs out with us all the time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-27"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, great. You know what? I’ve already mooched dinner off you guys. I don’t need to listen to this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-28"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>There’s your answer, free food.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-29"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right, I’ve taken the liberty of drafting these workflow charts which outline our various duties and the path we will follow as we develop our ground-breaking new app.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-30"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Hey, why am I in charge of phone support? Seems a bit racist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-31"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>A customer service representative with an Indian accent will create the impression we’re a vast enterprise that uses overseas call centres.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-32"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh. Very clever. But still racist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-33"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Duly noted, Steve from Wichita.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-34"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Why am I listed as your executive assistant?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-35"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Because the word secretary has fallen into disrepute. FYI, my mother’s birthday is coming up. I’m going to need you to pick up a present.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-36"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, we need to stop for a minute.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-37"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Leonard, please, we can talk during our break. We have one coming up at midnight. We’ll need snacks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-38"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, you’re not in charge. It’s my idea. I’m in charge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-39"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, of course you are. Look at the organizational chart. You’re clearly listed as founder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-40"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, yes, and you’re listed as Chief Executive Officer, Chief Financial Officer and Chief Operating Officer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-41"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You missed Chief Science Officer, Chairman of the Board, and Head of the Secret Santa Committee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-42"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay. You need to get clear on this right now. I am in charge of this project.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-43"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Ooh. Leonard’s going all alpha nerd on Sheldon’s ass.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-44"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right. All right, I’m not going to argue with you. Sheldon Cooper is nothing if not a team player. Dr. Hofstadter, you have the conn.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-45"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Thank you. I thought we might start by talking about the user interface.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-46"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, dear Lord, we’re doomed.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>So this button here will allow you to scan a new equation, but over here, you can press this, and just substitute new values for the coefficients.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Good one, boss.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>This diagram. I assume you were opening with a joke. It certainly buoyed up this employee’s esprit de corps.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It’s not a joke. It’s the real design.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>In that case, may I offer 27 little tweaks to make it slightly less embarrassing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, I think this will work. Let’s just try it my way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, I’m, I’m sorry. I assumed that you wanted candid truth-telling from your employees, but I realize now, you want the mindless nattering of complacent yes-men.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Are you done?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>If you say so, boss.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>So right now, this button-press event is just triggering a dummy procedure call…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>How about this for the app name? The Surprisingly Helpful Equation-Linked Differential Optimized Numerator.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>So it spells Sheldon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Does it? A happy accident.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>We’re not doing names now. Howard?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Like I was saying, right now it’s just a dummy procedure, but eventually, it will drop us into…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right, fine. If we’re not going to give it a name, can we at least give it a secret code designation?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, but hear me out. The atomic bomb was The Manhattan Project. Windows 95 was originally Project Chicago. For our app, I would humbly suggest Project Nodlehs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That’s just Sheldon backwards.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Another happy accident.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>We’re not wasting time with names right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I see. Is that decision open for discussion?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Is the decision to not discuss it open for discussion?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Again, right now it’s just a dummy procedure, but eventually, it will drop us into…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I call for a vote of no confidence and an immediate change in leadership.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh Sheldon, stop it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>When in the course of human events, it becomes necessary to dissolve the bonds that tie three competent scientists together…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That’s enough, Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right, let’s get right to the vote. Show of hands all those opposed to Leonard and his reign of tyranny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-23"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, that’s it, you’re fired.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-24"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Really? Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-25"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Because you’re impossible to work with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-26"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I see. And is that open for discussion?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh. Good morning, shoemaker. I think you’ll be pleased with what the elves were up to last night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>But I fired you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, I know. I’m now an independent contractor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, you are now nothing. You have no connection to this project whatsoever.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>But I made it better.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t want it better. I want it my way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, that speaks volumes, doesn’t it? All right, I suppose I’ll go put on my bus pants.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What the hell are bus pants?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>They are pants one wears over one’s regular pants when one sits on bus seats that other people have previously sat on. But perhaps from your lofty heights atop the corporate ladder, you’ve lost touch with the struggles of the common man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Look, I’m still happy to drive you to work. Nothing’s changed in that regard. We’re still roommates, we’re still friends.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Except you identified me, your best friend, as a gangrenous limb that needed to be severed from the organism and tossed away. The desperate act of a little man with a big Napoleon complex.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You know what? Go put on your bus pants.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Mm. Last night, I had a dream we got so rich from the app, you and I bought matching side-by-side mansions. But there was a secret tunnel connecting your front yard to my back yard. What do you think that means?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>It means after we play handball, I’m showering at home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Good morning, Friend Howard. Friend Raj. I see you gentlemen are enjoying beverages. Perhaps they would taste better out of these.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>World’s Greatest Astrophysicist?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Don’t thank me. You earned it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Howard Wolowitz. Why not World’s Greatest Engineer?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m sorry. I typed that into the label maker, but I just couldn’t press enter. Now down to business. What would it take for you to abandon Leonard and join me in a rival company? Unless, of course, the mugs are sufficient, in which case, welcome aboard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>We’re not quitting on Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I understand. And your loyalty is admirable. But what if I were to up the ante?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>What are you talking about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Monogrammed key chains with a built-in laser pointer. No? How about can cosies emblazoned with our university mascot? Go, Beavers. I’ll be back.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Okay, let’s try this one. Spherical Hankel function.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hold on. That’s it!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Eureka!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Hey, we agreed when it was Eureka time, we were all gonna say it together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Fine. Let’s say it together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No. The moment has passed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Greetings, gentlemen. How goes your little project?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You mean, Project Lenwoloppali?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Ah, a combination of all your names. Very clever. I assume Koothranardowitz was taken?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>We’re actually scanning equations and getting good results.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, well then, by all means, carry on. I wouldn’t want to impede your progress.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Howard, did you solve the install time problem yet?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No. It’s a little tricky. I’m gonna try having it pick up the libraries dynam…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What are you doing?!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Playing the theremin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No. I mean, what are you doing with a theremin?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Playing it. I’ve loved the theremin from the first moment I heard the original Star Trek theme. And it’s been killing me that it just sits in my closet, gathering dust.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon! We’re working here!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s all right. I can barely hear you over my theremin.  Well, that was a little uncalled for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, that was completely called for. We need quiet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>So, your project is more important than mine?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-22"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, seeing as your project is to sabotage my project, yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Don’t beat around the bush, Leonard. If you don’t want me here, just say the word, and I’ll leave.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Could have beaten around the bush a little.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Sheldon (singing)</speaker><content>Nobody knows the trouble I’ve seen, nobody knows my sorrow-ow-ow-ow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What you doing? Trying to contact your home planet?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m practicing my theremin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Sheldon (singing)</speaker><content>Nobody knows the trouble I’ve seen. Glory, hallelujah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Something got you down, there, Sheldon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Leonard kicked me out of my own apartment. And his app team.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, honey, I’m sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>He wouldn’t drive me to work today. I had to wear my bus pants.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Is that so?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes. And they’re still sticky.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Aw.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Probably going to have to throw them away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey, you don’t need Leonard and his app. You can make one with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>With you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Seriously, I have a great idea for one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Is it better than your idea to move to Los Angeles and become a famous actress?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, look, when you see someone wearing shoes you like, you just snap a picture of them, and the app goes on the Internet to find out where you can buy them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s your app idea?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-20"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, you don’t like it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I didn’t say that. But no, I don’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-22"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Why not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, Penny, where do I begin? The simple-mindedness of your idea is exceeded only by its crass consumerism and banality.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-24"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>And Leonard didn’t want to work with you? Imagine that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-25"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I know, it’s baffling.  Nobody knows the trouble I’ve seen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-26"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sheldon, I’m gonna make some cocoa. Do you want some?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-27"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Do you make it with milk or water?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-28"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Milk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-29"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Real cocoa?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-30"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>That’s what it says on the packet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-31"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Do you have those little marshmallows?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-32"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-33"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, I suppose it’s appropriate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-34"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What does that mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-35"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>A disappointing drink for a disappointing day.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Hey, look at this. 20 people from the university have already signed up for our private beta.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m telling you, the Lenwoloppali Differential Equation Scanner meets a real need. We’ve got a hit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>What do you think we should sell it for?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Well, based on the fact that our potential market is about 70 or 80 guys, and you want a submarine, I’d say about a million dollars a pop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Well, what if we put out a lite version for half a million? You know, get the word of mouth going.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hi. I’m sorry to bother you guys, but you’ve got to come take your Sheldon back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What’s he doing in your apartment?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, he was moping down in the lobby, so I invited him over, and now I regret it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Why do you regret, uh, never mind, stupid question.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Look, can’t you just let him play with you until bedtime?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>We’re not playing. This is real work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>We’re going to be hundred-aires.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay. What if I got him to apologize and promise to behave?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Then I guess we would let him back on the app team, and while we’re doing that, you could take an aerial tour of L.A. on your flying pig.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay. Wait right here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I’ll tell you one thing. If I get rich enough, that’s the kind of girl I want to take on a submarine ride. And yes, that time, I meant it to be dirty.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Really? Leonard wants me back?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, yes. He says they are lost without you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, we sure saw that coming.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>That’s right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You know what I’m going to do? I am going to sit here and just let them stew.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, no, no. You know, they have suffered enough. Everybody’s suffered enough. The thing is, you’re going to have to offer him a face-saving way out of this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>How?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Say you’re sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, no. Mrs. Mary Cooper didn’t raise her no liars.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay. Um, how about this? You know how you’re always trying to learn about sarcasm?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I was being sarcastic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh. Good for you. So all you have to do here is say you’re sorry to Leonard, but say it sarcastically.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Of course. He will hear it as an attempt to mend fences, as opposed to the withering condemnation you and I will know it to be.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah. Yeah, that was my plan. All right. Come on. Let’s go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, by the way, thank you for the delicious cocoa.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-18"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, you’re welcome.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Boy, I’m getting good at this.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, now that you’re back on the team, let’s get you caught up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Before you begin, let me say again how deeply sorry I am for my earlier behaviour and how much I respect and admire your leadership.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Thank you. So as you can see, not only can you store your favourite equations, but you can forward them to your friends or post them on Facebook right from the app.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, I must say, I am impressed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Thanks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You all have clearly put in a lot of hard work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>We have.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>As a result, you have taken the most important step on the road to success, learning what not to do. Now, let’s start fresh. Howard, we’re going to need some tea.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, these are Uggs. These are Crocs. These are knockoff Manolo Blahniks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Bored.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Look, you said it yourself, we have to create a database before you can write an alga-thingy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Algorithm. You see, Penny, Alan Turing defined an algorithm…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Bored. Okay. These are Steve Maddens. These are Nine West. These are Target. Oh, but don’t they look like Chanel? These are Michael Kors. These are Roxy. These are Sachel’s. Oh, these are Betsy Johnson, they’re so cute…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>Sheldon (singing at the same time)</speaker><content>Nobody knows the trouble I’ve seen, nobody knows my sorrow…</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>