<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, seriously, I think I’ve finally figured out my problem with women.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>The capybara is the largest member of the rodent family.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What does that have to do with me and women?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Nothing. It was a desperate attempt to introduce an alternate topic of conversation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>My problem is, I don’t project confidence. So I decided that the next time I meet a woman I think is attractive, rather than holding back and being cautious, I’m going to assume the mantle of self-assurance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, yeah? What’s that look like?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hi. I’m Leonard. And you are beautiful. You pop, sparkle and buzz electric. I’m going to pick you up at eight, show you a night you will never forget.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Where are we going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Good news. I made it onto the team for the new Defence Department laser-equipped surveillance satellite.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Excuse me. If we’re changing topics, I believe I have first dibs with capybara, a rodent the size of a baby hippo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Congratulations Howard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Thanks. Listen, I have to get a security clearance, so you guys might be hearing from the FBI.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Whoa, whoa, whoa! I don’t want to speak to the FBI.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Why not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I’m brown and I talk funny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>They’re just doing a background check on me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>It doesn’t matter. They’ll find a reason to give me a one-way ticket back to Gandhi-ville. By the way, when I say that, it’s not offensive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Don’t be ridiculous, Raj. You’re here legally.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Nobody cares. Do you know how long it’s been since I got through airport security without being given a colonoscopy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You know, I try very hard to make our lunch hours educational and informative, but your insistence on talking about your own lives stymies me at every turn.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Fine, Sheldon, tell us about your giant rodents.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, you squandered your time with me, and the moment has now passed. Feast on your disappointment, much as the capybara feasts on its own waste.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, Bella, don’t you see? Edward’s only pushing you away because he loves you.  Coming.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Woman at Door</speaker><content>Dr. Koothrappali?  I’m Special Agent Page, FBI. May I come in?  I’d like to talk to you about Howard Wolowitz.  Oh, thank you. All right. Well, how long have you known Mr. Wolowitz?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Raj (Holds up finger to indicate he will be right back. Runs to kitchen. Tries to drink wine but bottle is empty. Looks in fridge and finds rum cake. Comes back stuffing a piece in his mouth)</speaker><content>Rum cake?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>No, thanks. Now, about Mr. Wolowitz.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Seven years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>I see.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I’m in this country legally, you know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>I’m sure you are. Now, to your knowledge, has Mr. Wolowitz ever committed a crime?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Of course not. I’m here on an H-1B visa, which means I can’t be associated in any way with crime or criminal activity. And I’m not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>Good. To your knowledge, does Mr. Wolowitz have any foreign contacts?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No, just me. Oh, there it is. Here comes a cavity search.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>Excuse me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Please don’t send me back to India, it’s so crowded. It’s like the whole country is one endless Comic-Con, except everybody’s wearing the same costume, Indian Guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>Dr. Koothrappali, I’m not…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I love this country! The-the baseball, the freedom, the rampant morbid obesity! From California to the New York Island, I’m a real Yankee Doodle boy!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>Dr. Koothrappali, please.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>My country ’tis of thee, duh duh duh liberty, It’s really great.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>So, when Howard said the FBI would be contacting me, I was expecting Mulder. Glad to see I got Scully.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>Who?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Mulder and Scully. X-Files. The truth is out there. Never mind. Uh, so, what would you like to know?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>You work with Mr. Wolowitz here at the university, correct?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yes. Of course, we’re in different departments. He’s an engineer and I’m an experimental physicist. You know, one of those guys who examines the building blocks of creation and says, Hello, maker of the universe, I see what you did there. Good one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>Right. Now, how would you characterize your relationship with Mr. Wolowitz?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Good. It’s a good relationship. Of course, most of my relationships are good. Probably because I exude confidence. People are drawn to that, you know? Confidence, not exuding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>Do you know of any groups Mr. Wolowitz is a member of?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You are beautiful, you know that? You pop, sparkle and buzz electric. I’m going to pick you up at eight, show you a night you will never forget.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>Sounds great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Really?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>Yeah. Can my six-foot-two Navy SEAL husband come with us?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Is that, oh, my, I didn’t see the ring with my glasses off, so, look at that, I’m starting to exude.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Want to get that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Not particularly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Could you get that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I suppose I could if I were asked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Would you please get that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Of course. Why do you have to make things so complicated?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>Dr. Cooper?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>I’m Special Agent Page, FBI.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You say you’re Special Agent Page, FBI.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>Here’s my I.D.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And here is my Justice League membership card. But that doesn’t prove I know Batman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>I just want to ask you a few questions about Howard Wolowitz.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh. All right. I doubt anyone would risk the stiff penalties for impersonating a federal officer just to ask questions about a minor league engineer with an unresolved Oedipal complex.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>For the record, I truly support the FBI in the mission which is expressed through their motto?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>Fidelity, bravery, integrity?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Correct. Now to business. 18 years ago, I sent the FBI Crime Lab samples from a bag of excrement that had been lit on fire on my front porch for fingerprinting and DNA analysis. Why haven’t I heard back yet?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>Well, the FBI Crime Lab does have a lot on its plate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s of little comfort to a nation attempting to scrape burning feces off its shoes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-21"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>Would you mind if we talked about Mr. Wolowitz now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>A little, but go on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-23"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>Thank you. Would you characterize him as responsible?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-24"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m going to answer that with a visual aid. This is my nine-disc complete Lord of the Rings trilogy blu-ray set.  Mr. Wolowitz borrowed it, damaged plastic retention hub number three, and then returned it to me, hoping I wouldn’t notice. Would you characterize that as responsible?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-25"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>That’s really not the sort of thing we’re interested in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-26"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You heard me say blu-ray, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-27"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>I did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-28"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Very well. Would you be interested in knowing that Mr. Wolowitz once snuck onto my World of Warcraft account and changed the name of a certain level-80 warlock from Sheldor to Smeldor?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-29"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>I’m afraid not. Is there anything else?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-30"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Is there anything else? Where would you like to start? He refuses to pay fines when he’s overdue with books I lend him. He crashed the Mars Rover while attempting to impress a woman. He recommended that I go see the third Matrix movie because it was, and I quote, just as good as the first one. If that’s not irresponsible, I don’t know what is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-31"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>The Mars Rover?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-32"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Did I say Mars Rover?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-33"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>You did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-34"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That was actually a poorly chosen example, as it had nothing to do with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-35"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>Yes, well, let’s talk about it anyway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-36"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I don’t want to. Not that my disinclination to discuss the topic should be interpreted as evidence of Howard Wolowitz’s culpability in the destruction of government property worth millions of dollars.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-37"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>Thank you, Dr. Cooper. I think I have all I need.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-38"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, good. I was afraid you were going to fixate on that Mars Rover incident.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Hey, buddies. Guess who didn’t get security clearance to work on the giant space laser?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Apparently, the background interviews didn’t go well. You guys wouldn’t know anything about that, would you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Well, actually, I may have gotten a little tipsy when I talked to her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>And I may have hit on her a little bit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I may have thrown up rum cake on her shoes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I see. Well, it’s good to know, when I need you guys, I can always count on you to step up and ruin everything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I feel awful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Ah, me, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>To tell you the truth, I thought if anyone was going to screw things up for Howard, it’d be Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, your expectations have been subverted. Aha.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What are you doing up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Sleep eludes me, Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Really? Maybe sleep has met you before.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Mockery? That’s all you have to offer?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m sorry. Why can’t you sleep?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Who knows? I haven’t watched any scary movies recently. I’m no longer obsessing over why the predicted mass of the quantum vacuum has little effect on the expansion of the universe. And it’s been weeks since I took that accidental sip of Red Bull.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Did something happen today that’s bothering you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, I did mention the Mars Rover incident to that FBI agent and probably cost Howard his security clearance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>But why should that keep me up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Because you feel guilty?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Interesting. So you’re saying my insomnia is caused by a guilty conscience.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Actually, you don’t have insomnia. You’re sleeping now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Excuse me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You’re having a guilt-ridden dream.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Do you have any evidence to support that hypothesis?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>How about that Gorn sitting on the couch?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That seems fairly conclusive.  No, Gorn, no. That’s where I sit.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Thank you for agreeing to see me, Agent Page.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>Thank you for filing a complaint with my superior, Dr. Cooper. I understand you want to recant your statement about Howard Wolowitz.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>Was your statement untrue?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>Then I’m afraid you can’t withdraw it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m sorry. I don’t recall you saying no backsies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>Is there anything else?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes. I’d like to offer a laudatory statement about Howard’s many excellent qualities that I believe will tip the scales back in his favour. Howard Joel Wolowitz. H is for honesty, of which he has much. O’s for outstanding, which he is such. W’s for witty, he’s quick with a joke. A’s for artistic, his ability…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>I’m sorry, Dr. Cooper, this matter is already closed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>But I still have rd Joel Wolowitz left to go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>It’s closed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I don’t understand why you people are picking on my friend, Howard, when there are much more serious security threats to pursue. For instance, when I first met Leonard, he was on the verge of giving away rocket secrets to a North Korean spy, and not one agent ever investigated that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Page</speaker><content>This is Leonard Hofstadter?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, it’s a different Leonard. He’s Chinese, red hair, six fingers. Good-bye.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Raj. Have you seen Howard?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I think he’s eating lunch. Uh, Sheldon, I want you to meet Neil deGrasse Tyson from the Hayden Planetarium in New York.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m quite familiar with Dr. Tyson. He’s responsible for the demotion of Pluto from planetary status. I liked Pluto. Ergo I do not like you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Dr Tyson</speaker><content>But I actually didn’t demote Pluto. That was a vote of the International Astronomical Union.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>If ifs and buts were candy and nuts, we’d all have a merry Christmas. Think about that, Dr. Tyson.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Dr Tyson</speaker><content>Is that the guy you were telling me about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, yeah.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Howard. The person at fault for you not getting a security clearance is me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes, but before you get upset, I want you to know I went to the FBI and retracted my statement.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>And they were okay with that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No. If anything, I made it worse. In any case, I have been riddled with guilt, which is causing Gorn-infested REM sleep. So, I’m here now to say I’m sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Are you kidding me? You’ve set my career back at least two years, and you think you can make it right with I’m sorry?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes. I followed the social protocol. I attempted to right the wrong, and when I failed to do so I delivered a heartfelt apology. Now you say apology accepted, and I will offer you a one-time-only high five.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Your apology is not accepted.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You’re tricking me. It really is, isn’t it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Leave me alone, Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Dr Tyson</speaker><content>Dr. Cooper, I just wanted you to know I’m sorry for the role I played in the Pluto matter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, shut up.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sheldon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hello.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What are you doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I have troubles, Penny. I’ve come to pour them out to the sympathetic ear of the local barkeep.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You know, they have a really nice bar over at the Olive Garden.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I don’t like the Olive Garden. They treat me like family.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, Sheldon. What can I get you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Alcohol.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Could you be a little more specific?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Ethyl alcohol. 40 millilitres.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I’m sorry, honey, I don’t know millilitres.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Ah. Blame President James “Jimmy” Carter. He started America on a path to the metric system but then just gave up. He wonders why he was a one-term president.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Penny (pouring out a shot of tequila)</speaker><content>Would you say that’s about 40 milliliters?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>More or less.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Great.  Now, where were we?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I believe you were about to ask me to choose a cocktail. Fortunately, thanks to computer-savvy alcoholics, there’s an app for that. Let’s see. Harvey Wallbanger. Eh. Sex on the Beach. I hardly think so. Rob Roy, Silk Slipper, Mad Hatter. Ooh! I’ll have a Rosewater Ricky.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>A what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You’ll need pitted, brandied cherries, gin, rosewater, angostura bitters and overproofed rum. Now, first, dust the cherries with sugar, then spray them with a mixture of rum and bitters. Then ignite the rum, caramel…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-19"><speaker>Penny (pouring out a shot of tequila)</speaker><content>Here you go, one Rosewater Ricky.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s not how it looks in the picture.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-21"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, yeah, you know, every bartender makes it differently. Why don’t you give it a try.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right. To the metric system.  I can’t taste the cherries.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-23"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>All right. Sheldon, what’s on your mind?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-24"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I wronged Howard, and he won’t accept my apology.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-25"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, right, that. Yes, Leonard told me. Sorry, honey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-26"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Penny, you face failure on a daily basis. How do you cope?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-27"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I drink.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-28"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>To drinking.  Nope. Oh, if only there were some way to force Howard to accept my apology so I could escape this miasma of guilt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-29"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You know, sometimes stuff just happens, and there’s nothing you can do about it. For example, Lisa Peterson hasn’t talked to me since the 11th grade, because no matter how much you apologize, you can’t go back and un-dry-hump someone’s boyfriend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-30"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I see. You’re saying I’m facing Starfleet Academy’s unwinnable command scenario, the Kobayashi Maru.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-31"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Exactly. Sometimes you can’t win.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-32"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Captain Kirk won.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-33"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Kirk cheated.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-34"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Impressive that you know that. It’s hard to believe I’m actually having this conversation with you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-35"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Right there with you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-36"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Kirk beat the Kobayashi Maru by reprogramming the simulator. That’s it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-37"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-38"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’ll reprogram Howard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-39"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What? Sheldon, you can’t reprogram people.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-40"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, you can’t reprogram people. To James Tiberius Kirk. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hello, all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Hello.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Howard, you’re feeling better about me today, aren’t you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Not really.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes, you are. I’m using neurolinguistic programming to modify your thought patterns.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh. Go away, Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>There’s a nine ninety five e-book down the drain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>What’s in the bag?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It’s for Howard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh. Sheldon, you can’t fix this with gifts.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Nevertheless, I’ve hurt you, and whether you forgive me or not, I want you to have this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You’re giving me a couch cushion?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No. The cushion is merely symbolic. I’m giving you my spot on the couch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>But you love that spot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No. I love my mother. My feelings for my spot are much greater. It is the singular location in space around which revolves my entire universe. And now it’s yours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, my God, dude. Now you have to forgive him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-18"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>All right. Apology accepted.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>High five. Not too hard. Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-20"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I haven’t cried like this since Toy Story 3.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I got to tell you, Sheldon, I understand why you chose this spot. I mean, the temperature is good, but there’s no draft. I can see the television, but I can still talk to…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I changed my mind. Get out of my spot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>How long?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>94 seconds.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>