<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Here’s what I wonder about zombies.  What happens if they can’t get any human flesh to eat? They can’t starve to death, they’re already dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You take this one. I spent an hour last night on how do vampires shave when they can’t see themselves in the mirror?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well-groomed vampires meet in pairs and shave each other. Case closed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yeah, okay, so, zombies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I guess it depends on the zombies, Raj. Are we talking slow zombies, fast zombies? Like, in 28 Days, if those zombies didn’t eat, they starved.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You’re thinking of 28 Days Later. 28 Days is where Sandra Bullock goes to rehab and puts the audience into an undead state</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Hey, don’t bag on Sandra Bullock! You think it makes you look cultured, but you just come off as bitter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, Dr. Siebert, twelve o’clock.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Why’s the president of the university slumming in the cafeteria?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Perhaps he’s emulating Shakespeare’s Henry V, who dressed as a commoner and mingled among them, to find out how he was being perceived by his subjects. Course, if he’d have read any of the thirteen hundred e-mails I’ve sent him on the subject of his administration, he could have saved himself the trouble.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Or maybe he heard it’s Tator Tot Tuesday. That’s why I’m here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Dr. Seibert</speaker><content>Hey, there’s my favorite geniuses! How are we doing today?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That depends, how much longer do you plan on fondling my shoulder?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Seibert</speaker><content>Sorry, Dr. Cooper, I forgot you have a touch phobia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It’s not a touch phobia, it’s a germ phobia. If you’d like to go put on a pair of latex gloves,</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Seibert</speaker><content>Yeah. So, listen, fellas, who’s up for a little party this Saturday night? Open bar, good eats, might even be a few pretty girls.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Sounds great!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’m in!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hold on. Just because the nice man is offering you candy, doesn’t mean you should jump into his windowless van. What’s the occasion?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-20"><speaker>Seibert</speaker><content>Just a little fund-raiser for the university.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Aha! The tear-stained air mattress in the back of the van.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-22"><speaker>Seibert</speaker><content>I understand your reticence, Dr. Cooper, and I sympathize, but the hard facts are, occasionally, we have to shake a few hands and kiss a few butts to raise money for our research.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I don’t care, it’s demeaning. And I refuse to be trotted out and shown off like a prize hog at the Texas State Fair. Which, by the way, is something you don’t want to attend wearing a Star Trek ensign’s uniform.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-24"><speaker>Seibert</speaker><content>All right, let me put it this way. You’re gonna put on a suit, you’re gonna come to this party, and you’re gonna explain your research to a bunch of old people, or I swear to God, I’ll blind you with a hot spoon, like they did to that little boy in Slumdog Millionaire.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-25"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, you don’t want that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-26"><speaker>Seibert</speaker><content>So, Saturday night! It’s gonna be off the hook.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-27"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Ugh!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-28"><speaker>Seibert</speaker><content>Get over it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-29"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, boy! Tator tots and a party invitation? What a great day!</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>There you go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Are you sure this is right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, just tuck that part in your pants;  you’ll be fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Okay, let’s go smooch some rich, wrinkled tuckus.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, Howard, I can’t believe Bernadette let you go to a fancy party wearing a dickey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Excuse me, my girlfriend doesn’t pick out my clothes. My mother does.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh. We should get going.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What about Sheldon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Sheldon is not going.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Really? What do we tell Siebert?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Tell him Dr. Cooper feels that the best use of his time is to employ his rare and precious mental faculties to tear the mask off nature and stare at the face of God.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sheldon, it’s Saturday night, you’ll be doing laundry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Don’t tell him that, tell him the mask thing.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Hey, put your tie back in your pants.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Thanks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Nice place. Reminds me of my parents’ house back in New Delhi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You’re kidding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No. We are very wealthy. But the only difference is, we have more servants.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>More than this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>More than we can use. You see, in India, we don’t make the mistake of letting our poor people have dreams.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Seibert</speaker><content>Ah. There’s my band of brainiacs. Where’s Dr. Cooper?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>He’s tearing the mask off nature to look at the face of God.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Seibert</speaker><content>The board of directors insists he has a beautiful mind. I think he’s just bananas. Come on, let me introduce you to one of the university’s leading donors.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I think we were misled about the cute girls.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Seibert</speaker><content>Mrs. Latham, I’d like you to meet three of our outstanding young researchers. This is Dr. Leonard Hofstadter, Dr. Rajesh Koothrappali and Howard Wolowitz.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>Well, what happened to you, Wolowitz, couldn’t stick with it long enough to get your PhD?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’m an engineer. Most engineers don’t bother with a PhD. But you may be interested to know I designed the zero-gravity waste-disposal system for NASA.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>Got it, you’re a space plumber.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’m gonna go hit the bar.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>Tell me about these two.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Do him first.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>Seibert</speaker><content>Dr. Hofstadter is representing our experimental physics program tonight. I think you’ll really enjoy hearing about his fascinating work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-20"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>Right. Fascinate me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh.. b.. d.. uh.. uh..</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-22"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>They’re cute when they’re about to wet themselves, aren’t they? I’ll make it easy for you. When you arrive at the lab in the morning, what sort of machine do you turn on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-23"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Coffee maker?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-24"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>All right, Dr. Kooth… uh, whatever it is, you’re up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-25"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>It’s Koothrappali. I have to tinkle.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And so, instead of bowing to pressure, and going to that pointless soiree, I stayed right here and did a load of whites.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Amy (on webcam)</speaker><content>Well, normally I respect your macho rebellious attitude toward The Man, but, in this case, I think you’ve made a foolish mistake.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Unlikely. But make your case. Keeping in mind that your critical attitude is ruining our Saturday night together, and I’m not above minimizing your window.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon, like it or not, until you manage to upload your intelligence into a self-sustaining orbiting satellite, equipped with high-speed Internet and a cloaking device, you will be dependent on other members of the human race.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s it. Prepare to be minimized.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I’m not finished. All scientists have to fund-raise, Sheldon. How do you think I paid for my lab?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Your lab is funded by some Middle-Eastern dilettante?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Technically, Faisal is my fiance. But I do have a state-of-the-art two-photon microscope and a place to stay in Riyadh for the winter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, that explains those puzzling camel race photos on your Facebook page.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>And consider this, without you to make the case for the physics department, the task will fall to people like Leonard and Rajesh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Are you trying to scare me? ‘Cause you’re succeeding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Well, then prepare to be terrified. If your friends are unconvincing, this year’s donations might go to, say, the geology department.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, dear,not, not the dirt people!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Or worse, it could go to the liberal arts.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Millions of dollars being showered on poets, literary theorists and students of gender studies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, the humanities!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>On the bright side, I don’t think President Siebert will be making us go to any more fund-raisers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>It was so much easier at my bar mitzvah. The old people just came up to you, pinched your cheek and handed you a savings bond.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, don’t be such gloomy Gusses. Look at the size of these shrimp! At what point do we start calling them lobsters?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Face it, Raj, we crashed and burned tonight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>Oh, you didn’t do that badly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Mrs. Latham, the first machine I turn on in the morning is the helium-neon laser, ’cause it needs to warm up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>I no longer care, dear. But don’t worry, I really enjoyed meeting you this evening.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You’re kidding. That was good for you? ‘Cause I was sweating through my T-shirt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>Excellent! There’s nothing I like better than making smart people feel ill at ease.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>Oh, I don’t know, it’s one of the fun things you get to do when you have lots of money. Watch. Hey! Who said you could eat that shrimp? See? Fun.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Sheldon (behind them)</speaker><content>No, no, no, I’m just here for your money. I don’t want to shake anyone’s germy hands. Explain it to them, Siebert.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Sheldon (on phone)</speaker><content>I must confess I don’t understand you, President Siebert. First you say you want me to appear at your fund-raisers, but now you say you never want me to go anywhere near your fund-raisers. Forgive me, but that sounds like a mixed message. Here we go again. If there’s simply no talking to me, why did you call? I’m sorry, someone’s on the other line. Why don’t you see if you can organize your thoughts, and we’ll try again later. Cooper-Hofstadter residence. Go for Cooper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hello, Mrs. Latham. Yes, I live with him. I don’t, I, I really don’t know why. Tonight? Sure, that’d be great. Okay, I’ll, I’ll see you then. Bye. She wants to have dinner and talk about my research.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>An entire dinner to talk about your research? Where you going, the drive-thru at Jack in the Box?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, wherever we’re going, she’s sending a car to pick me up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Okay, I see what’s happening.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>My stature intimidates her, so she’s using you to get to me. Crafty old gal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Excuse me, but you are not the only distinguished scientist in this apartment. I’ve been published in peer-reviewed journals, I received a Dissertation of the Year award for experimental particle physics.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, that can’t be it. And since you seem to have forgotten, the reason we live together is we’re best friends. And I got your back, Jack.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Secne</speaker><content>Mrs Latham’s car.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That was a great meal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>I’m glad you enjoyed it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>The only time I eat this well is when my mom’s in town and she takes me out to dinner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>Is that so?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You kind of remind me of her. She enjoys making people uncomfortable, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>Well, you remind me of a boy I dated in college.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No kidding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-18"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>Sweet boy. Very smart. If only he’d had money.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, um, so, hey, speaking of money, how are you feeling about helping the physics department get a cryogenic centrifugal pump and molecular sieve?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-20"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>Well, I must say, you make a very persuasive case for it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, good, good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-22"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>And I’m seriously considering taking it to the next level.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-23"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Terrific. Great. What level is that?  Okay, now you don’t remind me of my mom.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m sorry, so, eventually, zombies are going to attack the rehab facility where Sandra Bullock is?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yes, Sheldon. Keep watching.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You know, it’s a shame, all that work she’s doing to get sober, only to be torn apart and eaten alive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Hey. How was dinner?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Swell. I need a drink. Do we have any alcohol?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No. But we have potatoes, I could make you vodka. It’ll take two weeks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Leonard, are you okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Um, I’m not sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What’s going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, Mrs. Latham said she was seriously considering donating money so we could get a cryogenic centrifugal pump.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, wow!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yes!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Then she stuck her tongue down my throat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, we can’t keep explaining everything. Read that book we got you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>She hit on me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Wait-wait-wait. Are you telling us that old lady wanted to have sex with you in exchange for giving your department millions of dollars?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I think so.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You lucky duck.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-20"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You’re really a broken toy, aren’t you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I was able to get out of there before anything else happened, but she wants to see me again tomorrow night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Excellent! What are you planning to wear?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-23"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-24"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Penny, you’re an expert on trading sexual favours for material gain, walk him through this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-25"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, n-no, hold on a second, I’m not going to sleep with her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-26"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>But we need a cryogenic centrifugal pump.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-27"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, forget it! It’s not gonna happen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-28"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, come now, Leonard, this may be your only chance to make a real contribution to science!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-29"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I repeat, not gonna happen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-30"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What was all that about me trading sexual favours for material gain?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-31"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It was a compliment. I believe in giving credit where credit is due.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Sheldon (on phone)</speaker><content>Okay, fine. I’ll tell him. Leonard, Mrs. Latham’s car is here for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I won’t be too late. I’m just gonna make a final pitch for the funding and then say good night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hold on, I have something for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What’s this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Just a few things you may need tonight. There’s, uh, baby oil, condoms and, uh, a little something I procured from the school of pharmacology. They say it is to Viagra as Viagra is to a green M_M.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I am not going to have sex with her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Maybe this will overcome your reluctance. I went on the Internet and found a photograph of a 25-year-old Mrs. Latham to get your libido humming. Check out those saddle shoes. Rar!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Are you insane? I’m not going to prostitute myself just so we can get some new equipment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, come on! Why not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Good night, Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Given how much time you spend engaging in pointless self-abuse, you might consider, just this once, using your genitalia to actually accomplish something!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>He still won’t shag the old lady, huh?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No. But thank you for asking.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey. Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>Hello, Leonard. I hope you’re hungry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m very hungry. For food, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>Oh, I made you uncomfortable last night. I’m so sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, that’s okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>No, it most certainly is not. Leonard, I’m making the donation to your department regardless of what happens between us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Really?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>Well, of course. There’s no quid pro quo here. You and your colleagues are doing remarkable research, and you deserve the money.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh. Then what was last night about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>I took a shot, sue me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>You’re a very handsome man, Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>It was foolish of me to think someone your age might ever be interested in someone like me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, don’t say that. You’re a very attractive woman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>Oh, please.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, it’s true.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>Well, aren’t you sweet. Just for the record, you’d remember a night with me for the rest of your life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m sure I would. But why, why, exactly?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-20"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>You’re a very smart man. How do you think I landed such a rich husband?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I hadn’t really given it much thought.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-22"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>Well, think about it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-23"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Do you mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-24"><speaker>Mrs Latham</speaker><content>Yep. I’m that good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-25"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, what the hell.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Good morning, slut.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, please, I recognize the walk of shame when I see it. All you’re missing is a little smeared mascara and a purse with panties wadded up in it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What’s going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, nothing’s going on. Excuse me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Are you just getting home?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s a good sign, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m so proud of you! You sold yourself out like a common streetwalker!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, I didn’t do it for the money.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>She stiffed you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I believe that’s what your roommate did to her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Again, read the book we gave you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, I mean, I, I, I got the money first.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Smart. Get paid up front. Yeah, I think you have a real knack for gigolo work, Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh, I’m gonna go lie down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s a good idea, get your rest. There are a lot more rich old ladies out there, and Daddy needs a new linear accelerator. And I thought he didn’t learn anything from his relationship with you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-20"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Another compliment! Learn to recognize them.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Seibert</speaker><content>Ah, there he is! The man of the hour! He took one for the team!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I didn’t do it for the money!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Seibert</speaker><content>Keep telling yourself that, it makes it easier. Trust me, I know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Cool, buddy! That’s awesome!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>How was she?</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>