<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>So what kind of cruise is this you’re going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>It’s called the Born Again Boat Ride. Christian Quarterly gave it their highest rating, five thorny crowns. I do wish you’d come with me, Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, Mom, if I did, it would be conclusive proof that your God can work miracles.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>You’re missing out. It’s gonna be wall-to-wall fun. It’s all themed. There’s Jonah and the Whale Watching, all-you-can-eat Last Supper Buffet, and my personal favourite, Gunning with God.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What’s Gunning with God? I’m afraid to ask.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Oh, it is a hoot and a half. You write your sins on a clay pigeon, they fire ’em up in the air, and you pulverize them with a 12-gauge shotgun full of our Lord’s forgiveness.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Frankly, Mom, I’m encouraged to see how advanced your group has become, willing to sail out into the ocean without fear of falling off the edge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>For example, if Shelly was aboard, he’d write “smart mouth” on his pigeon, and then bam!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>The Lord giveth and the Lord bloweth away. Well, Mom, according to my itinerary for our weekend together, the fun begins with fried chicken.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Sounds delicious.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Good, ’cause I got you everything you need to make it. You are in for a treat. My mother’s fried chicken is why we had to buy my dad the extra large coffin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, she just got off the plane. She doesn’t want to cook.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Of course she does. Making me food is her way of saying I love you. Making me food when she’s too tired to cook is her way of saying I really love you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Actually, I wouldn’t mind going out for a bite, Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Won’t that spoil our appetites for the chicken you’re going to make me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>All right, that settles it, we’re going out. Do you like sushi? There’s a great little place down the street.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>I’ve never had it, but there’s no harm in trying something new.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>There’s a lot of harm in trying something new. That’s why we test out drugs and cosmetics on bunny rabbits.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, you’re talking like a crazy person.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-20"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Actually, I had him tested as a child. Doctor says he’s fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Told you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-22"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Although, I do regret not following up with that specialist in Houston.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>All</speaker><content>Irasshaimase!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Stop yelling! I’m not happy about this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What’s the last thing you were ever happy about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>The prospect of fried chicken.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>This is exciting. Back home, the diner on Route Four serves sushi, but it’s just cut up fish sticks and a side of Uncle Ben’s. They put it on the menu in those kung fu letters, but that don’t make it sushi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh, kung fu letters might not be politically correct.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Oh, I thought the one we couldn’t say was ching chong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, yeah, that, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>So, Shelly, what’s up with you and your friend Amy, if you don’t mind a mother prying a bit?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, there’s actually big news on the Amy front. She’s been studying the neurobiology of addiction in lower animals. She is this close to getting a starfish hooked on cocaine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Do you have any idea what’s going on with those two?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It’s kind of like the Loch Ness monster. Maybe there’s something there, maybe there isn’t. We’ll probably never know. But sometimes it’s fun to creep yourself out thinking about it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>How are you doing on the young lady front? I hear you’re in some sort of a long distance situation?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh, yeah, it’s Raj’s sister. It’s kind of tough. She’s in India. Also, her parents aren’t happy she’s dating someone white.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Oh, that’s a funny turn, isn’t it? You never think about it going the other way. Well, you can’t force things. You need to figure out if you’re in a relationship or if you’re just calling it one. It’s like they say, a cat can have kittens in the oven but that don’t make ’em biscuits.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And that reminds me of another saying. You can lead a chicken to Crisco, but you can’tmake your mother fry it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Sheldon, you pester me one more time about chicken, I will put you over my knee right here in this restaurant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Please pester her. Please, for me.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>So, Mrs. Cooper, what did you think of the sushi?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>It was good. The only thing that would have made it better is if it was cooked and if it was beef. Sheldon, when is your landlord going to fix the elevator?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I don’t know. Lately we’ve been talking about converting it into a missile silo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Your son seems to think we need to launch a pre-emptive strike on Burbank.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Get them before they get us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Raj (Sitting against their front door, drinking a beer)</speaker><content>Hey, look who decided to show up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Raj, what are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I couldn’t find you guys so I bought six new friends. Three, sadly, are dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Mom, you remember Rajesh? Rajesh, my mother.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Of course. Mrs. Cooper. So nice to see you again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Well, it’s so nice to see you, too. I thought it was our Indians that had the occasional alcohol problem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>We don’t say that, either. I’ll make you a list.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Oh, that would be mighty white of you. So, Raj, what pain are you trying to cover up with alcohol?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Nothing, I’m fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Are ya?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>That’s better. Now tell me what’s bothering you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I’m so lonely.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, yes, born alone, die alone. It’s a tragic human condition. Now, Raj, if you’ll excuse my mother, she’s about to make a pecan pie that’ll be so good I’ll almost forget how she blew it with the fried chicken.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-20"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Sheldon, your friend is hurtin’. What do we do when someone’s hurtin’?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Offer them a hot beverage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-22"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>And when they’re drunk as a skunk, what beverage do we offer?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Coffee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-24"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>And what do we do it with?  Now you listen to me. I know you feel like you can’t find someone, but there’s a lock for every key. Back home, there’s a girl works at the Wal-Mart. Tall, tall girl. Woman could hunt geese with a rake. Thought she’d never find a man, then one day, wouldn’t ya know, Harlem Globetrotters come to town. Long story short, today that woman travels the world with a semi-professional basketball player and two beautiful mixed-race babies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-25"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I didn’t get a lot of that because of your accent, but the general tone was soothing and somehow I feel better.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-26"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m not going to get my pecan pie, am I?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-27"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You want some Oreos?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-28"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Double Stuf?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-29"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, regular.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-30"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Nice. Kick a man when he’s down.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m glad we’re finally getting to do something together, just the two of us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Sure. One thing you really miss when you’re on vacation is laundry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Careful, you’re using too much Downey. You know if my clothes get too soft it makes me sleepy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Well, this takes me back. Me doing your laundry, you next to me criticizing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It is nice, isn’t it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Penny (arriving)</speaker><content>Mrs. Cooper. Hi!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Oh, hello, darlin’.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sheldon, you didn’t tell me your mom was coming.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It was in my weekly e-mail blast. Right between beet season is finally here, and uh-oh, red stool from beets leads to cancer scare.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>So, how’ve you been?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Good, good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>I hear that Leonard has a new girlfriend. How are you doing with all that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, fine. You know, it’s been a while. I’m getting back out there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Let me ask you, when you get back out there, are you wearing this? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, it’s super cute on. That top has paid for itself in free drinks like ten times what it cost.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes, Penny has a lot of her money tied up in promiscuity futures.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Hon, you think maybe the reason why you’re having trouble finding a guy to settle down with is because you’re letting them ride the roller coaster without buying a ticket?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, they don’t always get to ride the roller coaster. Sometimes they only get to spin the teacups. Now I’m going out tonight. Would it be crazy to ask you to look at the outfit I’m going to wear?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Oh, not crazy at all. And don’t beat yourself up. When I was your age, you could have me for a car ride and a bottle of strawberry wine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Now that will not be in this week’s e-mail blast.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>So, this spring, I get to go to the International Space Station.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Oh, my word, a trip to the heavens. If you ever want to live there eternally, I’ve got a good book you could read.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Thanks, but I watch the Charlie Brown Christmas special every year, so I get the gist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>I bet your mom is really proud of you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Nope. She says if I don’t back out she’s going to go on a hunger strike. It would take years before she’d be in any kind of danger, but still.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’ve got a treat for us tomorrow, Mom. I’m taking you to see Saul Perlmutter give a lecture about his Nobel Prize-winning work in cosmology. And the best part is, at the Q and A afterward, I’ve worked up a couple of Q’s that will stump his sorry A.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>I don’t know, Shelly. I thought we could do a little sightseeing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What sight is better than your little boy embarrassing a Nobel laureate?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Come on, Sheldon, we’ll take your mom to see the Hollywood sign, the wax museum, the Walk of Fame.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Ooh, maybe a little Rodeo Drive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Well, I can’t spend twelve thousand dollars on a handbag, but it’s free to look upon those who do with righteous condemnation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What do you say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What do I say? I say you people need to stop ruining my mom’s visit with your sushi, and your sadness and your slutty shirts. Stop it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Howard (after Raj whispers to him)</speaker><content>He’s not talking about your shirt. Your shirt is fine.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>These are delicious.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>The trick to pancakes is bacon grease. I cook everything in it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Everything? Aren’t you worried about your health?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Oh, doctors are always changing their mind. One week bacon grease is bad for you. The next week we’re not getting enough of it. Good morning, Shelly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Mom, I want to apologize for my behaviour last night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Apology accepted.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Great. Now, you’re going to love the Perlmutter lecture. Look, he will be stating that the universe is older than 6,000 years, but I thought you could stick your fingers in your ears and hum Amazing Grace during those parts.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>I am still going out with your friends.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>But I apologized. And that was hard for me because I didn’t do anything wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Shelly, I hung out with you in enough dusty lecture halls while you were growing up. I want to go sightseeing. So why don’t you have some pancakes, get dressed and come with us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m not going, and you can’t make me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>You’re right, I can’t. Have a nice day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, I’m going to stand here until you change your mind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Well, then you are going to stand there all day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m just gonna take my bacon grease and slide over there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I can’t believe my own mother is abandoning me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>I am not abandoning you. Sheldon, abandoning you is leaving you in a basket on a church doorstep. I am going to Hollywood and thank a wax Ronald Reagan for his service to our country.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>We appear to be at a crossroads in our relationship, Mother.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-19"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Well, I guess we are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sorry. Syrup.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right, Mom. When you’re at the Ripley’s Believe It Or Not Museum, if they have an exhibit about a mother who threw away a chance to spend the day with the world’s most wonderful son, believe it, because it’s true. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-22"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I hadn’t…</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That lecture was a waste of time. I made more accurate diagrams of the expansion of the early universe on the nursery wall with the contents of my diaper. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Are you getting sick?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, I’m just allergic to people who get Nobel Prizes for no good reason.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon, is it possible that your foul mood, or, to use the clinical term, bitchiness, is because your mother isn’t making you a priority?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No. Or to use the clinical term, nuh-uh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Are you sure? The infant-mother pair-bond is the building block of primate psychology.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, there it is. It always comes back to monkeys with you. Just monkeys, monkeys, monkeys.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon, we’re all animals. And granted, there are aspects of you that are extraordinary, but when it comes to emotions and relationships, you’re just like everybody else.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Are you trying to suggest that my emotional problems are no different than those of a stupid person?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Actually, some research indicates that by not over-thinking, the less intelligent handle emotions better.  Sure you’re not coming down with a cold?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, yes, the common cold. Just like everyone else. You’d love that, wouldn’t you?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Oh, this one’s sweet. You know, for your rosary rattlers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Mrs. Cooper, we say Catholics, not rosary rattlers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>My goodness, it’s a wonder you people in California can talk at all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>This is like the worst Hollywood tour ever.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What are you gonna do? She wanted to see churches.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey, they have wine here, don’t they?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Raj (pointing at a crucifixion statue)</speaker><content>Hey, none of our gods have abs like that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yep, that’s the last Jew who did sit-ups. And look where it got him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Hey, while we’re here, why don’t we all do some praying? Let’s put a little church in this church.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, I’m not sure we should.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>It’s easy. I’ll show you how. Lord, Mary Cooper here. Coming to you from Gomorrah, California. I want to thank you for the blessing that is my little Shelly. I also want to thank you for the continued strength not to coldcock him with my Bible. All right, Penny, your turn.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, um, hey, God. What’s up? Um, I’m good, but, uh, it would be a big help to my family if you could get my brother to stop cooking meth. But no cops. Be cool.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>She also goes a little overboard on the love thy neighbour. Could probably use that chat you had with Mary Magdalene. Leonard, you’re up. Wasserman, you’re on deck.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay. I don’t know, it’s probably a little late to ask you to make me taller. Oh, um, if you could help out with me and my girlfriend. She’s all the way in India. That would be great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Hear that? Girl trouble. Turns out we were both wrong on that front. How about you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, me? No. Thanks, I’m good. I’m really just trying not to burst into flames.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Rajesh?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>He says he’s having trouble dropping those last five pounds.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Huh, I might have gone with the talking-to-girls thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-20"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No, you only get one wish.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Look at the two of us. Me, a highly regarded physicist. The kind of mind that comes along once, maybe twice in a generation. You, the common man, tired from your labours as a stockbroker, or vacuum cleaner salesman, or bootblack. But deep down inside, apparently we’re just two peas in a pod. A regular pea, and the kind of pea that comes along once, maybe twice in a generation. Rain. Another great equalizer. Falling on the head of the brilliant and the unremarkable alike.  Smarty-pants.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, Mrs. Cooper, it smells so good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>You take notes, darlin’. The real way to get a man is with melted cheese and cream of mushroom soup. He’ll die at 50 but his love will be true.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Sheldon (entering, soaked)</speaker><content>I need a tissue.This one got wet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Thank you. Yeah, I’ve learned something today. You and I, in so many ways, other than intelligence and what counts, we’re the same. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Sweetheart, are you sick?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I hope so, because if this is well, life isn’t worth living.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Oh, sugarpie, you are burning up. We’ve got to get you to bed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Don’t worry. Mama’s here to take care of her baby.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And just to be clear, only her baby and not these other people.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Of course.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Can I have tea with honey and toast with the crust cut off?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>You can have whatever you want.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Thanks, Mom.You’re the best.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Boy, last time I put VapoRub on you, you didn’t have hair on your chest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I know, it filled in last year. I didn’t get to spend a lot of time with you on this visit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>And whose fault was that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Shelly, you’re not eight years old any more. We have to have a different relationship.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, we don’t. The one we have works great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Sweetheart, you are a grown man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Or maybe I’m part of a new species, that lives for hundreds of years, which means I’m still basically a toddler.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Oh, I so should have taken you to Houston.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Does this mean you’re not going to sing Soft Kitty?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>No, I will always sing you Soft Kitty.  Soft kitty, warm kitty, little ball of fur…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>Leonard (at door)</speaker><content>Mrs. Cooper, were we supposed to take that pie out of the oven?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Get out!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Well, that was rude.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, I know, but he means well. Sing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-16"><speaker>Mrs Cooper</speaker><content>Happy kitty, sleepy kitty…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What are you trying to pull, Mom? From the top.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-18"><speaker>Mrs Cooper (to God)</speaker><content>This is what I’m talking about.  Soft kitty, warm kitty, little ball of fur…</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>