<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Aaargh. What the hell?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Emergency preparedness drill.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, no, come on!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, you know how it works. Once a quarter, keep our readiness up. Now, rise and shine, sleepy head. Half the town is probably dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I have to get a lock for my door.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I think you’ll like the drill tonight. I’ve tried to make it fun. Each of these cards contains a detailed scenario of a possible apocalyptic event. Everything from wild fires to a surprise invasion by Canada. Pick a catastrophe, any catastrophe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, Canada is not going to invade California.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, really? You think those hippies in Washington and Oregon can stop them?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All righty! An 8.2 magnitude earthquake devastates Pasadena, reducing mighty edifices to dust, engulfing the city in flames. The streets flow with blood and echo with the cries of the wounded. Oh, excellent choice. Now, put on your hard hat and safety vest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, fun. I get to spend another night in front of our apartment dressed like one of the Village People.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You make that joke every three months. I still don’t get it. Leonard, wait. What are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t know, what am I doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Look around you, there’s hypothetical broken glass everywhere. Really? You’re going to face Armageddon without your orthotics? All right, your choice.  Uh-oh, hypothetical aftershock!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Aah!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And that’s why we wear hard hats.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Check it out, press release from NASA.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Um, Expedition 31 will launch this spring to the International Space Station. Crew members will include Commander Tom ‘Tombo’ Johnson, astronaut Mike ‘Supernova’ Novacelik and Payload Specialist Howard Wolowitz.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>This is going right into my synagogue’s newsletter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Dude, if you’re going to be an astronaut, you need to pick a cool nickname.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I don’t get to pick it. The other guys have to give it to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh. If I had one, it would be Brown Dynamite.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Are you not listening to me? The other astronauts have to give you your nickname.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Are you not looking at me? I am Brown Dynamite. Why do you put six sugars in your coffee?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Because the cafeteria doesn’t offer little packets of methamphetamine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Emergency drill night last night, huh?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh-huh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>How’d you do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’ll tell you exactly how he did. Readiness: unsatisfactory. Follows direction: barely. Attitude: a little too much. Overall: not only will he probably die in a fiery inferno, his incessant whining would most certainly spoil everyone else’s day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You know what, I’m so tired I can’t even think straight. I’m going home. Will one of you guys give this nutbag a ride back later?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You can’t go home. You have to take me to the dentist at four o’clock.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, can’t you take the bus to the dentist?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Of course I can. It’s coming back under the residual effects of the anaesthesia, that’s the problem. Two years ago after a deep gum cleaning, I thought I got on a bus but somehow wound up on a booze cruise to Mexico.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>They put you under for a cleaning?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, they have to, I’m a biter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Whatever, Sheldon. I’m exhausted. I’m not taking you to the dentist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Wrong, sir. Wrong. Under section 37B of the roommate agreement, miscellaneous duties, you are obligated to take me to the dentist. See? It’s right here after providing a confirmation sniff on questionable dairy products.”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-22"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You know what, I am sick of the roommate agreement. It’s ridiculous. I’m your roommate, not your chauffeur. You know, I had better things to do yesterday than drive you all the way to the good model train store in Garden Grove because the one in Pasadena has gotten too big for its britches.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, it has. Ask anybody.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-24"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t care. I’m done.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-25"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hold on. Are you saying that you want to invoke Clause 209?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-26"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t know what that is, but if it means I can go home and sleep, then yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-27"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Think carefully here. Clause 209 suspends our friendship, and strips down the roommate agreement to its bare essentials. Our responsibilities toward each other would only be rent, utilities and a perfunctory chin jut of recognition as we pass in the hall.  ‘Sup?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-28"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Where do I sign?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-29"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Right here. Use your finger.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-30"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>There. Done.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-31"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right. That’s it. We are now no longer companions, boon or otherwise. We are now merely acquaintances. To amend the words of Toy Story, you have not got a friend in me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-32"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m gonna go home and take a nap.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-33"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, well, tell it to someone who cares.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I got pretty exciting NASA news today. Next week I fly to Houston for orientation and zero-gravity elimination drills.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What does that mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>He’s gonna learn to poop in space.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Open the pod bay doors, HAL.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Maybe your nickname should be Brown Dynamite.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hello, dear friends. And Dr. Hofstadter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>‘Sup?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>‘Sup? My apologies. I would’ve been here sooner, but the bus kept stopping for other people to get on it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I saved you a dumpling.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, your concern for me is touching. It will serve you well when you take me to the dentist tomorrow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I’m sorry, Sheldon, I’m busy. I’m right in the middle of my addiction study. I’ve got a lab full of alcoholic monkeys, and tomorrow’s the day we switch them to O’Doul’s.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You’re my girlfriend and you’re not going to cater to my every need? Oh, where’d the magic go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sheldon, that’s not what girlfriends are for. Although, you don’t use them for what they’re for, so what do I know?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Howard doesn’t make me do his shopping, or take him to the dentist, or pick up his dry cleaning, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Absolutely. But when Ma’s hips give out, you’re up, kid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, if Amy’s too busy, that gives the rest of you an opportunity to make my life easier, thus assuring yourselves a footnote in my memoirs, tentatively entitled You’re Welcome, Mankind. All right, then, just shout when you hear the task you want to undertake. Uh, dentist. Okay, we can circle back to that one. Um, well, who wants to take me Wednesday morning to get new heels put on my dress shoes? Anyone? Oh. That one had hoot written all over it. Um, all right, uh, dermatologist? Allergist? Podiatrist? Supercuts? Okay, okay, here’s a fun one. Um, I need a new picture frame and I have a hankering for Swedish meatballs. Who wants to spend the day with me at IKEA?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Their meatballs are pretty good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What’s that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Nothing, nothing.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hello, Stuart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Oh, hey, Sheldon. Can I help you find something today?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, no. I was just sitting at home thinking about how it might be nice to catch up with my ninth favourite person.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Ninth?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You moved up one. My pen pal in Somalia was kidnapped by pirates. So, uh, how are you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Uh, not so good. My shrink just killed himself and blamed me in the note.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Great. Great. So, what’s new with your family? How’s your mother? Is she alive?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And your father? Alive?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>How about your grandparents, they alive?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, I’m so sorry for your loss. On a cheerier note, I have a teeth-cleaning appointment this afternoon. What do you say you take me over there, buddy boy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>I’m sorry, you want me to take you to the dentist?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes. And now, I can’t make any promises, but that’s the sort of thing that gets a fella on the short list for the number eight friend slot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Sheldon, I’m working. I can’t take you to the dentist. Also, and I can’t stress this enough, I don’t want to take you to the dentist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Can’t help a friend out in a time of need, huh? I see where your therapist was coming from.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Ooh, ooh! What about we make your astronaut nickname Howard “Buzz” Wolowitz?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You can’t do Buzz. Buzz is taken.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Buzz Lightyear is not real.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No, that’s not what I’m talking about.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Well, are you talking about when he thought he was real?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Okay, um, how about Crash”? Howard “Crash” Wolowitz.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, terrific. The other astronauts would love to go hurtling through space with a guy named Crash.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>All right, um, how about, oh, how about Rocket Man?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That’s not bad, Howard “Rocket Man” Wolowitz.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, it’s great, but I told you, I don’t get to pick my nickname. It has to come from the other astronauts.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Maybe there’s a way to get them to come up with it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Like how?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Once I tried carrying around a Duncan yo-yo, hoping the other kids would start calling me Duncan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Did it work?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, they ended up calling me Sock Mouth. Because they took away my yo-yo and stuffed their socks in my mouth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Okay, uh, what if we make Rocket Man your ringtone, and the next time you talk to those guys, I’ll call you and they’ll hear it. Plant the seed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-18"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>That’s actually not a terrible plan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-19"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>They don’t call me Brown Dynamite for nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-20"><speaker>Leonard (to Sheldon, entering)</speaker><content>‘Sup?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>‘Sup?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-22"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey, did you ever make it to the dentist?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Not necessary. No. I found a service that’ll send a van to your house for a teeth cleaning. Mostly they cater to dogs, but the fellow on the phone seemed to have an open mind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-24"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>All right, Sheldon, if you need me to take you to the dentist, I will take you to the dentist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-25"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Are you suggesting that you’ve come to your senses and wish to re-establish the mutual benefits that stem from full participation in the roommate agreement?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-26"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Absolutely. If you admit that you’re a 30-year-old man who’s incapable of functioning on his own.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-27"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Ooh, Sock Mouth’s got him on the ropes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-28"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I will admit nothing of the sort. And now if you’ll excuse me, I have to call my dentist and see if I can also get my hair shampooed and my nails clipped.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Penny (entering)</speaker><content>Oh, good, your power’s out, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Why is that good?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Because last month, I sent the electric company a Starbucks gift card, an apology note, and a few snapshots of me in a bra.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Power failure. Implementing power-failure protocol.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What happened to all your glow-in-the-dark-emergency-exit stuff you had painted on the floor?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, that was wildly carcinogenic. Anyway, it’s too bad you’re no longer entitled to the full benefits of my friendship, because I happen to be extremely prepared for such an emergency. Please try not to see anything by this light. It’s not for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It’s just a blackout, I’m sure the power will be back on soon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And I’m sure some fool in the Donner party said the snow would stop any day now. I like to think they ate him first.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You know, I got some candles in my apartment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>But candles? During a blackout? Are you mad? That’s a fire hazard. No, Pasadena Water and Power recommends the far safer glow stick.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Leonard (pulling out a toy lightsabre)</speaker><content>You call that a glow stick? That is a glow stick. Come on, let’s go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Before you go, consider this. Not only do I have a deep-cycle marine battery power source which is more than capable of running our entertainment system, I also have all 61 episodes of the BBC series Red Dwarf and Fiddle-Faddle. All yours if you’re willing to reinstate the roommate agreement.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I’ve got wine at my place and some bubble wrap we could pop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, he’ll be back. Wine and a girl in the dark, he’s gonna be bored out of his mind.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>To wine and bubble wrap. And to not having to watch Sheldon demonstrate his reverse osmosis machine that converts urine into drinking water.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You know, in Girl Scouts, Tammie Dinisha said you could do that with panty hose. Boy, was she wrong. Anyway, you want to make out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I thought because our relationship’s in a beta test, you wanted to take things slow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay. Do you want to make out slow?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I can go so slow it’ll be like there’s a snail in your mouth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Ugh. Well, lucky for you, there’s nothing else to do right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Excuse me, Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Since when don’t you knock? It’s like the only good thing about you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Social niceties have been suspended, Leonard. We’re in a state of a emergency. The world has descended into darkened turmoil. Lawlessness and savagery are the order of the day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Fine, what is it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m making s’mores. I wanted to alert you in case you smelled caramelizing marshmallows and thought a nearby candy factory was on fire.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>S’mores, huh? Good for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes, or good for us if you sign here and reinstate the full roommate agreement.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, thanks. I’m good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Really? Huh! Okay. In that case, I will have a s’more by myself. And then I’m gonna have s’more. By myself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Aw.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, don’t aw him. He brought this all on himself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>But he’s sad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, he’s crazy. Sometimes crazy looks like sad so it’ll suck you back in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-20"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I think he misses his little buddy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Fine. But mark my words, this frustrating, bogus teenage make-out session is not over.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I thought you said candles were dangerous.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>This is a Bunsen burner. I’m a scientist, I know what I’m doing. Oh, drat.  Aw. It took me a gallon of urine to make that water.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Listen, Sheldon, this is stupid. I don’t see why we can’t be friends. And I’m willing to drive you around and help you out with stuff. I just don’t want to do it because of some silly roommate agreement.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What are you proposing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That we go back to the way things were. But when I do something for you, you show a little appreciation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And how would I do that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You say thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Every time?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It’s not crazy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Counter-proposal. We reinstate the full roommate agreement with the following addendum, in the spirit of Mother’s Day or Father’s Day, once a year, we set aside day to celebrate all your contributions to my life, both actual and imagined by you. We could call it Leonard’s Day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I kind of like the sound of that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Of course you do. It’s about you, like everything else.  Oh, thank goodness. I don’t think I had it in me to make another glass of water.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>So, do I get breakfast in bed on Leonard’s Day?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Can I sit in your spot?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Can I control the thermostat?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Do I get a card?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Of course you get a card. It’s Leonard’s Day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-21"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey, guys, the building manager said the reason the power went out is someone went down into the basement and just pulled the main breaker switch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-22"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Really. Who do you think did that, Sheldon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, I don’t know. But whoever that mystery man was, you should be eternally grateful, for without him, there would be no Leonard’s Day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-24"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Leonard’s Day?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-25"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, no pressure. Just get him a crummy card, you’re good.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>All right, test my ring tone. That really is a good song.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, yeah. There’s a reason he’s Sir Elton John. They don’t make you a knight for writing Wake Me Up Before You Go Go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Mrs Wolowitz (off)</speaker><content>Howard, are you coming down for breakfast?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Ma, I told you I have a video conference with NASA. I said don’t bother me!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Mrs Wolowitz (off)</speaker><content>Oh! Listen to Mr. Big Shot Astronaut.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yes, please listen to Mr. Big Shot Astronaut. Hey, good morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>NASA Guy (on skype)</speaker><content>Hey, Howard, thanks for getting up so early.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No problem, Dr. Massimino.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Dr Massimino</speaker><content>The guys here call me Mass.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Mass. That’s a cool nickname. ‘Cause force equals mass times acceleration.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Mass</speaker><content>Yeah. It’s just short for Massimino. Anyway, the plan for this morning is to go over the…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Sorry. My phone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Mass</speaker><content>What is that? Is that Rocket Man?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, my ring tone. Kind of my favourite song, Rocket Man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>Mrs Wolowitz (off)</speaker><content>Howard, your Fruit Loops are getting soggy!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Not now!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>Mass</speaker><content>Who’s that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>My mom. Sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-19"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No problem, Fruit Loops.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>