<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>So, Bernadette, how goes the hunt for bridesmaid dresses?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Well, if you don’t mind looking like an orange traffic cone, great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Girlfriends, I have the answer to our dress problems.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Really?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Twelve years ago, my cousin Irene and her entire family died in a horrific carbon monoxide accident the night before her wedding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>That’s horrible.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Yes and no. All those bridesmaids dresses remain unused and available to us for free. So it seems that cloud of odourless deadly gas had a silver lining after all. Check it out, still in the bags. The gowns, not the bridesmaids.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I don’t know. Dead people’s dresses?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, and cap sleeves? U-u-uh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Uh, I was hoping you wouldn’t notice. Irene was always a slave to a good bargain when it came to clothes, and sadly as it turned out, space heaters.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Ladies, please. These four walls once housed an intellectual salon where the mind received nourishment as well as the stomach. But through no one’s fault, Penny, the quality of dinner conversation in this apartment has declined. And again, I’m looking at no one in particular, Penny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Fine. What would you like to talk about, Sheldon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What would you like to talk about, Sheldon? Why do you hate us?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’ve prepared a number of topics that should appeal to both the advanced and novice conversationalists.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, that time you looked at me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Who didn’t? Your skin is like alabaster. Do you even have pores?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Topic one. Faster-than-light particles at CERN, paradigm-shifting discovery or another Swiss export as full of holes as their cheese? And converse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>All right, who wants to go to my apartment and look at bridal magazines?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Oh, me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-20"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Through no one’s fault, Sheldon, we’re leaving.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-21"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Wait for moi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You’re leaving?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-23"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon, sometimes you forget, I’m a lady. And with that comes an oestrogen fuelled need to page through thick glossy magazines that make me hate my body.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-24"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Ah. New topic. Women, delightfully mysterious or bat-crap crazy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-25"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Totally. What’s wrong with cap sleeves? If you have the right figure for it, they’re adorable.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey, Amy, what brings you to our neck of the woods?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Your neurology department loaned me a culture of prions for my research on bovine spongiform encephalopathy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>She popped by to borrow a cup of mad cow disease.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>It’s hard to make degenerative brain maladies hilarious, and yet somehow you do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>That’s fun to have in a lunchroom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>The real fun starts when you get to pick the rat you’re going to feed it to, and maybe you choose the beady-eyed little mother who’s been biting you all week.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Please, we’re eating. Can we get that off the table and change the subject?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Can we? Stand back while I turn this conversation into a conver-sensation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>This time, it’s your fault.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I have 100 alphabetized topics from artichoke, come on, people, it’s just a giant thistle, to zzz, the onamona-poetry of sleep.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Amy, how long would it take for that mad cow disease to kill me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I don’t know, four or five years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, it’s not gonna do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oy. Bernadette keeps texting me pictures of Penny in bridesmaid dresses.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>They’re out shopping right now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Just the two of them?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I guess.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>That’s cool, that’s cool.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Why are they asking me about this stuff? What guy knows what a sweetheart neckline is? </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Leonard’s coming down the home stretch! Come on, horsey, you can do this! Damn. Come on, thigh muscles, you can do this! Yes! First place. I would have been a great jockey if I weren’t too tall. And scared of horses. Sheldon, you’re up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Come on, it’s your turn. We said we’d get more fresh air.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Sorry. I’m a little distracted. I can’t seem to get in touch with Amy. I tried e-mail, video chat, tweeting her, posting on her Facebook wall, texting her, nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Did you try calling her on the telephone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>The telephone. You know, Leonard, in your own simple way, you may be the wisest of us all. Voice mail. Curiouser and curiouser.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>If you’re worried, we can go over there and see if she’s all right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Okay. You know, I heard in the news a bobcat has been spotted in her neighbourhood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t think Amy was eaten by a bobcat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Who thinks Amy was eaten by a bobcat?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Leonard, I was just mentioning an interesting local news item. Now, thanks to you, I’m worried Amy’s been eaten by a bobcat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Forget about the bobcat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>How can I? You won’t stop talking about it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Amy (singing)</speaker><content>Everybody hurts, sometimes everybody cries. Everybody hurts, sometimes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Sheldon (outside)</speaker><content>She sounds weepy. I don’t like weepy. Let’s go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh, she’s your friend. Step up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content> Amy.  Amy.  Amy. Bye.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Where are you going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m single, I don’t need this crap.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon, what are you doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You didn’t respond to any of my electronic communications.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I wanted to be alone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Would you like to talk about it? And keep in mind that no is a perfectly viable answer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon, my world is crumbling around me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Point of order. As you’re in distress, it would be customary for me to offer you a hot beverage. But I’m a guest in your home, so it would be customary for you to offer me a beverage. How do you want to proceed vis-a-vis beverages?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>It doesn’t matter. Nothing matters.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>If you’d like to take your mind off what’s troubling you, uh, word on the street is a bobcat has been spotted.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Penny and Bernadette went shopping for bridesmaids dresses without me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And that made you feel sad?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I knew it. Just keep going, I guess I’m good at this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>It’s just, I thought they liked hanging out with me, but I guess I was fooling myself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>When they were over here, did you fail to offer them a beverage? ‘Cause I can see how that could stick in someone’s craw.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-21"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon, I’m going to ask you something, and I’d like you to keep an open mind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Always.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-23"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>At this moment, I find myself craving human intimacy and physical contact.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-24"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, boy. You know ours is a relationship of the mind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-25"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Proposal. One wild night of torrid lovemaking that soothes my soul and inflames my loins.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-26"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Counterproposal. I will gently stroke your head and repeat, aw, who’s a good Amy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-27"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>How about this? French kissing, seven minutes in heaven culminating in second base.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-28"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Neck massage, then you get me that beverage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-29"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>We cuddle. Final offer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-30"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Very well. Oh, boy. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-31"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I’m just saying, second base is right there.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Mm, I’m thinking about adopting some quirky affectation, like a pipe or a monocle or a handlebar moustache.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>For all those girls out there looking for the Indian Monopoly man?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>This is not a safe place. You can’t share anything here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>The two of you need to get your women in line!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Last night I was strong-armed into an evening of harp music and spooning with an emotional Amy Farrah Fowler. This on a night that I had originally designated for solving the space-time geometry in higher-spin gravity and building my Lego Death Star. And why? Your gal pals, Penny and Bernadette, went out shopping for some wedding nonsense without Amy, an action they took with no thought or regard as to how it would affect me, the future of string theory or my Lego fun time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What do you want us to do about it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You clearly weren’t listening to my topic sentence, get your women in line! You make them apologize to Amy and set things right. I am a man of science, not someone’s snuggle bunny!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Why do I have to talk to Penny? She’s not my girlfriend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You invited her to lunch four years ago. Everything about her is on you, you make it so!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Moo-shu is Penny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Thank you. Where’s Sheldon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, he was up late last night, so I gave him an early dinner and put him to bed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>That’s so sweet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, but now he’s gonna be up at dawn and want to play.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>So, listen, guys, the reason he was up late is because he was taking care of Amy. She’s kind of upset.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Her feelings got hurt because you guys went dress shopping without her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I told you that would happen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, look, this is her first time being a bridesmaid and she’s just getting a little crazy with it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>She keeps on telling us stories about bridesmaid traditions in other cultures, and they’re all about getting naked and washing each other.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, and she keeps trying to figure out if our cycles have synced up so we can call ourselves the Three Menstra-teers</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>We thought it would be easier to look at dresses one time without her. I feel terrible.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I know. Me, too. We’ll talk to her. Hey, wait, how did she find out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Raj did it. And he says he would do it again. Okay, I’m sorry. You sent me the picture, I wasn’t thinking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Oh, Howie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Well, hey, I’m usually pretty good at not blabbing. You tell me tons of stuff about these guys, and I never repeat it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-18"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What do you tell him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-19"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Oh, you know, just pillow talk. You guys have nothing to worry about.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hold on, did you talk about us when we were dating?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-21"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No. All your little secrets are fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-22"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Yes, absolutely fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-23"><speaker>Howard (after Raj whispers to him)</speaker><content>I’ll tell you later.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Come on, tumour. Come on, tumour, Mama needs an aggressive little glioblastoma. Yay, brain tumour! Probably not the same reaction you had when you got the news.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Hello.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>What are you doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, look, we just wanted to apologize for not bringing you with us the other day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>That’s not necessary, it’s like Sesame Street says, one of these things is not like the other, one of these things should die alone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Look, come on, Amy, look, let us make it up to you. We’ll have a girl’s night, we’ll do whatever you want.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>We can go down to the Korean baths and do that thing you were talking about where we wash each other.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>With-with loofah mitts, no hands.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>It’s okay. I’m glad this happened. I can stop pretending that some beautiful girl and her cute-in-</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Amy, we’re really sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, we feel awful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Don’t. I’ll be okay. You’re not the first girls I thought were friends with me who ended up shunning me. It’s like elementary school, junior high, high school, undergrad, grad school, and that semester abroad in Norway all over again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, come on, Amy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You don’t get it. Look at this brain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I don’t really want to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>This is us. Bernadette, you are the analytical, scientific left hemisphere. Penny, you’re the creative, spontaneous right hemisphere. And where’s Amy? She’s right here, the sad little tumour no one wants to go dress shopping with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Amy, you’re not a tumour. Penny, tell her she’s not a tumour. .</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Did you know that when Alexander Graham Bell invented the telephone, he proposed answering it with ahoy? Ahoy. I like it. Amy? Is that you? Have you been drinking? I’m sorry, I bet my sweet what? Well, all right. We’re on our way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What’s going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It would seem Amy is drunk in a liquor store parking lot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Really? Amy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Leonard, be glad you can’t keep a woman. They are a handful.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Oh, look. It’s Sheldon and little Leonard. Hi, little Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hi, Amy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Hey, Cuddles.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Cuddles?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes, Cuddles. We cuddled. Grow up, Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Amy, what are you doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Well, I came here to get a bottle of wine like Penny taught me to do when you’re sad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, but why didn’t you go back to your apartment?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Didn’t you go to high school, Leonard? Parking lots are where all the cool kids hang out. Not that the rat bastards ever invited me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Maybe we should get you home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Oh, hang on, hang on, hang on. Sheldon, what would it take for you to go into that liquor store, buy a bottle of hooch, take me across the street to that motel, and have your way with me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, Sheldon, what would it take?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m begging both of you, please, let’s go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay. Come on. Upsy-daisy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Whee! Ooh, finally someone found second base.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I know how you feel. I got a knife slicing through my frontal lobe, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>What do you want? Do you want me to give the friendship bracelet back?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I never gave you a friendship bracelet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>When we first met, I made one and pretended you gave it to me. You can have it back if you want.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, you made that for you, I want you to have it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>We know you’re upset, and you have every right to be, but if it’s okay with you, we’d like a second chance to make things right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>We are really sorry, and we were trying to think of some way to show you how much we care about you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Which is why it would mean so much if you would agree to be the maid of honour at my wedding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>What? Wait, is this some kind of practical joke? Like in Norway, when my friends trapped me in a sauna with a horny otter?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>No. I, I want you to be the maid of honour.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Oh, my gosh. No one’s every asked me to be the maid of honour before. Well, that’s not true. Once, but then they all died.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>So is that a yes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Yes. Yes. Oh, my gosh, I, I have so much to do. There’s the bridal shower and the bachelorette party. What should we do for the bachelorette party? Oh, I know, we’ll go to a Native American sweat lodge, we’ll take peyote, roll around in the mud, and paint fertility symbols on Bernadette’s naked body. So that’s happening.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, sure, sure. Vegas is fun, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I feel like crying. Of course, I could just be hormonal. Oh, wait. Maybe our menses are finally syncing up. Bernadette? No? Penny?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-18"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Really?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-19"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-20"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Yay!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Maid of honour Amy Farrah Fowler’s amazing behind-the-scenes wedding video, take one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>We’re just trying on dresses, do we really need to record this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I’m sorry, are you the maid of honour?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I am the bride.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>So no. And action.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Penny (in a red bridesmaid dress)</speaker><content>What do you think?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I love it!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>What are you, a nun? Come on, bestie, let’s see some skin.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Oh, Amy! Looking sexy!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You think they don’t have mirrors in there? I know how I look.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh! Bernadette, you look beautiful!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Not Penny beautiful, but beautiful.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Come on, bestie, you’re up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>Penny (off)</speaker><content>Give me a minute.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>What is taking you so long? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, Amy! Get the hell out of here!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>– Sorry, sorry. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, God. Amy!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sorry.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>