<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Howard Wolowitz.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Voice</speaker><content>Hey, Howard. Dave Roeger here at NASA. We need to talk about your upcoming mission.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yes, yes, I’ve been doing my push-ups. I’m still stuck at nine, but that’s going all the way down with no one holding me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Roeger</speaker><content>That’s great, uh, but that’s not why I called. We’ve run into a bit of a snafu. Your Soyuz capsule failed the pressurization test, so bottom line, mission’s been scrubbed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Howard (Picks up receiver)</speaker><content>You’re kidding. So what does that mean? Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Boy, I got to tell you, I’m really disappointed. This was my dream ever since I was a little kid. Okay, well, uh, thanks for the call. Yep, you, too.  Yes! Thank you! Oh! Oh! I’m not gonna die in space! I’m gonna die the way God intended, in my late 50s, with a heart full of pastrami.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Sheldon (off)</speaker><content>I’m going to need a larger shirt. This one’s a little tight under the arms.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Assistant</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Do you think maybe it’s tight because you’re wearing long underwear?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes, of course that’s why it’s tight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>All right, let me rephrase the question. Why are you wearing long underwear?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You’re kidding. Shouldn’t the question be why aren’t you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, it should be: why are you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Leonard, these rental tuxedos have been worn by hundreds of sweaty strangers. I don’t like my own sweat touching my skin, how do you think I feel about theirs?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Assistant</speaker><content>Why don’t you slip this on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Said the hangman offering a noose.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Well, that wasn’t as entertaining as when he rents bowling shoes, but it was right up there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Well, that’s it. My orders have been rescinded. I am officially no go to space.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m sorry, Howard, but I got to tell you, I’m a little relieved you’re not going.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Come on, you were gonna go up in a rocket designed in the 1960s by the Russians.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, so?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>When was the last time you were at Best Buy and you heard someone say, ooh, check out this Blu-ray player, it must be good, it was built in Russia”?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Well, their technology isn’t that bad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>When you come back to Earth in a Soyuz capsule, you free-fall from space at 500 miles per hour, and the only thing that slows you down is a little parachute that pops out right before you crash into the ground. And the whole thing was designed by the same brilliant minds who were unable to capture Rocky and Bullwinkle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>All right, well, whatever. I wasn’t worried.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You weren’t?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-22"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Let me explain the difference between you and me. You watch Star Trek. I live it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-23"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, please. I don’t remember the episode of Star Trek where the guy never goes to space and brags about it in a tuxedo store.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-24"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Make all the jokes you want, but there’s only one of us here brave enough to almost do what I almost did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-25"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Ah, much better.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-26"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You must be burning up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-27"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>A little. But not more than your urethras will be after whatever’s in those pants swims up them. Well, I cut quite the dashing, yet hygienic figure, don’t I? I look like the Flash about to get married. Oh! A tissue! A tissue! Oh, good Lord!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-28"><speaker>Assistant</speaker><content>Uh, where’s he going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-29"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>He keeps emergency Purell in the car.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-30"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Keys! Keys! Keys!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey, you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Before I come in, you should know, I have gas. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>For the record, not your worst opening line.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Check it out. It’s the gas I use in my free-electron laser to support high voltages. But it also has an interesting secondary use. Here. Breathe this in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>B-Before I do it, if you’re a cop you have tell me, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Just try it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay.  What’s it supposed to… Oh, my God, this is so freaky!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Leonard (in low voice)</speaker><content>You’re a mean one Mr. Grinch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay. Me, me, me. Ready?  Leonard, I am your father.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I have never been more attracted to a woman who sounds like a man in my life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, Mm. Hey, you know how we’ve been taking things slow?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Mm-hmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, I’ve been thinking, and maybe I’m ready to take things a little faster.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Mm-hmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>And I promise, after waiting four months, fast is what you’re gonna get.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You know, just-just one thing. Look, we’re in a really great place right now, and I don’t want to do anything that will make stuff all weird again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>So we won’t let it get weird.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay. Oh, and just a heads-up, mm, since the last time you saw me naked, I got a Cookie Monster tattoo. The acceptable responses when you see it are awesome or nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What about  Cookies!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content> Amy?  Amy?  Amy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Seven o’clock, right on time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It’s not an accident. I waited outside your door for twenty minutes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Well, dinner’s almost ready.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I must say, I was surprised you chose to spend our date night in your apartment. As I mentioned, the Pasadena City Council is debating longer crosswalk times, and later, the LEGO store is having a midnight madness sale. You ask anyone, that’s a hot date.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Tempting choices, but I have something special planned for tonight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What can be more special than having an adequate amount of time to cross the street on your way to buy a tiny LEGO Indiana Jones?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>With our friends moving forward in their relationships, I’ve decided that we should make progress in ours as well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, dear Lord. Two years ago, we didn’t even know each other, and now I’m in your apartment after dark. How much faster can this thing go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I had a feeling you’d be reluctant, which is why I’m going to dip into my neurobiological bag of tricks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, you brain monkeys kill me. Dip away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I have devised an experiment that I believe will increase your feelings for me in an accelerated time frame.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And how do you propose to do that? Uh, hope you’re not thinking about some sort of LSD thought control. Because there’s only one mind-expanding drug that this man enjoys, and that’s called school.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Human beings form emotional attachments as they grow up. In your case, to your mother, superheroes, et cetera. I’m going to attempt an experiment that will get you to transfer those feelings to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, seems what’s on the menu tonight is malarkey with a big side of poppycock.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>We’ll see. Let’s start with a little romantic dinner music, shall we?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Super Mario Bros. theme?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I see what you’re doing. You’re attempting to build on the work of Ebbinghaus by triggering an involuntary memory of me playing that game, admittedly the happiest 600 hours of my childhood, but it won’t work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-20"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Fine. There’s no reason we still can’t have a lovely dinner. Why don’t you have a seat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Da-da-da da-da dum, boink, boink.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-22"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>May I offer you something to drink?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You know I don’t drink.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-24"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Not even strawberry Quik?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-25"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I love strawberry Quik. It’s my favourite pink fluid, narrowly beating out Pepto-Bismol.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-26"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Oh, I know. I think it will go nicely with what I have prepared for dinner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-27"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Spaghetti with little pieces of hot dog cut up in it!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-28"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Just like your mommy used to make.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-29"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh yummy, yummy! We should do this more often. Uh-oh.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m sorry. I did, I crossed a line. I didn’t mean to!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Who says something like that right in the middle of sex?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t know, it just came out. People say weird things during sex all the time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, well, they sure as hell don’t say that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It was the heat of the moment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, the heat of the moment is, ooh, yeah, just like that, not will you marry me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m sorry. Just, just give me another chance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Why, so you can crawl under the covers and go, hey, baby, want to go look for houses in neighbourhoods with good schools?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Again, I’m sorry. You know, with Howard and Bernadette getting married, I got caught up in a little wedding fever. I take it back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You can’t take something like that back. I mean, what are we even supposed to do now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, at some point, we’ll look back and this is going to be a funny story. Why don’t we just start doing that now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You’re kidding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No. Hey, do you remember that time when I proposed to you in bed? And you were all, like, what are you doing? That was so funny. So funny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>It’s not funny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Give it a minute. Is that a little smile I see there? I should go.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Hey, I was thinking. For our first dance at the wedding, what if we learn the final number from Dirty Dancing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>You’re kidding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No, come on. How cool would that be? Me running into your arms, you lifting me up into the air.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Oh, you’re in a good mood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, well, why wouldn’t I be? You know, I’m marrying the girl of my dreams, and I finally got my mother to agree not to come on our honeymoon.  Oh, hang on. Oh, it’s NASA. Wolowitz. Oh! Hi, Dave. What’s up? No kidding. Really? Well, that’s great news. Great, great news. All right, I’ll watch my e-mail for the details. Okay, talk soon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>What’s so great?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>It looks like I’m going into space after all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Oh, Howie, that’s wonderful!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Uh-huh, wonderful. Yay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>What happened? I thought they cancelled your mission.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Th-They did. But NASA really wants my telescope up on the space station, so they’re putting me on an earlier launch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>When?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>A week from Friday.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>What? We’re getting married that Sunday.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You’re right. I, I can’t go to space. I have to get married, and no one can say that’s not a good reason. I’ll call him back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Wait. I don’t want to be the one who stands in your way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Well, too bad, you already did. It’s a done deal. Oh, well. But I forgive you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-18"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>No. That’s not how I want to start our marriage, killing your dream. We’ll have the wedding when you get back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-19"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>But what about all the plans and the guests?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-20"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>We’ll call them. Although my dad’s gonna go a little nutso over losing his deposits.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-21"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You’re right, he is! Your dad’s gonna be furious. There’s no way he’s gonna let us postpone this wedding. Well, we tried.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-22"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I’ll talk to him. He won’t say no to his little girl.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-23"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No. I, uh, I should talk to him, man to man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-24"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>But, Howie, my dad can be a bully. He’s gonna make you cancel your space flight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-25"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>We can only hope… that he doesn’t.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Bishop to queen four, level two. Check.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, knight takes bishop. You all right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Are you? You left your queen exposed from above, you trapped your knight in the corner, and you keep sighing and saying, why me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Very well. Can I ask you a question about women?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>We got you that book last year. Wasn’t everything in there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, I’m having a relationship problem with Amy. And by the way, that book gave me nightmares.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, if it makes you feel any better, I screwed things up pretty good with Penny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Look at us, Leonard, engaging in the social convention of men bellyaching about their ol’ ladies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I guess we are. So, what’s going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Believe it or not, Amy has embarked on a campaign to increase my feelings for her by making me happy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m sorry, that must be very difficult for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It’s awful. This morning, she arranged for me to be an Amtrak junior conductor for the day. It, it’s usually only open to children. She got them to make an exception.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Shame on her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>They let me blow the whistle, Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>She’s good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I know. And it gets worse. Her efforts are causing me to have affectionate feelings for her at inappropriate times.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You mean, like in bed or in the shower?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No! Would you please stop referencing that infernal book? For example, this morning, I was calculating the random motion of virtual particles in a vacuum, when suddenly the particles morphed into an image of Amy’s dandruff gently cascading down onto her pale, slightly hunched shoulders. Oh, what has that vixen done to me, Leonard? And how do I make it stop?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, if you had a physical relationship, I’d say propose during sex. Turns out that’s a real mood killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I assume we’re talking about you now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-22"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>So, that’s how this works? I complain, and then you complain, and no one offers any solutions?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-24"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Pretty much.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-25"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, no wonder the women are winning.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Mr. Rostenkowski, are you busy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Mr. Rostenkowski</speaker><content>I’m just looking at some old pictures. Come on in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Family pictures, or… holy crap, that’s a dead person.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Mr. Rostenkowski</speaker><content>Last murder case before I retired. How many bodies do you see there? Careful, it’s a trick question.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’m not sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Mr. Rostenkowski</speaker><content>Nah, you’ll never get it. It’s a fraction.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>How about that. Anyway, sir, I need to talk to you about something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Mr. Rostenkowski</speaker><content>Walnut?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No, thank you. I’m allergic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Mr. Rostenkowski</speaker><content>Oh, sure. My partner used to have that. He’s dead now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>From nuts?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Mr. Rostenkowski</speaker><content>Nah, his wife shot him. But she was nuts, so in a way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Nice story. Anyway, the reason I wanted to talk to you is NASA has moved up my launch to the International Space Station.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Mr. Rostenkowski</speaker><content>Yeah, so?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>So, the date is going to conflict with me marrying your daughter. Now, I know what you’re going to say, I made a commitment to Bernadette and to your family and I’ve got a hell of a lot of nerve coming in here and demanding that we postpone this thing. Well, message heard and understood. Mission cancelled. Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>Mr. Rostenkowski</speaker><content>Where are you going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’m sorry. May I be excused?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>Mr. Rostenkowski</speaker><content>No, you may not. Let me tell you something. When I first met you… You just gonna stand there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’m sorry, I didn’t know, is this going to… Well, I should sit… May I be seat… Well, I’ll just sit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-20"><speaker>Mr. Rostenkowski</speaker><content>When I first met you, I didn’t like you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-21"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’m aware of that, sir.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-22"><speaker>Mr. Rostenkowski</speaker><content>But then you and I had some time together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-23"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Uh-huh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-24"><speaker>Mr. Rostenkowski</speaker><content>It did not get better.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-25"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Right, right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-26"><speaker>Mr. Rostenkowski</speaker><content>That silly Beatle haircut and you riding around on a red Vespa, and you still living at home with your mother. To be honest, I thought Bernadette chose you to punish me. But then I heard about your astronaut thing, and I realized I judged you too fast. Maybe you are the right guy for my little girl.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-27"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, I am. And just so you know, I’d still be an astronaut, even if I didn’t go to space. I’ve got an I.D. Card and a NASA golf shirt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-28"><speaker>Mr. Rostenkowski</speaker><content>No, no, you got to go. You can’t turn down an opportunity like this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-29"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>But what about the wedding and all the money you put down for the reception?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-30"><speaker>Mr. Rostenkowski</speaker><content>You let me worry about that. You go up to that space station, and you make me proud.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-31"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Um, okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-32"><speaker>Mr. Rostenkowski</speaker><content>You got a problem with that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-33"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>All right, look, I’m gonna level with you. I’m terrified about going into space. What if I don’t make it back?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-34"><speaker>Mr. Rostenkowski</speaker><content>It’s gonna be okay, son.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-35"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You really think so?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-36"><speaker>Mr. Rostenkowski</speaker><content>Of course. A pretty girl like Bernadette, she’ll find a new guy.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey. Off to work?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Have a nice night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, you, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Penny, just, wait. I’ve been thinking about what I said when we were in bed the other night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, I’ve been thinking about it, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I noticed you never answered me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You’re right.  No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh, follow-up. Are we still dating?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yep.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Is it still weird ’cause I proposed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yep.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I have a couple more quick questions. Do you want to call me from the car?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I played that pretty well. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Hello, Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-19"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>We’re playing doctor. Star Trek style.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m in hell, Leonard. Don’t stop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-21"><speaker>Teleplay</speaker><content>Bill Prady, Steve Holland _ Maria Ferrari</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-22"><speaker>Story</speaker><content>Chuck Lorre, Steven Molaro _ Jim Reynolds</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>