<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>The entrance to the dungeon is a moss covered door. You manage to open it only to find yourself face-to-face with a hideous, foul-smelling, moss-covered ogre. What do you do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I say, hey Ma, what’s for dinner?”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Seventeen. The ogre is amused by your joke and allows you to pass. By the by, I liked it, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey, how go the wedding plans, Howard?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Great. We spent five hours last night at Macy’s registering for gifts. Looks like I’m finally going to have that darling little earthenware asparagus dish I’ve always wanted.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>See, this is the good thing about having a girlfriend 9,000 miles away. I can spend my nights doing whatever I want.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You mean like playing nerd games with us and then taking a suspiciously long shower?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Maybe. We enter the dungeon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You see a dragon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Really? So we’re playing Dungeons and Dragons, and we walk into a dungeon and see a dragon? Isn’t that a little on the nose?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>When you play Chutes and Ladders, do you complain about all the chutes and all the ladders?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Are you gonna eat that whole pie?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Maybe. Why not? Who do I have in my life to watch my figure for?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, God, did you watch Bridget Jones again?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No, it’s just that everybody’s got someone. Sheldon’s with Amy, Howard’s getting married, you’re dating my sister.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Now that Howard’s getting married, maybe he’ll inflate one of his old girlfriends for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You know who I blame for my loneliness? The United States of America. Your movies and your TV shows promised streets paved with beautiful blonde women with big bazongas.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Eat another pie, you’ll have your own bazongas.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>That’s cruel. You know it goes straight to my hips.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Gentlemen, please focus. You’re facing a fire-breathing dragon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-21"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I don’t know if I want to play anymore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Because you don’t have a girlfriend? Well, good Lord, if that becomes a reason not to play Dungeons and Dragons, this game’s in serious trouble.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Now, I assume we use this same wax later on to neaten up each other’s bikini regions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, my bikini region is fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Who’s shocked? I’m not. So, Bernadette, how’s the wedding planning going? And I’m not asking as a prospective bridesmaid. Pick me! Pick me!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>We went cake-tasting yesterday. Raj came along. He cried and ate half the samples.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, the poor guy’s so lonely. We should set him up with someone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>You know, I met a really cute girl at work. She’s married to a guy in one of our drug trials.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, hello? She’s married.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Yeah, but her husband is in serious congestive heart failure, and a little birdie told me he’s in the placebo group.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, so future grief-stricken widow is the one to beat.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Are we ready to order?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>One moment. I’m conducting an experiment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>With Dungeons and Dragons dice?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes. From here on in, I’ve decided to make all trivial decisions with a throw of the dice, thus freeing up my mind to do what it does best, enlighten and amaze. Page 14, item seven.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>So, what’s for dinner?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>A side of corn succotash. Hmm. Interesting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Um, Howard, can I see you for a minute, please?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Uh, I don’t want to show any more of your friends how I can fit in the booster seats.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Uh, no, that’s not it. Just come with me, please.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Let’s see what I’ll be washing that succotash down with. A pitcher of margaritas.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Do you really want that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s the great thing. It doesn’t matter. My mind is freed up to think about more important things.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>What’s it thinking about now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hamburgers and lemonade.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Um, Raj, there’s someone I want you to meet. This is my friend Emily. I know her from my spin class. Raj, relax. She can’t hear you. She’s deaf.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>Howard (signing)</speaker><content>Emily, this is our friend Raj.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh! Look at you guys just hitting it off. I am so good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>She says it’s nice to meet you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-20"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Does she really mean that or was she signing it sarcastically?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-21"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Raj says it’s nice to meet you, too. She says she has to go back to her family, but Penny has her number if you want to text her and get together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-22"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Okay, I’m going to play it cool. Tell her, maybe. Whatever, babe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-23"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>He’ll text you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-24"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Ah, look at that. I have a date. I love America again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-25"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And now for dessert, come on, hot fudge sundae, come on, hot fudge sundae. Bam! That’s what I’m talking about!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Okay, as soon as she gets here, so she knows I’m cool with it, I’m going to make a joke about her being deaf. I was thinking, hey, did you hear the one about…? Oh, no, I bet you didn’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Maybe we should revisit your lonely fat guy plan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, she’s here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No joke. Oh, she says she’s sorry she’s late.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Tell her it doesn’t matter. Tell her, her eyes shimmer like opalescent lilies in the lake of the palace of the celestial maidens.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Really? That’s the first thing you want to say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I worked on it all night. Use it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Look, I don’t know the sign for opalescent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Then spell it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I don’t know how to spell it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You’re blowing this for me!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>He likes your eyes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You’re making me sound like a caveman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>She says, thank you, you have nice eyes, too.”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Really? Ask her how many children she wants, and whatever number she says, say, me too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Fine. Tell her I have a deep, sexy voice like James Earl Jones.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>She doesn’t know what James Earl Jones sounds like.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Great. Then she won’t know I’m lying.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Let’s see, what else can I tell you about me that would make you like me? Ooh, I love music. Do you love music?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You really want to ask her that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You’re right. Everyone loves music.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>She says, do you play an instrument?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No, but when I was six years old, I tried to start a boy band called Frankie Goes to Bollywood. But I couldn’t get any other boys to join, so my parents asked the servants to be my backup dancers. Wait, when you sign servants, don’t sign it like I’m bragging. Sign it in a way that I sound humble with just a hint of, that’s right, I had servants.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Do you hear yourself</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yes, but she doesn’t. So get signing, hand monkey.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Howard (translating for Emily)</speaker><content>I think I wrote a letter to Santa Claus every day. And then on Christmas morning, under the tree is a little puppy with a red ribbon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>What are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Texting Bernadette that I’m gonna be late.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Dude, what is she saying?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>It’s a funny story about a puppy. Just smile and laugh. Quick, quick, stop smiling.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>What? Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>The puppy died, it choked on a doll head. Sad face, sad face!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>It’s a little hard to see with the city lights, but that W-shaped constellation is Cassiopeia. And she was the mother of Andromeda who’s over there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Look, pretty stars. This is her car. She hopes she can see you again sometime.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Good, good. Oh, boy, help me out here. Does she want me to kiss her or not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I speak sign language, I don’t read minds.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>If you were me, would you kiss her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, but I’m a make out king. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I was so smooth on that date.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You? I made you smooth. You were an idiot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Whatever, dude. She kissed me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>It might’ve been on your lips, but it was my kiss.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, fine. Let’s agree she kissed both of us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Mustache is looking good there, Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Don’t thank me. Thank the dice. They told me what percentage of my face to shave.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Why are you still doing this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Because it’s working. In the past few weeks, unburdened by trivial decisions, I’ve co-authored two papers in notable peer-reviewed journals, and I’m close to figuring out why the Large Hadron Collider has yet to isolate the Higgs boson particle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You left out, got chafed testicles because you no longer wear underpants.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>The dice giveth and the dice taketh away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Is Raj out with Emily again?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, every night for the last month.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Wow, can’t believe he has a girlfriend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Sheldon (rolls dice)</speaker><content>Me neither.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Here’s some other fun news on the Raj/Emily front. He gave her a pair of diamond earrings and leased her a car.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You’re kidding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You think she’s taking advantage of him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, of course not. She wouldn’t do something like that. She’s deaf.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Deaf women can’t be gold diggers?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Handicapped people are nice, Leonard. Everyone knows that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, I actually have information about Raj that would be helpful with this discussion.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Could you tell us?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Let’s see.  Snake eyes. Sorry, bud.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-20"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Wait, hang on. Doubles. Roll again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Okay, get this. It doesn’t matter if he’s showering her with gifts, because the Koothrappalis are vastly wealthy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-22"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What do you mean, vastly wealthy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, wealthy means a lot of money, and vastly means even more. I’m not sure what’s tripping you up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-24"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Look, I know they have money. I don’t think it’s that much.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-25"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, you’re wrong. See, as you know, a few years ago, I achieved one of my lesser dreams and became a notary public. Well, from time to time, I notarize banking documents for Raj. The Koothrappalis aren’t just rich, they’re Richie Rich rich.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-26"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, so how much is that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-27"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>About halfway between Bruce Wayne and Scrooge McDuck.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-28"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What the hell? The last time we went to the zoo, that son of a bitch made me buy him a churro.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-29"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Listen, guys, I’m sorry, I don’t mean to be rude, but I need to go call Raj’s sister, who I love so much. So vastly much.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-30"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, so he’s got money, and it’s a few gifts and a car.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-31"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>And she got him to pay off all her credit cards.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-32"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What? He paid off her credit cards? Damn it, I could’ve dated Raj for a couple months. But I, I wouldn’t have, because I’m not that kind of girl. We should really talk to Raj.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-33"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>He’s not going to listen, he’s in love.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-34"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Can’t figure out what to do? I remember those days. Now, if you’ll excuse me, I have to…  stay right here.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, this is a bad idea. We should go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No. I’m the one that introduced him to her. I’ve got to say something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Wow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You’re engaged to my friend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Hey, Bernadette doesn’t mind where I get my motor running, as long as I park in the right garage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I can’t believe you’re engaged to my friend. Oh, here she comes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Smart. Whisper so the deaf chick can’t hear you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Howard (translating)</speaker><content>Oh, hey, hi. Nice to see you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Um, can we talk to you about Raj?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>She says, sure, what about him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, um, gosh, how do I start? Um, see, Raj is kind of naive. I mean, he hasn’t dated a whole lot of women. And I’m concerned that, without meaning to, you might be taking advantage of him. You know, by letting him buy you a bunch of expensive things.And I.. I… Howard, focus. Tell her what I’m saying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Right. Are you a gold digger or not? Oh, uh, something, something, who the something do you think you are? Mind your own something business and go something yourself. Oh, wait, I got this now.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I’m so mad at you!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, wait…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>How dare you ambush my girlfriend at the gym!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>We didn’t mean for it to be an ambush. Just, it’s kind of impossible not to sneak up on deaf people. And hey, since when are you so chatty?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I’m hammered.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Raj, come here. This girl is trouble. I mean, what kind of relationship is it where you buy her gifts and she gives you sex?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>The best one I ever had!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, come on. You know you can do better.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Aha. I see what’s going on here. You and I had our crazy night together, and now you can’t stand to see me with another woman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>It’s okay. I can’t get mad at your feelings.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I don’t have feelings.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yeah, that’s good. Keep telling yourself that. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>He is cuter now that I know he’s rich.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I have a surprise for you. Cover your eyes. Open them. It’s a real ruby. It was a little expensive, but no one can put a price on love. Although, the people at Cartier took a pretty good shot at it.  Oh, Mummy, Daddy. What a nice surprise.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Dr Koothrappali</speaker><content>No, it’s not a nice surprise, it’s a bad surprise.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Mrs Koothrappali</speaker><content>Penny called us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Penny?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Mrs Koothrappali</speaker><content>She told us you’re spending all our money on your new girlfriend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I just got her a couple of things. She gives me things, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Dr Koothrappali</speaker><content>Yeah, yeah, I’m a gynaecologist. I know exactly what she gives you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Mrs Koothrappali</speaker><content>You need to find a nice Indian girl from a good family. If you keep seeing this woman, you’re cut off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>What? You’re going to make me choose between the woman I love and the money I have very strong feelings for?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Dr Koothrappali</speaker><content>It’s up to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Well, I choose love.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>Dr Koothrappali</speaker><content>Hah. You’re an idiot. Love doesn’t last. Well, he’s going to find out eventually. Think about it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>My parents are making me choose between money and you. I choose you.  No, I think we’ll have to return the car.  And that necklace, yeah, that, too. But none of those things matter, because we have something better. We have love.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, Penny, I hurt so bad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I know, I know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Sometimes I put the TV on mute just to pretend she’s still with me. But I can’t watch the closed captioning without crying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, I’m so sorry. I wish I could make you feel better.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Seriously? I’m heartbroken and you’re hitting on me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What? No!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Look, Penny, you’re great, but I had a long talk with my parents, and they said if I date an Indian girl, I get a Maserati.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Mmm. Oh, cheesecake, you’re just as good as a woman, even though I can’t have sex with you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Try throwing it in the microwave for a few seconds.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Should I use the rest room or wait until we get home? Come on, papa needs to void his bladder. Oh, that’s not what you want to see after three buttermilks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Here you go, boys. I’ll pick it up when you’re ready.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Thanks for dinner, buddy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, real big of you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hurry, hurry, hurry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, and don’t cheap out on the tip. We all know you’re loaded now.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>