<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Hey, want to spend some time playing the new Star Wars game this weekend?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, I don’t know. I kind of promised myself I’d get off the computer, be more physically active. Get some exercise.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You’re about to walk up three flights of stairs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Good point, I’m in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You know what would be great? Let’s do it like the old days.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You mean, are you talking gaming marathon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yeah. Start Saturday morning, go 48 hours, sleeping bags, junk food.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Turn off our phones so our moms can’t call.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It would be like our World Of Warcraft a few years ago when the neighbours called the cops on us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>They called the cops because of the smell. They thought we were dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>We were badass back in the day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>All right, let’s do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>48 hours of Star Wars gaming.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>It’s on like Alderaan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey, Sheldon, clear your weekend. Starting Saturday morning, Star Wars marathon</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Woo-hoo!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Movies or video games? Or board game? Or trading card games? Or Lego’s? Or dress up? Or comic books? Or dramatic readings of novelizations? Yes to all!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>We are going to play the online game.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>The online game? Bully!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-20"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Gentlemen, as much as I’m sure Sheldon would enjoy playing intergalactic make-believe, he and I have other plans. We are attending my Aunt Flora’s 93rd birthday party.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Just tell her I can’t come.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-22"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>She’ll be disappointed if we don’t show up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>She’s 93. She won’t be disappointed for very long.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-24"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>No, hang on. I followed all the protocols set forth by you in the relationship agreement. I made a written record request 72 hours in advance. I checked the tyre pressure on the car. I even contacted the Centres For Disease Control to find out what shots they recommend for travel to Orange County. FYI, it’s none.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-25"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Amy, the relationship agreement was not designed for either one of us to get our way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-26"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You use it to get your way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-27"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I use it to get the right way. The fact that the right way is also my way is a happy coincidence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-28"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You gave me your word. You’re coming with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-29"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>We’ll miss you, Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-30"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, well, who wants to spend the whole weekend, running around a bunch of pretend planets battling made up monsters. That’s for babies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-31"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, but it’s got lightsabres.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-32"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, please, Amy! It’s got lightsabres!</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hello Stuart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Hey Sheldon. Help you with anything?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes. I’m attending a party this weekend, for a 93-year-old woman. Can you recommend a gift?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Uh, I don’t know. Could put a tennis ball on the end of Excalibur. Make a pretty badass cane.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Do you supply the the tennis ball?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Then no. What else?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Hmm. Oh, have this collectors edition Batman utility belt. Maybe she can use it as a wearable pill caddy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, she’d just look silly wearing that without the rest of the costume.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>I’m sorry Sheldon, that’s it. That’s all I got.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, it’s not your fault. I’ve been to the model train store. I’ve been to Radio Shack. This woman is impossible to shop for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’d make fun of Sheldon for having girl problems if I wasn’t in shock that Sheldon has girl problems.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, Leonard, go ahead and mock. Like my daddy always said, Shelly, women aren’t anything but flippin’ pains in the bottom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That’s what your father used to say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, I took out the bad words and the yeehaw, but you get the gist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Look, if you don’t want to go to the party, just don’t go. You’re a grown man. Act like one. Tell Amy you want to spend the weekend having a sleepover and playing video games with your friends. Maybe she’ll dig it. Women like a firm hand on the tiller.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I can never find the tiller. I got a book; it didn’t help.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, I always thought if I were ever enslaved, it would be by an advanced species from another planet, not some hotsy-totsy from Glendale.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Now, I downloaded an app that might be helpful in this situation. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You’re right. I’m smart as a whip. I should be able to figure this out.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey, listen, I kind of made plans with the guys this weekend, but then I wondered, because we’re in this relationship-beta-test, if I should have asked you first. Then I thought if I did check with you first, you’d think that I was taking things to seriously. And then, then I got a nosebleed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You don’t have to check with me. Do whatever you want.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh. I guess I was hoping for a different reaction, but okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Really, what were you hoping for?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t know, maybe that you’d be a little upset, and then you’d realize that I’m a stallion that has to run free. And that would turn you on a little.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, I’m an actress. Ask me again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Do you mind if I spend the weekend playing video games with the guys?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Whu… the entire weekend? You mean I wouldn’t see you at all? But I ju… No, no, I knew what I was getting into. You can’t put a saddle on Leonard Hofstadter. Oh, my, is it getting hot in here? Ay, papi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Ay papi? What is that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>An acting choice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh. So you chose that when you become turned on, you turn into Speedy Gonzalez?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Choo got a problem with that, papi?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh-uh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content> Penny!  Penny!  Penny!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sorry, Stallion. Your weird friend Giraffe is here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hello, Penny. I just stopped by to bring you this gift.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Gummy bears? Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Now that you’re in my debt, please manipulate Amy into releasing me from my commitment to attend her aunt’s tedious birthday party.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Not a chance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right. I thought the candy might not be enough so let me up the ante. These are Cooper Coupons. These are for various things I can do for you. Um, oh, this one is for one free grammar check. Uh, you could use it for emails, letters, tattoos, what have you. Um, oh, this is fun one. This is an afternoon with me at the California Science Center, where I point out their mistakes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Keep an eye on those expiration dates, I’ve been burned more than once.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-22"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>All right, sweetie, I’m not going to get involved in your relationship.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, come on. It’s just a simple favour. Now, when’s the last time I asked you to do something for me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-24"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yesterday. You made me look in your ear to see if there was a ladybug in it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-25"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>When is the last time I asked you to do something that wasn’t a medical emergency?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-26"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yesterday. You made me look in your ear to see if there was a ladybug in it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-27"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right, then, I have no choice but to go on to plan B.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-28"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What’s that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-29"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m going to run around outside with a wet head and try to catch a cold.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Good morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hello.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I think you’re really going to enjoy yourself today. Not only do you get to meet my relatives, but since my aunt’s nursing home is catering the party, all of the food is incredibly soft. It’s like a vacation for your teeth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You sure you’re okay with this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes. I decided to find a way that I could have this experience and enjoy it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Thank you. That means a lot to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, don’t thank me. Thank wireless technology. I realized, I can go to your aunt’s awful party and still spend the whole day gaming with my friends.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon, my relatives are going to want to talk to you, and you’re going to be sitting there playing a game? Isn’t that a little rude?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, I got that covered. Headset. I won’t hear a word the old geezers are saying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You know, if playing that game is more important to you than honouring your commitment to me, and you don’t mind me showing up at a party all by myself after I’ve already told everybody I’ll be bringing somebody, then, fine. Go home and play your game.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Thanks. Ooh, listen, I wouldn’t mind a piece of birthday cake, provided the old gal’s candle blow is clean and dry.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Here you go. I’ve got everything we’ll need for the big game. Low fat turkey jerky, low-carb beer, 100-calorie snack packs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You pick up a Y chromosome while you were there? You might be short one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Hey, I plan on levelling up in the game, not my swimsuit size, thank you very much.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Gentlemen, the game offers us a choice between playing for the Republic and the light side, or the Sith Empire and the dark side.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, we’re always the good guys. In D_D, we’re lawful good, in City Of Heroes, we’re the heroes, in Grand Theft Auto, we pay the prostitutes promptly and never hit them with a bat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Those women are prostitutes? You said they were raising money for stem cell research.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Hey, guys, I got a surprise.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh, if it’s yoghurt that helps ladies poop, I think Raj beat you to it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No. Bernadette’s going to be playing with us. So, that’s pretty cool, huh? Right? Sure it is, yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>What, you invited your girlfriend? This is supposed to be our weekend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I had no choice. Last night, she said, why don’t we go out for brunch tomorrow and then maybe the Arboretum. And I said, well, no, I promised the guys I was going to play a video game with them all weekend. And she said, that sounds like fun, can I come, too? And then I didn’t answer for a second, and then she said, well, do you not want me to come? And then I bought her a new laptop and the game, and she’s parking the car right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Is the whip sound app contextually appropriate here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh, it is, but I think you might’ve waited too long for it to be funny.  I was wrong, it’s still funny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, good. Hah-hah!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Amy, what’s wrong?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>My boyfriend’s a jerk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, I know he didn’t cheat on you, so what happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I had to go to my aunt’s party all by myself, and everybody was like, where’s this boyfriend you’re always talking about? Is he real, or did you make him up like Armin the miniature horse breeder?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Who’s Armin the miniature horse breeder?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>The pretend boyfriend I invented to get my family off my back. It unravelled quickly when I couldn’t answer the question how’d you two meet?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I would have thought at a miniature horse show.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Oh, that’s good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Mm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I panicked and said Woodstock. I just wanted to show Sheldon off to my family.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sure, I get that. I mean, he’s your first boyfriend and all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Not just my first boyfriend, he’s the best boyfriend. I mean, think about it. I’m dating Sheldon Cooper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yes. On purpose.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>He’s handsome, he’s lanky, he’s brilliant, and his skin has that pale, waxy quality.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, sickly is the new sexy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Mm. You know, Amy, sometimes when you’re in a relationship with someone you really care about, the sucky part is, it leaves you open to getting hurt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-18"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Do you ever worry about Leonard doing that to you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-19"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>That’s hilarious. No.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Get that guy! Get that guy! Pew! Pew! Pew! Pew!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Dr. Rostenkowski, it may interest you to know that saying pew, pew, pew isn’t as effective as pressing your blaster key. In the same way that saying whee doesn’t make the land speeder go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Pew!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Raj, Imperial Troopers on your tail.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Got him. When Gandhi advocated his philosophy of non-violence, I bet he didn’t know how much fun it was killing stuff.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>All right, I think we got them all. Let’s divide up the loot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Ooh, look at this pretty purple robe I just got. You should put on yours and then we’ll match.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>But I worked hard to get this armour.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Sorry, I just thought it’d be nice if people knew we were a couple.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Fine, I’ll change. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hah-hah!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I don’t think I want to play a game.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, come on. They’re playing one across the hall, we should, too. Okay, we are gonna take turns bouncing a quarter off the table, and if it goes into this cup, the other person has to drink. Then you get to go again…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Like that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Wow. Yeah, b-beginner’s luck. So, now I will drink this entire cup of beer, and you will go again and we can… uh… all right. So, yeah, okay, now I’m gonna drink this entire cup and then I’m going to drink another one… Okay, seriously, stop. What the hell?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Spent a lot of my childhood throwing coins into wishing wells hoping for friends. At a certain point, you start doing trick shots just to keep things interesting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Whoa, whoa, give me a second to catch up here. Hold on. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>That’d be my boyfriend. Happier playing his dopey Star Trek game with his friends than hanging out with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Wars.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Star Wars. They get all cranky when you mix the two up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>What’s the difference?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>There’s absolutely no difference.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>How do I get him to treat me better?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>All right. Let me give you a little girlfriend 101. Usually the first move out of the gate is you withhold sex, but that will work better after Sheldon hits puberty. So, I’d say give him the silent treatment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>No, he loves that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Our record for sitting in a room together and not speaking to each other is six-and-a half hours. He said it was a magical evening.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>All right, then we’re gonna have to go with an oldie but goodie, making a scene.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I don’t think I’d be good at that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-20"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>That’s why you’re lucky to have me. Back in Omaha, there are two different restaurants I’m not allowed into. Both Chili’s.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Bernadette, remember, your character’s the healer in our group. You’re in charge of healing all of us, not just Howard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I can’t help it. My Howie Wowie has an owie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That is the most sickeningly sweet thing I have ever experienced. And I am sipping Kool-Aid through a Red Vine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Amy (bursting in)</speaker><content>Sheldon Cooper, I’ve got a bone to pick with you, and I’m about to do it in front of all your friends.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, you pick that bone. You pick that bone clean!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I’m gonna publicly shame you, and then sit back as societal pressure compels you to modify your behaviour.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Ooh, burn!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>And if you don’t start treating me better, I’m leaving you for a miniature horse breeder named Armin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Armin who?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Armin… damn it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sheldon, she wanted to show you off to her family, and you stood her up, okay? Look at this adorable, smushy face. Smush, smush, smush, smush.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You’re hurting me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, Sheldon hurt you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Before; now it’s you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I think I understand. You’re the one person who can say Sheldon Cooper is your boyfriend, but that rings hollow if you can’t lord him over others in the flesh. I forget what I bring to the party and what I take away when I leave. Please accept these valuable Cooper Coupons as restitution.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sheldon, she doesn’t want your stupid…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Ooh, Science Center. Redeeming. Let’s go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well played, Amy Farrah Fowler. Let me get my coat.  Oh, grow up, Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-20"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>But e-excuse me, I have something to say. None of you may realize it, but I was very much looking forward to this weekend. It was gonna be like the old days, the four of us hanging out playing video games before you guys all got girlfriends. Do you have any idea what it’s like to be the only one without a girlfriend? Even if I get one someday, I’ll still be the guy who got a girl after Sheldon Cooper!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-21"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>And that’s how a girl makes a scene. I’m sorry, sweetie. You’re right. You deserve your weekend. Come on, Amy, let’s go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-22"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>What about the Science Center?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-23"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I’ll let you hold my hair while I throw up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-24"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Rain check.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-25"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I’m gonna go, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-26"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’ll miss you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-27"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I’ll miss you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-28"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’ll miss you more.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-29"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>No, I’ll…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-30"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Just leave! Okay, now. This is the way it’s supposed to be. Men together, fighting the forces of evil.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-31"><speaker>All</speaker><content>Hear! Hear!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-32"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I can’t believe this is only 64 calories.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Mrs Wolowitz (off)</speaker><content>Howard Joel Wolowitz! I’ve been worried sick for two days, and I know you turned off your phone! You open up this door right now because I’ve had it up to here! I have been to the morgue and the hospital, and I spent the last half hour walking up these ferkakta stairs!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>That’s my ride, got to go. </content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>