<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m just gonna run to the store and get a few things. I’ll pick you up when you’re done.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Okay. I like it a little better when you stay, but all right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Barber</speaker><content>Hey, Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hello. I’m here for my haircut with Mr. D’Onofrio.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Barber</speaker><content>I’m sorry, Uncle Tony’s in the hospital. He’s pretty sick.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, dear, Mr. D’Onofrio’s in the hospital. Why do these things always happen to me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Barber</speaker><content>I can cut it for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You’re not Mr. D’Onofrio. I get my hair cut by Mr. D’Onofrio. You believe this guy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Excuse us for a second. Sheldon, it’s okay, he can do it. He’s a barber.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>He’s not a barber, he’s the nephew. He’s an example of the kind of nepotism that runs rampant in the barbering industry. Besides, Mr. D’Onofrio knows exactly how I like my hair done because he has all my haircut records from my barber in Texas.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What are you talking about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>When I first moved here I was nervous about finding a new barber, so my mother had all my haircut records sent here to Mr. D’Onofrio.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>There’s no such thing as haircut records.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes, there are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Have you ever seen them?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, but my mother assured me they were sent here, and I’ll bet you dollars to doughnuts that this one doesn’t have them. Uh, excuse me. Do you have access to my haircut records?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Barber</speaker><content>Your what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>To paraphrase T.S. Eliot, this is the way the world ends, not with a bang but with a nephew.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, you’re a grown man, he’s a professional, and your haircut is number three on that poster from 1946. Just sit down and let him do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Fine, but if I come out of this looking like a dork, it’s on you. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-21"><speaker>Barber</speaker><content>So my kid said the funniest thing today.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Nope. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-23"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>When you tell this story later, the word we usually use is quirky.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Can you pass the Parmesan cheese?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sure. What are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m trying to get the hair out of my eyes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, you are one day late for your haircut.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Thank you for captioning my nightmare.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Lookie here, I got my travel orders.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Payload Specialist Howard Wolowitz is requested to report to the NASA Johnson Space Center, Houston, Texas, for astronaut training Monday eight a.m.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, but it’s from NASA, so it’s oh eight hundred.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>But it says eight a.m.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You read it as oh eight hundred.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>It doesn’t have an oh in front of it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You know what does have an oh in front of it? Oh, my God, I’m an astronaut, and you’re dying of jealousy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>So, what kind of things are they…  will you stop that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I can’t help it, I feel like a teen heartthrob.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You know, Sheldon, I used to cut my brother’s hair. I could do it for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Penny, I know you mean well, offering the skills of the hill folk, but, um, here in town we don’t churn our own butter, we don’t, uh, make dresses out of gunny sacks, and, uh, we sure as shootin’ don’t get our hair cut by bottle-blonde…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, be nice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m sorry, it’s the bad boy attitude that comes with this hair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You could go to my guy. He’s at Juan-Juan in Beverly Hills. They bring you a cup of tea, they’ll massage your scalp. It’s about two hundred dollars, but sometimes you look in the next chair and you see a superstar like Tony Danza.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Quick question here, have we actually changed the conversation from I’m going</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Now who’s dying of jealousy? Oh, it’s you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I’m a cowboy, on a steel horse I ride. I’m wanted… I’m wanted… wanted, dead or alive. Sheldon, you’re ruining girlfriend-boyfriend sing-along night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m sorry. I’m looking for a barber and I’m running out of time. My hair is growing at the rate of 4.6 yoctometers per femtosecond. I mean, if you’re quiet, you can hear it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>What about Supercuts?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I tried once. They do men’s and women’s hair in the same room at the same time. It’s like Sodom and Gomorrah with mousse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Well, this isn’t a crisis. Why don’t you just let your hair grow out a little?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Why don’t I let my hair grow out? Um, why don’t I start wearing Birkenstocks and, uh, uh, seeking validation of my opinions by asking can you dig it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Well, I don’t know. I think you might look sexy with long hair. The kind that flows down to your shoulders and blows back while riding on a horse, bareback and bare-chested. I’m gonna go brush my teeth, it might take a while.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Howard (on Skype)</speaker><content>Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Hi, sweetie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I miss you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I miss you, too. So tell me all about your first day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, wow, where do I even start? I got to experience zero gravity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Cool. How do they do that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>It’s pretty neat. You get in this plane that goes almost straight up for, like, 20 seconds, and then straight back down like it’s going to crash, and they do it over and over again, you know, no matter how many times you throw up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>You threw up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, and the craziest part is, because there’s no gravity, the throw-up kind of floats there, in a little ball, and if your mouth is open because you’re screaming, sometimes it just floats right back in. Boy, does everyone laugh at you when that happens.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>That sounds mean.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No. Yeah, I would have laughed, too, but I didn’t want the vomit to come back out. Anyway, oh, could you do me a favour and overnight me some more underwear?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Sure, why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I got a look at the centrifuge they’re going to spin me around in tomorrow, and I have a hunch I packed a little light.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Mr. D’Onofrio? It’s Sheldon. They didn’t have anything barber-themed in the gift shop, so I got you this. I don’t know if you can read his little T-shirt. It says, um, get well bear-y soon. Trust me, if you were even a little conscious right now, you’d be laughing. Anyway, there’s new studies that show, people in comas are aware of everything going on around them. With that in mind, if you can hear me, move away from the light and toward the sound of these scissors.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Nurse</speaker><content>Can I help you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes. Do you have something I could use as a cape?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Nurse</speaker><content>Oh, dear, did we spit out our pills, slip out of the ninth floor, and go on a little adventure?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, no, no, I’m just here to get my hair cut.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Nurse</speaker><content>I-I see. J-Jus-Just wait here one moment. Security!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I got to run. But not with scissors, that would be unsafe.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>So, if I move my horsey here, isn’t that checkmate and I win?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, is it or isn’t it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You know, I think this is a good stopping point. Uh, it’s your first real game. I threw a lot of information at you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, no, I mean, your king is trapped. He can’t go here because of my lighthouse, and he can’t go here because of my pointy-head guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Like I said, complicated game.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>So did I win or not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Did you have fun? Because if you had fun, then you are, you are a winner. Now that’s, that-that’s what chess is all about.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hello.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, hey. Sorry, Sheldon, I’ll move.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Eh, why? My spot, your spot, what difference does it make?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, what just happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t know. Between you playing chess like Bobby Fischer and Sheldon being okay with you in his spot, I’m guessing someone went back in time, stepped on a bug, and changed the course of human events.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Uh, sweetie, are you all right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, I’m not all right. It’s been six days since I was supposed to get a haircut and nothing horrible has happened.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, I’m sorry, I don’t understand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Leonard, explain it to her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, uh, he’s crazy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I have spent my whole life trying to bring order to the universe by carefully planning every moment of every day. But all my efforts, our dinner schedule, my pyjama rotation, my bowel movement spreadsheet, it’s clear now, I’ve been wasting my time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Good. I’m taking that disgusting chart off the fridge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-22"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You know, Sh-Sheldon, sometimes it’s nice not knowing what’s coming. I mean, look at me and Leonard. We went out, we broke up, now we’re trying again. We don’t know what’s gonna happen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, please, everyone knows what’s going to happen. But I see your point.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-24"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I think this could be good for you. Maybe it’s time for you to shake things up a bit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-25"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You’re right. I should embrace the chaos.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-26"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Great. What are you going to do first?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-27"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I don’t know. I could do anything. All bets are off. The world is my oyster. I got it. I’m going to put on my Tuesday pyjamas tonight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-28"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I got to tell you, I’m a little worried about him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-29"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>If I were you, I’d be worried that a girl who’s never played chess in her life just kicked your ass.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Howard (on Skype)</speaker><content>Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Howie, what happened to you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>We did overnight survival training in the wilderness. Big fun. Big, big fun. I was gonna freshen up for you but I blacked out a little on the way to the bathroom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Survival training? Is that like camping?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Uh-huh. Except you don’t have food or water, and they don’t have a sunset Sabbath service like they do at Camp Hess-Kramer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Do you sleep in tents?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No. I slept in a hole I dug in the ground with my bare hands. And at some point during the night, an armadillo crawled in and spooned me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Poor baby.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>But I did it. I survived. I wasn’t sure I was going to when the sandstorm hit. I just pulled my turtleneck up over my head and waited for death. But somehow as I sat there, wrapped in a cocoon of my own neck-sweat, I found that primal part of the human spirit that just wants to keep on living, no matter what the cost.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>You’re so brave. I’m proud of you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I ate a butterfly. It was so small and beautiful, but I was so hungry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Are you crying?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No, I don’t think it’s possible. I’m severely dehydrated. My pee is like toothpaste.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Howie, if you’re not able to do this, come home. It won’t change how I feel about you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Thanks, honey, but I can’t quit. If I do, I’ll just be a guy who had a chance to be an astronaut and gave it up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Well, is there anything I could do to help?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No. Wait. Send more underwear.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Leonard (going to living room)</speaker><content>Don’t let this be Sheldon playing bongos. Please don’t let this be Sheldon playing bongos.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hello, Leonard, do you like my bongos? Bet you didn’t know that I had bongos.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, it’s three o’clock in the morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Three in the morning is a good time for bongos.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I was sleeping.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Leonard sleeps while I play bongos.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, he doesn’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Leonard no sleep while I play bongos. Bongo solo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Stop! Stop it! Stop! Stop! Stop it!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Penny (entering)</speaker><content>What the hell?!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, hi, Penny, guess what? Sheldon got bongos.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Why did you get bongos?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Richard Feynman played the bongos. I thought I’d give that a try.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Richard Feynman was a famous physicist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, Leonard, it’s three o’clock in the morning. I don’t care if Richard Feynman was a purple leprechaun who lived in my butt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Penny meant if he were a purple leprechaun. Penny forgot to use the subjunctive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, go to bed. You have work in the morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Maybe, maybe not. Maybe tomorrow I start a bongo band and tour the world.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>W-w-wuh, no, no, hang on,uh, uh, roommate agreement. No hootenannies, sing-a-longs, or barbershop quartets after ten p.m.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Roommate agreement? Are you kidding? We are living in a world of chaos. Roommate agreement.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-21"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Where are you going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Wherever the music takes me, kitten. I play bongos walking down the stairs.  Oh! Oh! Never play bongos walking down the stairs.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Surprise.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What are you doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I’m here to help you get through this. You can’t do it on your own, you need someone to take care of you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, I love you so much.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Oh, I love you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Mrs Wolowitz (off)</speaker><content>Howard, your bath is getting cold!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Don’t worry, once she falls asleep, I’ll spoon you like an armadillo.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>He showed up in the middle of the night with his bongos. I foolishly thought it was some sort of musical booty call.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Poor guy. He must have been exhausted. Sheldon like to sleep while Leonard play the bongo!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>That was kind of uncalled for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, it was called for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What’s going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>All right, Sheldon, this craziness has gone on long enough. Please come home so I can cut your hair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Penny, you’re not trained. You’re not licensed. Most importantly, you don’t have access to my haircut records.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>All right, honey, look, we’ve known each other for a long time now, right? I’ve taken you to Disneyland, I kicked a bully in the nuts for you, I sing you Soft Kitty when you’re sick, you’ve even saw me naked once.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m sorry, duh, what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>It was a long story. Anyway, Sheldon, I promise I know what I’m doing. Please let me cut your hair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Amy, what do you think?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>There’s not a hair on my body I wouldn’t let this woman trim.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Fine, let’s go. Thank you for letting me sleep on your couch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>There’s only so many times a woman can say how about the bed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What’s this about Sheldon seeing you naked?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, relax. It was just her bottom and her breasts.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Almost done.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>At the end of the haircut, Mr. D’Onofrio would tell me a dirty joke.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, sorry, I don’t know any dirty jokes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s okay, I never understood them anyway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, what do you think?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hmm, well, it’s a little Hollywood. But I think I can pull it off. Well done, Penny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Ha, told you. Okay, I’m just gonna clean up your neck a little and then you are good to go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Fun time. Hah. Sorry, sometimes the clippers tickle me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay.  Okay, yep, we’re all done now. It’s just, it’s good. Let me just take that away from you. Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Sgeldon</speaker><content>Thank you very much.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You are welcome. Yeah, I’m gonna have to move.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>