<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I wish you could all be inside my head. The conversation is sparkling.  Fine, I’ll tell you. A lichen is an organism made up of two separate species, fungi and algae. If you could merge with another species, what species would you pick and why? Hint, there is a right answer. None of you will get it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Okay, uh, I’d pick swan because, uh, the resulting hybrid would have the advanced industrial civilization of a human and the long graceful neck I’ve always dreamed of having.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Wrong. Leonard?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Horse, but mostly just for the height. A little bit for the genital girth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Wrong, and let’s keep it clean, shall we?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Kangaroo, uh, I’d be a Kanga-Jew. The first of my people to dunk a basketball.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Also instead of just living in your mother’s house, you could actually live inside her body.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Clever, but also wrong. No, the best organism for human beings to merge with is the lichen itself. That way, you’d be human, fungus, and algae. Triple threat. Like three-bean salad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Give me one circumstance in which that would be useful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right, picture this, a beautiful outdoor concert. Now, as a human, I appreciate Beethoven. As a fungus, I have a terrific view, growing out of a towering maple tree. And no thank you, expensive concessions. Because as an algae, I’ll just snack on this sunlight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>He got us again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, he didn’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Anyway, if it’s okay with you, we should talk about Howard’s bachelor party.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, seems like a bit of a let down after our lichen conversation, but, what do you know, you’re half swan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I’ve been doing some research on strippers. One agency I spoke to, said I could get us a great price if we’re flexible on age range and number of limbs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Sounds like loads of fun, but I promised Bernadette no strippers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You don’t want strippers? You’re the king of strippers. The one club in North Hollywood named a pole after you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What can I tell ya, I’m not into that stuff any more.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Good for you, Howard. I’m proud of you. And still, you’re the first one of us to get married. We have to do something special.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You know Germans have an interesting pre-wedding custom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-21"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Well, it’s probably not for me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-22"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Maybe we can go up to Napa Valley. They’ve got that wine train.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Boo, wine! But yay, trains. I’m in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-24"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Anyway, it’s a beautiful time of year. Uh, you travel through the vineyards. There’s a tasting on board. And all the wild flowers are in bloom. It’s magic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-25"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Look at that, in 30 seconds, we went from hiring women to being them.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>So, I hear you and the lost boys are having a bachelor party tonight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, just going to a restaurant, get some steaks and scotch. Nothing to worry about.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Why should I worry?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, I don’t know. It’s a bachelor party. There could be strippers. Wouldn’t that make you a little jealous?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, come on Leonard, it’s you. What’s going to happen? I mean, even if there was a stripper, all you’d do is avoid eye-contact and maybe offer to help her kid with his homework.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey, I am a young man in his sexual prime. Under the right conditions, I-I-I am capable of just, really crazy stuff.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Really? What is the craziest thing you’ve ever done with a woman? And the time you and I had sex in the ocean does not count.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, come on, that’s got to count. There was a really strong undertow, we could have died.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, have fun tonight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, I will. There is no telling what might happen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, there is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You know, there’s nothing wrong helping some woman’s kid get through their S.A.T.’s.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey, I got to hand it to Raj, he found a really nice spot to have a bachelor party.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It’s not bad. Unless you compare it to a train; then it stinks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Are you drinking whisky?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Indeed. If I’m to participate in the social convention that is the stag night, then I must embrace all its components, including tobacco, swear words, and yes, alcohol. Jeepers! That’s yucky.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Whoa, it’s a little early to start dropping J-bombs, don’t you think?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Wil Wheaton</speaker><content>Hey, you guys.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, hey, Wil. Nice of you to make it out tonight for Howard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Wil</speaker><content>Well, it was either this or another hot tub party at George Takei’s house.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m confused. I thought since our reconciliation, I was your friend in this group.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Wil</speaker><content>Oh, I’m friends with Howard too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh. I guess you’re just friends with anybody.  Aagh!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Hey, uh, Leonard, things are a little tight at the comic book store. I might need some help covering my share of the check.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, yeah, no worries.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>And maybe a few bucks for the valet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, all right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>And gas money to get home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Great. You know what? This is my grandfather’s watch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-20"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>18-carat gold, got it in Europe during the war.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Wow, that’s very nice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-22"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Mm-hmm. A hundred bucks and it’s yours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-23"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Hey, everybody! The bachelor boy has arrived! For he’s a jolly good fellow…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-24"><speaker>All (joining in)</speaker><content>For he’s a jolly good fellow, for he’s a jolly good fellow, which nobody can deny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-25"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>Yes, yes, yes. He’s a jowwy good fewwow. What time do the stwippers awwive?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-26"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Actually, Barry, we’re not going to have strippers tonight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-27"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>Ah, then what the fwig did I get two hundwed dowwaws in singles out for?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-28"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>You want to buy a watch?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Amy (into a mini-cam)</speaker><content>This is Maid of Honour Amy Farrah Fowler, bringing you the wedding activities just weeks out from the big day. Let’s check in with a beautiful, radiant young woman, and her friend who’s about to get married. Ladies, can you tell us what you’re doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Um, these are gift bags we’re going to put in the hotel rooms of our out-of-town guests. This is a map of Pasadena. This is a list of local restaurants. And then, for Howie’s relatives, we have antihistamines, antacids, and medicine for diarrhoea and constipation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, we labeled them stop and go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>All right, pivoting to the big question. Bernadette, on your wedding night you’ll be consummating your marriage. What do you think your first sexual position will be as husband and wife?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Amy, please.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Keeping in mind that whoever’s on top may set the tone for the marriage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, show’s over.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Hey, they may conceive a child on their wedding night. Don’t you think the kid might get a kick out of knowing how it happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I don’t care. Ask her things like are you going to take Howard’s name? Not who’s going to sit on who?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I’ve actually been thinking I’m going to hyphenate: Bernadette Mary-Ann Rostenkowski-Wolowitz.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Nice. You know, you should totally get BernadetteMaryAnnRostenkowskiWolowitz.com before someone snaps it up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Howard already took care of it. Plus, he set up our beautiful wedding website with cute little facts about our family histories. Do you know, for a while in Poland, my family and his family were neighbours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, that’s cool.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>No, it’s not. I’ll explain it to you later.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>May I have your attention, please? We are hear tonight to celebrate the upcoming nuptials of my best friend Howard Wolowitz.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>All</speaker><content>Hear! Hear!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And, apparently, Wil Wheaton’s best friend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Wil</speaker><content>Sheldon…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Talk to the hand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Does anyone have any words they’d like to say about our man of the evening?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, I do. . As is the tradition, I have prepared a series of disrespectful jokes which generate humour at Howard’s expense. Prepare to have your ribs tickled. Howard, I always thought you’d be the last one of us to ever get married, because you are so short and unappealing. Am I right? Let’s see here. Oh, seriously though, Howard, you’re actually one of the most intelligent people I know. And that’s a zinger, because you’re not. I’ve always thought that you’d make someone a fine husband someday. Assuming you’d be able to get the parts, and develop the engineering skills to assemble them, which I don’t see as likely. Hacha! Okay, let me see here. Okay, kidding aside, Howard, you are a good friend. And I wish you nothing but happiness. Bazinga, I don’t!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Doubleazinga! I do! Good luck following that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>So, Howard Wolowitz tying the knot. Leaving his crazy bachelor days behind. He was a wild one. Well, I guess we all kind of were. I remember this one time, I was with this girl at the beach. We were in the ocean and we started making out. I know, it was crazy. I wasn’t even wearing my Aquasocks. Then…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>Nobody cares, Hofstadter. Wwap it up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Right. To Howard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>All</speaker><content>To Howard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I totally had sex in the ocean.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Okay, I’ll go. Howard, when I think about you and Bernadette starting this wonderful life together, I can’t help but get a little choked up. I mean, look at you. You have everything. Look at me. I’m 37. I sleep in the back of a comic book store, and I have the bone density of an 80-year-old man. To Howard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yeah, to Howard. Um, uh, who’s next?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>I’ll go. Howard, I’m gonna say something to you that evewybody’s thinking but no one has the couwage to say out woud. When you invite a man to a bachewor pawty, the impwication is, there will be stwippews. Maybe not compwetewy nude, but at weast pasties and G-stwings. That’s not unweasonable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-18"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Hear, hear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-19"><speaker>All</speaker><content>Hear, hear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-20"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Okay, uh, anybody else? Huh? No? Okay, it all comes down to me, the best man. Ooh! This grasshopper is kicking my ass-hopper. Okay, when I first came to this country, I-I didn’t know how to behave or how to dress, or what was cool, I was pretty lonely. But then I met Howard, and suddenly, my life changed, because we could be lonely together. This man became my whole world.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-21"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>Yeah, nice speech, Fwancine. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-22"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I’m not done, but thank you.  I think back to all the good times we had, like, uh, when we went camping and spent that night telling each other all our secrets. I told him I’m addicted to pedicures and he told me he lost his virginity to his cousin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-23"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>She was my second cousin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-24"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And the first woman you ever disappointed sexually. Ba-da-bazinga!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-25"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, oh, yeah, and then there was the time when Leonard and I took Howard to Las Vegas and paid a hooker to pretend she was Jewish and that she wanted his little kosher pickle. Of all the Howard humping hookers stories, that one’s my favourite!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-26"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Okay, buddy, that’s it. Sit down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-27"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, oh, what about that tubby girl in the Sailor Moon costume at Comic-con?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-28"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Don’t remember. Please sit down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-29"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>The only threesome I’ve ever had in my life, and I’m proud to say it was with this man right here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-30"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, please shut up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-31"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, oh, don’t get me wrong, nothing happened with me and Howard. There was about 200 pounds of Sailor Moon between us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-32"><speaker>Wil (filming on his phone)</speaker><content>Oh, Internet, this is so going all over you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-33"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Jeepers, I’m drunk.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Thank you for picking us up. There’s a warning, right there, on the scotch bottle. You cannot be operatin’ heavy machinery after you had a snootful of this, laddie!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Funny. You boys have a nice time?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, it was great. And low-key, like I promised. No hanky-panky, no strippers. Just the guys telling jokes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>That’s nice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>How about you? Did you have a fun night? Yeah, we, uh, made gift bags, had wine, and then went online and saw this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Raj’s Voice</speaker><content>Of all the Howard humping hookers stories, that one’s my favourite.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You know, we’re not that far from my apartment. If you stop the car, I can walk from here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>You ain’t goin’ anywhere, Threeway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Bernadette, listen…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>You lied to me. You said you told me about all the girls you’ve been with, but you never mentioned your cousin, the prostitute or Raj!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Seriously, you don’t even have to stop the car. Anything under ten miles an hour and I can combat-roll into the street.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Okay, just to set the record straight, I didn’t hire the prostitute, she was a gift from him. Shame on you, Raj. That is not how we treat women in this country.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Don’t you try and blame this on him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Thank you, Bernadette.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Zip it, pervert!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I don’t know what I’m going to do. I’m supposed to marry Howard in a couple of weeks and I’m not sure I even know who the man is any more.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I’m curious what’s bothering you most, the borderline incest, the prostitute or group sex with the girl dressed as the children’s cartoon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Amy, remember when we went over things that would be helpful and things that wouldn’t?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Right. And that was…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>When I first met Howard, he seemed so innocent to me, just a sweet little guy who lives with his mother.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, if that’s what you like, I’ll take you to the comic book store, the place is full of ’em.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Wait a minute. You set me up with Howard. Did you know about all the creepy stuff he was into?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, a little. You hear stuff.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Why didn’t you tell me</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, I was gonna, but I didn’t think it would go past the first date. Then, when it did, I thought for sure it wouldn’t go past you meeting his mother. Definitely not past the two of you sleeping together. I mean, the warning signs were there, this is really on you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>My God! I thought you were my friend. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I don’t think that was helpful.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Hi, Bernie, it’s me again. Please call me back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Dude, I am so sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>It’s not your fault, it’s mine. I did all that stuff, not you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Actually, you did do one of them together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What is this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You’re upset. The convention is to bring an upset person a hot beverage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No, but what is it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Chicken broth. It seemed culturally appropriate. Also, there was a single cube of chicken bouillon in the cupboard when I moved in and it’s been bothering me for the last eight years. So, as they say, two birds.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I don’t know what my next move is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, Howard, I don’t know much about women.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, uh, that, that’s it. I don’t know much about women. Raj, you got anything?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I’ve got the phone number of the tubby girl from Comic-Con.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’m not calling the girl from Comic-con.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>All right. More Sailor Moon for me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I just threw up the bachelor party.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Please come out, Bernadette. Let’s talk through this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>No, leave me alone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Perhaps you should give him a taste of his own medicine. Do you have a cousin who you find attractive?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Amy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Hey, you introduced him to the sleazebag. I’m just trying to clean up your mess.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Howard (at the door)</speaker><content>Oh, hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I need to talk to Bernadette.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, I don’t think she wants to talk to anyone right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>All right, well, could you at least give her a message?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, sure, I guess.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Tell her I’m really sorry, and if she doesn’t want to marry me, I get it. But what I really want her to know is the guy that she’s disgusted by, is the guy that I’m disgusted by, too. But that guy doesn’t exist any more, he’s gone, and the reason is because of her. So, if this relationship is over, let her know that she made me a better man, and tell her thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, my God, Howard. That’s the most beautiful thing I’ve ever heard. And it came out of you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Howie?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Penny has a message for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I heard. Your voice, not unlike your mother’s, travels through walls.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Do you want me to go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>No. Come here. I’m still really mad at you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-19"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I get that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-20"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Is there anything else about your past I should know?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-21"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Couple things, but, you know, most of them happened overseas. I’ll tell you later.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-22"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-23"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>So, is the wedding still on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-24"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Yeah, the wedding’s still on. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-25"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Oh, thank God. I’m still a maid of honour. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-26"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, what the hell. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-27"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>This is kind of hot.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hello.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What’s with the robe?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Leonard (taking it off)</speaker><content>I’m gonna have sex with you right here, right now, on that washing machine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, you’re not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Come on, please.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>If you want to do something, you can help me fold this sheet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Folding a sheet in my underwear, still pretty crazy.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>