<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Gentlemen, I think I’ve come up with a fun way to get young people interested in science. Physics Mad-Libs. Now, give me a number.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Five.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Uh-huh. And an irrational constant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>E.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And a funny Greek letter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Gamma.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I said funny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Upsilon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Good one. And an electrical charge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Positive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Ha. Perfect. Okay. Get this. Professor Jones told the symposium he had a new method for calculating the mass of a muon. Five times the limit of E to the upsilon as in a . Okay. No, no. I’ll start over. Professor </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I haven’t seen him laugh that hard since the day Leonard made that multiplication error.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, Oh, Lord, that multiplication error! He thought he carried the one. But he didn’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It’s not funny. That mistake got published.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Stop! I’m going to wet myself!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Hey, guys, guys, President Siebert is headed this way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I wonder what he wants.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Doesn’t look happy, so I’m guessing he wants to talk to Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>Seibert</speaker><content>Dr. Cooper?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Told ya.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, President Siebert, I assume you’d like to respond to one of the suggestions I put in the box by your office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-22"><speaker>Seibert</speaker><content>No, and stop installing suggestion boxes everywhere.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You don’t like written suggestions. You don’t like when I give them to you while we’re urinating in the men’s room. If I didn’t know any better, I’d say that you’re one of those stubborn people who are not open to suggestions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-24"><speaker>Seibert</speaker><content>Dr. Cooper, the physics department chair tells me you’re refusing to take your vacation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-25"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I don’t need a vacation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-26"><speaker>Seibert</speaker><content>You’re obligated to take one. And I’d also like you to know the most-often received suggestion in my suggestion box you installed without asking me is can Dr. Cooper take a vacation? Okay, settled, then. I’ll see you all on Monday, except for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-27"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>But if I don’t come into work, what am I supposed to do with myself?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-28"><speaker>Seibert</speaker><content>Read, rest, travel. I hear Afghanistan is nice this time of year.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-29"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Sarcasm?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-30"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No. You should go.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That tonight’s gonna be a good night, and tonight’s gonna be a good night, and tonight’s gonna be a good, good night! Tonight’s the night, uh, uh, let’s live it up, uh, I got my money, let’s spend it up…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Sheldon (appearing in the back seat)</speaker><content>Good Lord! Would you stop that caterwauling!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What the hell are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Bleeding from my ears.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What are you doing hiding back there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m sneaking into work. Now, if the guard at the university asks what’s under the blanket, you tell him it’s some lobster traps.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Lobster traps?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes. That’s how Velma and Scooby smuggled Shaggy into the old lighthouse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What are you going to do when you get to the university? People are going to recognize you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Will they, Leonard? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Fine. Just get back under your blanket, and I’ll drive you there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And no more singing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I have GPS on my phone. I know you turned around.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I’m so glad you talked Howard out of having your wedding invitations in Klingon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Turn it over. I’m hoping my relatives think it’s Hebrew.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>This is really happening. I’m gonna be a maid of honour. I’m gonna wear a beautiful dress and walk down that aisle and, finally, I will have my special day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>You mean my special day?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>They’re gonna need an extra-large veil for somebody’s head.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>If I ever actually ever get married.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Why wouldn’t you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>My dad. Because I make a lot more money than Howie, he’s putting a lot of pressure on me to get a pre-nup.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Ouch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Yeah. Howie’s gonna freak out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Parental pressure can be daunting. I remember the battle with my mother about shaving my legs. Last year, I finally gave in and let her do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I just don’t know how I’m gonna break it to him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You know, I’m a big believer in breaking bad news to a guy when you’re in bed with him. That’s how I told my high school boyfriend I slept with his brother. That’s how I told his brother the same thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I don’t know, I don’t want to manipulate him with sex.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, sweetie, that’s what sex is for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You know, the connection between marriage and money is nothing new. In fact, the term wed referred to the money and livestock that the groom paid the bride’s father. For example, you’re adorable, intelligent and a good earner. I could conservatively see you going for at least two oxen and a goose.  You would fetch a unicorn.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, there are a million great vacations you could take. What about Hawaii?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hawaii is a former leper colony on top of an active volcano where the disappointing ending to Lost was filmed. Mahalo for nothing, Hawaii.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>How about Florida? They’ve got Cape Canaveral, they’ve got Disney, they’ve got my Aunt Ida and the world’s largest collection of diabetic candy. Plus, if you get sweaty enough, her plastic-covered furniture is like a flume ride.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>My family took a trip to Florida when I was a child. A seagull stole a hot dog from me on the beach. I got the message.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You know, if I had a week off, I’d go back to the Two Bunch Palms Resort and Spa in the desert. I tell you, an hour on the massage table with Trevor, and you’ll feel like you were born without bones.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I don’t think I could ever let a guy give me a massage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Really? What was I doing to your neck last night while you were playing X-Box?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It’s like I’m living in a dictatorship. You must take a vacation, you must have fun, you must enjoy life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I don’t think you have a good handle on dictatorships.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, everybody takes vacations.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>One time they tried to make Richard Feynman take a vacation, but he chose instead to expand his mind and learn something new. He went to work in his friend’s biology lab. Richard Feynman was a famous American physicist, part of the Manhattan Project.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Everyone in the world of science knows who Richard Feynman was.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Now you do, too. Oh! I have a brilliant idea. Amy’s a biologist. I’ll go work in her lab.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Isn’t that just Feynman’s idea?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Ten seconds ago, you never heard of him. Now you’re an expert.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey, you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Is that your laundry? You only have, like, six things in there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, I didn’t have any quarters, so I’ve been sneaking stuff into other people’s loads all day. Hey, if I tell you something, will you promise not to tell anybody?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It doesn’t matter what I say, you’re gonna tell me anyway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What? That is not true. Bernadette wants a pre-nup.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Wow. That’s rough.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>So you’re saying if I became a famous movie star, we got married, you wouldn’t sign a pre-nup?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Absolutely not. If I’m gonna be stuck at home with the kids while you’re on location cheating on me with Ryan Gosling, then Leonard gots to get paid. So, you think about us getting married?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I think about a lot of things. I think about us getting married, I think about us breaking up. Once in a while, I think about how I didn’t leave a note on that Mercedes I dinged in the parking lot last month, but then I have a glass of wine and it passes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Joke all you want, but you think about it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, tell you one thing, if I ever do get married, no Klingon invitations.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Good luck catching a man with that attitude.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Boy, oh, boy. This vacation is off to a wonderful start. The smell of formaldehyde, the whir of the centrifuge, the distant chatter of lab animals being dispatched for dissection. Mm, I can already feel my cares just melting away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I’m excited to work with my boyfriend. It’s gonna be romantic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Way to kill the mood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Come on, Sheldon. We can be like Marie Curie and her husband, Pierre, who spent their days working side by side, bathed in the glow of their love and the radium that ultimately killed her. Screw Beauty and the Beast, that’s the love story Disney should tell.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Okay, what do we start with? Maybe splicing some genes, clone a sheep, perhaps grow a human ear on a mouse’s back? Ha-ha, I’m a freak!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Oh, I’m gonna be doing some brain stem histology while you put yourself on the business end of a sponge and wash those beakers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Wash those bea… Oh, I get it, a little hazing for the new fella. Yeah, I’d better keep and eye out for, what, shoe polish on the microscope, or mad cow disease in my grilled cheese sandwich?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>No, I just need those beakers washed. Hippity-hop, quick like a bunny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What? Excuse me, you have Dr. Sheldon Cooper in your lab. You’re gonna make him do the dishes? That’s like asking the Incredible Hulk to open a pickle jar.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon, you’ve never worked in a lab like this before. You have no experience in the field of biology.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I have plenty of experience in biology. I bought a Tamagotchi in 1998. And it’s still alive. Let’s do this.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Where’s Howard?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No hi, Raj? No how are you, Raj? Just straight to where’s the other white guy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m sorry. So, listen, I heard something about him. Can you keep it between us?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Ooh, gossip. When I first got here, I thought you Americans really gossiped around the water cooler. So I hung out there for, like, a month, but the only gossip I ever heard was about some creepy guy hanging out by the water cooler.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Bernadette wants to get a pre-nup.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, that’s a shame, he’s gonna be devastated.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I never know what to do in these situations. Should I give him a heads-up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Hmm. I’m gonna give you the same advice I yell at the TV when the Bachelor’s handing out roses. Follow your heart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Check it out. Look at the size of that Rice Krispie Treat. Same price.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey, Howard, I need to tell you something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I know, it’s not on my wedding diet. I don’t care.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh, listen, I heard that Bernadette’s thinking about asking you for a pre-nup.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>A pre-nup? Wow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What are you gonna do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I don’t know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Follow your heart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You know what, it’s not a big deal. She makes more money than me. She wants to protect her financial interests. It’s completely reasonable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, actually, it’s good for both of us. I have assets to protect, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Like what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-20"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’ve got some rare comic books. The Vespa’s almost paid off. And Ma and I have a primo double cemetery plot at Mt. Sinai right near the guy who played Mr. Roper on Three’s Company.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-21"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Mr. Roper’s dead? You can’t just spring that on a guy.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Here you go. This is now the only lab with glassware washed by a man with two doctorates and a restraining order signed by Carl Sagan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Soap spots. Wash ’em again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Y-you’re being ridiculous. Those are perfectly clean.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon, this beaker used to contain cerebral spinal fluid from an elephant that died of syphilis. If it’s, in fact, perfectly clean, drink from it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Biologists are mean.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>All right, perhaps this task will be a little bit more up your alley. I need you to count the bacteria spores on these petri dishes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>There was something wrong with that detergent. That was way too bubbly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I’m sure it was.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I intend to write that soap company a strongly worded letter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Yeah, good for you. Now, start counting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You know what this place needs? A suggestion box.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>366… 367…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>How’s it going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>How’s counting going? When I was in kindergarten, I recited pi to a thousand places for the school talent show. I think I got this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Aw, nuts! One…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>This is preposterous. I think you’re giving me these tasks because you’re afraid if you give me anything meaningful to do, I’ll show you up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Really? Is that what you think?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes, that’s what I think. And I’m super smart, so it’s probably true.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-20"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Hey, I’ve been training in the field of neurobiology for 12 years. You’ve been here for three hours, and you’ve spent one of them in the bathroom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m sorry. It takes me a while to get things going on an unfamiliar toilet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-22"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon, I’ve given you the simplest things to do, and you haven’t done one of them right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Maybe that’s because I’m not being challenged. It’s the same reason Einstein failed math.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-24"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Maybe the math was too bubbly for him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-25"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You think you’re doing science by cutting up that brain? They could do the same thing at any Quiznos. And they’d offer to toast it for me, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-26"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Okay, smart guy. I’m about to remove the locus coeruleus, which is incredibly delicate work. Have at it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-27"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right. I’m no stranger to a little gray matter. Locus coeruleus. Locus coeruleus.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-28"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You’re getting warmer, it is, indeed, in the brain. Hope your hands are steady. It’s the width of a single hair. But this is just biology, so I’m sure it’s no problem for a genius like you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-29"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It’s not. I’ll have you know, in the field of physics, we work with particles so small, they make fat jokes about the locus coeruleus, i.e., when your locus coeruleus sits around the house, it sits around the house.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-30"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Oh, are we nervous, Dr. Cooper?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-31"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No. What you see is a man trembling with confidence. Does a locus coeruleus normally bleed that much?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-32"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>No. But your thumb does.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-33"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, dear. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-34"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Yeah, you’re a biologist.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What are you doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m on vacation. Social convention dictates that I let my hair down at a local watering hole. Social convention is stupid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What happened to your thumb?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You know, I have ten fingers and ten toes. If I tell you a story about each one of them, we’ll be here all day, let’s just move on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Barman</speaker><content>What can I get you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Ah, seeing as I’m on vacation, a pina colada seems appropriate. Extra pineapple slices, extra whipped cream, extra cherries, extra umbrellas, and, uh, hold the rum. Don’t let me have too many of those.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey, what are you guys doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>We’re grown men, we drink at bars.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No and no. Everything okay with you and Bernadette?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, yeah, sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You and Amy? Good?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, better than good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You know those girls text me every detail of their lives as it happens.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’m not signing a pre-nup.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>All right, Howard Wolowitz, listen up. You sign anything she puts in front of you, because you are the luckiest man alive. If you let her go, there is no way you can find anyone else. Speaking on behalf of all women, it is not gonna happen, we had a meeting. And you, a grown man fainting at the sight of a little blood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Excuse me, this is a fairly substantial wound. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content> Amy?  Amy?  Amy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>What do you want?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I was kind of hoping I could continue vacationing in your laboratory. After all, I did book the whole week.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Do you honestly think you can just waltz back in here after the way you behaved yesterday?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I was not myself. I had lost a lot of thumb blood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>That’s not an apology.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That is your opinion.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I want a real apology.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m sorry that you weren’t able to…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That my genius…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That the soap was…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Fine. Sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You’re forgiven. Now, if you want to stay, get started on those beakers. They’re still dirty from yesterday.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Next year I’m going to Epcot.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Are you mad at me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No. I’m not mad at you. I just wish you would have come to me, so I didn’t have to hear it through the nerd-vine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>So, what are we gonna do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You really want me to sign a pre-nup?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I don’t know. My dad’s pretty insistent on it, though.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Why don’t I talk to your dad, man-to-man?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Really? Oh, that’d be so great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Done.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I should probably give you a heads-up about a couple of things. Even though he’s retired from the police force, he still carries his gun. But don’t worry, he won’t shoot it. It’s more of a fashion statement.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>And just to be safe, when you talk to him, don’t bring up Jimmy Carter, gardeners, foreign people, homosexuals, Sean Penn, Vatican II, gun control, organic food, the designated hitter rule, recycling or the fact that you’re Jewish.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Got it, got it. Will you e-mail me that list?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>So the thing to watch for, if he’s shouting at you, you’re okay, but if he starts to get real quiet, leave as quickly as you can without making eye contact. Not in a straight line, throw some zigs and zigs in there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You know, this isn’t that pressing. Why don’t I talk to him about it in May.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>In May you’re gonna be on the International Space Station.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>They’ve got a phone.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>