<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t know why I avoided the Harry Potter books for so long. These are great. I just started number six.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s a good one. Dumbledore dies in that one. Yeah, I know, I didn’t see it coming, either.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Why would you say that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You brought up the subject. I contributed an interesting fact on that subject. It’s called the art of conversation. Okay, your turn.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That was a huge spoiler.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What is wrong with you? If I did that, you’d bitch about it for weeks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, really, Leonard? Are you going to have another one of your hissy fits?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hissy fits? I have hissy fits?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes, and I have a theory why. Because of your lactose intolerance, you switched over to soy milk. Soy contains estrogen-mimicking compounds. I think your morning Cocoa Puffs are turning you into a hysterical woman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You are unbelievable. I don’t know why I put up with you. You’re controlling, you’re irritating.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>There you go again, nag, nag, nag. You’re only proving my point, little lady.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You know what? Screw you, Sheldon. You are the most annoying person I have ever met.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What? I’m annoying? You criticize my behaviour all the time. Sheldon, don’t talk about your bowel movements over breakfast. Sheldon, when the president of the university is giving a eulogy at a funeral, don’t yawn and point at your watch. Sheldon, don’t throw away my shirts ’cause you think they’re ugly. You’re impossible.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That’s it. I don’t, I don’t have to put up with this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Actually, I have your signature on a roommate agreement that says you do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Aw. Here’s what I think of your roommate agreement.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You pick that up right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Roommate agreement, section 27, paragraph 5, the roommate agreement, like the American flag, cannot touch the ground.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t care. I don’t have to do anything you say because I don’t think I want to live here anymore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Where are you going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-23"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>To live with Penny and not you, you crazy bastard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-24"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Crazy bastard?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-25"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-26"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Leonard, wait.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-27"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-28"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Dobby the elf dies in book seven.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Here you go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Great. Come on in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>What, you don’t say thank you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>It’s my suitcase. I lent it to you two years ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Well, then, I should tell you I broke the wheel and the handle. So, is everyone from Bernadette’s company going to Vegas?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No, just me, her and a couple of the big wigs. It’s part of a bonus she got.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Cool. Did she discover a cure for something?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Not exactly. They spent a ton of money developing this dandruff medication that had the side effect of horrible anal leakage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Is there a good anal leakage?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Anyway, it was Bernie’s idea to rebrand the stuff as a cure for constipation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Way to make lemonade. You know, from around the corner where fudge is made.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Hey, I got a favour to ask.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>My mom’s been kind of an emotional wreck since that dentist she was dating dumped her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Dumped her? What, did he use a forklift? Sorry. There’s nothing funny about morbid obesity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>She’s huge. It was funny. Anyway, I was just hoping that maybe you could check in on her tomorrow night and make sure she’s doing okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Dude, I’m a single man. Saturday night is my party night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Really? What do you got going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I don’t know, maybe drive down to Hollywood, hit a few hot spots, see if I can get lucky.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, tell me if this sounds familiar. You pay fifteen dollars to park, you stand on the pavement for an hour until you break down and give the bouncer twenty bucks to let you in. You push your way to the bar, where you drink an eighteen dollar cosmopolitan, then you stare at a pretty girl and imagine your perfect life together. Your children, grandchildren. Meanwhile, she leaves with a guy who claims he wrote Beverly Hills Chihuahua. Then you give up on anyone ever loving you, go to Marie Callender’s, buy a pie and eat it in your car in the parking lot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I told her around seven.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I swear, that man is the most egotistical, insufferable human being I have ever met.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, but you two make such a cute couple. Like Burt and Ernie. You guys even teach me stuff about words and numbers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, I’ve had it. I am done. I can’t, I can’t live with him for one more minute.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Wow. Where are you going to go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I was thinking here with you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That a problem?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, not at all. No, it’s, it’s great. It’s terrific. I, you know, I just can’t help feel bad about Sheldon. I mean, how’s he going to get by without you? Ernie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>He’s got Amy now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, he does, but it’s not the same.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Um, well, um, all right. You, you know how in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, Ron didn’t abandon Harry just because Harry started dating Ron’s sister?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Harry and Ginny get together?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sorry. Spoiler alert. My point is, as much as I want to live with you, I can’t do it knowing how much Sheldon needs you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Please, the only thing he needs me for is to be his whipping boy, his, his stooge, his doormat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, you know what they say, if it ain’t broke.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Wow. It sounds to me like you don’t want us to live together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No. No, no, I do. I do. It’s just, I mean, it’s a really big step.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Is it? We’re together all the time. Financially, it makes great sense. Can you think of one reason why we shouldn’t do this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-20"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, um, I’m just a little thirsty.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-22"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I got nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-23"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Great. I’ll go get my stuff.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-24"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah. Okay, all right, don’t freak out. You can make this work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-25"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, could you clear off a shelf for me in the bathroom? I take a lot of medicine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-26"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, please let some of it be Xanax.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Mrs Wolowitz (off)</speaker><content>Are you ready for dessert?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No, thank you, Mrs. Wolowitz. As it is, I’m going to have to carry my stomach out of here like I’m a fireman rescuing an infant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Mrs Wolowitz (off)</speaker><content>Oh, please. You’re a tall glass of brown water. Have dessert.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Well, I, I really couldn’t. But, uh, I’ve had a lovely time eating your brisket and hearing about the things you’ve had removed from your body over the years. Didn’t know you could have a cyst inside another cyst.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Mrs Wolowitz (off)</speaker><content>The doctor said they were like Russian nesting dolls. Well, if you have to go, how about I put a little doggie bag together for you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>That would be lovely. Thank you.  Mrs. Wolowitz, uh, are you okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Mrs Wolowitz (off)</speaker><content>Don’t mind me. I just cry when I’m lonely and have nothing to live for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I, uh, I suppose I could stay for some dessert.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Mrs Wolowitz (off)</speaker><content>Great. You like chocolate chip cheesecake?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Mrs Wolowitz (off)</speaker><content>I’ll make one.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>One vintage Mr. Mxyzptlk action figure. That’s Leonard’s.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Children’s toy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>One Star Trek: The Next Generation phaser. That’s Leonard’s.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Children’s toy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>One Game of Thrones collector’s edition Longclaw sword. Oh, Leonard and I bought that together. That’s a bit of an ethical conundrum. Eh, I’ll keep it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>So, uh, what’s your plan moving forward?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Uh, suppose I’ll have to find and cultivate a new roommate. What a task that will be. Do you know how uncivilized Leonard was when I took him in?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, it took me forever to get him on a bathroom schedule. He would just go whenever the mood struck him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Like a dog-boy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Exactly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>What if you could find a roommate who was a scientist and already familiar and comfortable with your ways?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That would be ideal. If a person like that existed, I would sign on, no further questions asked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Great. Here I am!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Wait. Here who is where?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Me. Aren’t I your perfect roommate?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Um…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-18"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Think about it, Sheldon. I’m not a stranger, we’re intellectually compatible, I’m willing to chauffeur you around town, and your personality quirks, which others find abhorrent or rage-inducing, I find cute as a button. What do you think?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Um…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-20"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Tell me one reason why this isn’t a fantastic idea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Um…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-22"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>See? You can’t. I’m gonna go see if Leonard’s room is big enough for my water bed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Um…</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content> Good buddy Leonard.  Good buddy Leonard.  Good buddy Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What do you want?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hey, good buddy. So, uh, I was just talking to Amy, and she made me realize that this little dust-up between you and me is much ado about nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Is that so?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes. All is forgiven, so come back home. I’ll make you some soy hot chocolate, and then I’ll you tell you about our exciting new devil-may-care bathroom policy.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Okay. Amy’s decided she wants to move in with me, so I need you to come back home, you lovable scamp. That’s a lot of product.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey. What’s going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, get this, suddenly, Sheldon wants me back because Amy wants to move in with him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Really? Interesting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, too late, pal. I’m not going anywhere. Penny and I are very happy living together. Isn’t that right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>It’s like the happiness won’t ever leave the apartment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Leonard, please. You know Amy moving in marks a level of intimacy our relationship isn’t ready for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yes. That is a real thing. And it doesn’t mean you don’t care about each other, it just means things are moving at a pace you’re not comfortable with, and that’s fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, if he doesn’t want to live with her, then he should tell her how he feels.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, maybe he doesn’t know how to say it without hurting her feelings.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Feelings? What am I, a hippie at a love-in? No. The problem is, she laid out a series of logical arguments that I couldn’t refute.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>That is the worst, isn’t it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m sorry, Sheldon. I can’t help you. Oh, spoiler alert, this door’s about to slam in your face.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Oh, there you are. When do I get a key to our apartment?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Um…</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Hello?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Hey. How’d it go last night with my mom?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Okay, I guess.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What time did you leave?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Actually, I’m still here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What? You spent the night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yeah. Uh, after dinner, we watched a rerun of Rockford Files, and then she opened a bottle of, uh, cream sherry, and the next thing I know, she was tucking me into your bed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You wore my pyjamas?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Mm-hmm. How do you sleep in these things? Silk pajamas on satin sheets? I slid out of the bed, like, three times.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Mrs Wolowitz (off)</speaker><content>Rajesh! You up? You ready for breakfast?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, boy. Breakfast.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Okay, Raj, listen to me. You need to get out of there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>But I have a cream sherry hangover and I smell blintzes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>If you don’t leave now, she’ll use food and guilt to keep you there for the rest of your life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, Howard, stop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Trust me, you’re not Jewish. That’s how they get you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You’re being silly. I can leave whenever I want.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, really? Where are your clothes and your shoes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>They’re on the chair, right over… Oy vey.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hello, home wrecker.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What did I do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You gave Leonard somewhere to go. Thanks to you, Amy’s out buying his and hers bath towels. Like I’d ever dry myself with something that has a possessive pronoun on it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay. Listen, the truth is I don’t want him living with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Great. Kick him out. Break his heart. Everybody wins.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, I don’t want to break his heart. I love him. This is just happening too fast.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You think this is fast? It’s just a matter of time before I see Amy’s leg stubble in my shower.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, and I’ve seen those legs. You might want to get some Drano.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hold on. If you don’t want to live with Leonard, why don’t you just tell him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, you know how he is. He’s sensitive and emotional.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s because he drinks too much soy milk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, I don’t know what else we can do but tell them the truth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I suppose there’s no choice but to face the crying, angry accusations and the high-pitched wails of despair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah. And who knows how Amy will react.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Here’s some more ice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Oh, thanks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What were we thinking? We should have just done it the regular way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Those Chinese acrobats in Cirque du Soleil made it look so easy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Honestly, if I could bend that far, what would I need with you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>If you could bend that far, you’d be doing us both a favour. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Hey, Raj. What’s up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You were right. I can’t get out of here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You’re still at my mother’s?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I’m trapped. My clothes have been in the laundry all day, and she hid my keys. I think they might be in her bra, because she jingles when she walks. What do I do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Hey, you wanted a woman in your life. Now you got one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Come on, Howard, help me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Mrs Wolowitz (off)</speaker><content>Rajesh, tatellah, I ran you a bath.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, my God. She’s not gonna bathe me, is she?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Gee, I wish I could tell you no. All right, well, thanks again for helping me out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>But, Howard…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-17"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Should we go back and rescue him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-18"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>It’s too late. We’ll see him at his Bar Mitzvah.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Here you go. I picked up the Chinese food just the way Leonard used to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Is it kung pao chicken?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Brown rice, not white rice?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Spicy mustard from the Korean deli?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Yes. I did good, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes. Amy, are you worried that us living together will take the mystery out of our relationship?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, why would you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Oh, and, uh, check this out. I took the liberty of scripting a new outgoing voice mail message for both of us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hello. This is Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>And this is Amy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>We’re not home right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>‘Cause we out dropping science, son.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-16"><speaker>Together</speaker><content>Leave a message.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-17"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Beep.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You can’t live here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-19"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>What? Why? Is it the message? I only used urban slang to sound tough so people wouldn’t break in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No. It’s not the message.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-21"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Well, what is it, then? I did everything just the way you like it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-23"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Then what the hell, Sheldon? We have been going out for over two years, and I have been nothing but patient with you. I watch your dopey space movies. I signed your ridiculous contract. I even stopped wearing lip gloss ’cause you said it made my mouth look too slippery. I am the best girlfriend you’re ever gonna have. You give me one good reason why I can’t live here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-24"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It’s Penny’s fault.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-25"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-26"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>She doesn’t want to live with Leonard, so he has to come live here again. She’s the snake in our garden. She’s the reason we can’t be happy.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey, Ames.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Yeah. Hey, Ames, nothing. I was all set to move in with Sheldon, and now I hear I can’t ’cause you don’t want to live with Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Leonard (off)</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sheldon, what did you say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I said the truth. You don’t want to live with Leonard, and you know it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Since when don’t you want to live with me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, don’t get all huffy. You’re the one who decided to move in without even asking me if I was ready.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, I think we should talk about that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>And since you love the truth so much, why don’t you tell Amy you don’t want to live with her instead of blaming it on me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I thought we were talking about the other thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You’re a coward.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, the evidence does support that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Come on, Amy, let’s go drink wine and talk about what jerks our boyfriends are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You know what would show them? I should move in here with you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Um…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Do you want to catch up on some Walking Dead?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>‘Kay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Have you seen the one where Lori dies?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Or maybe she doesn’t. Let’s find out.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Mrs Wolowitz (off)</speaker><content>Where you going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Raj (screams)</speaker><content>No!</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>