<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, dear. Penny, have you been recording shows on our DVR again?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Answer honestly. This is not a trial. That’ll come later.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Absolutely not. Help me out here, I can’t afford another demerit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah. Uh, maybe we were hacked. You know, the Chinese have been hacking everything lately.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Why would the Chinese make our DVR record Paul Blart: Mall Cop?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t know. It’s a fat guy on a Segway. That’s funny everywhere.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m deleting it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, hang on. Maybe the Chinese haven’t finished watching it yet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You know, if you’re trying to make space on the DVR, why don’t you just get rid of some of the stuff you’ve already watched? Like, um, Alphas.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, that’s the season two finale. That was quite the cliffhanger. I’m going to re-watch it before season three starts.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>There is no season three. They cancelled that show.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, they can’t cancel it. It ended on a cliffhanger.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>They did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Uh, Sheldon, there are two dumplings left. Do you want them?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Dumplings? Don’t you understand what’s going on here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>As a rule, no.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That show ended with all the residents of New York either dead or unconscious. Oh, now I’ll never know what happened.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, why don’t you make up your own ending?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, sure, what a wonderful idea. And after that, I’ll make up my own rules of oral hygiene. You know, instead of flossing, I’ll rub pudding on my gums. I’m going to get the number of the SyFy Channel and give them what for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, please, don’t do that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No. They can’t just cancel a show like Alphas. You know? They have to help the viewers let go. Firefly did a movie to wrap things up. Buffy the Vampire Slayer continued on as a comic book. Heroes gradually lowered the quality season by season till we were grateful it ended.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-23"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I feel bad for whoever gets that phone call.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-24"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Ah, don’t. If they didn’t want to be yelled at by crazy nerds, they shouldn’t have started a sci-fi channel.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I think you’re gonna be really happy with this security camera. The optics are great, it’s got infrared technology, and there’s even a backup battery when the power goes out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Whatever. I can see my little princess while I’m at work, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Why can’t you just watch porn like a regular guy? I need your laptop so I can configure the software.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Wait, hold on. This is weird.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I was Googling that girl I’ve been dating, and I found her blog.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Cool. Anything juicy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>She said she recently went on a date with a guy named Roger? And he’s Indian? And he’s an astrophysicist, too?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You know what’s going on, don’t you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yes, Mummy was right. American girls are sexually voracious devils.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I can’t believe I have to explain this. People change names on blogs to protect their privacy. Roger is Raj.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh. I always thought, if I had a white name, it would be Gavin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Keep reading. What does it say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No, no, I don’t know if I should. If she wanted me to know about her blog, she would’ve told me. It’s almost like I’m reading her diary.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>It’s exactly what it’s like. Keep reading.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No, this is creepy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, I think we were looking at creepy in the rearview mirror when I put up that camera.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>It’s not creepy. Don’t listen to him. Oh, look who’s got the sweetest kisses.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Should I go?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>With all the TV Sheldon was talking about, I had the greatest idea ever. It even blows away my idea for a Star Wars themed coffee shop called Brewbacca’s. You need to watch Buffy the Vampire Slayer. It is the perfect show for the two of us. It’s got action and jokes and hot vampires and romance. I cannot oversell this. What do you say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>It’s six thirty in the morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I thought you grew up on a farm.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Sheldon (on phone)</speaker><content>Hello, SyFy Network? Yeah, this is your vice president of programming. Now, we have made a horrible mistake regarding Alphas. Yeah, we need to uncancel it immediately. Well, you just put me through to the people who handle that, you tell them it’s me, and I don’t want to answer a lot of questions about if I really am who I say I am, you know? I just. I want this done. No, I am not the person who just called. That man was clearly a cowboy. Yeah, who was plumb concerned about y’all cancelling his favourite show. Why do they keep hanging up on me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I’m sorry you’re upset. You know, Sheldon, sometimes people seek the comfort of physical contact in moments like this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I am not flying back to Texas just so my mom can give me a hug.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Okay. Well, what I think is going on here is you have a pathological need for closure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, that’s nonsense. I mean, you tell me stories about your day all the time. I don’t care how they end.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You know, I might be able to help you with this. There’s a whole field of behavioural neuroscience that examines ways to retrain your neural pathways so stuff like this bothers you less.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, but I just told you, I don’t have a problem with closure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You sure about that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, quite sure.  That proves nothing.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Ready to go to lunch?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Do you think I’m feminine?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah. Let’s go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Thanks a lot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What’s going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I broke down, and I read Lucy’s blog, and in one of the entries she said, when we first met, I struck her as a little feminine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Just a little? That’s great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I have to talk to her about this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, geez, why do you girls always want to talk about things? Listen to me, if she’s writing about your relationship, use it to your advantage. Rig the game.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Well, that doesn’t seem fair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Is it fair that girls like confident, normal guys more than nervous weirdos?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No, it’s not. I’ve always thought that was unfair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>So take what’s in that blog and use it to get her pants off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Why do you have to make everything so filthy? Why couldn’t you just say the blog is like her giving me the key to her heart?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>The key to her heart. That’s nice. Were you quoting someone or is it tattooed on the small of your back?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I was quoting a man who knows a thing or two about women, Sir Elton John.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>So, did you love it? Of course you loved it. How could you not love it? Tell me how much you loved it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>It was cute.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, don’t say cute. That’s the worst.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What’s wrong with cute?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It just makes things seem small. It diminishes them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>So you want me to stop calling your little tushy cute?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You can try, but nobody’s gonna believe you. I just, I don’t understand how you can watch a show that great and not be excited by it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I liked it. I’m excited.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, then, tell your face.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What do you want from me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You know what? Never mind. We gave it a shot. Let’s just see what else is on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, come on, don’t be like that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I’m sorry I called it cute. Let’s watch another one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Really?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, it was fun. Kind of reminded me of my high school. But instead of vampires, we had meth heads. But both came out at night and had messed up teeth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>All right, cool. I think you’ll like the next one better. All the cheerleaders are suffering from an evil curse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-18"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh. Well, that’s like my high school, too. But instead of a curse, it was crabs.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I’ve come up with a series of exercises to help with your compulsive need for closure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I take issue with the word compulsive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>All I’m saying is, we live in a world where closure isn’t always an op…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>…tion. Okay. For the sake of argument, let’s say I have a problem. What would be your plan for addressing it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I’m going to recondition your brain so that the need for completion isn’t so overwhelming.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>By playing tic-tac-toe?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Yep. Your turn.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, Amy. And you wonder why people think neuroscience is nothing but a goofy game for diaper babies. Tic-tac-toe can only end in win, lose or draw, none of which will deny me closure. Especially since I’m about to win.  B-But we didn’t finish.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Exactly. How does that make you feel?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>The same way any normal person would. I feel like I want to peel off my own face and tear it in two and then again and again until I have a handful of Sheldon-face confetti.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>And that’s exactly the feeling we want to address with this course of treatment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Or you could pitch in, grab a nostril and help me get this face off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Come on, you can do this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You don’t know what it’s like to feel completely frustrated. To have a desire build up within you and be denied any opportunity for release.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Yeah, sounds like a drag.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, help me out here. Why does he love this show so much?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Well, there was action, it was funny. I mean, you do get that usually the monster chases the pretty girl, but this time the pretty girl chases the monsters?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yippee, it’s backwards. I get it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Why does this bother you so much?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I don’t know. It’s just, he’s so passionate about so many different things. I just don’t get that way. Do you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Well, sure. I’m pretty passionate about science. I remember the first time I looked through a microscope and saw millions of tiny microorganisms. It was like a whole other universe. If I wanted to, I could wipe it out with my thumb like a god.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>See? I wish I had some of that fire in my life. I mean, I want to care about things and get excited like you guys.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Well, there’s no reason you can’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You think?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Absolutely. All we need to do is spend a little time and find something you’re passionate about.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Ugh, that sounds like a lot of work.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Howard (on webcam)</speaker><content>Hey, what’s up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Uh, Lucy’s coming over. I need some advice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>However long you think the foreplay should be, triple it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Just tell me which one you think is more manly. This hockey jersey or this football jersey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I don’t know. Go with hockey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Good, black is more slimming. Oh, that’s her. I got to go be butch. Toodles. Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Come in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>Oh, look how cute your little doggy is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yeah, well, I wouldn’t get too close. If I give the right command in German, she’ll rip your face off.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>1. Amy (singing)</speaker><content>O’er the land of the free, and the home of the… Next.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>2. (Sheldon is laying out an intricate pattern of dominoes) Amy</speaker><content>That’s quite an impressive layout, isn’t it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Let’s box it up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Let’s box it up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>3. (Sheldon is turning the handle on a jack-in-the-box. Just before the end of the tune) Amy</speaker><content>That’s enough. Sheldon, Sheldon, give it!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>4. Amy</speaker><content>Okay, Sheldon, make a wish and blow out the candles. Oops, missed one. Now your wish can’t come true.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Lucky for you, ’cause I wished you were dead.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>I like your jersey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Thanks. I love hockey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>Oh, cool. So does my dad. We watched it all the time growing up. Who’s your favourite player?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Not Brian Boitano, that’s for sure. How’s your burrito?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>It’s still a little frozen in the middle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Probably because I didn’t read the instructions. No wrapper’s going to tell me what to do. Unless his name is Jay-Z.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>Is something going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>What do you mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>Well, you’re acting all weird, and I’m pretty weird, so I think I know what I’m talking about.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I don’t know. Maybe it’s all those steroids I’ve been taking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>I think I’m gonna go. Thank you for the burrito and the pork rinds and the 20-minute lecture on why monster trucks are better than regular trucks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Wait, wait. I, I found your blog here you wrote about me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>Oh. I kind of just write that for myself. I didn’t think anybody actually read it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No kidding. You didn’t make it easy to find. I spent hours digging around online. For the record, you have excellent credit scores. And your diabetic aunt seems to be adjusting to her new leg just fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>Why were you acting so strange tonight?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-16"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You called me feminine. And I, I wanted you to think I was more manly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-17"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>Raj, I didn’t say feminine was a bad thing. I meant that you’re sweet and thoughtful and your skin looks so much like caramel, I just want to dip an apple in your face.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-18"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I do have a pretty balls-to-the-wall moisturising regimen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-19"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>So, are you okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-20"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-21"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>Good. Do you even like hockey?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-22"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No. Bought this at the Staples Center when I went to see Taylor Swift.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>So, I was thinking how excited you get about stuff like Buffy or science or which TV remote you and Sheldon should buy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>The Harmony One was fine. We didn’t need to upgrade to the eleven hundred, which he knows is too big for my hand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>See, that’s the kind of passion I didn’t think I had. But then I realized I’m passionate about you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, my cute little tushy strikes again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, I’m serious. Look, I’ve always had these plans. I was gonna be in movies and live this glamorous life, and anything less than that just wasn’t worth getting excited about.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Those things can still happen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, obviously it’s gonna happen. Yeah, a psychic at a bachelorette party told me so. Anyway, what I meant was, I shouldn’t wait, you know? I’ve got you, I’ve got Sheldon, all these wonderful friends. My life is exciting right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That’s a big deal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>It is, isn’t it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>So, does that mean we get to do stuff like talk about cool shows or get dressed up in matching costumes and go to Comic-Con?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Leonard, I had an epiphany, not a stroke.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Amy, I must say, I was sceptical at first, but this has truly been a transformative evening.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I’m a little surprised to hear you feeling so positive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, you’re an excellent neuroscientist, you’re a wonderful girlfriend, and…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>And?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Doesn’t matter, does it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I’m proud of you, Sheldon. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And a complete sucker.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>1. (Redraws tic-tac-toe board) Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>3. (Winds up jack-in-the-box until it pops out.) Sheldon</speaker><content>There he is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>4. Sheldon (singing)</speaker><content>And the home of the brave.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>5. (Knocks over first of intricate domino pattern) Sheldon</speaker><content>Don’t stop. Yes, keep going. Just like that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sheldon, you big weirdo, I want you to know that I love that you’re in my life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I love you, too.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hello. Uh, is this the Bruce Miller who wrote the season finale of Alphas? Oh, smashing. Yeah, you already sound nicer than the last Bruce Miller who suggested I have sexual relations with myself. Now, down to business. Um, your show ended on a cliffhanger. Could you please tell me how you planned to resolve it? Uh-huh. Mm-hmm. I see. Well, that all stinks. No wonder you got cancelled. Bye.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>