<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Try to keep up, Howard, I’m killing it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, I wish we looked as cool dancing in clubs as we do right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Don’t worry, this is exactly how you look when you’re dancing in clubs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You’re welcome, ladies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Paradigm-shifting news, gentlemen. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Dude! I was about to Bollywood this bitch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Earlier today, I invited Professor Stephen Hawking to join me in the popular online game Words with Friends. Moments ago, he accepted my request. Do you understand what that means?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>That somewhere right now Stephen Hawking is saying, damn it, I meant to click no.”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’ll walk you through it. The game is not called Words with Strangers. No, it’s not even called Words with Acquaintances. It is called Words with…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I’m not finishing your sentence. You pulled the plug on my funk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Friends! It’s Words with Friends! Which Stephen Hawking and I officially are. Now all I need is a bunk bed with a slide, I’ll have everything I’ve ever wanted since I was six years old.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That’s really nice, Sheldon, I’m happy for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And I’m happy for you, too. You are now friends with someone who is officially friends with Stephen Hawking. Enjoy it, boys. You may have peaked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Sheldon, I know Stephen Hawking. I worked with him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And if they ever come out with a game called Words with People You Once Worked With, you’ll be off to the races.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, I don’t think this actually means…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hold that thought! Professor Hawking has made a move. Boy, oh, boy. Oh, it’s only a matter of time before we’re coming up with fun nicknames for each other. I’ll be Coop. He’ll be Wheels. If he’s okay with that. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Raj (putting game back on and removing shirt)</speaker><content>All right. Crank up the AC, boys, it’s gonna get hot in here!</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>So, I was taking a shower this morning, and when I got out, I started to dry off with what I thought was a towel but turned out to be Howard’s mom’s underwear. I had to take another shower. It wasn’t enough. Nothing will ever be enough.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I once looked in Sheldon’s underwear drawer. He yelled at me. But now I know what it looks like and he can never take that away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>There’s a book under here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, I’ll get that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I got it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, no, it’s…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I got it. Why do you have a history textbook?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, it’s not a big deal. Just taking a class at the Pasadena Community College.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>That’s great. I didn’t know you wanted to go back to school.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>It’s just one history class. Look, I didn’t finish college, so I thought I would give it a try.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Not to mention, your acting career is going south like Sherman. Read about it in your book.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Why would you be embarrassed to tell us?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, I’m not embarrassed. I just didn’t want anyone to know because I haven’t told Leonard yet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Why wouldn’t you tell Leonard?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Because it’s me going back to school, and he’s gonna be all “you can do it,” and “how can I help?” and “I’m so proud of you.” Ugh!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I just can’t believe you could keep something like that from him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You guys have got to be the weirdest couple I know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Really? You can’t think of anyone weirder?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I can, but she’s sitting right there.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes. I play the word quiver with a triple letter and a double word score for 72 points. That ought to let the air out of your tyres, Hawking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Wow, my boyfriend is friends with Stephen Hawking and my new dandruff shampoo doesn’t smell like tar. Everything really is coming up Amy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It is glorious. One of the greatest intellects of our time has agreed to engage with me in a gentlemanly battle of wits. And I’m spanking him so hard his grad students won’t be able to sit down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You know, when one male dominates another, his testosterone level rises.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What’s your point?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>It’s exciting to think you might be getting a testosterone level.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Ooh, my friend Stephen just played the word act for 18 points. That’s right, I call him Stephen now, because I checked, and he was not okay with Wheels.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Oh, you could turn his act into extract , and it would be for double points.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Amy. Why would you give me a word? Now, if I play extract it would be cheating.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Although, I could play the completely unrelated and better word extract . Ethical conundrum avoided. Thanks, brain.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Spaghetti okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It’s crunchy. Just the way I like it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, I don’t think the water was really boiling.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It’s great. I love it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, listen, there’s something I need to tell you. I’ve been thinking about going back to school for a while now. So a couple months ago, I started taking a history class at the community college.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh. That’s great. Great, great, great. Why wait so long to tell me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I don’t want you to make a big deal out of it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Why do you think I’d be like that? I get it, you’re taking one class. It’s nice. Maybe if it goes well, you take another, you enrol full-time. Ooh, be sure to keep an eye on which credits transfer to a four-year college.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You’re making it a big deal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sorry. Whatever. It’s all good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Anyway, that’s it. I just thought you should know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Am I allowed to ask how the class is going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>It’s really good. We’ve been talking about the origins of slavery. Turn in my first paper tomorrow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Great topic. I can help with that. There are lots of different perspectives you can take, economic, sociological, political.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey hey hey, this is my paper. And my perspective is that slavery is bad. Oh, and my professor’s black, so I’m pretty sure that’s the right answer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Can I take a look?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, Leonard, this is my thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, I get it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It’s like when I started doing chin-ups, I didn’t want you to see until I could do one. FYI, really close.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-21"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Thank you. Now behave yourself and eat your dinner. Maybe later, if you’re lucky, you get to sleep with a college girl.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-22"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Really? ‘Cause I went to four years of college and five years of grad school, that never happened once.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I think the next time I have to speak to a call centre in India, I’m going to try using an American accent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Because when I use my regular voice, I feel like I’m making fun of them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>That’s ridiculous. Not to mention, your American accent is terrible.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Dude, my accent is brilliant.  Hey, my snow-white American friends, let’s put some cow meat on the barbecue and eat it until we’re all obese.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>This is what you sound like. I think I’m talking in an American accent, but it really sounds like I’m wearing a set of giant dentures.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Sheldon, do I really sound like that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Tell him he sounds like that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Sheldon, you okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It’s been three days. Why hasn’t Stephen Hawking played a word?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>The guy’s a genius. Maybe you weren’t challenging enough for him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Not challenging? I was humiliating the man. I was thinking of writing a book called A Brief History of the Time I Made Stephen Hawking Cry Like a Little Girl.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>There’s the problem. You can’t beat Hawking like that. He hates to lose. Everyone knows the guy’s a big baby. I mean, forget the wheelchair, he should be in a stroller.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Really?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>One time when I was working with him, he said that Johnny Depp was in The Matrix. I told him he was wrong, but he kept insisting. So I looked it up online and showed him. Well, the next day, he had a pizza party, and everyone got invited but me. And then he was all, your invitation must have gotten lost in the matrix.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Good Lord, what have I done?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>Raj (in American accent)</speaker><content>Good Lord, what have I done?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-18"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Terrible.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-19"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>All right, hotshot, let’s hear your Indian.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-20"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I can’t sit on that elephant, my ass is on fire from eating all this curry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-21"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Okay, yeah, that’s pretty good.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Please be good. Please be good. Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Okay. She writes like she cooks.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Play. Play. Play. Play. Play.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Trying to use a Jedi mind trick to control Stephen Hawking. Play. Play. Ugh! He must be wearing a tinfoil hat or something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I did a bad thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Does it affect me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Then suffer in silence. Play. Play. Play.  Stephen Hawking.  Stephen Hawking.  Stephen Hawking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Penny started taking a class. She wrote a paper, she didn’t want me to read it, I went behind her back and I read it anyway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Stephen Hawking hates me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t know what to do. I mean, the paper’s terrible. But if I tell her, she’ll know that I read it and she’ll get really mad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I was beating him so bad, he doesn’t want to be friends anymore. Why does everyone love me except Stephen Hawking?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Is it possible we’re having two different conversations?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>How would I know? I’m not listening to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hang on. Okay, here’s what we’re gonna do. Chess clock. We each get five minutes to talk about our problems. We’ll take turns. Each turn will consist of a statement and a helpful response from the friend. Begin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I humiliated Stephen Hawking in a game of Words with Friends. He stopped playing, and now we’re not friends anymore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>He’s probably busy. You’re worried about nothing. Give it a couple more days. I’m sure he’ll play, and you’ll see that everything’s fine. My turn. I can’t let Penny hand in a bad paper, but how do I tell her it’s bad without letting her know that I read it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hmm. Beats me. Now, I know Hawking’s not busy because I can see he’s playing other people right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Maybe since you’re so good, he’s taking his time to meet the challenge. I want Penny to enjoy school…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Wolowitz told me he’s a big baby. But I didn’t know that, and I played extract for 82 points. It’s all Amy’s fault. She told me to play it. I have got to cut her loose.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, I wasn’t done talking. She hands in the paper tomorrow. I know I could help her. And she’s my girlfriend. I, I should be allowed to help her. Why aren’t I allowed to help her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, I hear you, brother.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-22"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No. You need to give me some advice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Fine. Women, huh?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-24"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, specific to my situation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-25"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Blonde women, huh?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-26"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Empathetic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-27"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It sucks to be you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-28"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I quit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-29"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Leonard, wait. No. I listened to your dumb thing. Leonard, come back. Leonard, come back. Leonard, come back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-30"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-31"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, of course, it only works on the weak-minded.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Good morning, sunshine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Leonard. It’s eight a.m. It’s like the middle of the night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I know, but I have to go to work, and I made you breakfast.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, wow, that’s so sweet. Hey, what’s this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh, before you open that, um, are you familiar with the story of The Shoemaker and the Elves?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Elves? Come on, Leonard. It’s too early for Lord of the Rings.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, no. Listen, um, once upon a time, there was this shoemaker and when he went to bed at night, elves would sneak in and they would make all these amazing shoes for him. And when the shoemaker woke up in the morning, he, he would be super happy, not mad at the elves at all. Open it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay. An examination of the economic, cultural, and political roots of slavery in the Old South, 1619 to 1865. What the hell is this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Don’t ask me. A little elf did it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>So let me get this straight. You just assumed my paper would be bad so you wrote one for me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, I assumed it would be good. Then I read it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, I, I mean, it was good. There were just a few things that needed a little polishing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You changed every word.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That’s not true. Uh, slavery. 1619. Your name at the top. That’s all you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You are such an ass. This is exactly why I didn’t want to tell you I was taking a class in the first place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Please don’t be upset. I just, I didn’t want you ending up with a bad grade and get discouraged and give up on the idea of going back to school.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Right, because me being in school is so important to you. That way, you wouldn’t have to be dating someone who’s only a waitress.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, come on, you know that’s not true.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-20"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Do I? Listen to me. I need to do this on my own. If I fail, I fail. If I pass, I pass. Do you get it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m sorry. I was just trying to help.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-22"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, well, next time don’t. Oh, and since you like stories so much, this is not The Shoemaker</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You ever hear back from Hawking?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No. It would appear as if I’ve lost him. Stupid brain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>It’ll be okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>How can it be okay? Stephen Hawking’s a genius and he talks like a robot. It’s everything I’ve ever wanted in a friend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yeah, but if he’s a sore loser, maybe you’re better off without him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You’re right. I guess I just have to make lemonade out of the two of you. He played! He played! Coop and Rolling Thunder are together again. He was okay with that nickname.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>So, now all you have to do is let him win.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, way ahead of you. I will play the word at for two measly points, throwing the game and thus securing my friendship with the smartest man in the world.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What are you waiting for? Hit send.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I can’t. Losing on purpose is intellectually dishonest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>So don’t do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, but I want to be Hawking’s friend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>So do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, but if I do, I’ll be a phony, a sellout, a Hollywood poser.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Then don’t do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I won’t. This feels right. My mother always said, to thine own self be true.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Good for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>‘Course she also told me that every animal in the world got on one boat, so what does she know? And send.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, hey. Haven’t heard from you in a couple days. You still mad at me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Nope. I have no reason to… “B” mad at you. Minus.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Wow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>That’s right. On my paper. Not yours, mine, you punk-ass elf.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t know what to say.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hmm, how about, gee, Penny, you’re smarter than I thought. You may be the one in school, but I’m the one who learned a lesson. I’m so stupid, Penny. Duh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>She sounds exactly like you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>How’d it go with Leonard?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I don’t think he’ll be making that mistake again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>So, I know this goes without saying, but if either of you tell Leonard you helped me rewrite this paper, I will beat you both with a bag of oranges.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Understood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Got it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Now, ladies, we got a B-minus on this paper. I think if we put our heads together, on the next one we could get an A.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Uh, but we got you a B-minus on purpose to make it believable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Believable? You saying I’m not smart?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>No, no!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You’re smart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>That’s better.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I feel like I’m in high school again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Yeah, doing the prom queen’s homework so she’ll like us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I know. It’s finally working.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It’s Stephen Hawking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well answer it. I want to hear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Professor Hawking, how nice of you to call.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Stephen Hawking</speaker><content>Hello. I really enjoyed our game, Dr. Cooper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, me, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Stephen Hawking</speaker><content>Or should I say Dr. Loser? Ha, ha, ha.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes, congratulations. You won fair and square. Uh, very impressive, sir.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>Stephen Hawking</speaker><content>Do you like brain teasers?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, I love brain teasers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>Stephen Hawking</speaker><content>What does Sheldon Cooper and a black hole have in common? They both suck. Neener neener.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>