<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, I must say, Leonard, when I first heard your idea for Giant Jenga, I was sceptical.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I can’t blame you. Tiny Twister was a complete bust.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, I was wrong. The looming threat of being crushed under a pile of lumber does add a certain spice. I’ve never felt so alive.  Oh, hello, Alex. Uh, let me go get you last night’s recordings.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What recordings?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, you remember when you told me I talk in my sleep? Well, it occurred to me that, like most things I say, it’s probably pure gold. So I started recording it all, and now Alex gets to comb through eight hours of what I like to call Sheldon After Dark.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Alex</speaker><content>Hey, Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey. Just playing a little Giant Jenga here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Alex</speaker><content>Oh, I know, I’m the one who had to buy him the helmet. So, do you have any plans this weekend?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, most of Saturday’s gonna be figuring out where to put this game when we’re done. How about you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Alex</speaker><content>Oh, I’m gonna go see Kip Thorne give a lecture on subatomic space-time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Ooh. That’s his take on John Wheeler’s quantum foam. That should be great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Alex</speaker><content>Well, if you want, you can come with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Ah, I’d love to, but I’m supposed to hang out with Penny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Alex</speaker><content>Well, bring her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, she’s not really into that kind of stuff.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Alex</speaker><content>Yeah, okay. Well, if you want to hear about the lecture, I can tell you all about it at work, or, you know, over dinner sometime.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Leonard (jumping and knocking over the Jenga)</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Jenga, I win!</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, come on, that can’t be true.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I did the research. Tony the Tiger, Dig’em the Frog, Cap’n Crunch, Toucan Sam, Count Chocula, Trix the Rabbit, Snap, Crackle and Pop. Not one cereal mascot is a girl. It’s a total breakfast sausage fest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Are we done with this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Almost. Franken Berry, Boo Berry, Sugar Bear and the Honey Nut Cheerio bee, I believe his name is Buzz.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Terrific. Something weird happened and I don’t know what to do about it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What’s going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon’s assistant asked me on a date last night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>How could you do that to me? You know I’ve been working it with Alex for weeks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Working it? You can’t even talk to her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I talk with my eyes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You look like my little cousin when he’s dropping one in his diaper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>She knows I have a girlfriend. It’s so weird.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, my God. You’re loving this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>To my bones. I mean, I’m not gonna do anything about it. I love Penny. It’s just nice to have a young, attractive woman sniffing around the goods.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I both hate you and want to be you. This is Ryan Gosling all over again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Ah, gentlemen, what is on the conversational menu this morning?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Leonard stole my woman, and he knew full well I was only six to eight months away from making my move.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I didn’t steal anyone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Your assistant is totally hitting on this jerk and he loves it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, that’s not acceptable. I mean, I’m her boss. She needs to be solely focused on my needs, not distracted by your pasty, androgynous brand of sexuality.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m androgynous?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, please. Look at you with your pouty bee-stung lips.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-23"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What do you guys think I should do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-24"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I say you tell Alex your heart belongs to Penny, I provide her a shoulder to cry on, and then roughly half a year later I give it to her good.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I want to thank you all for coming on such short notice. Uh, in the past, I’ve reached out to each of you individually, but I believe my present situation requires the collective wisdom of the group, which as you can see from your commemorative T-shirts I have dubbed Sheldon Cooper’s Council of Ladies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What is happening?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I need your advice about a delicate workplace situation. Uh, to protect those involved, I’ll be changing their names.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Who’s involved?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, a short, bespectacled colleague of mine who lives in the shadow of his brilliant roommate. Let’s call this colleague Ricardo Shilly-Shally.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You’re talking about Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, no, Shilly-Shally has red hair and, uh, he briefly served in the Mexican Navy. Anyway, despite the fact that he has a girlfriend, Shilly-Shally has been the recipient of inappropriate workplace flirtations from a young lady.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>It’s your assistant Alex, isn’t it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No. No. No. This is Tondelaya della Ventimiglia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Wait, what the hell’s going on with Leonard and Alex?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, uh, no, I’m sorry. Who’s talking about Leonard and Alex?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Fine. Ricardo and Tondelaya.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Okay, look, it’s not really about Ricardo and Tondelaya. It is really about her boss, who doesn’t quite know how to handle this situation and could use your advice, which is surprising because Dr. Einstein Von Brainstorm, he’s usually pretty smart about these things.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I’m gonna kill her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I’m sure you’ve got nothing to worry about. Leonard would never cheat on you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>She’s right. But say the word, I got a lab full of cocaine-addicted monkeys with nothing to lose. One of them could end up in the backseat of her car. Or her shower.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Ladies, ladies, please. We’re not here to talk about Penny, okay? We’re here to talk about me. Uh, I mean Einstein Von Brainstorm. Oh, darn it! All right, I guess the cat’s out of the bag. Let me explain what’s going on. Ricardo is really Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>We know what’s going on, Sheldon!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, what should I do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-20"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Well, Alex is your employee. If she’s doing something that’s making Leonard uncomfortable, you should talk to her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, no, he’s not uncomfortable at all. No, he’s loving it. Yeah, he’s strutting around like he’s five-foot-six.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-22"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What? He’s loving it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-23"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Sheldon, you need to talk to Alex right away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-24"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Talk to her? That’s all you’ve got? With a cool name like Sheldon Cooper’s Council of Ladies, I really expected more. Give me back the T-shirts.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Alex, check my schedule. What does my afternoon look like?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Alex</speaker><content>I think it’s pretty wide open. Oh, wait. Here’s something at four o’clock. Give Alex a talking to?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, that snuck up on us, didn’t it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Alex</speaker><content>Is there a problem?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Let’s not call it a problem. Let’s call it an opportunity. To solve a serious problem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Alex</speaker><content>What did I do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You don’t know? Oh, you poor dear. Your ovaries are squirting so much goofy juice into your brains you don’t even know which way is up. You made an inappropriate sexual advance towards Dr. Hofstadter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Alex</speaker><content>What? I didn’t make a sexual advance on anybody.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Now, there’s no need to get defensive. I’m not unsympathetic to your plight. My father used to say that a woman is like an egg salad sandwich on a warm Texas day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Alex</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Full of eggs and only appealing for a short time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Alex</speaker><content>This conversation is making me uncomfortable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, you and me both, sister. Now, please understand, I don’t hold you responsible for your behaviour because, see, from an evolutionary standpoint, you’re a slave to your desire to reproduce. But during the work day, when you feel possessed by amorous intent, may I suggest that you suppress it by leafing through this illustrated book of sexually transmitted diseases? Let’s see here. Oh, yes. Check out this oozy doozy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Alex</speaker><content>I have to go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>So does this fellow, but he can’t without it burning like hot soup.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey, pretty lady.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, you seem extra happy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh, I guess I am.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Any particular reason why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t know, just having a good day. This morning Sheldon fell asleep on the way to work, so I got to listen to the radio. That was pretty crazy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Mm-hmm. Anything else?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Mm. I found this quiz online called Which Star Trek Character Are You? and it only took me four tries to get Captain Kirk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>That’s great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh. It. Was.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hmm. Well, I’m glad you’re having such a great day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah. And the one thing that could make it even better is an evening with my special girl.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, and who’s that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What do you mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, I just didn’t know if you meant me or Alex.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Um, why would I mean Alex?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Because I know she hit on you and I know you liked it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-18"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Don’t play dumb with me, Ricardo Shilly-Shally!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m missing something.  Did you say something to Penny about Alex?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, yes. Yeah, and a fat lot of good it did me. All she did was get mad at you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Why would you do that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I needed advice about a woman. I would have asked you, but if the last few years have proven anything, it’s that you can’t tell a uterus from a unicycle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-23"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>At least I know not to blab to a girl about somebody flirting with her boyfriend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-24"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Good to know. Yeah, a few more helpful hints like that, you may find yourself on the Council of Ladies.  Hello. I see. Uh, what time? Very well, then. Huh. That was the Human Resources Department at the university. Apparently, my assistant Alex has filed a complaint accusing me of inappropriate behaviour in the workplace.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-25"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, my God, what did you do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-26"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hmm, let me think. Nothing. I’m a delight.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content> Human Resources Department.  Human Resources Department.  Human Resources Department.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>HR Woman</speaker><content>Come in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hello.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>HR Woman</speaker><content>Ah, Dr. Cooper, have a seat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>HR Woman</speaker><content>I called you in today because your assistant Alex Jensen has lodged a complaint against you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>So I’ve been told. But I can’t understand what she has to complain about. I mean, she has a front-row seat as I make scientific history. There’s string cheese in my mini-fridge, and that’s for anyone. Yeah, and just yesterday I led her away from a life of sexual promiscuity by making her look at pictures of disease-ridden genitalia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>HR Woman</speaker><content>Cancel my next appointment. This is gonna take a while. Dr. Cooper, you said things to your employee that you just cannot say in the workplace.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Like what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>HR Woman</speaker><content>Well, according to Ms. Jensen, you said that she was a slave to her biological urges and called her an egg salad sandwich. I don’t even know what that means, but I’m gonna go ahead and tell you you can’t say it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh! I see the confusion here. No, no, Alex thought I was singling her out. No. I meant that all women are slaves to their biological urges, you know? Even you. You’re a slave.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>HR Woman</speaker><content>I’m a what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, y-you, I-I’m just saying, you know, at a certain point in a woman’s menstrual cycle…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>HR Woman</speaker><content>Whuh-ah! Woah! You can’t talk about that, either, Dr. Cooper. Your language is entirely inappropriate, and I’m gonna advise that you shut your mouth right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I don’t see why I’m the one being persecuted here. Dr. Hofstadter, he was bragging about his sexual desirability to anyone who would listen. You know, and Howard Wolowitz, he spent two years using university resources building a six-breasted sex robot. Oh, and at the office Christmas party, I heard Rajesh Koothrappali refer to you several times as Brown Sugar.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>HR Woman (writing)</speaker><content>Hofstadter… Wolowitz… and the last one was Rajesh Koothrappali?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes. No, yeah, but in his defense, that wasn’t racist. He’s also brown.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Leonard (singing)</speaker><content>I’m sorry Alex hit on me, hit on me, hit on me. I’m sorry Alex hit on me, I’d no idea I’m cute.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, damn it, you are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Please forgive me. I should have told you about Alex.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I don’t care about Alex. Fine, I care. Okay, I hate that bitch. But what really hurt is that you liked it so much. I mean, do I need to be worried?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Of course not. No. Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Because, she is pretty and smart, and when you talk about work, she doesn’t have to go home and look up words in the dictionary to understand what you said.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You do that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hang on. Are you feeling insecure? Because that’s my thing, and if you take it away, I don’t know what I’m bringing to this relationship.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yes, Leonard, I am insecure. Happy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, I’m not happy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Why are you smiling?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m sorry. I just never think of you having feelings like that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, I do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Why? Nothing is ever going to happen between me and Alex.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Come here. Tell you a secret?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What’s that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>With all these women chasing me, I kind of do feel like Captain Kirk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-20"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Can I tell you a secret?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-22"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Keep talking about Captain Kirk, and we’re all gonna stop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-23"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Message received. Ah, excuse me.  Hello. This is Dr. Hofstadter. Okay. All right, thank you. That’s weird. I’m getting called in to Human Resources.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-24"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What did you do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-25"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t know.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Huh. I just got called in to Human Resources.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I don’t know.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Huh. That is so strange. Human Resources wants to talk to me tomorrow.  Could you stop licking your ass for two minutes? I have a problem here.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Do you really think you should be drinking right now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>How else am I supposed to talk to the Human Resources lady?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I don’t know. Seek professional help?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I did. The guy at the liquor store said this stuff tastes great in coffee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Wait, you got called in, too? What is going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon threw us all under the bus.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I feel like I’ve been called down to the principal’s office. Although I wouldn’t mind if Brown Sugar suspended me. From a sex swing. This may have been a mistake.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Relax. Everything’s gonna be fine. Before I met Bernadette I was in here every other day. Uh, little tip, turn off your I Like Big Butts ringtone before you go in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Well, this is all your fault.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>How is this my fault?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>If you weren’t screwing around with Sheldon’s assistant, none of this would be happening.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I wasn’t screwing around with anyone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, of course not. She was just sniffing around your goods because she was hunting for truffles.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>HR Woman</speaker><content>Ah, Mr. Wolowitz, it’s been a while.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Hey, Janine. How are Tom and the kids?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-17"><speaker>Janine</speaker><content>Fine. You must be Dr. Hofstadter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yes, but I think this is all a big misunderstanding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-19"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yeah, yeah, me, too. I didn’t do anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-20"><speaker>Janine</speaker><content>Is that alcohol on your breath?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-21"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Howard built a sex robot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-22"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>That is not true. All I did was build a robot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-23"><speaker>Janine</speaker><content>Did it have six breasts?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-24"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’m sorry, I’m a feminist, I don’t notice things like how many breasts a robot has.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-25"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, hello.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-26"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What are you doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-27"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Actually, I came to speak to Mrs. Davis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-28"><speaker>Janine</speaker><content>And I’m a little busy right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-29"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>But I came to file a complaint. Somebody has made me feel uncomfortable in the workplace by using language of an inappropriate and sexual nature.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-30"><speaker>Janine</speaker><content>And who was that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-31"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You, you dirty birdie. I-I thought about the things you said to me yesterday, and I realized I’m deeply offended. Now, be a dear and get me one of those complaint forms.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-32"><speaker>Janine</speaker><content>That’s it. All of you, in my office now!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-33"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And thanks to you, I know better than to ask if you’re menstruating. And based on your behaviour, I don’t have to.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It has been pointed out to me that some of the things I said to you could be construed as offensive, and I would like to offer you my sincerest apology.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Alex</speaker><content>Thank you, Dr. Cooper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, additionally, you should know that the university has mandated that I take an online sexual harassment seminar so this sort of thing doesn’t happen in the future.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Alex</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah. Now, unfortunately, uh, my time is much too valuable to waste on nonsense like this, so, um, I’m gonna need you to take it for me. Oh, and, uh, you’d better ace it, they’re pretty mad.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>So, hey, I was thinking about that stuff with Alex.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, would you stop worrying about that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I can’t help it. But, look, I figured I could sit around and feel insecure, or I could do something about it. So I got a course catalogue at school and looked at some of the science classes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That’s great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, it isn’t, they are extremely boring. I mean, how do you not kill yourself, like, every day? Anyway, I decided I don’t need to be a scientist, I could just look like one. So I bought these.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Glasses? I really don’t think that’s gonna change… oh, my God, you look so smart and hot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I know, right? Watch this. Molecules.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, come with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Where are we going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>To my bedroom, so I can take everything off but those glasses. And maybe the boots.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>