<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, now holding sides of hearth in position, lower mantelpiece assembly onto top tabs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Look at that, I built a fireplace with my own two hands.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You’re so butch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Aw, I got a little paper cut.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Of course you did. Your hands are softer than veal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, before I forget, Saturday I’m planning a little Dungeons and Dragons night with the guys.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Really? That’s how you’re gonna spend your Saturday night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, come on, I hardly ever get a chance to play anymore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, you poor thing. Is having a real-life girlfriend who has sex with you getting in the way of your board games?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Little bit, yeah.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Oh, great! I’ve always wanted to play Dungeons and Dragons.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, oh, I’m sorry. I should’ve mentioned this earlier. You’re not invited.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Why not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Amy, from time to time, we men need to break free from the shackles of civility and get in touch with our primal animalistic selves.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>By rolling dice and playing make-believe with little figurines?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, like a bunch of savages.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Saturday night? But I’ve been working late all week. That was gonna be our night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>But I have to go. We play as a group. If-if I’m not there, then everyone will blame you. They’ll be all, Bernadette ruined everything. She’s the worst. So, you see? I have to play Dungeons and Dragons for the marriage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>You’re an idiot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’m your idiot. Forever.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>So, listen, I know we talked about getting a bite to eat in Silver Lake, and then seeing the Christmas lights in Griffith Park, but Leonard’s talking about a big D and D game at his place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Saturday night just went from crazy to epic. Woo-hoo!</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>All right, Sheldon, to start our quest you need to open this little Christmas gift I got you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>A Christmas gift? You know I don’t enjoy Christmas.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>What’s wrong with Christmas?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, where to begin? Trees indoors. Overuse of the words ’tis and ’twas. And the absurd custom of one stocking. Everyone knows socks belong in pairs. Who uses one sock?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Actually that helps, thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Would you just look inside?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, a scroll. I like scrolls. They’re my third favourite system of transmitting the written word. After stone tablets and skywriting. You have all been summoned to join a thrilling Dungeons and Dragons adventure. Your quest begins in a secret northern village of elves who have all been massacred. I like where this is heading. Your task is to rescue their leader from a dungeon of ogres. Oh, that’s a saucy twist. That leader’s name, Santa Claus. No, no, no.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It’s actually ho, ho, ho, but you’ll get the hang of it. Thought it’d be fun to make a quest with a holiday theme.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Fun? Mixing Dungeons and Dragons with Christmas is like making a sandwich of grape jelly, the best-tasting jelly, and petroleum jelly, the worst-tasting jelly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, here we go. You find yourselves in the smoking remains of Santa’s village. Clearly, a great battle has taken place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, man, the first monster I see, I’m gonna sneak up behind him, whip out my wand, and shoot my magic all over his ass.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Do you hear yourself when you say these things?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, there are ogre tracks and a trail of broken candy canes in the snow. Sheldon, what do you do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I signal my contempt for your cruel plan to shove Christmas joy down my throat by making a gesture that says get a load of this guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Fine. Howard, what do you do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I follow the ogre tracks, checking for secret doors along the way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>And you discover a secret door leading to a dark corridor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-18"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Okay, guys, let’s make a plan, spell casters in the back, warriors in the front.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-19"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No, screw that noise, I’m going in. Hang on, Santa, I’m coming for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, you run into a room full of weapons, hit a trip wire, a cannon blows your face off, you die, you’re out of the game.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-21"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>But, a cannon? Am I really out of the game?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Lucky.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-23"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, come on, moving on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-24"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Wait, doesn’t anyone have a rod of resurrection? Because if you’ve got one, I need it bad. Get in here with your rod and give it to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-25"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Okay, you need to say these things in your head before you say them out loud.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-26"><speaker>Penny (entering)</speaker><content>Hey, guys. I don’t mean to interrupt your little game, but I thought you’d like to see what you’re missing out on. So, Bernadette? Bernadette’s wearing leopard-print pumps and a rack-tastic red dress from Forever 21. And there’s Amy, showing all kinds of ankle. In an outfit I’m assuming is from Forever 63. And I, myself am wearing a little number that got me out of two speeding tickets and jury duty.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-27"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I know they’re making a rhetorical point, I just don’t know what it is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-28"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>See you, boys. We are going drinking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-29"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Uh, wait, can I come with you? My character died.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-30"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Sorry, Raj, it’s girls’ night out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-31"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Maybe another time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-32"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-33"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Come on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-34"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Ooh! Girls’ night, girls’ night! Ooh! Ooh!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-35"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>How does he not hear that?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>So, what’s the plan? Are we gonna teach our fellas a lesson by getting stinking drunk, luring strange men into the bathroom, and turning the toilet stall into a temple of the senses?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>No!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Geez, who’s Forever 63 now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Can we get another bottle of champagne for the table? Don’t worry. It’s my treat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Thanks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Wow, you should come to girls’ night more often. And not just because if you weren’t here, this would be a can of Pabst.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>My pleasure, nothing makes me happier than the chance to spoil a lady. Just ask my dog. My vet says if I give her any more foie gras, she’s going to die of gout.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Hey, let’s help Raj meet a girl tonight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No, no, no, I’m fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, wait, are we talking one-night stand or do we want to get him into a relationship?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Let’s get him laid!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Stop it. You’re ruining girls’ night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Raj, you’re a great guy, you’re in a bar full of single women, let us help you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Yeah, you’re a real catch. I know you’re shy, but that doesn’t mean you shouldn’t have someone wonderful in your life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>That’s sweet of you. But what can you do to help?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>We’ll nose around, see if we can find a nice girl, and then introduce you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-18"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Okay. Well, a couple of things. Don’t tell them I come from money. I want them to love me for me. They must be insanely hot. Like, nines or tens.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-19"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Nines or tens?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-20"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Okay, an eight is acceptable if she’s willing to bring another eight to the hot tub.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-21"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Bottom line, you’ll take any woman who’ll have you, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-22"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>In a New Delhi minute.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>I don’t remember you buying these miniatures in my store.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, uh, yeah. I got ’em on Amazon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Sure. I get it. Why support a friend when you can support a multinational conglomerate that is crushing the life out of that friend?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I know, but when I shop online, I can do it on the toilet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Have you seen my store? The whole place is a toilet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Can we please move this along?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, sorry. Uh, you come to the end of the tunnel and find a large chest. What do you do? And, Howard, do not say, I feel up the large chest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Excuse me, I’m a married man now. I wasn’t going to say anything so juvenile.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Great. What do you do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I walk up to the large chest, bury my face in it and go “blublublublublublublublu”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I open the chest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It’s locked, but suddenly the door behind you slams shut and now the walls of the room start closing in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>That’s not good. My character and I both have claustrophobia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Glowing letters appear on the chest that read, If squashed to death you wish not to be, sing of Svaty Vaclav and his victory.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Who the hell is Svaty Vaclav?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Walls are getting closer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Oh, boy, happy place, happy place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Wait, Svaty Vaclav was the Duke of Bohemia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You’re ten seconds away from getting crushed. Nine, eight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-20"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What are we supposed to do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Seven, six.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Wait, wait. Svaty Vaclav is better known as Good King Wenceslas from the beloved Victorian Christmas carol.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-23"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Never heard of it. Must be the one Christmas song not written by a Jewish guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-24"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Three, two.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-25"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Somebody sing the damn song.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-26"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Good King Wenceslas looked out, on the feast of Stephen. When the snow lay ’round about, deep and crisp and even</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-27"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>The walls are getting slower.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-28"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Brightly shone the moon that night, though the frost was cruel. When a poor man came in sight gathering winter fuel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-29"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>That was amazing, Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-30"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>How did you know that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-31"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It was simple. I combined a well-known historical fact about Bohemia with the memory of my grandparents, Mee-Maw and Pop-Pop, singing Christmas carols while I sat in front of the fire and tried to build a high-energy particle accelerator out of Legos.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-32"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, continuing our quest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-33"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>W-W-Wait. There’s still four more verses. You don’t sing a song and not finish it. Hither, page, and stand by me, if thou know’st it, telling. Yonder peasant, who is he? Where and what his dwelling? Brightly shone the moon that night, though the frost…</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Looks like he’s doing pretty good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Of course he is. Look, that girl just got dumped by her boyfriend. She’s angry, she’s drunk, and her favorite movie is Slumdog Millionaire. I mean.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>That is some low-hanging fruit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Oh, here he comes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>So, how’d it go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Great. I bought her a couple of drinks, and she gave me her e-mail address.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Ooh!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Jennifer at not-even-if-you-were-the-last-guy-on-earth dot loser.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I’m sorry, Raj.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Why can’t I find someone? I’m smart, I’ve got a cool job, and my naturally bronzed complexion means I can pull off mustard yellow in a way most guys can’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, honey, it’s not you, it’s them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No, it’s not. She was too beautiful for me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Why would you say that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>It’s true. I’m always attracted to women I can’t have. I do it all the time. I did the same thing with the two of you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>The two of them? I don’t understand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Well, uh, there was a time when I had a thing for Penny, and I thought she was into me, too, because she got drunk and naked and climbed into bed with me. But apparently I misread those signals.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>And you liked Bernadette also?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>That was before Penny. I make it a rule to only fall for one of my friends’ girlfriends at a time. I’m very old-fashioned that way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-20"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>So at, uh, some point, you probably had a thing for me, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-21"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No, not really.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-22"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, come on, Raj, not even a little bit?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-23"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Not that I can think of.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-24"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Think harder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-25"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Nope. I guess the heart wants what the heart wants. Or in this case, doesn’t, I mean, at all. What?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Ye who now will bless the poor, shall yourselves find blessing. Ba-da-bum.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Done?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I think the word you’re looking for is bravo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, you leave the room and find yourself standing before a pool of melted snowmen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Melted snowmen? Are there carrots and lumps of coal in the water?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t know. What’s the difference?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well it’s a game of the imagination, Leonard. Paint a picture.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Fine. You leave the room and find yourself standing before a pool of melted snowmen. There are carrots and lumps of coal in the water.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What happened to the top hats and the corncob pipes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You see those, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, it’s like I’m really there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>I gotta tell you, this, this is the most holiday fun I’ve had since my therapist changed my anxiety medication and I stopped caring about the blood in my stool.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Good story.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What are you drinking there? A little eggnog?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes. What, is there a problem?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, it’s nice to see you enjoying a holiday beverage. Pretty Christmassy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Since when is eggnog a Christmas drink? Eggs are available all year ’round. I’ve been known to enjoy this poolside.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Come on, Sheldon. You know all the Christmas stories, and the carols, you’ve got an eggnog moustache going on there. Just admit it. You’re getting a little Yuletide spirit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, don’t be silly. Christmas is a bunch of baloney created by the tinsel industry. Why is this so important to you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Honestly, because I had enough crappy Christmases as a kid and I’m tired of you sucking the joy out of them now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-21"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>What was so bad about them?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-22"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I grew up in a house full of crazy academics. Instead of leaving Santa milk and cookies, we had to leave him a research paper. And in the morning, you could tell he’d been there because the paper would be graded.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No wonder you love Christmas. That sounds amazing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-24"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It wasn’t amazing. I got a C-minus four years in a row.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-25"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, I’m familiar with your work. C-minus was your gift.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Amy, I’m really sorry. I didn’t mean to upset you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>It’s fine. I’m used to being the girl who never gets looked at twice. I didn’t have my first kiss till I was 22, and the guy only did it so I’d give him back his insulin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Sometimes the pancreas wants what the pancreas wants.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Forget it. I don’t expect you guys to understand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I understand. In seventh grade, I played Spin the Bottle and it landed on Alina Shankar. She said if I came near her, she would break the bottle and cut me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You think that’s bad? In college, I passed out at a frat party and woke up with more clothes on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Sometimes I get so lonely, I sit on my left hand until it goes numb, then I put it in my right hand and pretend I’m holding hands with another person.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I do that, too. Sometimes the left hand tries to cop a feel. And I let it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>It’s kind of nice to talk to someone who understands what it feels like to be alone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>It is, isn’t it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>But you’re not alone anymore. Now you’ve got Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I do. And don’t worry, someday you’ll have somebody, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Thank you. I hope she’s half as lovely and amazing as you are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Thank you, Rajesh. He wants me, I’m good. We can go now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Damn it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Now that I know she doesn’t like me, I’m kind of into her.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right. I think I cracked the code to lower the drawbridge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Great. Let’s do it. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>The drawbridge is lowering.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>My carpal tunnel’s acting up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Play through the pain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You did it. The drawbridge is down. You cross the chasm and find yourself in a small dungeon room. And in the corner, chained to the wall, you see a bloodied and beaten Santa Claus. He says, ho, ho, help me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yes, we found Santa. Christmas is saved. Don’t ever tell my mother I said that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>I take out my skeleton key and run to Santa to unchain him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>But first, I cast a spell of paralysis on Stuart and Howard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Wait, what are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You can’t talk, you’re paralyzed. I get right up in Santa’s big, fat face and say, well, well, well, jolly old Saint Nick, we meet again. Yeah, I believe the last time we spoke was in the Baybrook Mall in Galveston, Texas, when I was five years old, isn’t that right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh, okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>My mother dragged me there and she plopped me down on your lap and you asked me what I wanted for Christmas. And I told you, my Pop-Pop, because that was the year my grandfather died. I missed him and I wanted him back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>This is weird, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Pop-Pop was the only one in my family who encouraged me to pursue science. But you didn’t bring him back, did you? No, instead, I got Lincoln Logs. Well, you can build a lot of neat things out of Lincoln Logs, but Pop-Pop ain’t one of ’em. And now you’re here asking me for something, to save you. Well, sorry, Mr. Kringle, but today’s not your day. I’m leaving you here to rot, and I hope the ogres feast on your bones. I take the skeleton key, and I toss it into the chasm, and on the way out, I give Santa a swift kick in his bowl full of jelly!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay. So Wolowitz and Stuart are paralyzed, Santa’s dead, and I picked this over having sex with my girlfriend.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Santa?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Santa</speaker><content>Oh, hello, Sheldon. You should be asleep.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, then, you shouldn’t have jingle bells on your boots.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Santa</speaker><content>Oh. I’ve been wanting to talk to you. I’m sorry I disappointed you when you were a little boy. I can do a lot of magical things, but unfortunately bringing your Pop-Pop back isn’t one of them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I understand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Santa</speaker><content>But I do have something special for you. Close your eyes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, I hope it’s a train.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>Santa</speaker><content>Oh, it’s better than a train.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Two trains?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>Santa</speaker><content>Better.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m getting three trains.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>Santa</speaker><content>Okay, open ’em.  This is for leaving me in the dungeon to be eaten alive by ogres!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Wait, uh, uh, hang on. In my defense…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>Santa</speaker><content>Ho, ho, ho, ya big dork. </content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>