<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>So, anyway, last night on video chat, I spent, like, twenty minutes just staring into Lucy’s eyes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, that sounds romantic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>It was until I realized the screen had frozen. Still one of my top three dates of all time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>So, are we ever gonna hang out with this girl?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I’d love that, but she’s not really comfortable around people.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, I used to be uncomfortable around people, but then I learned a trick. I pretend everyone I meet is a beloved character from Star Trek.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>How’s that been working for you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, like a charm, unnamed crewman in a red shirt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Leonard, I may have gotten you a job.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I have a job.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes, he does. He caters to my every whim.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No, in a couple of weeks, Stephen Hawking’s team is sending an expedition to the North Sea to test hydrodynamic simulations of black holes. One of their experimental physicists dropped out, and I recommended you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, do you really think I have a shot?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, I’ve worked with Hawking. I talked you up. He knows your research. I think this could happen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>He knows, wow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, now, but do you think that’s a good idea? Uh, you know Star Trek. Should a guy with no name and a red shirt really go on an expedition?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Hey, don’t discourage him. This is a fantastic opportunity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No one asked you, Uhura.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Would you like to hear a classic Sheldon Cooper factoid?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What do you think?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Great. I’ve been doing some reading about vehicular safety. Did you know that the highest number of drowning accidents happen on or around boats?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Interesting that you would bring that up when I might go work on a boat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, that’s the thing about factoids, they’re interesting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I know what you’re doing. You don’t want me going on this research trip because you’re afraid to be alone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m not afraid to be alone. On land. On the sea, it would be terrifying. Because of all the drowning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Fine, no more drowning talk. I’ll change the subject. Oh. Who do you think would win in a fight, you or a shark?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Look, I appreciate your signature blend of concern for me and incredible selfishness. If I get the chance to do this, there is nothing you can say that’s going to stop me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Very well. Things between you and Penny have never been better. I hope four months apart doesn’t change anything. I should have opened with that, huh?</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>If you look carefully at Venus, you should be able to see the International Space Station pass by.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>Wow. Your friend was actually up there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yeah. He brought me back a T-shirt that said My Friend Went to the Space Station and All I Got Was This Lousy T-Shirt</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>Did he take the T-shirt to space?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Nope. It’s exactly as lousy as advertised. Speaking of friends, they have been asking to meet you. I was thinking maybe we could all hang out sometime?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>I don’t know. How many are there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Let’s see. Six. That’s pretty cool, I have six friends. Kind of like Sinatra.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>Six strangers? That’s a lot of pressure. Staring at me, asking me personal questions. Like, what do you do? Where are you from? Why did you lock yourself in the bathroom?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Okay, how about you just dip your toe in and meet one of them?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>Will you be there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Of course.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>Well, that’s two. Three if you count me. Oh, this is getting out of hand.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>So, then, during my afternoon shift, I spilled an entire tray of drinks on myself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, that’s awful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Not really. My shirt was soaking wet. I got, like, the biggest tip of my life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>So, listen, do you remember when I said the similarities of the equations of general relativity and hydrodynamics suggest you could find the equivalent of Unruh radiation in a large body of water?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I thought I said that to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Anyway, Stephen Hawking’s team is looking into that, and I’ve been invited to join them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Wow, Hawking. Good for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, it is. Just, you know, I’d be gone for a while.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, how long?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Three, four months.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Whoa. When would you leave?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Couple of weeks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Wow. Oh, okay, well, I’ll just come visit you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That’s the thing, you can’t. I’ll be on a ship in the North Sea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>On a ship? Aren’t they afraid Hawking will just roll overboard?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh, he’s not gonna be there. He’s just sending a team to research his theory.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, sure. Like when you send me to kill spiders in your bathtub. Wow. Okay. Four months.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah. And I’m a little worried because things between us have been so great, and I’d hate to do anything that screws that up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, sweetie, if you’re gonna screw things up, it’s gonna be while you’re here, not while you’re away. No. I mean, look, you have to go. It sounds like an amazing opportunity. And I’m just basing that on how much I didn’t understand what you said about it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay. I’ll confirm the travel arrangements in the morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-21"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay. Good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-22"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I do have to ask you one favour.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-23"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-24"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon’s nervous about me leaving. Just keep an eye on him while I’m gone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-25"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, I don’t know. Remember what happened when I took care of your goldfish?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-26"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, flush Sheldon down the toilet and get me a new one.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Really, you guys do not need to throw me a going-away party.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Are you kidding me? How often can you say bon voyage to somebody when they’re actually going on a voyage?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Hello, Rajesh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Howard (in Raj accent)</speaker><content>Hello, Amy. Nice to see you. What can I say? It’s funnier with the accent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>There’s beer in the fridge. Anyway, you guys really don’t need to make a big deal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Leonard, you’re being selfish. We need to give you a proper send-off so we’ll have closure when you die at sea and crabs eat your face.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sheldon, sweetie, shut up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>You know, one of the things that helped me get through Howard being in space for so long was getting married before he left.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Bernadette, sweetie, shut up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Okay. I have a request to make.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>And now he can talk. I want to cut open your brain and see what the heck’s going on in there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>The only person allowed inside this head is Dr. Phil. Anyway, I, I spoke to my new lady friend about meeting you all, and she thought it would be easier for her to start with just one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, gee, I don’t know. My schedule’s a little busy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Actually, I was thinking Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh. Thank you, Raj. I’d be honoured.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What the hell? I thought I was your best friend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You are, but you’ve got kind of a big personality, with your flashy clothes and your Woody Allen swagger.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-18"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You know, maybe she’d be more comfortable meeting a girl first.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-19"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Good idea. Bernadette?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-20"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What the hell?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-21"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Well, you’re very pretty. That could be intimidating to another woman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-22"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-23"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Hey, you don’t think I’m pretty enough to scare your girlfriend?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-24"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Calm down, Bernie. You’re very scary.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-25"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>It should be me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-26"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Why? So you can make jokes about cutting open my brain?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-27"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>A, that was not a joke, that was a sincere request. And B, more importantly, I was the outsider to this group, and I know how frightening that can be. But you guys took me in and made me feel loved, like I was family.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-28"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Fine, I’ll do it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>So, after I started dating Sheldon, I met Leonard, and then everybody else, and they’ve all been so wonderful to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>That’s really nice to hear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Maybe next week, we could all get together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, Lucy, you don’t have to answer that. Don’t put her on the spot. She hates that. Am I right? Tell her how much you hate being put on the spot. Go ahead, tell her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Ignore him. He’s a little nervous ’cause he doesn’t think I understand the severity of your social anxiety.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>What the? Are you crazy? You can’t talk about social anxiety to someone who has social anxiety. It makes them socially anxious!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Excuse me, but I’m a neurobiologist. I think I’m a little more qualified than you to understand what’s not working in your girlfriend’s brain!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Don’t call her my girlfriend. We haven’t discussed whether or not we’re girlfriend or boyfriend yet. Now that it’s out there, are you my girlfriend? By the way, if you say no, I’ll never be happy again. Not to put you on the spot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>I think I have to go to the bathroom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>We might as well go ahead and eat. She’s not coming back anytime soon.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>This is ridiculous, we’re shopping for a party and this store doesn’t even have a party section.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, it does, and here we are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You know, I have to say, Penny, I don’t understand why you of all people are encouraging Leonard to do this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, I’m his girlfriend, of course I’m gonna support him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, well, you’re his girlfriend for now. You know, maybe you’re not aware of this, but there is a rich tradition of men at sea finding comfort in each other’s arms and britches.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Honey, this is a big deal for Leonard, okay? He gets to work with Stephen Hawking. Who, by the way, will not be on the boat. I checked it out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It’s not that big of an opportunity. And even if Hawking’s theories are correct, all they prove is where the universe came from, why everything exists and what its ultimate end will be. I mean, me? I’m interested in the big questions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, my God, Sheldon the genius is jealous of Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m not jealous. I’m just very unhappy that good things are happening for him and not happening for me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Look, sweetie, this is a natural thing to feel, okay? But just because good things are happening to Leonard doesn’t take anything away from you. You know what? Let me tell you a little story. Once there was a girl who worked at the Cheesecake Factory, and she wasn’t very good at her job.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It was you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>It wasn’t me. But she was also an actress, and we were both up for the same part in a toothpaste commercial. She got it. Look, I was so jealous. But instead of ripping out her fake blonde hair…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You ripped out your own fake blonde hair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I, looked her in the eye, smiled and said, I’m happy for you. Because that’s what friends do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>They lie so they don’t look petty.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>How?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Like this. I am so happy for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Wow. No wonder you didn’t get that toothpaste commercial.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Raj (on skype)</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I want to apologize for Amy last night. She was completely out of line. Are you, are you not speaking to me or did the screen freeze again?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>Amy wasn’t the problem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Okay. I know. It was me. I, I pushed too hard. I’m sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You know, I, I’ve been thinking that maybe meeting somebody one-on-one is too intense, so Friday night, my friends are having a party.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>A party?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>A little one. It’s, it’s a farewell for Leonard, so all the attention will be on him. If you wear something brown and sit on the couch, they won’t even know you’re there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>I’m not sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, please?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>Raj.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Come on. Don’t make me beg. And I’m from India, so I know how to do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Lucy</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yeah, thank you! This means a lot to me. My friends are like my family. Unless you don’t like them, in which case, they’re dead to me.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>So, have you ever spent a long time on a boat before?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Are you referring to the time we got stuck on the Small World ride at Disneyland?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’m proud of you, Leonard. Working out on the North Sea for months, that’s really something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I know. As far as science goes, this is the adventure of a lifetime.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Maybe your lifetime. I went to space.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It’s not a competition.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You’re right, you’re right. I’m really proud of you, and I’m gonna miss you when you’re gone. And space beats water.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Rajesh, I thought Lucy was coming.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>She is. She’s just running a little late. You know how it is, girls always fussing about their hair, their makeup. She’ll be here. Just give it a rest, okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Um, can I have your attention, everyone?  That’s, uh, B-flat, for those who don’t have perfect pitch. I would like to propose a toast to my best friend, Dr. Leonard Hofstadter. He has been presented with a wonderful opportunity, and I couldn’t be happier for him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Thank you, Sheldon. That must’ve been very hard for you to say.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, I mean it. I’m really happy for you. And that’s how you get a toothpaste commercial. Cheers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Cheers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Cheers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>It was really nice of you to try to be happy for Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-19"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>It must’ve killed you when I went to space.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-20"><speaker>Raj (Looking at phone)</speaker><content>Oh, no.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-21"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Buddy, you okay? Oh, man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-22"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>What’s going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-23"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Uh, go ahead. Read it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-24"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Raj, I can’t come to the party. This is all just too much for me. I don’t think we should see each other any more. Sorry. Lucy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-25"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Excuse me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-26"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Raj, I’m so sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-27"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Me, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-28"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It did not kill me when you went to space. Monkeys went to space.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, here we are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yep. I’m really gonna miss you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I’m gonna miss you, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Penny, we’re in the red zone. The white zone is for loading and unloading. We’re breaking the law.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, there’s no space in the white zone, so…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Anyway, we can e-mail, and I think the phone connections are pretty good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right, you have to get out of the car right now. I’m not going to jail for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Would you just relax?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, I see a space in the white zone. Quick, circle the airport.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Did you bring enough inhalers?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>And, uh, extra Dramamine? You remember what happened on It’s a Small World.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m covered.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, dear Lord, a police officer’s glancing in our direction. We’ve been made.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Calm down. I’m getting out. I have something I want to give you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It’s just a heart-shaped locket with a picture of Leonard’s face in it. He got it at the mall on clearance. Now move, move, move.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-19"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I love you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I love you, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Don’t worry, Officer. They just love each other. We’re not smuggling drugs.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Raj, it’s Penny. Are you in there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Hang on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey. I’m just coming back from the airport. I wanted to see how you’re doing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>That’s, that’s very nice of you. Uh, come, come. Come on in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Can’t stay long. I left Sheldon in the car with the window cracked open. He’s gonna go through that activity book in, like, 30 seconds, so… Are you okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh. I’m so sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No. It’s my fault. You know, I finally found someone who was right for me, and I, I drove her away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, Raj.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Penny, I, I miss her already.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I know how you feel. I miss Leonard, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>What’s like, what is wrong with me? Why, why can’t I ever have love?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You will.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No, I, I won’t. I’m, I’m unlovable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>That’s just the booze talking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-16"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No, it’s not. I haven’t had a drink since last night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You’re talking to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-18"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I am. And now I’m crying for a whole different reason!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-19"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, me, too.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>So I guess what I’m saying is I get where Lucy’s coming from.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>That’s great. Do you want some wine?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Uh, no, water’s fine. Anyhow, I’ve been thinking about it a lot and, and I totally see why Lucy did what she did. I pushed too hard. But you know what? If I back off and give her enough space, maybe there’s still a future for us. Yeah, the funny thing about life is that, you know, sometimes…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Does he ever shut up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>… but then it turns good again, and that means it’s better than if it had never been bad for a while. I know that now, thing’s aren’t good, they are in fact very very bad but at least my heart is starting to heal. Slowly but surely. And oh how I cried. It was like a little, uh, thunderstorm on my face. But I’m a man, okay? So I need to pull myself together, pick up a pen and get it all out in my journal. I mean, it’s not all bad, right? Having my heart broken has allowed me to finally speak in front of you, so, you know, a silver lining….</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>