<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>So then I went to Cambridge, which was wonderful not only because it’s a good school but because it totally looks like Hogwarts. That’s where I fell in love with astronomy, and now I’m an astrophysicist at Caltech, so I guess you could say, uh, Raj is my name and stars are my game. And rhyming is also my game. So, uh, two games. Uh, anyway, that, that’s enough about me. I want to hear everything about you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Girl</speaker><content>I have to go to the bathroom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I go to the bathroom, too. Sometimes more frequently than I care to admit. Oh, I’ve had it checked out, it’s nothing. Hmm. This is going great. Mmm, can I have a refill on my chai tea? Yes, I have a good feeling about this.  I should have bought condoms.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hello, I’m Dr. Sheldon Cooper. Welcome to Sheldon Cooper Presents Fun with Flags. My apologies that this episode is coming late. I did shoot one last week, in honour of Black History Month, but I was informed by my roommate that my spot-on portrayal of George Washington Carver could be considered wildly racist. My heart goes out to the members of the African-American community, who, like me, have been kept down by The Man. Now, Fun with Flags is not just for the flag aficionado, it’s also for the flag novice, so, to help me with that, please welcome my friend, neighbour, and flag virgin, yeah, not a real virgin. She’s had coitus many times. Sometimes within earshot of this flag enthusiast. Once while he was trying to watch The Incredibles. Penny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hello.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>So, Penny, I understand you would like to learn more about flags.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, I can’t tell you how many times I’ve been at a party where everyone’s talking about flags and I just couldn’t join in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah. Well, you came to the right place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Uh, I’m sorry, can we just pause for a minute?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What’s wrong?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I just think it might look more natural if you talked to me instead of the camera, you know, like, like a real conversation. It’s something we work on in my acting class.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Interesting. A few people in the comments section have said that my delivery is robotic. Perhaps that isn’t the compliment it sounds like.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, let’s try it again, and maybe, this time, you could work on your body language a bit. You know, when you’re all hunched like that, you’re shutting the audience out, but when you’re relaxed and open, you’re inviting them in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Right. And which one do I want?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Let’s try open.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>If our friend, the flag, has taught me anything, it’s to go where the wind takes you. As long as you remain firmly attached to a rigid pole. And, action. So, Penny, what sort of flag questions keep you awake at night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Um, well, I’m from Nebraska. So what can you tell me about the state flag?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Gosh, Penny, what’d you have for breakfast? A big glass of good question juice? The Nebraska state flag is simply the state seal on a field of blue. Spread your legs, invite them in.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’m telling you, something’s wrong. I can always feel it when Raj is in trouble.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Geez, how close were you guys before we got married?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Don’t look under that rock.  Raj, you okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You in there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Raj (off)</speaker><content>Go away!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Come on, buddy, open up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>We’re worried about you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Raj (off)</speaker><content>Oh, just because I’ve stopped going to work and answering my phone you think something bad happened? Maybe something good happened.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Did something good happen?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Raj (off)</speaker><content>Of course not. Nothing good ever happens. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Whoa.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Nope, just, just, whoa.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>It smells pretty ripe in here. You kind feel it in your eyes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Raj, what’s going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I was humiliated by yet another woman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You didn’t kill her and chop her up, that’s not what we’re smelling, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No. I took her for coffee, and she snuck out the bathroom window to get away from me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Oh, you poor baby.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-20"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I went and looked. It was a high and tiny window. She must have been very motivated.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-21"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’m sorry. That’s awful, but come on, you got to shake it off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-22"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, you can’t stay in your apartment for the rest of your life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-23"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Why not? With online shopping and overnight delivery, I can get anything I want. Look, I just ordered a case of Dinty Moore beef stew and two live lobsters on Amazon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-24"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Lobsters overnight?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-25"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, you’re kidding. Let me see. Well, I’ll be. Look, you can throw in a couple steaks and have a surf and turf.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-26"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>The surf and turf sounds good. See if they have corn on the cob.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-27"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Guys, we’re trying to get him out of here, not you in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-28"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You’re wasting your time. Just please, leave me alone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-29"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Now what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-30"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-31"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>We could go to Red Lobster and talk about it. We’re all thinking it. I just had the decency to wait for him to leave.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Amy (on webcam)</speaker><content>Hello, Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hello. How’s the final stage of your nicotine addiction study going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Fine. Just hold on. Mommy’s on the phone! Sorry. We’ve cut the monkeys down to one cigarette a day, so things are a little intense. Makes me miss my marijuana-abusing flatworms. Those guys were mellow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Good news. Uh, the latest episode of Fun with Flags is online.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Oh, that’s right. How’d it go with Penny?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Much better than I expected. She even gave me some helpful tips about acting and body language. Watch. Welcome to my world. Not welcome to my world. Welcome. Not welcome.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Subtle, but powerful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I know. I’m still learning to control it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Did you tell Penny how helpful she was?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Why would I do that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Because she’s your friend, and she did a nice job. I’m sure she’d like to hear it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I didn’t mean now. Hello? Yeah, yeah, you want a cigarette. Well, I’d like a normal boyfriend. Deal with it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, hi. What’s up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Um…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You need me to shut the door so you can do your knocking thing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No. I didn’t start yet, it’s fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay. So, what do you need?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, I was thinking about you helping me out last night  Penny. And I just wanted to tell you  Penny, that the answer to the question, who did a great job? is you,  Penny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Really?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes, you were very natural in front of the camera, and I found your suggestions extremely helpful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Aw, sweetie, you just made my day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey, my acting class is putting on a play Friday night. I could put you and Amy on the guest list.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, that sounds terrible. Why would I want to do that?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Amy (on webcam)</speaker><content>That’s right. They’re no good without the lighter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, so much for your advice on complimenting Penny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Why? What happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>She tried to rope us into going to her acting class to see a play. Don’t worry. Luckily, I had the good sense to drown that kitten in the river.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon, that’s very rude. She helped you with your show. The right thing to do is reciprocate by going to see her play.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, so many crazy rules.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>That better be Tootsie Rolls you’re throwing at me!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content> Penny.  Penny.  Penny. Oh yeah, much better.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Amy pointed out to me that since you did something nice for me, I’m obligated to do something nice for you. So, yes, I’ll go to your dopey play.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey, I don’t want you to go any more.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Why not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You should go ’cause you want to go, not because you have to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, Dear Lord, more rules? Where does it stop? Can I want to go because I have to want to go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay. Do whatever you want.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, but now, wait. Do whatever I want? Or whatever I have to want?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, for God’s sake, just come to the play.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right. I don’t want to, but at least that makes sense.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You know, I haven’t seen Raj in several days. Is he no longer a part of our social group? And if so, should we be interviewing for a replacement? Perhaps, this time, we go Latin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>He’s just decided he’s never leaving his apartment again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, brilliant. I’ve been itching to pull that trigger.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>He’s upset because he can’t get anywhere with women.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Would it help if I gave him some pointers? I’m just funnin’ ya.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Girl</speaker><content>Hi. I don’t know if you remember me, but I was here the other night at your party.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Oh, yeah, you left with Raj.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Girl</speaker><content>Uh, yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You’re the one? Okay, let me tell you something. That guy you blew off happens to be my best friend. Okay? He was devastated.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Girl</speaker><content>Sorry. Can you just give him this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Okay. But I gotta warn you, Raj is a proud, passionate man. If you go running out on him again, you’re only gonna get, like, three or four more chances before you are history.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Come on, she came back. This is good news. You should celebrate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I don’t want to celebrate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Not even a little? I mean, we could have a pants party. Go put some on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Why would I want her number? I don’t want anything to do with this woman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, come on, Raj.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No, you don’t get it. I want nothing to do with any woman. My heart is stone. From now on, I’m a monk. I renounce all worldly pleasures. Except for lobster. And garlic butter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Boy, I want to tell you it’s her loss, but you are not making it easy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You’re, you’re a good friend for trying to help, but, I’ve made my choice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>All right. Well, I’ll see you around.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>See you. No, wait, take her number. I don’t want the temptation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I must be strong so I don’t stray from my true purpose, the study of the universe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>All right. Thanks for ruining lobster for me.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Wait! Give me the number! Give me the number! Give me the number!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>So, Amy, what’s going on with your addiction study?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sadly, I’m no longer associated with that project.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Why? What happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Typical bureaucratic nonsense. You can get animals addicted to a harmful substance, you can dissect their brains, but you throw their own faeces back at them and suddenly you’re unprofessional.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m sorry. That I asked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right, let’s get this stupid play over with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh, hang on. Empty your pockets.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You know why. The Nintendo DS. And the PSP. Now the Gameboy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Aw, for Pete’s sake. Can we go now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, is that all of it?  Just set it down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Just so you know, this is not a stupid play. A Streetcar Named Desire is an American classic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It’s about streetcars? Oh, great. I won’t need this. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Just a sec. Oh, who says just a sec? I hate myself. Hello.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Girl</speaker><content>Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Uh, would you like to come in?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Girl</speaker><content>Oh, no, I can’t stay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Girl</speaker><content>I just wanted to say, I’m sorry for running out of the coffee shop. That wasn’t cool. So, uh, yeah. I’m sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Wait. Can you at least tell me what went wrong? It’s okay. I can take anything. Unless it’s something I did, or said, or am. ‘Cause those are, like, my buttons.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>Girl</speaker><content>No, it’s not any of that. It’s just, I kind of have a hard time around people I don’t know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Really? Then what were you doing at the comic book store that night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>Girl</speaker><content>I’ve been trying to force myself into situations that I’m not comfortable with. I saw the flyer in the store window, and I made myself go in. I don’t even like comic books.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yeah, me neither.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>Girl</speaker><content>Then what were you doing there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I lied. I love them. I only said that so you’d go out with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>Girl</speaker><content>Oh, you don’t want to do that. I’m kind of broken.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>That’s great. I’m broken, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-16"><speaker>Girl</speaker><content>Oh, no, you’re not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, I totally am. If it wasn’t for this beer, I couldn’t even talk to you right now. I’m a wreck. There are many things seriously wrong with me. And not quirks, either. Like, diagnosable psychological problems. Maybe brain damage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-18"><speaker>Girl</speaker><content>Well, how do I know you’re not just saying that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-19"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Go out with me on one date, and I promise you, you’ll see.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-20"><speaker>Girl</speaker><content>Okay. Text me. Bye.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-21"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You won’t regret it. I’m the most pathetic guy you’ve ever met. And that, boys and girls, is how it’s done.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Penny (as Blanche DuBois) </speaker><content>You love her very much, don’t you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Actor (as Mitch)</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I think you have a great capacity for devotion. You’ll be lonely when she passes on, won’t you? I understand what that is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>Actor</speaker><content>To be lonely?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>She’s pretty good, huh?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>She is. But when do they get to the part about streetcars?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>Penny (as Blanche)</speaker><content>…when I was a very young girl. When I was 16 years old, I made the discovery, love. All at once, and much, much too completely. It was like you suddenly turned a blinding light on something that had always been half a shadow. That’s how it struck the world for me. But I was unlucky. Deluded.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>She’s remarkable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>She really is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Our Penny’s a star.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>How can she remember all those lines, but as a waitress, she can’t remember no tomato on my hamburger?</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>