<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Ira Flatow</speaker><content>This is Science Friday. I’m Ira Flatow. My guest today is responsible for the discovery of the first stable super-heavy element. Welcome, Dr. Sheldon Cooper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Thank you. Uh, the university made me come here. I didn’t want to. Uh, big fan of the show.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Ira</speaker><content>So, I understand that you actually discovered this element by mistake.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Ira</speaker><content>And some people in the science community are calling it The Wonder Blunder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Who? Give me their names. I bet it’s Wolowitz.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Ira</speaker><content>It’s just such a fascinating story. Your calculations are way off, but they find the element anyway. It’s like misreading a treasure map and still finding the treasure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Can we talk about something else? Do you know that I yodel?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Ira</speaker><content>That’s interesting, but this could be taking you down the path toward a Nobel Prize. And in chemistry, no less. And wouldn’t that be unusual? Because you’re a physicist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes, yes, I’d be a physicist with a Nobel in chemistry. Everyone laugh at the circus freak. You know, I don’t need to sit here and take this, Flatow. It is because of bullies like you, every day more and more Americans are making the switch to television.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>President Seibert, I don’t know why you’re yelling. You’re the one who made me go on the radio. I was expecting a professional science interview, not an attack by some morning zoo shock jock. Well, if the university needs money so badly, perhaps you should start a swear jar. Whoa, that one’s worth a dollar.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I know you don’t like it, but every time you do an interview, it raises the profile of the university. That translates to funding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, well, I’m not just some trained monkey dancing for coins.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Of course you’re not. People love trained monkeys.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>How can you not be happy? You’re tall, thin and famous. Oh, my God, I’m jealous of Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Look, you’re gonna be doing this stuff for a while. You’re just gonna have to find a way to get used to it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>But none of you know what this is like. Being celebrated for something you wish you never did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Mmm, you clearly haven’t been with me at Mardi Gras.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Want to pause the video game and help me clean up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I am cleaning up. Look at the mess the Joker made of Gotham City.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Come on, it’s your friend who’s coming to stay here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Raj grew up in India. Trust me, he’s seen worse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Howie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I promise I’ll help out the rest of the week.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>The rest of the week? You said it was just gonna be a night or two.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, but if I told you a week, would you have said yes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Then you left me no choice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I love Raj, but that’s a long time for a house guest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I know, but they’re tenting his building. He can’t find a hotel he likes that allows dogs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>He’s bringing Cinnamon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>For a whole week, the nerve of some people.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Here comes the Embarrassment Express. With stops at Fraudville, Wonder Blunderberg, and Kansas City. Because it’s a hub.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon, can I come in?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Do you have cookies?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Good. I don’t deserve cookies. Come in. Wil?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Wil Wheaton</speaker><content>Hey, Sheldon. It’s been a while.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Why are you here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Wil</speaker><content>Amy said you were having a rough time, and I thought maybe we could talk. Is that okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Certainly. Although, right now, I’m having a rough time because there’s three people in my room, and it’s starting to feel like a discotheque.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon, you said you were unhappy getting attention for something you wished you never did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Wil</speaker><content>Yeah, I know a little something about that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, nonsense, Wil. Your endless tweets are not that bad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Wil</speaker><content>I remember why it’s been a while. Sheldon, I was actually talking about when I was a kid on Star Trek.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>How could you not like getting attention for playing Wesley Crusher? You were wonderful. A know-it-all boy genius with an eidetic memory. Who couldn’t relate to that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Wil</speaker><content>Well, not everybody felt that way. A lot of people really hated the character, and some of them hated me because of it. I would do interviews, and people would be mean to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That just happened to me. Next time you’re stuck for a tweet, feel free to say what a jerk Ira Flatow is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon, the point is Wil learned to embrace that part of his life and moved on to bigger and better things.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>Wil</speaker><content>Yeah, I’m an author now, I do public speaking, and I have my own Web series about board games.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Uh, we’re trying to cheer him up, so…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-20"><speaker>Wil</speaker><content>I’m just saying that there was a time when I thought I would never get out of Wesley Crusher’s shadow. But now, it’s just one small part of a pretty great life, and it’s a part that I’m happy is there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I do see what you’re saying. That helps.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-22"><speaker>Wil</speaker><content>Good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Would you two like to stay and play trains with me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-24"><speaker>Wil</speaker><content>Sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-25"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-26"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, great, now, I work the controls, I say all aboard. You sit quietly and watch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-27"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You should probably go.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You’re gonna brush your teeth on my couch?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No, I’m gonna brush Cinnamon’s teeth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Why bother? She spends half the time licking her butt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>And the other half licking my face. That’s why I’m brushing her teeth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Hey, guys. Sorry I’m so late. Did you already have dinner?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No, we were waiting for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Aw, that’s so sweet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah. So what do you feel like making?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Howard, the poor thing just got home from work. Let me get you a glass of wine. I’ll cook dinner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Bermadette</speaker><content>Oh, Raj, you’re our guest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Don’t be silly. Sit. You look like you’ve had a long day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No, she always looks like that. Because she married an idiot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Thank you, Raj.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Please, this is my way of thanking you for letting me stay here. Now, tell us all about your day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Okay, um, well, first, I was late to a meeting ’cause I was stuck in traffic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Well, I keep telling you to put that traffic app on your phone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Hey, when you got home today complaining that you felt sick from eating too many jelly beans, did I tell you how to fix it? No. I said, aw, that must hurt, and I rubbed your belly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-18"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I thought of you the whole time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-19"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>All I’m saying is there’s a time to just listen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-20"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-21"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>There’s also a time to stop eating too many jelly beans. And it’s when you’re ten.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hello, President Siebert. Thank you for taking my call. I just wanted you to know that you can now expect enthusiastic participation from me regarding my discovery. Oh, no, no, no, no. No need to thank mNo, thank my friend, Wil Wheaton. For your information, I have nine friends, hmm? Ten if we include you. Nine it is. Ah, it’s ten. I’ll count Wolowitz. Hello, friend Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey, you’re in a good mood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m in a great mood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, you’re about to be in an even better one. I didn’t want to say anything until I knew for sure, but, I’ve been re-running the tests on your element in my lab and I disproved it. Your element does not exist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, but what about the Chinese research team? They found it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, it turns out someone added simulated signals to the data files. They faked the results.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Really?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yes. Do you know what that means? That means all of this attention that you hate goes away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>So no more interviews?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, it’s all over.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I can’t believe it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, you’re welcome.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You robbed me of my greatest achievement.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m back down to nine friends. Make it eight, I’m sick of Wolowitz, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I, I don’t understand. All you’ve done since you discovered this stupid element was complain. I was trying to make you happy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>By taking away my only claim to fame? Well, if you wanted to make me happy, you could have told me a joke. Or shown me a cute video of a koala and an otter becoming unlikely friends.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, there is no winning with you. And koalas and otters don’t even live near each other.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s what makes their friendship unlikely,</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-20"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey, what’s with all the yelling?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Leonard disproved my element. Now all the attention is going to go away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-22"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, that’s great. You must be thrilled,</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s it, I’m down to seven friends.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-24"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>He’s counting hobbits and superheroes, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-25"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>When I thought the element was real, I didn’t want it. But now that Leonard made it not exist, I want it more than anything in the world.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-26"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>The, the element never existed. I didn’t take it away, science took it away. Be mad at science.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-27"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Don’t you dare use science against me. Science is my best friend. Oh, good, I’m back up to eight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-28"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Will you tell him he’s out of his mind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-29"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Actually, I get what he’s saying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-30"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, yes, nine. Welcome back, buddy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-31"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>It’s like if you’re dating someone you’re not that into, and then they break up with you and then you want them more than ever.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-32"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I have no idea what she’s talking about, but we’re ganging up on you so I agree.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-33"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, Sheldon, what do you want me to do, hide the information? If I don’t publish it, it’s just a matter of time before someone else does.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-34"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, no, of course you have to publish. That’s your responsibility as a scientist. Doing otherwise would be unethical. You have no choice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-35"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Fine, I’ll publish.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-36"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Can you believe this guy?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Aw! Raj did the dishes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>How do you know I didn’t do them?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Because once, when all the knives were dirty, you cut a bagel with your keys.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Good morning, everybody. I picked up coffee while I was out. Bernadette, here’s your soy peppermint mocha.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Aw, you didn’t have to do that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, my pleasure, and don’t worry about your presentation today. You’re gonna be great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, you’re gonna knock it out of the park.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>What presentation do I have today?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Just go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>He loves you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What are you doing? Are you trying to make me look bad?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I’m just being a good house guest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No, you’re being a better husband than I am. Doing the dishes, getting coffee, knowing about her life, who does that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, come on, I brought you one, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I don’t want coffee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>That’s why I got you hot chocolate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Give me that. Just stop showing me up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Howard, listen to me. You’re a great husband. Yes, your listening skills could use some work. But it’s amazing how far you’ve come given that you’re an only child raised by an over-protective mom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Um, is this getting weird?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-20"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Hang on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-21"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>So, yes.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey. I just wanted to let you know that I, I posted my findings.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I saw. And I just posted a retraction of my paper. Now the whole scientific community knows I was wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>These things happen all the time, Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Not to me. The only other retraction I ever had to issue was when I was seven and I conceded that my brother was the greatest ninja in East Texas. But that was just a ploy to get my face out of his armpit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Barry</speaker><content>Thew he is. It’s my favowite superhewo, the Wetwactor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Come on, don’t give him a hard time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Barry</speaker><content>I’m sowwy, Cooper. I wetwact it. By the way, Hofstadter, nice job dispwoving the Chinese team.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It’s not a big deal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Barry</speaker><content>It’s a huge deal. Cooper, maybe physics just isn’t your thing. Have you ever considered a caweer in wetail? That way you could take things back for a wiving.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, Barry, that’s enough.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, no, no, that’s okay. I can fight my own battles. Isn’t that right, Bawwy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Barry</speaker><content>Is? Is that a wefewence to my speech impediment? That’s pwetty hurtful. I, I can’t contwol it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You’re right, That was uncalled for. I take it back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Barry</speaker><content>Of course you do. Because you’re the Wetwactor.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Raj, this dinner was amazing. If you’re here much longer, I’m gonna have to buy bigger clothes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Nonsense. You need a little fattening up. You’ve been looking too skinny lately.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Aw. Howie, how come you never say anything sweet like that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What are you talking about? Remember last week, when I asked you if you were wearing Spanx and you weren’t? How’s that different?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Maybe you could try being more thoughtful, like your friend Raj.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, well, maybe you could try being more like Raj.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Oh, really?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, yeah. He packed me a lunch this morning. And there was a note inside that said go get ’em.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Like I don’t do enough around here. Now I need to pack your lunch? And by the way, why do you need a note telling you to go get ’em? You’re a grown man, you should know to go get ’em.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I do know to go get ’em, but sometimes it’s nice to have emotional support when I’m going and getting them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Hey, hey, do you hear yourselves? Let’s just, you know, all calm down and take a step back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>This is stupid. Why are we fighting?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I don’t know. I guess I was just feeling like I’m a lousy husband.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>You’re not a lousy husband. You’re a great husband. I was the one feeling like a lousy wife.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Are you kidding? You’re the best. I know what the problem is. It’s him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, what did I do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You made us feel like we’re not trying hard enough.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Yeah, we were totally fine half-assing our marriage till you showed up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-19"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Look, I’m sorry you’re upset with me, but I just have to say it’s nice to see the two of you on the same page.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-20"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, it does feel good to have you backing me up for once.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-21"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I back you up all the time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-22"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>That is not… he’s doing it again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-23"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>What is wrong with you?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I can’t believe they kicked you out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I can’t believe they’re still married. Oh, no, I forgot Cinnamon’s toothbrush at Howard’s. I guess you’re sharing with Daddy again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Bark once if you need me to call PETA.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What’s that animal doing in our apartment?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, relax, she’s in her crate. She can’t get out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I have two words for you, Jurassic Park. This day just keeps getting worse and worse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You know, if it makes you feel any better…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It probably won’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You’re probably right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon, it’s a beautiful night. Why don’t you and I go for a nice walk together?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, everything is just sex with you isn’t it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Sheldon, I think you might find the support you’re looking for if you realize that relationships are a give and take. She can only be there for you as much as you are for her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Thank you, Rajesh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>And, Amy, you need to be patient with Sheldon, instead of pressuring him to accept intimacy on your terms.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You should probably go.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Ira</speaker><content>I’m Ira Flatow, and this is Science Friday. I’d like to welcome back Dr. Sheldon Cooper, who thought he had discovered a new super-heavy element only to have it disproved by my next guest, Dr. Leonard Hofstadter. Welcome to Science Friday, gentlemen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Thanks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Thank you. Ira, if I may, I’d like to apologize for my behaviour last week.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Ira</speaker><content>It’s all right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Now, isn’t there something you’d like to say to me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Ira</speaker><content>No. Now, Dr. Hofstadter. Can you walk us through the process you used to disprove his theory?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I believe I can answer that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>He asked me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>As I was saying…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You’re telling it wrong. Ira, to really understand the story here, you have to start at the very beginning. A small town in East Texas, where a young genius named…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s right, Sheldon Cooper. He was bitten by his neighbour’s dog, leading to his first scientific breakthrough, the doggie death-ray. Which, sadly, he couldn’t build because Santa wouldn’t bring him enriched uranium.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>Ira</speaker><content>You know, I’d really like to hear it from Dr. Hofstadter, if it’s okay with you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What a surprise. Did you invite me back just so you could ignore me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-17"><speaker>Ira</speaker><content>Actually, I didn’t invite you. You came in, you took a seat, and I’m not comfortable with confrontation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, this interview is supposed to be about me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, that seems like a snooze. Even for public radio.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-20"><speaker>Penny (listening in her apartment)</speaker><content>You know, if we did a shot every time they said something embarrassing, this would be one hell of a drinking game.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-21"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>A little early for alcohol, isn’t it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You know, I don’t just say smart things about science. I also yodel. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-23"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I’ll get the vodka.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>