<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>So what’d you think?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>It was good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s it? Good”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I enjoyed it. When you told me I was going to be losing my virginity, I didn’t think you meant showing me Raiders of the Lost Ark for the first time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>My apologies. I chose my words poorly. I should have said you were about to have your world rocked on my couch. Anyway, thank you for watching it. It’s one of my all-time favourites.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>It was very entertaining despite the glaring story problem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Story problem? You, oh, Amy, what a dewy-eyed moon-calf you are. Raiders of the Lost Ark is the love child of Steven Spielberg and George Lucas, two of the most gifted filmmakers of our generation. I’ve watched it 36 times, except for the snake scene and the face-melting scene, which I can only watch when it’s still light out, but, I defy you to find a story problem. Here’s my jaw, drop it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>All right. Indiana Jones plays no role in the outcome of the story. If he weren’t in the film, it would turn out exactly the same.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, I see your confusion. You don’t understand. Indiana Jones was the one in the hat with the whip.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>No, I do, and if he weren’t in the movie, the Nazis would have still found the ark, taken it to the island, opened it up and all died, just like they did. Let me close that for ya.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hi. I thought you went to the comic book store on Wednesdays.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, but Sheldon and Amy were having date night and they don’t need me there to make it awkward. They have each other for that. So, how was school?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, good. Check it out, The Disappointing Child by Beverly Hofstadter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You bought my mom’s book?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah. It’s on the recommended reading list for my psychology class.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, come on. Not that book. It, it’s got, like, every horrible story from my childhood in it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, cool. Are there pictures?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Seriously, please find another book.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, come on. Why? How bad could it be?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>There, there’s chapters about potty training, and bed-wetting and masturbation. Basically, if something came out of me, she wrote about it. You know what? Do whatever you want, just don’t talk to me about it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Not even the chapter on the breast-feeding crisis?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It was not a crisis. Apparently, I favoured the left one, she got a little lopsided.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, my God, you still go left.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Which celebrity would you say I look like the most?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Halle Berry. Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Stuart and I are putting dating profiles online, and it’s one of the questions. And thank you, I’d kill for that woman’s bone structure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Why are you reading Pride and Prejudice?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’ll tell you why. Amy ruined Raiders of the Lost Ark for me, so now I’m trying to find something beloved to her and ruin that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Because her life wasn’t enough?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Wait, how can, how can anyone ruin Raiders? It’s perfect.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, except for the fact that Indiana Jones is completely irrelevant to the story. With or without him, the Nazis find the ark, open it and die.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>All</speaker><content>Aw!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Hey, wait a minute. No, the Nazis were digging in the wrong place. The only reason they got the ark was because Indy found it first.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Actually, they were only digging in the wrong place because Indy had the medallion. Without him, they would have had the medallion and dug in the right place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>All</speaker><content>Aw!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, I know you don’t want to talk about it, but can I just ask you one question about your mom’s book?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I just want to know why a five-year-old boy puts on his mom’s make-up and wears balloon boobies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>They weren’t boobies, they were muscles. And the make-up was green. I was pretending to be The Hulk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You were wearing her bra.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That was to keep my muscles from sagging. Can we please stop talking about this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, okay. But you know, as a student of psychology who got a check-plus on her first homework assignment, I think, sometimes, it’s good to open up about these things.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, fine. Do you want to know why I dressed like The Hulk? Because I was always mad at my mom and I wanted to smash my way out of that house.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, why were you so angry?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Gee, I don’t know. Maybe it’s because I was always the subject of her little experiments. Did you get to the chapter where she staged the Easter egg hunt with no eggs to see how long I’d keep looking? The answer, by the way, June.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sweetie, I’m so sorry. I wish there was something I could do to make you feel better.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I do, too, but there’s not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Really? Are you sure about that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Of course, who am I to argue with a check-plus student? Just warning you, I’m gonna go right. Don’t make a big deal out of it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Is make-up really necessary?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Well, when someone looks at your dating profile, the first thing they see is your picture. I just want to make sure you look fun and full of life and not like a body they just pulled out of the river. All right, here we go, and smile. Okay, uh-uh, that one’s in the bank. How about this? Turn away, and then turn back into it. But when you do, imagine the camera is the girl you want to meet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>You got it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Okay, uh, let’s try it again. Uh, but this time, pretend the girl you want to meet doesn’t want to hurt you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>I don’t think I can give you that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Come on. One more time. Yeah, it’s, it’s a little blurry, but I think that works in your favour. Do you want a beer?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Sure. Hey, have you finished writing your profile yet?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Almost. Oh, what did you put as the one-word description of yourself?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>I put unobjectionable. But now that I hear it out loud, it just seems like I’m being cocky. What did you put for your best feature?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>My parents’ money. Uh, what did you put for your best feature?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>I put: not applicable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Come on, dude, you’re being too hard on yourself. You’ve got a lot of good stuff going on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Really? Like what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Well, okay, you’re a, you’re a talented artist, you own your own business.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Neither of those things have ever helped me meet a woman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Okay, well, can we imply that you’re well-endowed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>I do have one oddly long testicle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-18"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Okay, now you’re talking like a winner!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Whatcha doin’?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, it turns out Amy’s beloved Pride and Prejudice is a flawless masterpiece. He’s got too much pride, she’s got too much prejudice, it just works.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>So you’re looking to ruin something for her in the funny pages?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Amy has a fondness for the comic strip Marmaduke.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Mm-hmm. And?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And I think I’ve got it. Consider, a family possesses a dog that is so large and poorly disciplined, he causes nothing but problems. Why do they keep him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Maybe they fell in love with him as a puppy and didn’t know how big he was gonna be.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Of course. You know, why couldn’t she just like Ziggy? Yeah? That thing’s riddled with plot holes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sorry, buddy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Ooh, I think she’s a fan of Garfield as well. Oh, darn it, now so am I.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’ll see you later. I gotta go watch a stupid football game with Penny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Wait, hang on. You’ve spent time with Amy. Can you think of anything she’s fond of that has a bunch of flaws she hasn’t noticed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I gotta go.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You ready to go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yep. Hey, and maybe this time you don’t try and talk sports with the guys.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Some sports bar. It’s like they never even heard of Quidditch. Do we really have to go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, come on. Every time we’re about to hang out with my friends, you don’t want to. It’s like, It’s too loud, or the bathroom’s too dirty, or they put a chicken wing in my ear. I mean…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, you’re, you’re right. Let’s just go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey, what’s going on with you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Nothing, I’m fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>All right, hang on. is this still about your mom’s book?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No. Not everything is about my mom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>‘Cause if you’re still upset about that, we don’t have to go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Except this is totally about my mom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I’m so sorry. I never should have read that book. You know what? You want to just get dinner and watch the game here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That sounds nice. Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Or, you know, we could get take-out and watch the Blu-ray extended version of The Hobbit movie with commentary track. On account of how sad I am about my mom.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Leonard, you ready for lunch?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>One sec. Hey. Sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Hi, Penny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hi. All right, sweetie. You hang in there today.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’ll try, but I might be sad again tonight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Wow. Sex at work?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Leave it alone. That’s my girlfriend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Who just had sex with me at work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Damn. How’d you swing that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, whenever I talk about how awful my mom was, Penny will do anything to make me feel better.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Seriously?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Look, I mean, I’m not proud of it, but it does work. I got her to watch a six-part documentary on Monty Python. Even I was bored, I just wanted to see if she’d make it to the end.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You sound kind of proud of it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I am, I’m really proud.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Amy (on webcam)</speaker><content>Hello, Sheldon. Is everything okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes. Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Well, the last time you made an unscheduled video-chat, there was a curly fry in your regular fries and you thought someone might be trying to slip you a mickey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>April 13, a dark night, indeed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>So what can I do for you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m calling to invite you to a spontaneous date night tomorrow evening.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Really?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes. You were kind enough to watch Raiders of the Lost Ark with me. So I’d like to return the favour by inviting you to watch an episode of your favourite childhood television series, Little House on the Prairie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>That sounds lovely. Why are you rubbing your hands together?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Um, I’m putting on lotion. Are you in or not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Of course I’m in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Excellent. Then I shall see you tomorrow. Good night, Dr. Fowler.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Good night, Dr. Cooper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Good night, indeed. What a rube. Why would I put on lotion when I have such soft hands?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>You were really quiet during dinner. Is everything okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah. I guess I was just thinking about my mom, and how sad my childhood was.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Yeah, I bet it sucked. I’m gonna take a bath, you do the dishes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>How about I take a bath with you and see what happens.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Here’s what’s gonna happen. I’m gonna take a bath, and you’re gonna do the dishes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>That’s it? No compassion?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Aw, poor Howie. We good? I’m gonna take a bath.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Bernie…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>God, what is going on with you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’m sharing my pain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>And I’m not buying it. Try again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’m learning to be a man in a culture where it’s increasingly difficult to know how?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Bermadette</speaker><content>Strike two.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’m copying Leonard. When he does this to Penny, they have sex and watch Monty Python.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Howard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I know. It was dumb, I shouldn’t have done it. And it’s making me feel sad. So sad. You know, why don’t you take a bath? I’ll do the dishes.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Three, two, one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>That’s it. Our dating profiles are live on the Internet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Attention all shoppers, my business is open for business!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>That’s right, ladies. For all you know, I’m confident and fun to be around.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, cool, it tells you when someone’s reading your profile. Jenny309. I hope that’s not her weight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>If it is, I’ll take her. Ooh, I got one, too. The ladies are coming to us. Oh, man, if I’d started this years ago, I’d be divorced two or three times by now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>What? Another one. You know, it, it’s weird. When they’re reading your profile, does it, does it make you feel exposed? Like they see you naked?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Well, they’re not running away screaming, so, no.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I love Little House. It made me want to live on a farm so much I tried to milk my cat. That tangy bowl of Cheerios was not worth the stitches.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, you sit back, relax and enjoy a beloved childhood memory. You see that cabin there? I read they were illegally squatting on Indian land. Yeah. Personally, I think what we did to the Native Americans was wrong, but this is your favourite show, not mine. Oh, look at little Laura Ingalls, eating that peanut butter sandwich. Peanut butter? Huh? That’s strange, since peanut butter wasn’t introduced until the early 1900s. If I knew this show was about time travel, I would have watched it much sooner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You’re trying to get back at me for what I said about Raiders of the Lost Ark.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s silly. Almost as silly as Dr. Baker having a telephone, since telephones only existed in large cities at that time. This is more like Little House on the Preposterous.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon, we’re in a relationship. When you get angry, just tell me. You don’t need to seek revenge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Are you sure? Every time my dad stayed out all night, my mom would put hamster poop in his chewing tobacco.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Well, that’s not how we’re going to do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Fine. I’m mad at you. Not only did you ruin Raiders for me, you may have ruined the whole franchise. Except for the fourth one, which was bad before you got your mitts on it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I shouldn’t have said it. I’m sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Do you feel better?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes. But not as good as I’m going to when I tell you that your precious Garfield has no reason to hate Mondays. He’s a cat. He doesn’t have a job.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey, I was just… what is happening?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, just a little treat. I know you’ve been feeling really bad about your mom lately.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, oh, I have. So bad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>And I wanted to make you feel better, so I planned something very special for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh-huh, I can already feel it working.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>Mrs Hofstadter (on webcam)</speaker><content>Hello, Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Mom?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>Mrs Hofstadter</speaker><content>I understand you have been whining about my parenting in order to emotionally manipulate your girlfriend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I… uh…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Bernadette told me everything. Now you don’t get the left or the right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>Mrs Hofstadter</speaker><content>Let’s discuss why you continue to involve me in your sex life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, please, Mommy. No, Mommy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-13"><speaker>Mrs Hofstadter</speaker><content>When you were six years old, you walked in on me and your father naked. I was swatting his bottom with your brand new Ping Pong paddle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I didn’t dream that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-15"><speaker>Mrs Hofstadter</speaker><content>How did that make you feel?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Penny, come back. I’m sad for real now.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>In the last two hours, 162 women have read our profiles. How many of them have sent us messages?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Combined?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Zero.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Dude, this is, this is brutal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>I don’t think I’ve ever felt so rejected. And I had a rescue dog who ran back to the pound.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>This is the worst. If we’re gonna get shot down, we might as well just go to a bar and do it old school.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>And make them look us in the eye.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yeah, anything is better than this.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Hello.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>Girl</speaker><content>Not interested.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I was wrong. This is worse.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Wait, wait, if it wasn’t for Indiana Jones, the ark would never have ended up at the warehouse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s true. He collected and delivered the ark to the proper authorities for filing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Like a hero.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>All</speaker><content>Yeah!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Although, technically, Indy was supposed to take the ark to a museum to be studied. He couldn’t even get that done.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>All</speaker><content>Aw!</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>