<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What are you working on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Can’t talk. In the zone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Do you know what he’s doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Could be anything. Last time he was like this, he figured out electron transport in graphene. The time before that, he was making a list of who’s allowed in his tree fort if fe ever gets one. Still can’t believe I didn’t make the cut.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Uh, Sheldon, you want to take a break? Your food’s ready.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, no, what are you doing? He’s both happy and quiet. It’s like seeing a unicorn and Bigfoot at the same time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Sorry we’re so late. Bernadette got stuck at work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Great news. A raccoon virus just crossed the species barrier and now can infect humans.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Why is that great news?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>In the pharmaceutical business we have a saying, mo’ infections, mo’ money.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Wait, Maybe you want to wash your little raccoon hands first.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Oh, calm down. If I had it, I’d be dead already.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Guys, listen up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Can’t listen, zone. Also don’t care.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Next week is the anniversary of my first date with Bernadette.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Really don’t care.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I want to do something special, and I was hoping you guys could be a part of it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Aw, what horrible thing are you trying to make up for?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Just putting something in the bank for what horrible thing I do next.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-20"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Ah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-21"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Look, she’s gonna be back any second, so here’s the deal. I’m writing a song, and I was hoping we could all play it for her together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-22"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Aw.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-23"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Oh, I love that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-24"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>That is so beautiful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-25"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Sheldon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-26"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>When did we get to the Cheesecake Factory?</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It’s really sweet what Howard wants to do for Bernadette.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah. Hey, how come you’ve never done anything romantic to celebrate our first date?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, for starters, you’ve broken up with me so many times, which first date are we talking about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Ooh, somebody call the burn ward. And back to the zone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>And besides, I do romantic things for you all the time. Can you even name one romantic thing you’ve done for me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I can name tons.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sex doesn’t count.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh. I know, what about that bed-and-breakfast?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, I took you there. All you did was…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I know what I did. I bet they had to throw out that rocking chair. You know, I can be romantic if I want to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It’s fine. And also not true.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, just you wait and see. I’m gonna romance your freakin’ ass off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That’s beautiful. Is that Shakespeare?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sheldon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Zone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>He’ll figure it out when he falls off the roof.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, I know you’re in the zone, but do you want some tea? All right, I can’t believe I’m gonna say this, but you haven’t spoken in hours and I’m starting to get worried. Please say something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Leonard, prepare to be humbled and weep at the glory of my genius.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Nope, it was better before.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Look at it. I feel like my mind just made a baby. And it’s beautiful. It’s not like human babies, which are loud and covered in goop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Holy crap, Sheldon, did you just figure out a method for synthesizing a new stable super-heavy element?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Did I? Well, that can’t be right. No one’s ever done that before. Except me, because I just did it. Sheldon and his brain, yeah. Sheldon and his brain, yeah. Sheldon and his brain, yeah. Sheldon and his brain, yeah. Sheldon and his brain…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, definitely better before.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>So I’m almost done writing the song for Bernadette. Are you cool playing the cello?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>If by cool you mean willing to, yes. If by cool you mean cool, clearly you’ve never seen me play the cello.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Great. Will you play the ukulele?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Of course. I’d be happy to shred it on my ax.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Or you could just play your tiny, ridiculous guitar.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Fine. I will melt her heart. And her face.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Gentlemen. Uh, no doubt you heard about my little breakthrough. Now, if your plan is to hoist me on your shoulders and carry me around the cafeteria, please refrain. I don’t care for heights, motion sickness or the thought of your necks touching my buttocks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Seriously, congratulations, Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yeah, I read your paper online. That technique for creating a new heavy element is inspired.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, well, thank you. Believe it or not, I just learned a Chinese research team at the Hubei Institute for Nuclear Physics ran a test on a cyclotron, and the results were extremely promising.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, that’s incredible.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, I know. They called it the greatest thing since the Communist party. Although I’m pretty sure that the Communist party made them say that. I like China. See, they know how to keep people in line.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>So, what happens next?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, more testing, more success, more fame. Yeah, but don’t worry, I will remain the same down-to-earth humble Joe I’ve always been.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Good to know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Now give me that cookie, I discovered an element.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Thank you so much for coming.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You called the right person. I believe I have the perfect romantic evening for you to give Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, good, ’cause I’ve been really struggling with this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>As I’m sure you’re aware, the quickest way to a man’s heart is through his…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Pants, but Leonard says sex doesn’t count.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh. You poor thing. You have one arrow in your quiver, and you just can’t use it. Fortunately, another pathway to a man’s heart is through his stomach.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I don’t know if I want to cook for him. He’s kind of a picky eater. I mean, it’s too salty, it’s too dry, it’s too burnt and frozen at the same time. Okay, come on, what else would sweep you off your feet?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Well, I’ve always had this fantasy that involves dancing. The sexual chemistry between my partner and me is electric. But boy, oh, boy, does my father not approve until he sees us in the big dance competition.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, that’s just the plot for Dirty Dancing. What else would you love? Other than being lifted over Patrick Swayze’s head.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, oh, uh, you could, uh, stand outside his window with a boom box in the air.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>That’s from Say Anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Look, I’m a lonely guy, I watch a lot of movies. Look, Penny, if you truly want to be romantic, it needs to come from you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I get that, but why is this so hard?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Well, you’ve probably never had to do this stuff ’cause you’re young and beautiful and men have always thrown themselves at you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, I’m trying to be sad about that. I can’t.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Let’s see, what’s next? Okay, here. This is the Magic Marker I was using when I made the discovery.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I don’t think the Smithsonian’s gonna want your marker.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And that’s why you’re not on a list for my tree fort. Ooh, guess who’s getting an article written about him in Physics Today? I’ll give you a hint. You measured the diameter of his suspicious mole yesterday.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon, I’m so proud of you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, you should be. My discovery is spreading like wildfire. Unlike my mole, which is holding steady at the size of a navy bean.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>What’s next?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>This is the very copy of The Handbook of Chemistry and Physics in which I looked up the reaction rates of mendelevium and…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>And what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No. No, no, no, no.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>What’s wrong?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’ve made a horrible mistake.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>What are you talking about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>This table, it’s in square centimetres. I read it as square metres. You know what that means?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>That Americans can’t handle the metric system?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Amy, I was off by a factor of 10,000.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>But the Chinese team found the element.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, well, they shouldn’t have. My calculations were wrong. There must be some resonance between the elements I didn’t know about.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-18"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>So you just got lucky?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Sheldon Cooper does not get lucky.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-20"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You and me both, brother. It doesn’t matter. The element was found because of you, and that’s groundbreaking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What matters is the greatest scientific achievement of my life is based on a blunder. I’m not a genius, I’m a fraud.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-22"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You know, Sheldon, in neuroscience, we’re forever finding something in one part of the brain that we thought was someplace else.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, great. Now I’m worse than a fraud. I’m practically a biologist.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You got to stop beating yourself up over this. I mean, you made a mistake, but it was a happy mistake.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>There’s nothing happy about it. I’m being given credit that I don’t deserve.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, people get things they don’t deserve all the time. Look at me with you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, Leonard, this is going to haunt me for the rest of my life. Every science classroom, every periodic table, every textbook, this mistake will be staring back at me. Like that time you let Koothrappali wax your eyebrows. I’ve got to find a way to stop this thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Buddy, I don’t think you can. I mean, once it’s out there, it’s out there. This thing is like the science equivalent of a sex tape.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You know, frankly, I’d prefer a sex tape.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You don’t know what a sex tape is, do you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Make sure you guys get to the restaurant by eight. Bernadette’s meeting me there at eight thirty and I don’t want to blow the surprise.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>We’ll be there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Got it. Now, uh, I have a question about the song. I was thinking at some point I could bust out a little rap.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>E-Ni-Ni-Ni-Ni-No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Come on, come on, you haven’t even heard it yet. Leonard, give me a beat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I will not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, please?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No, I want this to be romantic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>It will be. I don’t call anyone a ho, and the only time I use the phrase my bitch, I’m referring to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Voice</speaker><content>There he is. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Stop it. Stop celebrating me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Voice</speaker><content>Woo!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And no woos. Oh, not you, Dr. Woo. You’re fine. I want you all to know that you have no reason to applaud me. My so-called breakthrough wasn’t the result of my genius. It was nothing more than a boneheaded mistake. So please refrain from praising me for it in the future.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Wait, I don’t understand. They didn’t find the element?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, no, they found the element.  No, no, stop it. I don’t need to take this admiration from the likes of you people. How do I make them stop loving me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Invite them to live with us.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Boy, Bernadette is gonna love this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah. It must be nice to have someone do something so romantic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, you know what’s not romantic? Rubbing it in someone’s face.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Actually, it can be, but I told you sex doesn’t count.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’m getting worried about Bernadette. I’m gonna call and check on her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>The National Science Foundation wants to give me a substantial grant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, that’s a big deal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I know. When will this nightmare end?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey, I get that you feel bad about all the attention, but still, what you did is amazing. We’re really proud of you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I’m not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You’re not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon, I’ve been thinking about it, and you’re right. You don’t deserve any credit. All you did was misread some numbers on a table. A very easy table, too. Honestly, I’m embarrassed for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s the most romantic thing I’ve ever heard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Damn it, everyone’s better at this than me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Congratulations, Dr. Fowler. You just made the fort.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Guys, there was an accident at Bernie’s lab.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, my God, is she okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, but she’s at the hospital in quarantine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-19"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-20"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Poor Bernadette.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, no.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I hate to pile on the bad news, but I just got a raise.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, my God, Bernie, what happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Well, let’s just say the next time you move a dozen vials of raccoon virus to the fridge, make two trips.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You’re sure you’re okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Yeah, it’s just a precaution. If there was a problem, I’d be throwing up out of my eyeballs by now. Sorry I messed up our date.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, don’t worry about it. I brought the date here. Guys, come on in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>What’s all this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Well, tonight is the anniversary of our first date, and I wanted to celebrate it by writing a song for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Howie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon, get over here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>She might be contagious. Don’t you think I’m having a rough enough day?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Howard (singing)</speaker><content>If I didn’t have you, life would be blue, I’d be Dr. Who without the TARDIS.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Is it me, or does she not look so good?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Shh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>A candle without a wick, a Watson without a Crick, I’d be one of my outfits without a dick-ie. I’d be cheese without the mac, Jobs without the Wozniak, I’d be solving exponential equations that use bases not found on your calculator making it much harder to crack. I’d be an atom without a bomb, a dot without the com, and I’d probably still live with my mom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>All</speaker><content>And he’d probably still live with his mom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Ever since I met you, you turned my world around. You supported all my dreams and all my hopes. You’re like uranium-235 and I’m uranium-238, almost inseparable isotopes. I couldn’t have imagined how good my life would get from the moment that I met you Bernadette.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-18"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Oh, Howie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-19"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>If I didn’t have you life would be dreary, I’d be string theory without any string. I’d be binary code without a one, a cathode ray tube without an electron gun. I’d be Firefly, Buffy and Avengers without Joss Whedon. I’d speak a lot more Klingon, Heghlu’meH QaQ jajvam.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-20"><speaker>All</speaker><content>And he’d definitely still live with his mom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-21"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Ever since I met you, you turned my world around. You’re my best friend and my lover. We’re like changing electric and magnetic fields. You can’t have one without the other. I couldn’t have imagined how good my life would get from the moment that I met you, Bernadette.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-22"><speaker>All</speaker><content>Oh, we couldn’t have imagined how good our lives would get from the moment that we met you, Bernadette.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-23"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Howie, that was amazing. Look, I’m shaking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-24"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>She’s sick, I knew it. Bye.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I have to say, this is the best Top Ramen you’ve ever made.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I discovered a secret ingredient. The flavour packet. That sucker is well named. All right, lover boy, get ready, ’cause there is a crap storm of romance coming your way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Stop it, you’re gonna make me cry. All right. You seem pretty confident.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, I am. Maybe if you follow this trail, you’ll see why.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, rose petals.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yes. The most beautiful and shockingly expensive of all the flowers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You made the bed? You really are pulling out all the stops.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, I gave this a lot of thought, and I finally found something to show you how much I love you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, wow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>It’s a first edition of Hitchhiker’s Guide to the Galaxy. I remember it was your favourite book growing up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>This is great. It, thank you, it’s, so much.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Nothing. I love it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No. Something’s going on. What’s wrong with it? I remember you saying how great it would be to have a first edition.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It’s true, I did. I did say that. When we were at the used bookstore together and I saw the first edition and I bought it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, my God, I am the worst.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, no, it’s okay. It’s really thoughtful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-18"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, it’s not. I mean, what’s thoughtful is everything you do. Here, you know what? Look at this. Look, here’s the, the plane ticket you bought me when I was too poor to go home for the holidays. And the rose you left on my windshield just because. Here’s the, the thank-you letter you wrote me after the first time I slept with you. All 11 pages of it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I can’t believe you saved all this stuff.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-20"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Of course I did. It’s you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Come here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-22"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-23"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Is that a pregnancy test?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-24"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, yeah, just the first one. I didn’t save them all.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I can’t believe I read this table wrong. I blame you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Me? What did I do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You distract me. I’ve been distracted since the moment I met you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, you should be. Because all I can think about is how much I want to kiss you. And not just on the cheek, but on the mouth. Like mommies and daddies do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Oh, Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Sheldon (not in Amy’s daydream, now in the Cheesecake Factory)</speaker><content>Amy? Amy? Did you hear what I said?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Can’t talk, in the zone.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>