<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hello. I’m Doctor Sheldon Cooper, and welcome to Sheldon Cooper presents Fun with Flags, the final episode flagtacular. I knew it was coming. Still scary. Now, I’m sure you’re thinking, the final episode? Who will stand between us and flag ignorance?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I know I was thinking that. Is this a show on flags or mind reading?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>But the truth is I can no longer balance a full-time career, a popular Internet show, and a girlfriend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>And he really does have one, you jerks on the comment board.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>So as they say, all good things must come to an end.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>After only 232 episodes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>233 if we include the one somebody forgot to press record on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You said you weren’t gonna bring that up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And you said you pressed record. Anyway, please sit back, relax, and join us as we take our final lap, as indicated by the waving of this racing flag. And, of course, white flags can also represent surrender, the Stewards of Gondor, and the Japanese Minamoto clan, but I’m sure you remember that from episode sixty-two, White Flags, Who’s Wavin’ ‘Em and Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>That was a good one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It was so good.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You know, I thought cleaning out a dead professor’s office was gonna just be boring, but then I found his dentures and realized it’s also gross.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Doesn’t Professor Abbott’s family want any of this stuff?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t think he had a family.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>That’s rough.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I know. You can spend your whole life working, and at the end all that’s left are some papers in a box.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Makes you think. Oh, well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey. Hey, we’re supposed to look through all this stuff before we throw it away in case it’s important.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I did. It’s all outdated or disproved.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I don’t know. This old pen kind of proves gravity. When I tilt it, her bathing suit falls right off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, my dad used to have a pen like that. I dated it all through sixth grade.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It still feels weird just throwing away his work like this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Don’t feel bad. Someday someone will be throwing out your work, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That someone was Sheldon, and the day was yesterday. Hey, look at this. Dear Roger, to be opened upon your first great discovery. Love, Mom. Wow, look at the date. He saved this fifty years and never got to open it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>That’s intense.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Poor Roger Abbott.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Roger Abbott sounds just like Roger Rabbit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Roger Abbott, Roger Abbott, Roger Abbott. Oh, my God, Leonard, I know he’s dead, but try it. It’s fun. Roger Abbott, Roger Abbott.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>Penny. Oh, my rookie of the year.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, Dan. My boss who didn’t want to hire me and now’s a little hug machine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>Oh, look at you. Brand-new and already the third best sales rep.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Aw.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>Yes. Why don’t you come over to my table.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I’ll be right there. Bernadette’s just parking the car.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>Oh, good. Bernadette. Cute, sweet, vicious little Bernadette.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Come on. She’s not that bad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>Oh, yeah? At the company picnic she yelled at me and my grandson for losing the three-legged race. I mean, he still calls her that mean kid with the big boobies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I know she can be a little intense, but, I swear, she is so sweet once you get past all the…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Hey, what are you talking about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh. We were just talking about how much we love working with you. Isn’t that right? Dan?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Over the years here at Fun With Flags, we’ve had an opportunity to learn, laugh, wonder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>And, yes, even shed a tear or two.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Like when you do a two-hour Fourth of July spectacular and it doesn’t get recorded.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>How many times do I have to say I’m sorry?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>How about four thousand. One for every domino I set up to make that American flag. Please enjoy these highlights.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Crikey, what flag do we have today?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Australia, mate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And now it’s time for the speed round of Flag or Not a Flag.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>Fwag, fwag, not a fwag, fwag, I am cwushing this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Say, Betsy Ross, what you working on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I have no idea. Because the story of me sewing the first American flag is unsupported poppycock.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Then who did sew it, hmm?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Don’t ask me. I’m just a simple seamstress whose descendants are out to make a quick buck.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Fancy a dip, my dear?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Wait, that purple flag indicates that marine pests, such as jellyfish, are present.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Wow, that flag is a lifesaver.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No. This is. Stop looking at my legs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>Kripke</speaker><content>Not a fwag, fwag, fwag, not a fwag. Fwag. Ugh cwap.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>When stuff like this gets me down, you know what I like to do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Sing Hakuna Matata like an eight-year-old girl?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Wrong, smarty-pants. It’s Everything Is Awesome from The Lego Movie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Look at these notebooks. They’re full of pages and pages of data. He clearly spent years on this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Mmm. It’s just columns of random numbers. Toss it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, but what if this was a potential breakthrough for him? What if, what if this is the thing that would’ve finally let him open that bottle of champagne?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Maybe he didn’t know what to pair champagne with. Strawberries, caviar, oysters. All good choices. Yeah, that look right there is why people eat before they come to your parties.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>This has to mean something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Well, there’s no discernible pattern that I can see, but it shouldn’t be too hard to run the numbers and check.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, maybe we can get some time on the supercomputer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Sure. We could try multiple regressions with varying physical and experimental constants.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, we could run a pattern-matching algorithm against well-known unsolved physics problems.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Ooh, it might be a substitution cipher. We could start with basic cryptanalysis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Or we could talk to this guy he used to share an office with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, let’s do that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Because you don’t know how to do cryptanalysis, do you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, I’m not even sure if it’s the right word.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>So, Dan, you have a grandson. How old is he?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>Seven.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Oh, yeah. I remember him from the picnic. He was the one crying like a wuss the whole time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I heard he was being picked on by a mean kid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Just builds character. Like my dad said, nobody likes a crybaby except their mommies and Democrats.”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>I need another drink.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>What’s his problem?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, I don’t know. Maybe he didn’t like the fact that you called his grandson a wuss.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Well, I didn’t think you were supposed to say sissy anymore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, look, I know what a good person you are, but sometimes people think you might come off a little harsh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>What? I’m, like, the sweetest person I know. Look at me. I should be in a tree baking cookies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yes, but once in a while, people think you’re a little mean.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Oh, yeah? You one of those people?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No. No, no, no. I think the cookie thing.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Action.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Welcome back. Our guest today is a returning fan favourite. He puts the reading in your rainbow, the Geordi in your La Forge, and the Kunta in your Kinte, Mr. LeVar Burton.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>LeVar Burton</speaker><content>Thank you, Sheldon. Now, remember our deal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You do this, I delete your contact information.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>LeVar</speaker><content>While?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>While you watch me do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>LeVar</speaker><content>Great. Happy to be back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, since you’re here, I’d like to get your opinion on something. In honour of Black History Month, I portrayed George Washington Carver in a loving tribute that my roommate called wildly racist. What do you think?  Hi. My name is George.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>LeVar</speaker><content>Oh, hell, no.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You heard him, Leonard. No, it’s not racist.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Are we sure this is the place?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>The doorman said this is the right building.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I think if you’re pulling up your pants, you’re not a doorman. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Man (off)</speaker><content>Who is it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh, I’ve been looking for a Professor Sharpe?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Prof Sharpe</speaker><content>Hold on. Can I help you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hi. We’re from the university. We’re trying to get some information about Professor Abbott.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>We were cleaning out his office and found these books full of numbers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Any chance you know what it is?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Prof Sharpe</speaker><content>Yes, he was always working on this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I was thinking it might be some sort of interstellar coordinate system, maybe an updated version of Hubble’s law. I keep seeing the number 90 repeating. That could be the angle of perturbation of a distant galaxy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Prof Sharpe</speaker><content>It’s the number of calories in a yoghurt. That’s his food diary.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Really?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Prof Sharpe</speaker><content>Yeah, he wrote down everything he ever ate. He was convinced that calorie restriction was the key to living forever.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Does it work?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Seriously?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Well, he could have been hit by a bus. You don’t know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>Prof Sharpe</speaker><content>Sorry it’s not more interesting. On the bright side, you didn’t have to listen to his stomach growl for 35 years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>So, was there anything that Professor Abbott worked on during his life that came close to an accomplishment?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-20"><speaker>Prof Sharpe</speaker><content>To be honest, his research never amounted to anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-21"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You were his colleague. How did your research turn out? Great. Hey, this is the apartment you get when you win a Nobel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-22"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Well, you could be very frugal. I’m getting a little tired of everybody’s sarcasm.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I’m not a bully. I mean, maybe I come off a little strong, but that’s only because my dad raised me to be tough and not to take crap from anybody.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No. That’s fine, but there’s a difference between being tough and telling your friend her new pants look like a saggy diaper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I did say that, didn’t I?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, you did. I felt so self-conscious, I had to return them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Where? To Babies R Us?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You’re doing it again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Okay, sorry. Can we just go? I feel like everybody hates me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, come on, they don’t hate you, all right? They’re just a little intimidated. All you need to do is show everyone how sweet you really are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I think I’d rather go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, come on. You are not going anywhere, all right? I am here for you, and we are gonna fix this together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Even though your dress is ugly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, my little flag-keteers, it looks like the last episode of Fun with Flags is at an end. If I could, I would run each and every one of you viewers up a flagpole and salute you. And if you touched the ground, burn you. I’d like to take a moment to personally thank Dr. Amy Farrah Fowler, who you may or may not know is the first woman to co-host a flag or banner-related Internet info-tainment show.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Take that, glass ceiling.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And if I may get serious for a moment, hosting this show has been one crazy ride. But with all its ups and downs, I wouldn’t give it up for the world. Except for now, when I’m giving it up. Before I sign off, I’d, uh, I’d like to share with you all one last use for a white flag. It’s good for times like this. Good night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Cut. Sheldon, that was beautiful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>If you didn’t press record…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I pressed it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, that’s it. That’s the end of Roger Abbott.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>And we still don’t know who framed him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I still keep thinking about how an entire life can seemingly amount to nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I guess the sad truth is, not everyone will accomplish something great. Some of us may just have to find meaning in the little moments that make up life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That’s a nice way of looking at it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah for you, not for me. I went to space. I’m covered.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You know what? This bottle was meant to celebrate an achievement. Let’s make a pact. When one of us gets their first big breakthrough, we’ll celebrate by opening this bottle of champagne and toasting Professor Abbott.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I love that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yeah, me, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Then, of course, rubbing our success in Sheldon’s face.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, well, that’s the best part.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, yeah.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Dan, could I talk to you for a minute?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>Sure, go ahead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Just want you to know I didn’t mean to be rude about your grandson.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>No, it’s okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>No, it’s not. Penny told me that everyone’s scared of me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>What? What? Why would she say that? You know she drinks, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>No, she’s right, and I just want you to know that from now on, I’m gonna be much more sensitive. I don’t want anyone walking on eggshells around me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>Oh, well, okay, then, uh, one thing I’ve been meaning to tell you is that the company is gonna stop paying for our coffee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>No problem. When does that start?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>Five months ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Who’s been paying for my coffee?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>All of us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah. It comes from the swear jar we put money in when you curse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-17"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>What else don’t I know about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-18"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Uh, well, you know your private bathroom?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-19"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Yeah?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-20"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>That was supposed to be for the whole floor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-21"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>You’re kidding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-22"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>No, no. It’s okay. It only really affected Wheelchair Kathy, and she’s back in the hospital now, so it all worked out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-23"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I feel so bad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-24"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, then, maybe you shouldn’t have named her Wheelchair Kathy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-25"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Oh, my God. I thought everybody liked me, but I’m just a monster.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-26"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>But a cute one, like that, uh, eyeball guy in Monsters, Inc.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-27"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>No, I’m the worst. I’m a terrible person.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-28"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>Come on, don’t cry. It’s okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-29"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>It’s not okay. How can I even work here anymore?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-30"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Because this company needs you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-31"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>It’s fine. We don’t mind paying for the coffee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-32"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I can’t let you do that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-33"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>Maybe we could get you an espresso machine for your office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-34"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I guess that would be all right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-35"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>See? You don’t have to be mean to get what you want.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-36"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>You’re right. Now where did we land on my bathroom?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hello.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>How come you’re up so late?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I posted the last episode of Fun with Flags hours ago, and not a single person cared enough to comment. All that effort for nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Mm. I know how you feel. I spent the day throwing out a man’s entire career, and all that’s left is an old bottle of champagne and a naked lady pen that Raj took when he thought no one was looking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It’s not the same thing. I don’t think you know how I feel at all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sad?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hmm. You do get me. Someone left a comment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah. What did they say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Too bad your show is done. I kind of liked it. Leonard, did you hear that? Oh, the people are heartbroken. I can’t take this away from the world. Fun with Flags is back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Congratulations.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Let’s celebrate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, that wasn’t for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, no, I’m not going to drink it. I just wanted to hear the pop. Yeah, I knew it was coming. Still scary.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content> LeVar Burton?  LeVar Burton?  LeVar Burton?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>LeVar</speaker><content>Ugh. What are you doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You told me not to call, and I didn’t know how else to give you the good news. Fun with Flags is back, and you can be in the next episode.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>LeVar</speaker><content>Wil Wheaton said, get a gate. I don’t know why I didn’t get a gate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You, at least listen to the premise. Since you were born in Germany, I thought we could talk</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>