<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What colour would you like to be?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, I’d like to be green, but you know you always take it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s not true. Any colour’s fine with me. Yeah, I could be a-a combination of blue and yellow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Blue and yellow make green.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, then it’s settled.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hi. Ready to go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, good news, we ordered lunch, so we can all stay here and play Lord of the Rings Risk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon, we said that we would play games with you tonight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, no, we’ll still be playing it tonight, this game can easily take eight hours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sweetie, you really thought I’d want to do this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, did you tell him that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Did you say it out loud with words?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I don’t want to spend the whole day playing a board game.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, well, you may change your mind when you hear that this is the new expanded edition which contains a more complete map of Middle Earth, now including the Haradwaith Territories.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I will literally race you to the car.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, no, no, come on, don’t leave. Just try it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-20"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No. We’re always doing what you guys want. Just once, it’d be nice if you did something we wanted.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You want to be green?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-22"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You know, they really have tried to like a lot of the same stuff we’re into.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-23"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, we do game nights and video game nights and we watch movies with director’s commentary.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-24"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Oh, my favourite, George Lucas can talk all the way through Star Wars, I say one word and I’m banished to the kitchen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-25"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, today Amy and I are deciding what we’re all gonna do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-26"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You got it, you girls are in charge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-27"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-28"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-29"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Fine. Now that we’re not playing, you can be green.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-30"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-31"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And since you’re green this time, I can be it next time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-32"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>All right, let’s see. What’s something fun the guys would never take us to do? Oh, I know, we could go horseback riding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-33"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I actually can’t. My hips don’t open wider than 22 degrees. I rode a very thin pony once. On the first bump, just popped right off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-34"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>All right, well, what do you want to do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-35"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>There’s a craft and folk art museum on Wilshire.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-36"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, that’s Wilshire’s problem. Come on, you know, there, there’s got to be something fun we could do that the guys will hate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-37"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hang on, why do we have to hate it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-38"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Three words, Doctor Who convention.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-39"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I did not force you to go to that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-40"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You walked out of the house in a fez and bow tie. I went so you didn’t get beat up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-41"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I wasn’t gonna get beat up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-42"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You were, but somehow I held myself back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-43"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You know what you could make us do? Ice-skating. The cold air will trigger Leonard’s asthma and it plays right into my well-known fear of getting flattened by a Zamboni.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-44"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Now you’re helping them find ways to make us miserable?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-45"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, I’m sorry, Leonard, I’m a problem-solver, it’s what I do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-46"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I actually can’t go ice-skating. I have unnaturally brittle ankles.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-47"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Is there any part of your body that’s normal?</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Will you please relax?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I can’t take it, dude.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>You okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No, I’m not okay. I feel like I’m gonna jump out of my skin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I told you not to wax down there. It’s itchy when it grows back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I’m worried about the New Horizons space probe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>What’s he talking about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Nine years ago he was part of a team that launched a spacecraft to collect data about Pluto, and it’s finally close enough, so this morning it turned itself on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>We hope. The signal has to travel over three billion miles. So it’s gonna be hours before we know if it even survived.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Now we get to see him flip out because he’s worried it was demolished by space ice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Space ice is no joke. I can’t even watch Frozen anymore.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Ooh, the philharmonic is playing Beethoven downtown.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Before you say yes, it’s not the movie about the big dog.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>How come we can’t think of something we both want to do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Because you always pick what we do and I just go along with it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Ah, interesting, we’re being accused of making you do things you don’t like, and here you are, doing the same thing to poor Amy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You should point out the hypocrisy of that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That’s what I was doing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, that wasn’t clear. Try it again, but this time drive it home with how do you like them apples, Missy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>All right, keep thinking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You’re making it too complicated. Why not stick to the basics? Go shopping for clothes while Leonard and I sit in those uncomfortable chairs and hold your purses, hmm? I know I’d hate that. Leonard?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, then, it’s settled?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>What do you say? Sounds kind of perfect.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>It does, somehow he managed to take all the fun out of it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, once again, it’s what I do.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, another two hours to go. The wait is killing me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I know. I get it. When I was in the Soyuz capsule returning from the space station, plummeting toward Earth at 17,000 miles per hour…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Before you finish, is this a story about patience and waiting or just another reminder that you went to space?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>A story can do two things.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Ugh, I feel like I’m gonna have a heart attack.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You work in pharmaceuticals, don’t you have anything you can give him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>All I have is our new urine flow drug. Won’t help with his anxiety, but it’s so strong, when he pees he’ll fly around the room like he’s got a jet pack.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I can’t stop thinking about it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>You know, worrying won’t have any effect on what happens.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Maybe you need to do something more productive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Okay. If I make this shot in the trash can, the probe will have arrived in perfect working order.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>So, in addition to being crazy, you’re resting the fate of the mission on your athletic prowess.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>The man who crashed his stationary bike.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I didn’t crash it, okay? My playlist was too up-tempo, I got light-headed and I fell off. Okay. It all comes down to this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You happy? Now you can relax.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>What kind of scientist are you? Everyone knows you got to make two out of three.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>This isn’t so bad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s easy for you to say. Your chair’s not facing the lingerie section. Boy, that’s a lot of panties.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You guys comfy? This might take a while.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I don’t understand why women insist on making a big production out of buying clothes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, you’re right, we should do what you do. Have our mom send us pants from the Walmart in Houston.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>They have a man there who understands my personal style.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Bye.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh, I’ve got some bad news. There’s no cell service in here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh. Well, that’s all right. There were plenty of ways to pass the time before smart phones were invented.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That’s true.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’ll look them up. Son of a biscuit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, it’s fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, it’s not fine. What kind of store in the 21st century doesn’t at least have Wi-Fi? I’m going to call their corporate office. Son of a biscuit.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Let’s see, my armies are going to attack the Shire from Buckland. And I roll a five and a three.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay. And to defend, I roll two sixes. I win.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Boy, double-sixes again. You know, if I hadn’t seen it with my own eyes, I wouldn’t believe it. I wonder how long we’re gonna be stuck here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t know, but the girls do a lot for us. It’s the least we can do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, that’s true. I suppose it’s only fair we make compromises.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Look at you, being all mature.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I don’t know why you’re so surprised. If there’s one thing I know about after living with you for so many years, it’s how to compromise.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I, I’m sorry? You make compromises for me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All the time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>On Earth? In our lives? That, that, that we’re living?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, yes. I, just yesterday, you had a, a big piece of lettuce stuck in your teeth at lunch. Did I say anything? No. I compromised and kept my mouth shut. Like you should’ve, because everyone was laughing at you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That is not a compromise. A compromise is me driving you everywhere because you refuse to learn how.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, I learned how. Amy taught me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What? Then. then why don’t you do it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Uh, well, it’s scary. And sometimes I get the pedals mixed up. But, more importantly, driving me to work is one of the things that gives your life purpose. I can’t take that away from you, so what do I do? Oh, come on, I’m practically feeding you the answer. I compromise.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Hey, uh, thanks for keeping me company.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’m happy to. I think getting out of the apartment will do you good. So, where we headed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>If it’s okay with you, I’d like to go to temple.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Buddy, trust me, you don’t want to convert to Judaism. I mean, I know I make it look cool, but it’s not all briskets and dreidels.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I meant a Hindu temple.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh. Okay. It’s not like Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom, right? Some bald guy with horns isn’t gonna rip my heart out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Dude, that movie’s an imperialist fantasy that makes the followers of a beautiful and peaceful religion look like a bunch of bloodthirsty barbarians.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You love that movie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yeah, it’s pretty great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I’m surprised to see you suddenly get religious.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Well, because I’ve known you for ten years and you’ve never gone to temple, you never talked about believing in God, and last Diwali I watched you eat two pounds of sacred cow at a Brazilian steak house.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Religion is a very personal thing. I do go to temple, I just, I don’t talk about it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, but you’re a scientist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>So?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>So, as a scientist, you believe the way to understand the universe is through facts and evidence, and now you’re counting on some blue chick with a hundred arms to help you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>That is so offensive. Does everything you know about Hinduism come from Indiana Jones?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No. There’s also Apu from The Simpsons.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Well, lots of scientists believe in God. Okay? Newton, uh, Faraday, uh, Pascal, all were believers. Even Einstein was famous for attacking quantum theory on the grounds that God does not play dice with the universe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-20"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Well, of course he believed in God. he slept with Marilyn Monroe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-21"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Actually there’s no proof of that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-22"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You believe in your religion, I’ll believe in mine.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>How’s it going in there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Uh, not really a great outfit for work, unless something opens up in the hookers and whores division. Hey, can I ask you something?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Do I really force you to do things you don’t want to?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Yeah, but it’s okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>How is it okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I promised myself, if I ever got friends, I’d do whatever they said. Really, I’m lucky you found me before a cult did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, you know, that was a long time ago. You’re a different woman now. You’re smart, you’ve got great friends, you’ve got a boyfriend, you’re pretty, you have zero fashion sense, but, anyway, tonight we’re gonna do whatever you want.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Really?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Absolutely. You name it, we’re doing it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Basket weaving at the craft museum.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, you named it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, here’s another one. I wish that the apple pancake mix was on the top shelf because it starts with an A, but I don’t put it there because I don’t want you breaking one of your little legs when you’re supposed to be making my breakfast.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Is it my turn to talk about the compromises I make?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I wasn’t done, but go ahead. He said, compromising.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Because of you, I’m not allowed to adjust the temperature in my own home. I’m not allowed to whistle. I don’t wear shoes that might squeak.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, you’re a physicist, not a circus clown.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, do you realize I don’t live with the woman I love because of you? No other reason. Just you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Is that true?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yes, it’s true. The last time I brought it up, you had an emotional breakdown and got on a train and ran away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, given my history on the subject, t seems a little reckless to bring it up now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You have no idea how much you inconvenience the lives of everyone around you. It’s exhausting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You know what? You think you’re so tolerant, but the truth is you’re mean to me a lot. Yeah, you think that I don’t notice all those sarcastic comments and those eye rolls, but I do. Hmm? I have excellent peripheral vision. On a good day, I can see my ears.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, I, I’m sorry if I hurt your feelings. I’ve been holding a lot of this in for a while.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, I’m sorry, too. And if you want to live with Penny, then I think you should.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Do you mean that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes. Yeah, just put on your squeaky shoes and eee-eee-eee your way out of my life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Come on, don’t get upset.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m not upset. I’m just imagining a world without my best friend in it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It’s okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m not leaving your world. I’m just talking about living across the hall.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I understand. Either way, I want you to know that I’m aware of how difficult I can be. So I just want to say thank you for putting up with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-22"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Buddy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-23"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>How are you guys getting along? What? Why are there tears?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-24"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Everything’s fine. We just started talking about living arrangements.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-25"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Are you crazy? You know he’s a flight risk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-26"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s exactly what I told him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-27"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sheldon, we know this is a sensitive subject, and Leonard’s not gonna move out until you’re ready.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-28"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, what if you did it gradually?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-29"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>All right. How about we start with two nights a week I live with Penny?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-30"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>How about one night and I let you whistle?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-31"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-32"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>When I’m not home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-33"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You got it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-34"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>There we go, compromising again. We really are the best.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Here we go, my first Hindu temple.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You see behind the fountain, that tower that looks like a pyramid? It’s called a Sikhara. It symbolizes the, the connection between the human and the divine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Huh. I always thought it was mini golf.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>All right. Shall we?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah. Just, uh, is there anything I should know before I go in?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Like what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Like am I dressed okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Really? So every other place you’ve been, you thought this was fine?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I know you’re under a lot of pressure, so I’m gonna let that pass.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Sorry. You’re right. I’m so stressed. But you know what, whenever I walk into that temple I realize that whatever happens, it’s okay. We’re all part of an immense pattern, and though we can’t understand it, we can be happy to know that it’s, it’s working its will through us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>That’s nice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Whether you call it God or the universe or the self, we’re all interconnected, and that’s just a beautiful… Son of a bitch, that guy just dinged my car. S, seriously? You were just gonna drive away? Like my life isn’t hard enough right now. A space probe might be destroyed, my parents are going through an awful divorce, the guy who cuts my dog’s hair just gave her bangs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Raj.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You saw her. She looks like Jim Carrey from Dumb and Dumber.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Raj, you just got a text. The probe turned on. It’s fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, good. Namaste, Grandpa.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I thought this was gonna be boring, but it’s actually kind of fun.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Don’t tell Amy that. We’ll be here every Sunday.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon, that really is an excellent basket.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It’s not a basket. It’s a soldier’s helmet from 16th century China.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Very nice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, it looks great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I saw that.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, roomie, it’s only one night a week, but it’s a start.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I know. I’m really proud of Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, I’m proud of him, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Sheldon (in Penny’s living room)</speaker><content>Can you keep it down? Some of us are trying to sleep out here.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>