<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, we’re headed out, see you later.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Before you leave, could you test these noise-cancelling headphones?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Okay. Go ahead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hello, can you hear me? Sheldon, I haven’t changed the filter in the water pitcher in two years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Uh, Bernadette’s nickname for you is the virgin piña colada.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Your George Lucas autograph is really a me autograph.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, once I was too lazy to walk across the hall, so I used your toothbrush.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Ooh, and one time when you were asleep, Amy totally took off her… and that’s why you’re the best roommate ever.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Aw, now I’m sad I didn’t hear it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>So what do you need the headphones for?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, I’ve been struggling for months to come up with a theory of dark matter that doesn’t make protons decay. I’m hoping to finally tackle it by optimising my work environment. See, I’ve got, uh, my tea is at the perfect sipping temperature. Uh, I have fleece-lined boxer shorts to keep my tushie toasty. And then, oh, last but not least, this inspirational cat poster improved with the reassuring face of physics renegade Richard Feynman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Is that why you had to take him to Office Depot last night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t want to talk about it. There, the place is all yours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, have fun.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, I will, nothing more fun than a paradigm-shifting evening of science.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>And you thought it was soaping me up in the shower.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Bye.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Okay. Here we go. Proton decay. Proton decay.  Proton decay. Proton decay.  Proton decay. Proton decay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey, we’re home. Any progress?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>How could there be, with these constant interruptions?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-22"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I love him, but if he’s broken, let’s not get a new one.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What are you doing? It’s time to go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m not going to work today. And would you like to know why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Ah, you’re upset because you spent the whole night working on dark matter and didn’t make a breakthrough, and now you’re worried you made a huge mistake switching fields, and you’re gonna sit around and sulk all day?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Like a big old baby.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Call me if you need anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’ve been cooped up in here too long. Maybe I need some fresh air.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Penny (off)</speaker><content>Ugh! Ugh! Ugh! Ugh!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content> Penny?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Penny (off)</speaker><content>Ugh!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content> Penny?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Penny (off)</speaker><content>Ugh!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content> Penny?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Ugh, what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You sounded in distress. I was worried something unpleasant was happening to you. Like a murder. Or spontaneous coitus with Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, I’m just doing this awful workout. I hate it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, if you hate it, then why are you doing it? Although I could ask the same question about coitus with Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I don’t know, I guess I like that I hate it. It makes me work harder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And to clarify?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>The exercise, Sheldon. Shouldn’t you be getting ready for work?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m not going. Would you like to know why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Uh, you’re sad about not getting anything done last night, so you’re gonna sit around and pout about it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Boy, I’m not nearly as mysterious as I think I am.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I invented a game. You want to play?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>It’s called Emily or Cinnamon. I give you actual quotes I’ve heard Raj say, and you guess if he was talking to his girlfriend or his dog.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Go ahead, make fun. You can’t embarrass me, I’ve got a beautiful girlfriend and a dog who loves me so much she drinks my bathwater.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Okay, who was he talking to, Emily or Cinnamon? I want you to know, the bed feels so lonely when you’re not in it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I may not be liking this game so much.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Cinnamon. Give me another one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Okay, Emily or Cinnamon? Check it out, I got us matching sweaters.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>We all got the Christmas card, Cinnamon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You know, a man can care deeply about a woman and a pet. It’s not strange.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Ooh, Emily. I heard him say that to Emily. Hey, I thought you were staying home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, I was, but after talking to Penny, I realised something. I, first, she’s trying much harder to stay attractive in this relationship than you are. And second, the reason I may not be progressing in my research is I’ve created too pleasant of an environment for myself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What do you mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>According to a classic psychological experiment by Yerkes and Dodson, in order to maximize performance, one must create a state of productive anxiety. So I’d like to ask you all to do something for me. Keep me on my toes. Just throw me off my game. Essentially, go out of your way to make my life miserable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Hold on. What’s in it for us?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, I suppose…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Okay, we’ll do it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Done.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>33 seconds. Okay, that’ll be our baseline.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You know, I don’t want to tell you how to do your job, but when a mouse completes a maze, it gets a food pellet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>It also gets its brain plucked out with tweezers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And his last meal was a food pellet? You’re a monster.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>All right, next, we’re gonna introduce an anxiety-inducing stimulus, measure your stress levels and see how it affects your problem-solving rate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Very well. And good luck, I’m a pretty laid-back guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Ready? Begin. Why’d you pop it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m sorry, I was aiming for your heart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Look, I know you don’t like it, but that’s the point of the experiment. I need to irritate you to find your optimal anxiety zone. And you said no to tickling, polka music or watching me eat a banana.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Who eats them horizontally?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>My mother said that’s how good girls do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Perhaps this was a waste of time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon, you’re a remarkable scientist. Just be patient, I’m sure you’ll find the breakthrough you’ve been looking for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>And if you only do solid research instead of making a groundbreaking discovery, what does it matter?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Only do solid research? I come to you for help, and you insult me? I thought the least that you would do would be…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Look, your anxiety levels are right in the zone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Really? Oh, that’s fantastic. Now, wait, they’re dropping. Why are they dropping?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-20"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Because you’re happy they’re elevated.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, that is infuriating. Ooh, look, they went back up again. Terrific. Oh, no, they went back down.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>All right, guys, what game do you want to play?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Let’s see. How about Emily or Cinnamon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You know what? I think it’s a little weird that you remember me saying all these things. Maybe the truth is, you’re jealous of all my relationships.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, maybe I am. Who wouldn’t want to be the girl, or possibly dog, to hear the words you’re so lucky, you have the shiniest hair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That is a tough one. Uh, I know he brushes both of them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Gentlemen, I have figured out the perfect way for you to irritate me. I’d like you to be my intellectual sparring partners. From now on, when I make an assertion, I need you to challenge it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>So you just want us to disagree with whatever you say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>And you think that’s going to help?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Well, I don’t think that’s gonna help at all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, no, it will. See, by keeping my mind engaged, I’ll become more focused.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Howard’s right, that’ll never work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Stop fighting me on the premise. It’s scientifically valid. I’m going to advance propositions, I just want you to challenge me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I don’t think that’s what you want at all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Why, of course it’s what I want. Why would I say it’s what I want if it’s not what I want?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Because it is what you want, and it’s not what you said.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I ask you for one simple thing, and you can’t even do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-19"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yes, we can.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, well, then do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-21"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Nah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You guys are the worst. Thank you, I think that was helpful.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>So, whichever rep has the best sales for the quarter gets a trip for two to Hawaii.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>That would be so romantic for you and Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, clearly you haven’t seen him on the beach walking around with his metal detector.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>If I were going to Hawaii, I’d spend all my time at the Keck Observatory. Did you know that the telescopes there have better resolution than the Hubble?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Really? Want to go to Hawaii?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content> Ladies?  Ladies?  Ladies?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Come in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Ladies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What’s up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, as you may know, I’ve been experimenting with elevated anxiety levels, and I thought, what better way to increase my discomfort than to subject myself to an evening of tasteless uncensored crotch talk?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What exactly do you think goes on here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, conversations that you wouldn’t be comfortable having in front of the opposite sex. You know, who has the best cervix. Which sanitary napkin is all the rage right now. Men’s buttocks, and how you want to pat and squeeze them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>We were talking about Penny’s job.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And how difficult it is to do when she’s bloated, cranky and crampy? Continue.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sheldon, we are just people. We talk about the same things you guys talk about.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You talk about if werewolves can swim? See, Leonard says yes, but I say it depends on if the human could swim before he was bitten. What do you think?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Let’s just talk about our periods.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-18"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>No, hold on. All canines instinctively know how to swim. Why wouldn’t a werewolf have the same abilities?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-19"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Well, they’re not a hundred percent wolf. They’re a werewolf, that’s only part wolf. It’s like comparing apples to oranges.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Thank you. Oh, and technically, it’s apples that turn into were-oranges when the moon is full. Hey, this is fun. We should do it sometime when you aren’t all PMS’ing. Bye.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What is going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh. Uh, I need to keep my anxiety at the right level, so I’m using Darth Vader, the Joker, and Godzilla’s roar to keep me in that sweet spot. Uh, I tried including Taylor Swift in the mix, but turns out I love her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, at least listen to it through headphones. I’m trying to sleep. Good night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Boy, Taylor was right, haters gonna hate, hate, hate, hate, hate.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You’ve been working so much lately, I’m glad you didn’t forget about date night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Of course.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Maybe you want to put the notebook away and talk to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I can do both. My brain is working at optimal capacity. I can have a conversation with you and solve the dark matter proton decay problem at the same time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Fine. How was your day?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, you said it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon. Sheldon, I’m worried about you. You’re not eating, you haven’t slept in days, and, to be honest, that cap is starting to smell.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I know. It’s replaced Godzilla as my principle source of anxiety.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Okay, so it’s one vote Emily, one vote Cinnamon. Penny, you’re the tiebreaker.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Say the quote again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>It’s just so perfect that we’re both Libras.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Wow, this is hard. I’m gonna say Cinnamon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Come on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>That was the last one, I promise. We won’t play any more.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Thank you. ‘Cause if she ever found out, it would hurt her feelings.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Emily’s feelings?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yes, Emily. Whatever. Where’s Sheldon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Date night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That can’t be much fun for Amy. You know, at work today, he tried his first Red Bull.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>What happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>He chased a squirrel around the quad for a while and then threw up in my car.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Don’t you think you should make him stop all this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I don’t know, he’s not really hurting anybody.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You didn’t have to scoop vomit out of your glove compartment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>He is getting a lot of work done. He had a pretty interesting take on proton decay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-20"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Wow, if he cracks that it’s a game changer, guys. It’ll completely redefine our understanding of the physical universe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-21"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Hmm, it would. Okay, back to Emily or Cinnamon? How can such a little girl eat such a big steak?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon, I want you to take that cap off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That nagging tone is helping my anxiety, yeah. But if you could maybe just go ten percent less shrill, that’d really put the zip-a-dee in my doo-dah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I’m sorry, but you know we agreed not to bring work to date night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>There you go, perfect.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon, stop it, I’m not kidding. Take the cap off, and put the notebook away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>But after months of struggling, I’m finally making progress.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You don’t need to drive yourself crazy in order to be productive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Or do I, hmm? Sir Isaac Newton wrote his Principia while convinced he was an armadillo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>That’s not true.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, well, maybe it is, maybe it isn’t. I have been hallucinating lately.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon, this has to stop. You need to get some sleep and take care of yourself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Amy, I have gotten more done in the last few days than I have since I made the switch to dark matter. What if I stop doing this, and it all goes away?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Your thoughts and ideas come from you, not from your anxiety.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hmm, perhaps. But I’m not taking the cap off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>It’s one thing to make yourself miserable, but you’re making everyone around you miserable, too. Now, I’m telling you for the last time, take the cap off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, really? What if I don’t? And before you answer that, can I have my dessert?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And then she threw me out. Me, her very own boyfriend. When all I’ve done is try to help humanity reach of the world we live in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>Yeah, well, women, what are you gonna do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I knew you’d understand, Armadillo Isaac Newton.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Here we are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hey. What are you trying to pull? The president of science isn’t in here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You lie down, he’ll be here in a minute.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Okay. Hey, I thought you were trying to trick me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Now, you just get comfortable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, no, comfort is the enemy. You know what’s comfortable? Slippers and blankets and panda bears. Imagine a panda bear with Richard Feynman’s face on it. Warm up the car, Leonard, it’s poster time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Maybe in the morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, you get some sleep.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, I don’t want to go to sleep, you can’t make me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You’re right, we can’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, darn straight, you can’t. Try to tell a grown man to go to sleep.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>Penny (singing)</speaker><content>Soft kitty, warm kitty.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>Leonard (singing)</speaker><content>Little ball of fur.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s not gonna work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-16"><speaker>Penny (singing)</speaker><content>Happy kitty, sleepy kitty.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-17"><speaker>Together (singing)</speaker><content>Purr, purr, purr.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You know, he can be a lot of trouble, but when I see him lying here asleep like this, I just think how easy it would be to hold a pillow over his face.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-19"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Mmmm.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You look like you got some rest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, I’m feeling much better. And I’ve also been continuing to make progress without artificially raising my anxiety levels.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I turned on the heat in my car and some vomit came out, so my levels, right up there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Hey, guys. Mind if Emily joins us for lunch?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, no problem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Of course not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>Emily</speaker><content>So I hear you guys have been playing a little game.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Well, um, we were just kidding around.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>Emily</speaker><content>Well, you may think it’s funny that Raj is sweet and sensitive, but I think it’s sexy. Ugh, why is there dog hair in your mouth?</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>