<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Leonard, I’ve been working on an opening joke for our lecture at Berkeley.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, I like to laugh. But say it anyway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Okay, um, what do you say to a graduate of the UC Berkeley physics department? I’ll have fries with that. Because his education hasn’t prepared him for a career in the sciences.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You know, when they chase you out of there, you only have to run faster than Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Are you all set for your trip?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, I think so. I just restocked the old PRK.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>PRK?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Public restroom kit. Everything a boy needs for making pee pee in new and strange places.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I don’t see what’s crazy about bringing a backpack with your own toilet paper and Purell.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Keep going.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And rubber gloves, uh, air freshener. Um, noise-cancelling headphones. Oh, danger whistle. Um, pepper spray. Ooh, a multi-language occupied sign. Uh, let’s see, we have seat protectors, uh, booties for my shoes, a clothespin for my nose. Oh, and a mirror on a stick, so I can make sure the person in the stall next to me isn’t some kind of weirdo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You still worried some Berkeley girl is gonna steal him away?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Yes, who do you think gave him the danger whistle?</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Would you like to play a physics car game I invented called I Can’t Spy? It’s all the nail-biting tension of I Spy but the added fun of subatomic particles and waves outside the visible spectrum.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>If it’s half as much fun as One Times Ten to the Fourth Bottles of Beer on the Wall, I’m in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’ll begin. Uh, I can’t spy with my little eye something passing right through us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That soy Frappuccino I had.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Will you please play the game? I can’t spy with my little eye something passing right through us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t know, um, if 65 billion solar neutrinos pass through a square centimetre every second, given the surface area of this car is about 60,000 square centimetres, that means 3.9 times ten to the 15th solar neutrinos?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I don’t want to play anymore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>We haven’t been on a road trip in a while. This is fun.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>We get it, you won the game. Stop bragging.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, listen, we wrote a paper together. Now we get to go to a university and talk about it? That’s pretty cool.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I suppose it is. In fact, if you’d like to celebrate with a little music, I’d be okay with that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What? This road trip just got crazy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Play that funky music, white boy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m surprised you know that reference.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What reference?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>So, I put stickers on everything we’re gonna sell. We just need help taking it all out to the driveway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Can I be in charge of pricing? I’ve been going to garage sales my whole life. Can you believe I got these pantyhose for a nickel?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>All right, Amy’s in charge of pricing and being 75.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Hey, Penny, can you give me a hand with this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sure. Oh, we had one of these growing up. I used to play all the time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, yeah? I love Ping-Pong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, I meant beer pong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I had a table, too, but I didn’t have any friends, so all I did was serve.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>You know, you can leave one side up and play against it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>And if I had a friend, they might have told me that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Excuse me. Why is there a sticker on this? It’s my TARDIS from Doctor Who. I was planning on moving it in the house.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I think you just answered your own question.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Come on, one day, this may double in value and be worth half what I paid for it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Sweetie, we have a lot to do. We don’t need to decide this right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Well, I guess as long as you’re keeping an open mind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Of course.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>So they’re requesting that the white boy play the funky music, yes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And this music we’re listening to right now is funky as well?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Let me ask you this. Do you think this song is the music the white boy ultimately plays?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It could be.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>So it’s like the musical equivalent of Russell’s Paradox, the question of whether the set of all sets that don’t contain themselves as members contains itself?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Exactly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well then I hate it. Music should just be fun.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Making great time. Gonna be there pretty early.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Will our hotel room be ready?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I doubt it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Aren’t you worried that sitting in the lobby for a long period of time might attract the attention of the hotel detective?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>If we do, we’ll just tell him to hit the bricks, see?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Seems a little confrontational, but all right. You know, we won’t be very far from Skywalker Ranch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, that’s true. It’s not like we can get in there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Why not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t think George Lucas put his headquarters in the middle of nowhere because he wanted people dropping in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yoda’s swamp was in the middle of nowhere. Tatooine was in the middle of nowhere. Hoth was in the middle of nowhere. That’s code, Leonard. He wants us to drop in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>We do have time. I mean, we could drive by and just look at it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes. Oh, I’m so excited. And I just can’t hide it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-22"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m about to lose control, and I think I like it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What are you talking about?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>So when do you guys think you’re gonna move in?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>We’re still figuring how much remodeling we want to do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>It’s tricky finding the right balance between tasteful modern and Jewish mother tchotchke crapfest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Have you made a decision about the TARDIS? I think I can sell it if we call it Big British Porta-Potty.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>We’re not selling it, it’s mine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>You can’t just decide. How about I arm-wrestle you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>That’s not fair. It’s like me challenging you to a sexy pants contest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You could play Ping-Pong for it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I would do that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>How is that fair? You grew up with a table.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yes, but I mostly used it as a battlefield in an ongoing war between the Transformers and the ThunderCats for control of a bra I had found in the woods.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Bernadette, for every episode of Doctor Who Leonard has made me sit through, I will play on your behalf and send that TARDIS back to Gallifrey, where I hate that I know it belongs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Yes, Penny plays for me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>That’s not fair, she has upper body muscles.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Dude, three-time Sanskriti School for Well-Born Boys badminton champion.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>That’s right, okay, Raj can play for me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Ooh, you just chose champions. It’s like we’re re-enacting the ancient German practice of trial by combat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-18"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, it’s also like when the Mountain fought the Red Viper in Game of Thrones.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-19"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Leonard makes you watch that, too?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-20"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, no, I like that show. It’s got dragons and people doing it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-21"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>So it’s settled. The fate of Doctor Who’s TARDIS will be decided by a Game of Thrones inspired death-match on the battlefield of ThunderCats versus Transformers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-22"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>If you still have that bra, I’ll give you a nickel for it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>There it is. It’s just a gate. On a road.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Wasn’t even that hard to find.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>This is so amazing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I know. You want to get a picture?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I want more than a picture. I want to go in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, so do I, but they’ll never let us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Is that the attitude that helped you get Penny?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, but I don’t have three years to make that gate feel sorry for me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>There’s a speaker box. Drive up, push the button, and let’s see what happens.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, yeah. What do we have to lose? I’m a little nervous.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, get over it. Confidence is key in these situations.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You pushed it, are you out of your mind?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Voice</speaker><content>May I help you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Um, uh, uh, uh, we don’t have an appointment, and, and we don’t belong here, but we, we’re, like, crazy-big fans. I mean uh, buh, buh, crazy for Star Wars crazy, not crazy like we have a backpack full of duct tape, although we do have a backpack that you really don’t want to look in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You’re blowing it. We want to meet George Lucas and become his friends and play with him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>Voice</speaker><content>Hello? This speaker’s not working, just pull up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>And that’s how it’s done.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right, we’ve defeated the first challenge. Now we must steel ourselves to face the monster who defends the gate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>We’re trying to get past a security guard, not rescue Zelda.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I think what really needs to be rescued is your sense of whimsy, but one quest at a time. So what’s the plan?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh, I’m just gonna be honest with the guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Honesty will never get us in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, what’s your plan?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right, my plan is predicated on the assumption that they have a nurse’s office and your willingness to be lightly stabbed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Security Guard</speaker><content>Who are you here to see?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh, I’m just gonna tell you the truth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, you are killing me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>We don’t have an appointment. We, we’re just fans of Mr. Lucas’s work, and we thought we’d take a shot and see if we could get in and look around.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Security Guard</speaker><content>Sorry, guys, we get this a lot. Can’t let you in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What if I told you that I was the voice of Yoda? A recording session I must attend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m sorry, don’t listen to him. We’re actually physicists. We’re giving a lecture at Berkeley later today. We just, we had some time to kill.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Security Guard</speaker><content>Hey, listen, you seem like decent guys. I can’t let you in, but I got some hats and T-shirts I can give you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Thank you so much. See? Maybe honesty is the best… What are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Shedding the yoke of my oppressors, you blind, sad little man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>Security Guard</speaker><content>Don’t move. Code A-A-23, A-A-23.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>Voice</speaker><content>Copy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I can see the ranch, Leonard. Oh, it’s rustic, it’s lovely. I’d take a picture, but people are chasing me. I’m gonna make it. I’m gonna make it. They have Tasers, but they wouldn’t dare use… Aaaaaaagh!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Come on, Raj. You are the King Kong of Ping-Pong. You are the menace of table tennis. Put her away, ’cause I don’t have a third one. Yes. Woo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Rajesh eight, Penny four.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sorry, he’s really good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Hey, Raj. if Howard can’t keep the TARDIS, how great would it look at your place?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I don’t know much about Doctor Who, but if, um, you were to put this right outside your front door and open up the back, it would be like your entire apartment was the inside of the TARDIS, which is pretty cool ’cause on the show, the inside of the TARDIS is bigger than the outside. But then again, I don’t know much about Doctor Who.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Don’t listen to her. You and I go way back, we’re like brothers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>We are. We are. Oh, no. What a terrible serve. Sorry, brother.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Eight-five.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>This is ridiculous. I want a new champion. Amy, were you serious about being able to serve?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Uh, it, it’s been a long time. I don’t know. I’m probably pretty rusty.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Wow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>She’s my champion.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Well, if you can switch champions, so can I. I want Raj.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Oh, come on, like you even care.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I care. Oh, wait, no, I don’t. Good luck, Raj.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You know, I thought our friendship meant more to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-20"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>So did I.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Do you think they’re gonna call the police?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t know. Maybe they’ll call Imperial Officers to take us to a holding cell on the Death Star.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, I think that’s below the pay grade of an Imperial Officer. Stormtroopers are really the ones who…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, shut up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Nerdy Guy</speaker><content>He’s right. Uh, Stormtroopers actually combine both the function of infantry and military police.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh-huh, I’m normally very nice, but you shut up, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>So, what are you in for?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Nerdy Guy</speaker><content>Honestly, I just wanted to meet Mr. Lucas and say thank you. You know, growing up, the movies had such an impact on my life. I never really fit in anywhere. Till I discovered the worlds he created and finally found a place where I belong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>But why are you here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Nerdy Guy</speaker><content>Oh, I, uh, I hopped a fence, and they caught me in the sculpture gallery making out with a Chewbacca statue.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Excuse me. Leonard, they have a sculpture gallery.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Security Guard</speaker><content>All right, I talked to my supervisor, and we’re gonna let you go with a warning. But if you ever come back, we will call the police and press charges.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>We understand. Thank you so much.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Nerdy Guy</speaker><content>Uh, what about me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>Security Guard</speaker><content>No, you’re not going anywhere, kissy face. Let’s go. I have to take your picture to post at the guard gate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Uh, one question about that picture. Can it be with George Lucas? Ooh, grumpy you are.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Okay, this is the match that decides it all. First to 11 wins. Serve switches every five points. And just so you know, when this started, I was going to put the TARDIS in a discreet corner of the house, but I’ve since turned mean, and now it’s going right in the middle of the living room on a rotating platform with a sign that says suck it. Game on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Except, Raj is gonna win. Isn’t that right, Raj?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Uh, yeah, I mean, her serve was pretty good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Come on, get in her head. Be intimidating.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Okay, uh, I’m gonna own you, bitch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Whoa.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>That’s not nice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Let’s just play.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>One-zero. Two. Three. Four. Five-nothing. Wait, did you play badminton or sad-minton?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Don’t listen to him, all she’s got is a serve. Now, grab a fresh tampon and put her away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>What, and that’s not offensive? Where’s the line?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>It’s in your purse. Play.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>One-five. Two-five. Three-five. Four-five. Five-five.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Six. Seven. Eight. Nine. Ten-five.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Six. Seven. Eight. Nine. Ten-ten.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-17"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Well, that was an exciting 40 seconds.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-18"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>It was, and now the serve is back to you, and the game is over.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-19"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>You know, Amy, I, uh, can’t help but wonder how Sheldon would react if the TARDIS was at your place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-20"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Don’t listen to her, just hit the ball.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-21"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Keep talking.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>If this doesn’t get him into your bedroom, nothing will.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Are you still mad at me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yes, we missed our lecture, we were almost arrested, and you got me locked in a room with a man who forced his tongue down the throat of a stuffed Wookiee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Boy, some people are just glass-half-empty.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>The glass is empty, Sheldon. It’s completely empty. If you gave that glass to a man who was dying of thirst, he would be dead, do you know why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Before I answer, was he a smoker? I think you’re looking at this all wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Fine, then tell me how I should be looking at it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, not only did we go to Skywalker Ranch, we got in. And no one we know can say that. And for all the times you find me irritating, today you got to watch someone shoot me with a Taser.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That part was pretty good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>See?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You did flop around a lot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’ll take your word for it. I was too busy trying not to defecate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You know, when they were escorting us to the detaining room, I looked through a door, and I’m pretty sure I saw a display case with the Ark of the Covenant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s amazing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>And I saw Jabba the Hutt riding by on a motorcycle. Although that was right after the Tasing, so who can say for sure?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I guess this could count as an adventure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It was. And even though we’re not allowed back there, they can never take today away from us. Unlike my sense of smell, which hasn’t returned since the Tasing. No, I got nothing.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Amy, the Daleks are right on my tail, quick, we need to reset the time circuits. Oh, no, I left my sonic screwdriver behind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Really should have thought this through.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>