<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Excuse me. Is it at all possible that you’re knitting a pair of pants? Oh, well, no, you’re understandably terrified. But, you know, allow me to explain. 45 days ago, um, I embarked on a railroad journey of healing because my university was making me do string theory, and my favorite comic book store burned down, and when my room mate got engaged, my girlfriend wanted to move in with me, which was no doubt a ploy just to see my, well, excuse my language, but my bathing suit parts. Uh, sir, may I use your phone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>I don’t think so.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, well, I understand that I’m half naked, but there is a reasonable explanation. While I slept in my sleeper car, all my possessions were stolen. Now, typically, I wear pyjamas, but I recently adopted a hobo lifestyle and pyjamas are the sleep-pants of the Man. I’ll have you know, Mahatma Gandhi wore no pants and a nation rallied behind him. My good man, now, before you walk away, I know that I may appear deranged, but I am, in fact, a world-renowned physicist. Ask me the difference between a boson and a fermion. Go ahead, ask. Bosons have integer spin, fermions have half-integer spin. My legs are getting cold. Why won’t anybody help me?</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hi. Want to do yoga with me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Um, let me just have some coffee first, and then I’ll have the strength to tell you how much I won’t be doing that.  Hello?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hello, Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey, buddy. Good to hear your voice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Uh, I’m in Kingman, Arizona, and, uh, I need you to come pick me up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’d love to. I’m just about to do yoga with Penny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Leonard, I’m at the police station. I was robbed. They took my phone, my wallet, my iPad, everything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, my God, are you okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, I’m not okay. Uh, I’m wearing borrowed pants, I don’t have I.D., and one of the officers here won’t stop calling me chicken legs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay. Uh, I’ll, I’ll come get you. What’s the address?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey, what’s going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>He got all of his stuff stolen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>2530 East Andy Devine Avenue,</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hurry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon, hang tight. Hey, do you want me to bring anything?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, yes, please. A pair of pants. And my toothbrush. Yeah, and my mail. And a really good comeback for chicken legs, because “I know you are, but what am I?” was met with stony silence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’ll be there as soon as I can.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Is he okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-22"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, he’s fine, he’s just a little rattled.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-23"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-24"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Feel like driving to Arizona with me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-25"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I can’t, I have that job interview.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-26"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-27"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Besides, I don’t need six hours of your hair is different, why did you change your hair? I’m holding my breath until your hair grows back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-28"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>All right, fine. Hey, can you think of a reason I shouldn’t invite Amy to come with me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-29"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Nope.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-30"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Come on, you didn’t even try.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Thanks for the lift.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What’s wrong with your car?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I’m having my windows untinted.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Got a hot girlfriend now. I want the haters to know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What are you talking about? No one’s paying attention to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Wow. How’s that Hater-Ade taste, bro? Hey, this isn’t the way to work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I just want to pop in and make sure Ma’s okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I thought Stuart was looking after her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>He was, but now that her cast is off, he moved out. And honestly, I’m kind of glad. It was getting a little weird.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>How so?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I don’t know, they’re, chummy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Like us?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>No, not like us. Creepy chummy, like you and your dog.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>She feeds him out of her own mouth?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I mean, he calls her Debbie, she calls him Stewie and they’re all giggly around each other. And believe me, when food goes in that mouth, it does not come out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>So are you worried because he’s replacing you as a son or are you worried because he’s becoming her lover?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>First of all, no one can replace me as a son. I’m her little matzo ball. And secondly, my mother is well past having any kind of sex life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Okay, okay. Although many older women lead vibrant, active…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-20"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I said well past it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Excuse me, Officer Hernandez? Any leads on the person who stole my belongings?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Hernandez</speaker><content>Not yet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, perhaps I can help. Sherlock Holmes always says when you eliminate the impossible, whatever remains, however improbable, must be the truth. Now, have, have you tried doing that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Hernandez</speaker><content>Nope.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, maybe you should. There’s lots of books called Sherlock Holmes, and there’s no books called Officer Hernandez.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Thanks again for coming. Six hours was gonna be a long drive by myself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>My pleasure. And I’m not angry at all that my boyfriend was in trouble and called you instead of me. I love that,</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, time’s gonna fly by.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I haven’t been on a job interview in years. I’m really nervous.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Don’t be. You are built for pharmaceutical sales. You’re cute, you’re flirty and started that like there were gonna be three things.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I don’t have any experience in sales. Unless you count the bikini car wash I did in high school. But you already made me take that off my résumé.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>This job is a lot like being a waitress, except instead of pushing the fish tacos ’cause they’re about to go bad, you’re just pushing our antidepressants before the FDA finds out they may cause rectal bleeding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>They do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Maybe. But like our lawyers say, the world is full of things that can cause a rectum to bleed. Anyway, I talked you up to Dan. He’s the guy who’ll be interviewing you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, I really appreciate this. I just hope I’m not in over my head.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>You’ll be fine. Just be yourself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I wish I felt more confident.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Penny, I wouldn’t have put you up for this job if I didn’t think you could handle it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, thank you, but maybe I should cancel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>It’s too late to cancel. You’re going.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>But I don’t know anything about pharmaceuticals.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Oh, I understand. You want to do something you’re already good at. I know. Why don’t I get you a job at the Sitting Around All Day Wearing Yoga Pants Factory?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>They’re comfortable.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Ma, I hope you’re decent. Raj is here. You just started seeing naked women again, and I don’t want you to be confused about where the boobs should be.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Oh, hey, guys. What are you doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Uh, what are you doing here? I thought you moved out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Oh, yeah, I was going to, and then Debbie and I got to talking over dinner the other night. I didn’t have any place to go, she likes having me around, so we both said, why leave? at the same time. It was precious.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>It’s not that precious.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I’d like to back you up, but it sounds like it was pretty precious.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Mrs Wolowitz (off)</speaker><content>Stewie, I can’t find my glasses.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Be right there, Deb Deb. They’re probably on her head.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Or in her neck. Listen. You staying here seems like something she would’ve talked to me about.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Well, maybe if you called your mother more often, you’d know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>It wouldn’t kill you to pick up the phone.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Any word on my stolen items?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Hernandez</speaker><content>We’re doing everything we can.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You know, Sherlock Holmes liked to use cocaine to sharpen his focus. But I’m sure those Cool Ranch Doritos are doing the trick.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Leonard. Oh, I’m so happy to see you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Are you okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, I’m fine. Why did you come?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>What do you mean, why did I come? You’re my boyfriend. I haven’t seen you in over a month. I just drove six hours to help you out. Don’t you have anything to say besides why did you come?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I do, but, I feel uncomfortable saying it out loud in front of these police officers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Fine. Whisper it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Sheldon (whispers)</speaker><content>Shotgun.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>So, Sheldon, tell us about your trip. Where’d you go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Where didn’t I go? I went to New York, Chicago, Atlanta, Denver, Seattle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>How were they?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, I have no idea. I never left the train station.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hang on. You travelled across the entire country and never left a train station?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Why would I? That’s where all the cool trains are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’m sorry, so you never went outside?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Or had a single piece of fruit.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>So, why do you think you’d make a good pharmaceutical sales rep?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, I’m a people person. People like me. Some of my favourite people are people. I feel like I’m saying people a lot. People, people, people. Okay, I’m done.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>You sure?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>People. Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>Good. So, how do you feel your previous job experience has prepared you for a career like this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Uh, well, as a waitress, sales was a big part of my job. I mean, believe me, I convinced a lot of very large customers, who should not be eating cheesecake, to have more cheesecake. I mean, one of those chubsters even had an insulin pump.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>Uh-huh. I have an insulin pump.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>People.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>It’s weird, right? A grown man in his thirties living with my mother.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>That is weird. I thought he was, like, 45.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Come on, you don’t think it’s a little odd?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I don’t know. I mean, she’s lonely. He needs a place to stay. I doubt there’s any funny business going on. And even if there was, who cares? They’re both adults.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Who cares? You wouldn’t care if I slept with your mom?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You know what? You’re my best friend, and she’s in a bad marriage. I give you my blessing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>This is stupid. I’m just gonna call my mother and be honest with her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>‘Cause that’s what little matzo balls do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Stuart (voice on answerphone)</speaker><content>This is Debbie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Mrs Wolowitz (voice on answerphone)</speaker><content>And this is Stuart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Together</speaker><content>Just kidding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>Stuart (voice on answerphone)</speaker><content>Leave a message.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>This is the part where you talk.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>All right, let’s say a physician was prescribing one of our competitor’s drugs. How would you convince them to switch to ours?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Um, any chance his car needs to be washed by a girl in a bikini? No. Okay, I’m really sorry for wasting your time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>Don’t worry about it. Thanks for stopping by.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, thanks. Um, I’m sorry, listen, could you do me a favour and not tell Bernadette how badly I blew this interview? She’ll get upset. And honestly I’m a, a little terrified of her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>Wait, wait. You’re scared of Bernadette?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah, kind of.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>I thought it was just me. Everyone thinks she’s so nice with that squeaky little voice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I know, but she’s kind of a bully.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>Wll, she is. I didn’t even want to meet you, but, uh, I was too scared to say no to her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Me, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>Yeah, yeah. One, one time, I had, I had to tell her we were cutting the, the research funding for one of the drugs she was developing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>Dan</speaker><content>I couldn’t do it. She’s still working on it. Oh, we’re not gonna tell her about this, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, my God, no.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>At the hot dog stand in the Denver train station, Heinz ketchup. At the hot dog stand in the Salt Lake City train station, Heinz ketchup. At the hot dog stand in the Indianapolis train station?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t care.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Wrong. Hunt’s. Hey, Amy, what do you say? You ready to move on to the mustard round?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Have you not noticed that I’ve been sitting back here quietly stewing for the past two hours?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I just thought you were bad at the game.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I’m mad at you. How could you just go away like that without even saying good-bye, and then call Leonard for help instead of me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Amy, may I please have a moment of privacy to speak with my roommate?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>We’re in a moving car. What do you expect me to do? Stick my fingers in my ears?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, I was thinking put your head out the window like a dog, but that’ll work. Please? This’ll be quick. Leonard? As soon as we get home, I want to have coitus with Amy. Okay, she can’t hear. The reason I called you is because I didn’t want Amy to know I couldn’t make it on my own.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What’s the big deal?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, of course it’s no big deal to you. You idolize me, and nothing could ever knock me off that pedestal you put me on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-12"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, yeah, it’s true. You, you are a god to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-13"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Can I stop now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Just tell her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-15"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I called Leonard because I failed. And I didn’t want you to think less of me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-16"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You were worried about that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-18"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sheldon, it’s okay with me that you’re not perfect.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Can I have one more moment with Leonard?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-20"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Amy just hurt my feelings. I want to break up with her.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Now, I never thought I’d say this, but I’m kind of excited to see Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I never thought I’d say this, but Penny got a job today.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>She did?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Well, the only reason she got it is ’cause the guy who interviewed her loves me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>Howard (answering a knock on the door)</speaker><content>What do you want?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>I, uh, kind of got the feeling you might not be okay with me staying at your mom’s.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You’re right, I’m not. I think it’s weird.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Howie?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>It is. He’s a grown man. He’s just gonna live there rent-free? How is that gonna motivate him to get off his butt and get a job? I mean, do you even have a plan?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Hey, you’re not my father, okay? And besides, your mother and I were talking…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Your mother and I? You’re not my father.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-12"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>I didn’t say I was your father.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Well, I didn’t say I was your father.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-14"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Okay, calm down. You’re not his father, he’s not your father. Nobody’s anybody’s father.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-15"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>I, I’m sorry you don’t like my life choices, but it’s my life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Well, it’s my house, it’s my rules.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-17"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Oh, oh, okay, Dad, if I mow the lawn, can I have my allowance?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-18"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Hey, don’t you take that sarcastic tone with him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-19"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>I don’t have to listen to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-20"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Don’t talk to her like that. That is my mother. Wife. My wife. I said my wife.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-21"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>You know what? This isn’t getting us anywhere. When you’re ready to apologize, you know where to find me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-22"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, in my house.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-23"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>That’s right, sucka.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I wish I’d never gone on that trip. I feel no better now than when I left.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>But you still accomplished something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah. If you had told anyone that you were going away on a train by yourself across the country, do you know what they would have said?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That I couldn’t do it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Exactly. Right after they said yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>But you did do it. So what if it didn’t all go your way? That’s what makes it an adventure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s a good point. You know, I’m a lot like Gandalf the Grey. He fought the Balrog and emerged stronger than ever as Gandalf the White. I was robbed of my phone and pants, and I, too, came back stronger. And whiter, too, ’cause I wasn’t in direct sunlight for six weeks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>See? This trip was good for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Indeed. I was the world’s smartest caterpillar. And then after pupating in our nation’s railway system, I’ve burst forth as the world’s smartest butterfly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Butterfly could’ve gotten himself home from Arizona.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, I feel renewed. I’m ready to deal with any changes that come my way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-12"><speaker>All</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-13"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey, look who’s back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Your hair is different. You changed your hair. I can’t take this. I’m out.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Would you like to see pictures from my trip?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I thought your phone got stolen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, it did, but luckily all my photos got backed up to the Cloud.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>And you thought they all had a silver lining.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Here, day one, uh, this was the seat I was going to sit in but didn’t because there were cracker crumbs on it. As it was first class, I suspect Ritz. This is the train bathroom. This is the Imodium I took so I would never have to use the train bathroom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I cannot believe you travelled the entire country and never left the train station.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I know. You know, I almost died in a fire in Des Moines, but I stayed put. FYI, that’s when the Imodium gave out.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>