<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>So, what are you working on these days?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I’m studying one-celled organisms to try and find the neurochemicals that lead to the feeling of shame.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>What would a one-celled organism have to be embarrassed about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Same as all of us, getting out of a car without underwear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Bermadette</speaker><content>Speaking of underwear, I have some interesting news.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, if it’s sometimes Howie wears yours, Leonard already told us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>He was being funny. I’m pretty sure. Anyway, I was asked to be a part of a magazine article about the 50 sexiest female scientists in California. Isn’t that cool?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I think it’s awful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Why would you say that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Bernadette is a successful microbiologist. She should be celebrated for her achievements, not her looks. I mean, what kind of message does that send?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I think the message is check out the rack on that scientist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Why can’t someone be thought of as both smart and pretty?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I just don’t think a professional woman should have to flaunt her sexuality in order to get ahead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, what’s the big deal? Look, if it helps me make a sale with a physician, I don’t think it hurts to flirt a little. I mean, laugh at their joke, touch their arm, maybe crank up the AC in the car beforehand, you know, to wake up the girls.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Maybe it’s different in the world of sales, but it’s already hard enough for women to be taken seriously in science.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I was kind of excited about the article, but now you’re making me feel bad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, I think you should do whatever you want. You know, maybe if fashion magazines had female scientists in them, I would’ve become a theoretical physicist. Stop smirking at each other.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Man with Flowers</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, thank you. Delivery men are the unsung foot soldiers of our nation’s commerce. It’s because of people like you, people like me can limit our human contact. I’d shake your hand, but, well, you know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>I’m not a delivery man, I’m a doctor. Although I do often deliver alarming biopsy results to my patients.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>That’s humorous.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>All right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, I bet you leave your patients in stitches. That was also humorous.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>All right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Are you bringing flowers to a patient to cushion the blow of a terminal diagnosis? That wasn’t a joke.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>All right. These are actually for a nice woman who makes sales calls to my office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hmm. You know, they have delivery people that will do that for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>I was hoping to impress her by tracking her down on the Internet and then showing up unannounced at her door.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Making the extra effort. Good for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Great timing, food just got here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Ooh, Siam Palace?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Uh, mee krob and chicken satay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Uh, extra peanut sauce?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, but you can have mine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Eh, well, very well. Oh, and on the topic of sharing things that are yours, there is a gentleman caller bringing flowers to your fiancée as we speak.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What? Why didn’t you say that first?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-22"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Why didn’t you get extra peanut sauce? We can both play this game.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-23"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Can I help you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-24"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>Oh, hi. Uh, does Penny live here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-25"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>May I ask why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-26"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>Well, uh, I met her at my office, she winked at me. And, uh, I came hoping to initiate a romantic relationship.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-27"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Okay, um, look, I’m pretty sure she didn’t wink at you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-28"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>Oh, she did. Seductively, like this. And then she touched my arm for two Mississippis. Like, you know, one Mississippi, two…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-29"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I got it, I got it. Listen, um, I think there’s been a misunderstanding. See, Penny is my fiancée.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-30"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>Really? I’ve never seen her wear an engagement ring.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-31"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Really?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-32"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>So, am I to presume that her flirtation was just a sales technique?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-33"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I think so.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-34"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>When will I learn? It’s just like the cute girl at the pet store all over again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-35"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Excuse me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-36"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>Oh, uh, she touched my arm for five Mississippis, and I bought a two thousand dollar iguana habitat. Which she was always too busy to come over and see. You give these to Penny. You’re a, you’re a lucky man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-37"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Thank you. Sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-38"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>Oh, uh, you probably don’t want her to see this. It’s unnecessarily graphic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-39"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hold on, Doctor. Leonard, where are your social skills? This man is clearly upset. We should invite him in for a hot beverage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-40"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>He tried to score with Penny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-41"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>So have these two, and they’re having dinner with us.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>So, how was work today?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>It was fine, but you’ll be happy to know they pulled the sexy scientists article.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>What happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I don’t know. They just canceled the photo shoot and said they’re rethinking it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Well, I’m really sorry, but I think it’s for the best. You want people focusing on your achievements, not staring at your breasts in some magazine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I guess. It’s really not that important. Hey, up here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sorry, it’s just we’re, we were talking about them. So, look, I, I wasn’t going to say anything, but since you seem to be okay with the article being canceled, I have a little confession. I’m the reason it was pulled.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>What? How?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I sent the editors of the magazine a pretty scathing e-mail.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Amy, what did you say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I simply pointed out that they would never consider doing an article ranking male scientists on their sexuality, let alone showing them in various stages of undress.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Because no one wants to see Neil deGrasse Tyson in a wet T-shirt, bent over the hood of a Porsche.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Well, it doesn’t make a difference, because they agreed it was in bad taste, and now you agree, so Amy saves the day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>No, what happened was you got jealous, so you took away a chance for me to get some publicity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>But it was bad publicity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>That’s for me to decide, not you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I disagree. As a female scientist, I think what you do affects all of us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>And I think you don’t like people expressing their sexuality because no one wants you to express yours. Oh, Amy, I’m so sorry. That was over the line.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You have a nice night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-20"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Please don’t go. Up until my vicious attack, you were the one in the wrong.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Here you go, Doctor. Red Zinger with one teaspoon of honey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>Thank you. Neat Star Trek mug. I actually have one of the phasers from the original TV show.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, cool.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>How’d you get that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>Oh, easy, Gene Roddenberry needed a vasectomy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Sehldon</speaker><content>Wait a minute. You’ve snipped Gene Roddenberry’s vas deferens?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Wow, he really went where no man has gone before.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>I don’t like to brag,but, uh, you see, I’m kind of the doctor to the stars’ urinary tracts.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>All</speaker><content>Wow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>Uh, you, you want to see James Cameron’s kidney stone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>All</speaker><content>Ooh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>He was so happy after he passed it, he gave me a Terminator.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That is amazing. How long have you been collecting?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>Ever since I was a kid, but, uh, I didn’t really get serious until William Shatner’s bladder infection.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What’d you get? What’d you get?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>Well, he said it was a tribble. It could be a toupee, but either way, it’s pretty cool.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I would love to see your collection.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>Anytime. Uh, I’ve got some cool stuff. When I first started, I thought it would be a good way to meet women, but, well, you know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-20"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>We know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-21"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Preach.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-22"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>Can I ask you a personal question?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-23"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-24"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>Um, I mean, you’re a guy like me, so how’d you get a girl like Penny?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-25"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh. Well, you know, just being myself, really.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-26"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, please, you know, I’ll tell you how he did it. Implacable, relentless badgering. In urology terms, he was a drug-resistant staph infection. And she was a urethra that could not shake him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-27"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I don’t know that I’d call myself an infection.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-28"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>A gallant man would defend his fiancée for being called a urethra.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-29"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Can we please change the subject?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-30"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-31"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Well, that didn’t go your way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-32"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Dr. Lorvis, what are you doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-33"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>Uh, well, actually I came to see you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-34"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Really? Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-35"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Ah, that’s a good question. Apparently someone was being awfully flirty while not wearing their engagement ring, causing another someone to show up here thinking the first someone might be available.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-36"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, God. Don’t make it so hard on her. Look, the first someone is the deceitful you. The second someone is the delightful Dr. Lorvis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-37"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, this is very embarrassing. Dr. Lorvis, I am so sorry. I did not mean to lead you on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-38"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>You touched my arm for two Mississippis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-39"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh. That’s why you were mumbling Mississippi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-40"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Can we talk in private?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-41"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Please, yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-42"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I’ll be right back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-43"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>So what other celebrity genitalia have you handled?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-44"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>So, uh, what’s the deal? You take off your ring when you go to work?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-45"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What? No, no, I just put it on the other hand and turn it around. Keep that hand in my pocket.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-46"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-47"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, what do you mean why? Look, I make more sales if these doctors think I’m single. I did the same kind of thing as a waitress. The real question is, what is he doing in your apartment?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-48"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, he was upset. So Sheldon invited him in for a hot beverage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-49"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>You were okay with that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-50"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No. I got upset. And Sheldon made me a beverage, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-51"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, he just showed up at my door. Don’t you think that’s a little weird?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-52"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>A little, but he’s basically harmless. He’s actually kind of a nice guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-53"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay. Whatever, look, my company does not allow me to socialize with doctors outside of work. You got to get rid of him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-54"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Why am I the one that has to get rid of him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-55"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I can’t do it, he’s my best client.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-56"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>All right, I’ll get rid of him. But you owe me one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-57"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Hey, we’re going to Oliver’s house to see his collection. You want to go with us?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-58"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Yeah, sure. You owe me.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, my God.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Leonard, I was wrong. Heaven does exist. And it’s in the basement of a urologist’s house in Sherman Oaks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>Welcome to my Fortress of Solitude. This is where I go to get away from all my other solitude.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, come on. It’s a replica.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>Original.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, I think I just cheated on my wife.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>The gun from Hellboy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>Yup.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>How did you get it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>Bought it at auction.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, I was hoping for a juicy tidbit about Ron Perlman’s testicles.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Woman’s voice (off)</speaker><content>Oliver, I’m going to play bingo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>Okay, Mother. Have fun.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Still lives with his ma. Yikes, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yeah, I’m not quite sure how to respond.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Wow, Donkey Kong. This, this was my game when I was a kid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Because it’s a story of a pretty blonde girl tirelessly pursued by a small, oddly-shaped man?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-18"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, because I liked it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-19"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, now, don’t get defensive. You’re oddly-shaped, but you got the girl.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-20"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>So, I’ve noticed Leonard gets teased a lot 0about his relationship with Penny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-21"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yes. If you’d like to join in, the premise is their love seems unlikely and doomed to failure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-22"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>So, you think she’ll be single soon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-23"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, if you want to get in on the pool, you’re too late. All the squares have been purchased.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-24"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>Interesting. Excuse me, I have to take care of something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-25"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Leonard, as your friend I feel I should tell you something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-26"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-27"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I’m still upset about that peanut sauce.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>Oh, could you hold the door?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Nice flowers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>Thank you. They’re for a girl. Uh, I’m being implacable and relentless.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Isn’t she lucky?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>She keeps sending me mixed signals. But I think we both want the same thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>What’s that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>Unconditional love.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I guess that’s all anybody wants.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>I guess so.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Well, I hope you get it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>One Mississippi, two Mississippi.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Next game, let’s switch helmets.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, I’d look silly in that helmet.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I can’t take these.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>Why not? I mean, you want what I want. And we had two wonderful Mississippis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>But what about the other girl?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>Oh, right. I’ll tell her we should just be friends.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Dr. Lorvis?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>Penny, we should just be friends. Happy?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You think he bites?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Stick your head in there and find out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You fooled me with that goat at the petting zoo. You will not fool me again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I wonder where Dr. Lorvis is. He’s been gone a while.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Maybe he’s playing bingo with his mommy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>It’s sad how some guys can’t cut the apron strings.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Okay, now you’re messing with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Uh, guys, we’re locked in here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, this day just keeps getting better.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>So, you just left them alone playing games in your house?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>Well, they seemed happy and I thought that would give me time for you and I to get to know each other better. That was before we met.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>We all have a past.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Doc, you’ve got to see what you’re doing is, is a little creepy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>You sound just like Sigourney Weaver when I followed her into a restroom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, you can’t just go chasing after every girl who’s nice to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>Well, that’s not what Sheldon says. And he seems to know his way around the ladies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Penny (on phone)</speaker><content>Hey, Leonard. Guess who’s back. Dr. Lorvis. Yeah. You care to join us? What? You locked them in your basement?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>Well, they’re, they’re not locked in. The door just sticks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, so how do they unstick it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>They’d need the key.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay. Nope. That’s it. We are gonna go over there right now, and you are going to let them out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>Three Mississippi, four Mississippi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Move it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Oh, good, you’re here. Amy, I am so sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>That has to wait. This weirdo locked the guys up in his basement.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>She seems nice. Who’s she?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Just walk.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You can do this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>One ladder left.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh-hom yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Next level.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Leonard, are you okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Better than okay. I am having the game of my life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Dr. Lorvis, isn’t there something you want to say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>Yes. I’m very sorry for locking you in my home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah, that was very uncool. Get the hammer. Get the hammer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Got it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, Leonard, let’s go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Just hang on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>Well, while we wait, would you like to see Tobey Maguire’s prostate sonogram?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-16"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-17"><speaker>Dr Lorvis</speaker><content>Oh, spoiler alert. He was worried about nothing.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>