<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What a wonderful day, thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Oh, we’re glad you had fun.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Blue Icees and a trip to The Container Store? It’s like I died and went to the post-mortem, neuron-induced hallucination commonly mistaken as heaven.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I still don’t understand why you bought that pill caddie. You’re a young man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Age is a state of mind, Leonard. In here I’m 90. Why are you taking your bins over there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It’s just where I need them. You know, she doesn’t have a lot of closet space.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>What’s wrong with your closet?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Uh, well, honey, you know, now that Leonard and I are married, it kind of makes sense that we actually live together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>So that’s all this day was? A plan to butter me up before delivering bad news?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Come on, buddy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, I thought we were friends. You asked for a sip of my Icee. If you had your own straw, I might’ve said yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sheldon, please, we already feel bad about this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You know what they don’t sell at The Container Store? Something large enough to contain my disappointment. Although, if anyone did, it would be them.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Thank you for letting me come speak with you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Of course.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>As my relationships with Penny and Amy are currently strained, I’m turning to you for female comfort and encouragement.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Aw. I’m honoured.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I tried reaching out to my mother, but she was in Bible study. Leonard’s mother is on a book tour. My Mee-Maw was taking a nap, and after a while Siri started repeating her answers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>So, I’m your seventh choice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Yeah, I know, top ten, pretty exciting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>How can I help you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, in addition to Amy leaving me, Leonard’s moving in with Penny. It’s difficult not to feel abandoned.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Well, why don’t you look at this as an opportunity? You had other roommates before Leonard. Maybe this is a chance to find someone new.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Perhaps I could find someone better than Leonard. Someone I can rub in his face. Chris Pratt’s all the rage right now. I wonder how he’d feel about taking the smaller bedroom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Hey. You know who would be the perfect roomie?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Gandalf, but he’s a smoker.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Stuart. He’s been living with us for a while now. I’m sure he’d love to get us out of his hair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Nope, couldn’t be happier.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Well, Sheldon’s looking for a roommate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Nope.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>He’ll think about it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>No I won’t.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Have you seen this Archie comic? It’s actually Archie versus Predator.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>How could Archie defeat Predator?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I don’t know. Maybe Jughead’s a Terminator.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Hey, Stuart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Do you guys know any musicians?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>I was thinking it might be cool to have live music here a few nights a week. You know, give this place more of a staying in business vibe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>What kind of music are you thinking of?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>I like all kinds of music, but my favourite genre is free.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Hey, we’ve always talked about playing together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Well, it could be fun to try a little acoustic thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Oh, we could play filk music.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>What’s that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>It’s been around for years. It’s like folk music, but with a sci-fi/fantasy theme.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>I like it. It sounds exactly like something I shouldn’t be expected to pay for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Dude, if we do this, we’re gonna need a cool band name.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You know, I’ve actually had one I’ve been sitting on for years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Really?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-20"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>It was for this power trio I tried to put together in junior high, but I was short two friends.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-21"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>What is it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-22"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Footprints on the Moon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-23"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I just got chills.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-24"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>So did I.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-25"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Me, too. But I, uh, might have Lyme Disease.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Just a few more signatures, and we’ll be finished. Initial here to acknowledge that you’ve returned your key. Okay. As my future neighbour, I’d like you to have a key. Initial here to acknowledge you received it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>I’m proud of you. You’re taking this really well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Well, it’s not like I’m never going to see you two again. Which brings us to article 23 subsection C, please check here to reserve your spot at the ten year roommate reunion.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Do I really have to do that now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, but if you want chicken and get stuck with the fish, that’s on you. All right. Oh, and lastly, please initial here to confirm that ownership of the living room couch is hereby transferred to me in perpetuity all throughout the universe and all alternate universes except for those universes where owning a couch is forbidden by the hive queen. In which case, all glory to the hive queen. All right, now all that’s left is for us to sign and date the document, and we will officially no longer be roommates.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What’s the matter?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>It’s harder than I thought.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Let me help you. L. E. O. N.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>That helped.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>So I have an idea for a filk song. It’s kind of a, a power ballad, superhero crossover tale of epic proportions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Is it cold in here, ’cause, oh, my.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Okay, so it’s a, it’s a David and Goliath story. It’s about man against God. It’s called Hammer and Whip, The Untold Story of Thor versus Indiana Jones.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Thor versus Indiana Jones? You just blew my filking mind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Okay, I don’t have it all worked out yet, but I was thinking something like, um, Oh, Indy, oh, Indy, the skies are so windy. Is that a flying man with a killer bod? Wait, that’s no man, it’s a Norse god.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh yes, definitely. Hang on. Thunder clapped as Thor raised his mighty hammer. Indy rapped, that’s one bad mamma-jamma.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>That is, that is so good!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Right? Mamma-jamma just came to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Okay, and here’s the hook. Thor and Dr. Jones. Thor and Dr. Jones. One plays with lightning, the other plays with bones.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Together</speaker><content>Thor and Dr. Jones. Thor and Dr. Jones. One plays with lightning, the other plays with bones.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, man, that rocks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Hey, remember The Ark of the Covenant?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Yeah?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>That’s how much we’re gonna melt people’s faces off.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I appreciate your interest in the apartment. I just need to ask you a few standard questions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Bespectacled Man</speaker><content>Sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>It says here you’re a chemist. Which element on the periodic table do you feel is too big for its britches?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Bespectacled Man</speaker><content>Is that supposed to be a joke?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Looks like argon’s not the only one with an attitude problem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>In general, would you say that you smell better, worse or the same as you do right now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I was going to ask you what is the best fruit, but then I realized what I want to ask you is why is there a Band-Aid on your forearm, but then I realized what I really want to ask you is just can you just go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You’re healthy. You have a job in the sciences. I’ve got to say, if this credit report comes back good, you’re the frontrunner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Amy (on Skype)</speaker><content>I’m not gonna be your roommate, Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>But I met with 11 people, and they all walked out. And that Hollywood phoney Chris Pratt never tweeted me back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I’m sure you’ll find somebody else.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>I suppose. What happened to me, Amy? Years ago I was completely disengaged from my feelings. I’d say it was a happier time, but I was disengaged from my feelings, so who can tell?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I don’t know how to help you. You know, feelings are a part of life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>They didn’t used to be. You and Leonard and Penny, you all poisoned me with emotions. I was like the Tin Man, perfectly content until that evil wizard gave him a heart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I don’t think that was the point of the movie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Fine, then I was like Pinocchio before that jerk Geppetto went and made him a real boy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>There you go.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>So, what are you thinking for dinner?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Well, it’s Thai food night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, honey, you don’t live with Sheldon any more. You can have anything you want.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You’re right. But what? Mexican? Italian? German? Indian? Greek? Cuban? Chinese? Pizza? Barbecue? Korean? Korean barbecue?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>How about Thai food?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Oh, thank God.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hey, we’re going to dinner. You want to come?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Oh, I wish I could, but I realized I’ve become too emotionally vulnerable, so, like an operating system, I’m restoring my life to the last stable version, which was in 2003, the day before I met Leonard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>You heard him, no.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Hang on. Wait, you actually think it’s 2003?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, just because I’m living my life like it was 12 years ago doesn’t mean I’m delusional. And since it is 2003, I don’t know who you are, so please exit the premises before I call the police on my stylish new flip phone.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Are you doing okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I guess. I’m just, you know, worried about Sheldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, come on, he’s a grown man in his 30s pretending to be a grown man in his 20s. He’s fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I hope so.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>What else can you do? Move back in with him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>No, of course not. I just feel bad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, so do I, but don’t you want to live with your wife and set the thermostat to whatever you want and have your body tell you when it’s time to go to the bathroom, you know, not a schedule slipped underneath your door every morning?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I did like that he had the weather on it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Trust me, this is the right thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I know. And it’s not like we’re abandoning him. Plus, we can FaceTime him whenever we want, you know, once iPhones are invented in his universe.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I can’t believe Sheldon asked you to be his roommate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>I can’t believe he ran my credit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>Hey, if you’re open to living with someone great, I’ll give you a thousand dollars to take Stuart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>You really should’ve gone on the Internet and checked how long that kind of thing lives before you got one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Bernadette</speaker><content>I’m sorry. I just thought you might have a pasty, weirdo-shaped hole in your life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Hey, I know Sheldon’s quirky, but he’s also brilliant and insightful. I think calling him a weirdo is a little unfair.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>Hello, 2003.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Hey, we brought you Thai. Where is everything?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>In my present, it’s in the future. In your present, it’s been crammed in the bedroom by an enterprising young man I met in The Home Depot parking lot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>I know what you’re doing. You’re trying to get attention so we’ll feel bad for you, but it’s not happening.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, what I’m doing is trying to figure out how to live my life now that everyone is leaving me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Will you knock it off? We’re across the hall.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>As the kids are saying today, talk to the hand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>They’re not saying that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>They are in 2003.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>No, no, they’re really not.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Raj (singing)</speaker><content>Thor and Dr. Jones. Thor and Dr. Jones. One runs from Loki, the other runs from stones. So, what do you think?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Emily</speaker><content>Wow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Runs from stones means that, that big boulder, but I couldn’t rhyme anything with boulder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Emily</speaker><content>Colder, shoulder, soldier, folder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Right, yeah, right. But, what do you think?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Emily</speaker><content>I think it’s very cute.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Cute? It’s not cute. Cute is children dressed as vegetables.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Emily</speaker><content>Okay, fine, it’s not cute.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Just be honest. You don’t like it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Emily</speaker><content>I didn’t say that. I, I just like music you can dance to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You can dance to this. Um, uh, uh, Thor and Dr. Jones. Thor and Dr. Jones. One plays with lightning, the other plays with bones.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I’m telling you, dude, the song has no groove, you can’t dance to it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Who cares? I thought the whole point of Footprints on the Moon was to write songs that make people think.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>You can do both, like Michael Jackson’s Billie Jean. While you’re dancing you’re thinking, like, darn it, whose baby is it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Where’s this coming from? A few hours ago, we both loved this song.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>I still love it. I just think there’s room for improvement.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You played it for Emily, didn’t you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Yeah, so what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>You are such a wimp. She didn’t like it, now you don’t like it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>No, no. I’m just evolving as a musician. You’re the one who’s stuck in the past.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>The past was lunch. You know what’s really happening here? Your girlfriend is breaking up our band.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>She has nothing to do with this. I am my own man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Oh, please. Your brain belongs to whoever’s willing to sleep with you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>That is so not true.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Really? Remember when you were gonna get circumcised for Rachel Bernstein?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>That had nothing to do with Rachel. It was an overreaction to a bad zipper injury.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-16"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>I don’t need this. I’m quitting the band.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-17"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Fine, I quit, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-18"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Then get out of my house.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-19"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>With pleasure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-20"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Raj, wait.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-21"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>What took you so long?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Buddy, I know me moving in with Penny feels like a big change, but it’s not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>How can you say that? Amy’s gone, and you two are married now, so it’s only a matter of time before you’re gone, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, you don’t know what’s gonna happen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>No, I do. Eventually you’ll want more space, and you’ll move into a house, and then instead of dinner a couple of times a week, it’ll only be a couple of times a month, and then it’ll only be on special occasions, like when Bernadette divorces Wolowitz. Or, or, or like when Koothrappali’s weird girlfriend admits where she buried his body. Or Amy’s wedding, where she’s marrying someone better than me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Okay, look, we don’t need to rush into anything. All right? Maybe instead of Leonard moving in with me, we just leave things the way they are, and sometimes we’ll sleep over there, and sometimes we’ll sleep over here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>But mostly here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Wuh, what about what you said in the restaurant?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>Penny</speaker><content>Well, it’s not forever. It’s just for a while. If you want, we can think of him like he’s our dog.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>You can. I’m happy when you come home. And I’m scared of fireworks. By the way, on July Fourth, we’re all sleeping here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>Leonard</speaker><content>Fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-12"><speaker>Sheldon</speaker><content>All right, great. Just give me one minute, and I’ll get started on a new roommate agreement. Yeah. nothing from Pratt, we’re good.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>Howard (singing)</speaker><content>Indy’ whip snapped, Thor’s hammer missed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>Raj (singing)</speaker><content>It was Avenger versus archeologist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>Howard</speaker><content>Indy held his ground, and straightened his fedora.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>Raj</speaker><content>Thor said, that’s a nice look in nineteen fourty-foura.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>Together</speaker><content>Thor and Dr. Jones. Thor and Dr. Jones. One plays with lightning, the other plays with bones. Thor and Dr. Jones. Thor and Dr. Jones. One plays with lightning, the other plays with bones.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>Stuart</speaker><content>Play something we can dance to.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>