<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>


<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>POLICE LAWYER</speaker><content>Mr. Castle, be advised if you get injured following Detective Beckett to research your next novel, you cannot sue the city. If you get shot, you cannot sue the city. If you get killed--</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>RICHARD CASTLE</speaker><content>My lifeless remains cannot sue the city?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>LAWYER</speaker><content>Your heirs, Mr. Castle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>DETECTIVE KATE BECKETT</speaker><content>Do I have to wait for him to sign or can I shoot him now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>LAWYER</speaker><content>Mr. Castle, these waivers are a serious business. Perhaps you’d feel more comfortable by referring the matter to your attorney?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What, are you kidding? He’d never let me sign these. But fortunately it’s his job to get me out of trouble, and not to prevent me from getting into it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content/></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oooh wait, where are you going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I’ve work to do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What, we have a case?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, I have a case. You have paperwork. Oooh ow.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>DETECTIVE KEVIN RYAN</speaker><content>Mrs. Rosenberg, 9E here, comes down to put her clothes in the dryer, finds it’s occupied, comes down a half an hour later and she’s had enough. Decides to take matters into her own hands.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Come on, you’re telling me an old lady killed someone over a busy dryer?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>What? No, she’s just tired of waiting around. So, she opens up the dryer to take the other person's clothes out. Finds Miss Fluff and Fold here instead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>DETECTIVE JAVIER ESPOSITO</speaker><content>If that’s not a cautionary tale about poking around someone’s laundry, I don’t know what is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Dude, there is an etiquette involved. If the clothes were dry, Mrs Rosenberg had every right to put them in the basket. Now, if you're going to tell me that she folded them, then it gets a little creepy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I’m sorry, but if someone starts rooting around in my underwear without an invitation, I’m taking it as a serious breach of hygiene.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I thought you went commando, Esposito?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well. It’s a seasonal thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>All right, let's get her out of there with some dignity. I’m gonna need CSU to come down here, and the bleach bottle will have to go down to the lab, probably prints and photographs although I don’t know if it’s going to do us much good in a public area. I’m guessing she lived here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Worked. 12F, she’s the nanny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Thought you ditched me back at the precinct, didn’t you? Come on, Nanny McDead is found in the spin dryer, you don’t think the captain's going to let me in on that story?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You’re right, Castle. My bad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s hard to say. When I’m writing a new character it’s hard to tell when inspiration might strike.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I thought I was your inspiration.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, you are, Detective, and in so many ways.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, well, your inspiration might strike you sooner than you might think.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content/></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mrs. Peterson? Detective Kate Beckett, NYPD. I was wondering if I could ask you some questions about Sarah Manning?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>MRS PETERSON</speaker><content>Of course, please come in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Richard Castle. Just NY.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>MRS PETERSON</speaker><content/></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>MR PETERSON</speaker><content>Sarah was very close with him. She, she just has a gift with kids, you know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>MRS PETERSON</speaker><content>She was such a lovely girl.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I’m very sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>MRS PETERSON</speaker><content>The school called me at my office when Sarah didn’t come to pick up Justin. I tried her cell phone but it went straight to her voicemail. Then I tried here but the machine picked up so I hopped in a cab and went to the school. When we got home the police were already here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>When was the last time you saw Sarah?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>MRS PETERSON</speaker><content>My husband saw her last night when he got home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>MR PETERSON</speaker><content>We take Justin to school every morning, so we’re usually gone by the time she gets here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And what time is that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>MRS PETERSON</speaker><content>Today it would have been eleven. Sarah straightens up, does Justin’s laundry and then picks him up from school about two. One of us is then home for dinner. Last night it was my husband's turn.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So then you were the last one to see Sarah?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>MR PETERSON</speaker><content>I, I guess so?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Did she mention any problems she was having, maybe a boyfriend?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>MRS PETERSON</speaker><content>Sarah’s boyfriend?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>MR PETERSON</speaker><content>The, the doorman said the police told them that it was a break-in, which usually means a stranger did it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We can’t be sure what happened.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, maybe not, but statically speaking it's a much greater likelihood that it was someone she knew.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>MRS PETERSON</speaker><content>Oh my God.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Again, we can’t be certain who was involved.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>But she had a boyfriend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-21"><speaker>MR PETERSON</speaker><content>Brent, but they broke up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And when was that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-23"><speaker>MRS PETERSON</speaker><content>About a month ago, but Sarah never said that there was any trouble or anything like that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Brent? That was his name?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-25"><speaker>MRS PETERSON</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-26"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you know his last name?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-27"><speaker>MRS PETERSON</speaker><content>Uhh, I don’t think Sarah ever mentioned it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-28"><speaker>MR PETERSON</speaker><content>Not to me either.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-29"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Thank you both so much for your time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-30"><speaker>MRS PETERSON</speaker><content>Of course.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-31"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, let's go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-32"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What, that’s it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-33"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s it. Oh, do you know of any way I can reach Sarah’s parents?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-34"><speaker>MRS PETERSON</speaker><content>Oh God, I hadn’t even thought of that. Uhh, I’m sorry we don’t have their number.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-35"><speaker>MR PETERSON</speaker><content>They live in Atlanta, she was with them over Christmas.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-36"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What about Sarah’s things?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-37"><speaker>MRS PETERSON</speaker><content>There’s her bag and her jacket.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-38"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Maybe I could take it and check her cell phone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-39"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content/></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-40"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Because I actually like to investigate things myself first. Besides, neither of them is going anywhere. Ah, there’s no cell phone in here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-41"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Maybe it’s in the laundry room? Or in the dryer?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-42"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, if it is, CSU will find it.  She’s still got her Georgia license.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-43"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Are you really the one who has to call her parents?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-44"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Easier to write about than to live through, huh, Castle?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Three men huddled around a computer? That better not be porn. And if it is, I want in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>CAPTAIN ROY MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>Esposito and Ryan pulled security tape from the elevator in the rear entrance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Front door has a twenty four hour doorman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>ESPOSITIO</speaker><content>This is the elevator's cam. Our victim gets on the elevator with her laundry basket. Takes it down to the basement to put the kid's laundry into the washer. A few minutes later, gets back on and goes all the way back up to the apartment. Then about forty minutes later, rides the elevator back down to the basement again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>We figure probably to take the kid's clothes out of the washer and put them in to the dryer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>Cam never picks her up again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Only other person who rides the elevator all the way down to the basement during the next hour is the old lady who found the body.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So whoever attacked her must have used the stairwell. Otherwise the cam would have caught him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Three maintenance workers on duty that day; we’ll run their names tonight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Why only run the workers' names? Why not run all the neighbours' names?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What are you basing that on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’m basing that on, the neighbour would make a better story.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh come on, what do any of us know about our neighbours in this city? Do you think the guy living next door to the 'Son of Sam’ knew he was living next door to the 'Son of Sam’?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>He’s right. Neighbours in Berkowitz's building had no idea he was Son of Sam killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Thank you. What about the guy in 8B?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Who?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>8B. Quiet guy, you see him everyday, only you never notice him. He noticed Sarah, she’s young. Beautiful. The kind of girl a guy like him would never have the chance with.  We all know girls like that, don’t we? Well, first it’s just a game, figure out her schedule. When does she do her laundry? When is she alone? Then it becomes something more, something that he can’t control. He uses the stairs, obviously, to avoid the elevator's cameras, and then he just waits.  Concealed in the shadows - and when she comes into that laundry room, he pounces. And when he looked into her vacant lifeless eyes, he wanted to tell her, he never meant to kill her. All he ever wanted was to be noticed. That’s when he felt the heat of that dryer on his skin. So, he picks up her limp body in his arms and gently places it inside. He almost smiled at his good fortune when he found a quarter in his pocket, slipping it in to the slot, buying him time, to do what he does best…  disappear.  Just saying, better story. Coffee?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>Let's see what we can find out about those neighbours. And someone better tell me who the hell lives in 8B.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Let me guess, Gram cooked?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>ALEXIS CASTLE</speaker><content>Chicken masala.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Where is Hurricane Martha?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>In her room, taking a dramatic pause.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Leaving the mess for everyone else to clean up, as usual.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>I don’t mind. Dinner was fun.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, it’s our room, not hers. Just remember that, even despite that hideous bedspread she bought.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>If you’re hungry, there are lots of leftovers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, thank you. I grabbed a slice on the way home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>You really are turning into a cop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah? Do you think?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>So, who got killed today?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The nanny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Do they know who did it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, apparently in an actual homicide they don’t know who did it until after the guy gets caught.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>How come we never had a nanny?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, your mother and I decided if someone was going to screw you up, we wanted it to be me. Only you managed to turn out fine somehow anyway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-18"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Surprisingly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-19"><speaker>MARTHA RODGERS</speaker><content>Is that the prodigal son I hear return from working the night shift? Catch any 'perps' today, kiddo? I did an NYPD Blue once, remember?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-20"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>You were the crazy homeless woman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And some might say still are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-22"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>I was just asking Dad how come we never had a nanny when I was little.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-23"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I spared her any stories of my own personal experience.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-24"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>I had a real job as a working actress. You know, not everybody can sit at home in front of a laptop and claim to be employed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-25"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Really? You had a nanny?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-26"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, only we didn’t call them nannies then.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-27"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>What were they called?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-28"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh I don’t know? Alcoholics? Raving lunatics? No, no, no, wait, completely irresponsible middle-aged women who, instead of looking after me while you were acting, like they were supposed to, instead watched daytime television.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-29"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Oh, stop your whining, you didn’t turn out half bad. And don’t forget, the good half are my genes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-30"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, that’s just something we’ll have to take your word, for isn’t it? But I’m not asking for an apology, Mother. Actually, I got the plot of my first novel by watching One Life to Live.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-31"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>There you go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-32"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ah.  Detective Beckett, did you miss me already?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-33"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content> Which means, I’m one quarter responsible for your success as well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-34"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Really? Do they do those at night? No, for sure, I’m just, I’m just touched that you thought of me. Oh, ordered to call me, I see. Well, either way, I can leave right away.  OK. Gotta go, I would say don’t wait up, but you'll be asleep by eleven.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-35"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Ten thirty, it’s a school night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-36"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Are you sure she’s got either one of our genes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-37"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Ah well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-38"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You will help her with the dishes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-39"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>All right. Be careful, Flatfoot.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content/></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Really? I thought cops just stood around the body eating ham sandwiches, cracking jokes. You know, hardcore gallows humour.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>DR LANIE PARISH</speaker><content>The head trauma definitely contributed to the death. The force of the blows resulted in significant cerebral haemorrhaging. Mr. Castle, nice to see you again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Wish I could say the same, but my glasses are all scratchy. How often do they let you replace these?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Not everybody has your budget, Castle. So what killed her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>I'd say she was struck in the head with the bleach bottle, then fell forward and hit her temple on the edge of the table. That caused temporal bleeding. Without medical attention she didn’t stand a chance. But what I though you might find really interesting is the fact that she had sex within the hours before her death.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Sex?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’ll explain how that works later.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Might even have been within a few minutes of the murder. The heat from the dryer makes it hard to pinpoint.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So you're saying she was raped?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Hard to determine; there were no vaginal lacerations or presence of any semen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So what's the evidence of sex?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Traces of spermicide. The guy wore a condom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Condom?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Boy, it really has been a long time for you, hasn't it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>I mean it could have been a rape, but my best guess is…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She knew the guy.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Without evidence of trauma, I'm not ready to buy our attacker as a sexual predator, especially with him using a condom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Could be he's trying to hide DNA.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Dude, someone smart enough to hide DNA would have been smart enough not to have sex in the laundry room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You're missing the point. The laundry room afforded opportunity; it wasn't an accident she was killed there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>Esposito, where are we on her cell phone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I've pulled her records. Had her service provider ping it, triangulation puts it at or near the building.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>Well, maybe he took it so she couldn't call for help, then dumped it somewhere close by. What about her ex-boyfriend?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>We have his first name, Brent. But if we had her cell phone, he might be in her address book.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What about these calls?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What calls?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Last two months there are dozens of incoming calls from the same number.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Right, we're still running that down, but the number's a prepay. Besides, they stopped coming a couple of weeks before she was killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, but the outgoing calls to that number stopped even before that. Whoever it was, she didn't want to talk to them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>She was letting it go to voicemail.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>Find this kid Brent and bring him in for questioning.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content/></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Got it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Good. Brent Johnson?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>BRENT JOHNSON</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I'm Detective Kate Beckett, this is Mr. Castle. Suppose you know why you're here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>BRENT</speaker><content>Um, the cops who picked me up at my job said you had some questions about what happened to Sarah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I understand that the two of you were dating?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>BRENT</speaker><content>Yeah, ‘til about a month ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>A month ago? What happened then?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>BRENT</speaker><content>Nothing. We broke up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Whose idea was that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>BRENT</speaker><content>It was a mutual thing, I guess.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>A mutual thing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>BRENT</speaker><content>Hey, Sarah it's me, just call me back, okay? -- You can just call me back Sarah, don't be a *****. -- Come on, Sarah, I just want to talk to you, I don't know why you can't tell me who this other guy is? Do you know, you're just a little slut...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>There's plenty more of those.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yep, they make Alec Baldwin's messages sound like rainbows and unicorns.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>BRENT</speaker><content>How did you get those?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>From your service provider.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>A little advice -- when you buy a prepaid phone, don't use your credit card, it's totally traceable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-20"><speaker>BRENT</speaker><content>I wasn't trying to hide anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No? Then why did you just lie to me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>'Cause no man likes getting dumped. Am I right? Our egos can't handle it. This one time I had an ex-girlfriend, she dumped me. I drank every meal for a week, and I didn't even like her. If I'd loved her, WOW, I don't know what I would  ...have done.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-23"><speaker>BRENT</speaker><content>No, no, no way, it wasn't like that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh, no? So then how did you find out about Sarah if you two broke up a month ago?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-25"><speaker>BRENT</speaker><content>From a friend. Chloe, Chloe Richardson, all right? We all went to college together. Chloe was the one who got Sarah her job.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-26"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And how did this friend find out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-27"><speaker>BRENT</speaker><content>Chloe nannies for another family in the building, the two of them are pretty close.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-28"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So then where were you the day that Sarah got killed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-29"><speaker>BRENT</speaker><content>I was where those other cops found me, at my job. We have video cameras there and a sign in sheet. Look, I didn't have anything to do with this. Am I under arrest or something?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-30"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, you can go. But just don't leave town until we speak again. Do you understand?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-31"><speaker>BRENT</speaker><content>Yeah, yes ma'am.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-32"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Don't leave town? Don't you need probable cause for something like that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-33"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He doesn't know that, does he?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-34"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You can lie like that? That is so cool.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-35"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Doorman told Esposito that this is the playground where all the nannies in the building go, so hopefully we'll find Chloe here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That brings me back a bit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>A bit? I'm thinking it's a little bit more than that, Castle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I'm not talking about when I was a kid. I'm talking about when I used to take my daughter to the park.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You used to take your daughter to the park?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Spring, summer, fall, we were here every day. Alexis's mom was doing community theatre. She was on the road a lot, so I had custody.  What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Nothing, I just never figured you for Mister Mom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Some of the best days of my life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That's actually kinda nice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, tell me about it. Do you know how many lonely single mothers there are in a Manhattan playground? And there I was between marriages.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Exactly how many times have you been married, Castle?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Twice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That's it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Isn't that enough? How about you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Me? No. Never been.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Really?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yep.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You'd be good at it. You're both controlling and disapproving. You should really try it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I'm not an 'if at first you don't succeed' kind of a girl, Castle. When it comes to marriage I'm more of a 'one and done' type.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hmm, any serious candidates?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Doorman said she'd have a red vest on, that might be our girl.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-22"><speaker>CHLOE ROBINSON</speaker><content>Umm, right, right now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, it won't take long.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-24"><speaker>CHLOE</speaker><content>Yeah, ah, Maggie, can you watch Becca for a sec?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-25"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Sarah's boyfriend told us that you helped her get her job?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-26"><speaker>CHLOE</speaker><content>Ah, you talked to Brent?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-27"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Umhm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-28"><speaker>CHLOE</speaker><content>When we got out of school, Sarah couldn't find work. She was temping all over town. I nannied for a family in the same building, and heard that the Petersons were looking for someone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-29"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>When was the last time you saw Sarah?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-30"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I know what it feels like to lose somebody, Chloe, but we need to ask you these questions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-31"><speaker>CHLOE</speaker><content>Yeah. Um. Sometimes we'd meet up before work, get a coffee in Columbus and walk over to work together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-32"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Did you get coffee that day?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-33"><speaker>CHLOE</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-34"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Did she say anything to you? Did she seem upset?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-35"><speaker>CHLOE</speaker><content>Upset? Upset about what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-36"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Brent gave us the impression that Sarah was seeing someone else.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-37"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You know who it was, don't you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-38"><speaker>CHLOE</speaker><content>Sometimes Sarah would stay late.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-39"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Stay late where? At the Petersons'?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-40"><speaker>CHLOE</speaker><content>Yeah. We'd get off work at the same times so we'd take the train home together. I live with a roommate a couple of blocks from Sarah. Only the last few months she'd been staying late. Mr. and Mrs. Peterson kinda take turns coming home for dinner, you know?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-41"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, Mrs. Peterson told us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-42"><speaker>CHLOE</speaker><content>God, I don't want to say something and then… I mean, he's married.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-43"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Wait a minute, Sarah told you about him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-44"><speaker>CHLOE</speaker><content>No, not exactly. It's just the nights Mrs. Peterson didn't come home for dinner? Those were the only nights Sarah stayed late.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I told you we should have asked the husband more questions that day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And I told you I like to question my most likely suspects after I know more about them; that way they're tied to more specific answers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You suspected him too?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The husband? Duh!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You would really clean up at my poker game.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Right, you, James Patterson, and the rest of the Times Best Seller list. No, thank you, Castle. A little too rich for my blood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>We could always make it strip poker.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Sorry, but I prefer mystery to horror.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>MR PETERSON</speaker><content>No, yeah, I'm in the space right now, but like I told you guys, I'm going to need at least twenty thousand square feet.  Listen, I'm going to give you guys a call back to let you know if the client is interested, OK? Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hi, remember us?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>When was the last time you saw Sarah, Mr. Peterson?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>MR PETERSON</speaker><content>The night before she was killed, I told you that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Which was your night to be home for dinner, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>MR PETERSON</speaker><content>Right. What, what are you asking?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, Mr Peterson -</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We have information that suggests that Sarah Manning was having a relationship.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>MR PETERSON</speaker><content>Right, she had a boyfriend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Someone else.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>MR PETERSON</speaker><content>Someone else who?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hmm mmm hmmm </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>MR PETERSON</speaker><content>Me? You think I was having an affair with Sarah?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Bingo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>MR PETERSON</speaker><content>That is, that's crazy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Is it? We know that she stayed late some nights.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>MR PETERSON</speaker><content>Right, she helped us make dinner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Us? Well, what we heard was she helped on the nights your wife wasn't home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-17"><speaker>MR PETERSON</speaker><content>First of all, it's not what you think.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>When is it ever?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-19"><speaker>MR PETERSON</speaker><content>Yes. I was having an affair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So what happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-21"><speaker>MR PETERSON</speaker><content>What do you mean what happened? I cheated, strayed, whatever you want to call it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-22"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I mean in the laundry room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-23"><speaker>MR PETERSON</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You just said that you --</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-25"><speaker>MR PETERSON</speaker><content>Yes, I was having an affair, but it wasn't with Sarah, for God's sake. It was with another woman at my office. Look, every night that I was supposed to be home having dinner I wasn't. You can check the land lines from the apartment. I called to make sure that Sarah was OK every night. You can check cell phone records, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-26"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Don't leave town.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hey, what happened with the husband?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He was cheating, just not with our victim. Here, I need you to run it down. This is her name.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I'm telling you, true commitment is a thing of the past. I mean, name one happily married couple.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Degeneres and Di Rossi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Oooh, think he got you there, bro.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What is this, The View? Where are we on the boyfriend?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Story checks out, video and a sign-in sheet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Great, so all we have is a cheating husband with a possible alibi and no cell phone to run the perp's finger prints.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I got something better.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Please tell me it's that the mayor wants him out of here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Have you ever noticed how she gets a little grumpy when she doesn’t have a suspect?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>We got one now. Guess who wasn't where they say they were when Sarah Manning was killed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Who?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Come on, you gotta guess.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ryan. Ryan, I'm not guessing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-16"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>You're a killjoy, you know that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Exactly what I've been telling her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content/></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-19"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Pretty good huh? Told you, you should have guessed.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You weren't at the office the day that Sarah Manning was killed, were you? You lied to me, Mrs Peterson. Detective Ryan checked with your son's school, the day they called about Sarah not showing up. Your assistant said that you were unreachable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>MRS PETERSON</speaker><content>What are you talking about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I'm talking about Sarah Manning, Mrs Peterson. We're talking about why you lied about where you were the day she was killed. And we know you weren't in your office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It would have been easy to sneak into the building. Doorman could have been outside hailing a cab, taking a delivery.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>MRS PETERSON</speaker><content>My husband is having an affair, did you know that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Actually we did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>MRS PETERSON</speaker><content>All these months I had no idea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Then you found out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>MRS PETERSON</speaker><content>Yes. Sarah told me a few weeks ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Sarah told you about the affair?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>MRS PETERSON</speaker><content>Yes, and she'd been an absolute wreck about keeping it from me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, I bet she was.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-13"><speaker>MRS PETERSON</speaker><content>Did you know he was paying her extra?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, he didn't mention that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-15"><speaker>MRS PETERSON</speaker><content>Can you imagine putting Sarah in the middle of something like that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Something like what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-17"><speaker>MRS PETERSON</speaker><content>He used Sarah to cover for himself. I mean, it's disgusting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I don't understand, Mrs Peterson. If you had nothing to do with Sarah's death, then why did you lie?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-19"><speaker>MRS PETERSON</speaker><content>Because my cheating husband has no idea I'm about to serve him with divorce papers. I lied because I was at my lawyers' that afternoon. Howard's not the only one who can keep a secret.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Don't be... hello there, what are you up to?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Oh, you're not webcamming again, I hope.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I burned a DVD from security cameras that the police are looking at, and I've never webcammed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>That's your story and you're sticking to it, huh? The police just let you burn the DVD. You do realise you have to stop stealing evidence, right? I thought the whole purpose of following this detective around was to help you to write?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It's called research, Mother.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Oh, better hope this last Derrick Storm book sells, my boy, because research don't pay the bills. Is that the nanny?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Mmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>What married woman in her right mind invites a girl that pretty into her own home?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-12"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>What are you guys watching?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I'm watching, she's butting in. Police can't find the nanny's cell phone. They were hoping to lift some fingerprints from it. Thought I could see if she had it with her when she went down to the laundry room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-14"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>And?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It's in her hand the first time she brings her clothes down to the washer, then she doesn't have it when she goes down to use the dryer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-16"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>So she probably left it upstairs in the apartment where she worked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>They say they can't find it. Wait a sec.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-18"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>There's a five-second time difference.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-20"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>A five-second time difference in what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>She rides the elevator twice to the basement, the first time to put the clothes in the washer, the second time to put them in the dryer. Only the second time the trip takes five seconds longer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-22"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Why would it take her longer to travel the same distance?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-23"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It wouldn't.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Not quite sure where you're going with this, Castle?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Up. All right, thirty-two seconds. It takes thirty-two seconds to get from the basement to the twelfth floor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Great, I'll alert the media.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Only the second time, it took her thirty-seven seconds.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why would it take her five extra seconds?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Because the second time she wasn't coming from the twelfth floor, she was coming from the...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Fifteenth floor? This doesn't make any sense. The Petersons live on twelve.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, but I bet the guy who wears that condom lives on fifteen. By the way, that whole elevator thing -- I just did that because you smelled nice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, you can't just knock on people's doors.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Why not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-11"><speaker>OLD GUY</speaker><content>Who is it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Because you're going to freak them out. Police.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-13"><speaker>OLD GUY</speaker><content>You're the police?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>She is. I'm sorry, do you live here alone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-15"><speaker>OLD GUY</speaker><content>Yeah, why do you want to know?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Don't worry about it, you're not young enough.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-17"><speaker>OLD GUY</speaker><content>Young enough for what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>To have sex.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-19"><speaker>OLD GUY</speaker><content>What kind of cops did you say you were?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He's not a cop, I'm a cop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-21"><speaker>OLD GUY</speaker><content>And you're looking for someone to have sex with?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-22"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, look.  So sorry to bother you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-23"><speaker>OLD GUY</speaker><content/></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Pardon me. Is this little girl Becca?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>MRS HARRIS</speaker><content>I'm sorry. I'm not sure I'm following.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Prior to her murder, we believe Sarah Manning was coming from this floor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>MRS HARRIS</speaker><content>Well, I don't know anything about that. I was at work. Maybe she came up to see Chloe?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Chloe Richards?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>MRS HARRIS</speaker><content>She and Sarah were friends and our kids would get together sometimes for play dates.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>MR HARRIS</speaker><content>Hey babe, what's going on? I thought you were going out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>MRS HARRIS</speaker><content>It's the police.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>MR HARRIS</speaker><content>Police?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>MRS HARRIS</speaker><content>They think Chloe's friend Sarah might have been up here the day she was killed. You were home that day, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-10"><speaker>MR HARRIS</speaker><content>Umm, what day was that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Tuesday.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-12"><speaker>MR HARRIS</speaker><content>Yeah, yeah, I was here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So did you see Sarah?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-14"><speaker>MR HARRIS</speaker><content>I don't think so, no.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You don't think so?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-16"><speaker>MR HARRIS</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Mind if I use your bathroom? People never think about that, when do cops use the bathroom?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-18"><speaker>MRS HARRIS</speaker><content>It's right here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So, Tuesday?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-21"><speaker>MR HARRIS</speaker><content>Yeah, let me think a minute.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-22"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So you're saying that you can't say one way or the other.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-23"><speaker>MR HARRIS</speaker><content>After Chloe got here to take care of Becca I went inside to take a nap. I work most nights.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-24"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content/></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-25"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And what is it that you do, Mr. Harris?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-26"><speaker>MR HARRIS</speaker><content>I'm a musician.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-27"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Condoms in the bathroom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-28"><speaker>MR HARRIS</speaker><content>So, anyway, it's possible that Sarah was up here. I couldn't really say for sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-29"><speaker>MRS HARRIS</speaker><content>You know, maybe you should talk to Chloe about this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-30"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I already have.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-31"><speaker>MRS HARRIS</speaker><content>And what did she tell you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-32"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She said that she saw Sarah earlier in the day but she didn't say anything about Sarah being in your apartment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-33"><speaker>MRS HARRIS</speaker><content>What else would she be doing up here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-34"><speaker>MRS HARRIS</speaker><content>What's that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-35"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That sounds like somebody’s cell phone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-36"><speaker>MRS HARRIS</speaker><content/></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>MR HARRIS</speaker><content>Maybe she dropped it. I don't know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You told me you went into the bedroom to take a nap. How could she go into the room, drop the phone and you not see her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>She's right, it doesn’t make sense when you think about it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We're running a test on the condoms we found in your medicine cabinet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ho ho, now there's something you never want to hear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>If the spermicides match you're facing a murder charge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>MR HARRIS</speaker><content>I didn't kill Sarah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>But you were sleeping with her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-9"><speaker>MR HARRIS</speaker><content>Look, we had sex, OK. But when Sarah left my place she was fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You followed her down to the basement, didn't you? You followed her in to the basement and then you killed her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-11"><speaker>MR HARRIS</speaker><content>No, I wouldn't hurt Sarah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You wouldn't hurt her? You're a married man sleeping with her in your own bed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What time did she leave your apartment?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-14"><speaker>MR HARRIS</speaker><content>A little before one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>How can you be sure?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-16"><speaker>MR HARRIS</speaker><content>Because Chloe gets home from the park with Becca every day around one to give her her lunch. Sarah left maybe ten minutes before Chloe got back. Look, you ask Chloe, she will tell you there was no way that I could have killed Sarah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-17"><speaker>FRANK GARRISON</speaker><content>Detective Beckett, Frank Garrison. I've been retained to represent Mr. Harris, and I'm directing him not to answer any more of your questions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Your client can answer them here or he can answer them in front of a grand jury.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-19"><speaker>GARRISON</speaker><content>If you've got enough to charge him, do it. Otherwise he's coming with me. Let's go, Mr Harris.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I guess it's a lot tougher when they actually know the rules, huh?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Thank you. Lab says condoms are a match.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>So it proves they had sex.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Look, if Chloe got home at one o’clock then there's no way he had time to get down to the basement, kill Sarah, and make it back upstairs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Maybe we ought to pick Chloe up to see if she backs the story.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>We don't have to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>Why not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Because the elevator cam had a timestamp. Our suspect says that Sarah left his apartment at about twelve forty-five and the camera in the elevator has her headed towards the basement at twelve forty-eight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>We think she was murdered maybe ten minutes later.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>VIDEO TECH</speaker><content>So what are we looking for?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>The nanny who worked for the guy, we're just trying to check out her story.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-11"><speaker>MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>He claims she got home at one and he never left the apartment again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>There she is. Twelve fifty-four.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>OK, so that's six minutes after Sarah Manning got on the elevator.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-14"><speaker>MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>I guess Harris was telling the truth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Wait.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Where's the kid?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-18"><speaker>MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>Where's what kid?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Becca. The little girl that Chloe takes care of.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-20"><speaker>MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>She must have left the kid in the playground with one of the other nannies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Harris said that she came back with his daughter at the same time every day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-22"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>What difference does it make?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-23"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The difference is that there are no coincidences. Not when murder is involved.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Chloe would have known Sarah's schedule, and Chloe would have known that Sarah was in the basement at that time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-25"><speaker>MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>Pick her up.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>ROOMMATE</speaker><content>Can I help you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Does Chloe Richardson live here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>ROOMMATE</speaker><content>Yes, but she's not here right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Where did she go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>ROOMMATE</speaker><content>Into the city.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you mind if I take a look around?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>ROOMMATE</speaker><content>No. But I'm telling you she's not here. She left about an hour ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content/></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-9"><speaker>ROOMMATE</speaker><content>That's the family that Chloe works for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Not exactly the whole family. She cut the mom out of the picture.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Where in the city did Chloe go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-12"><speaker>ROOMMATE</speaker><content>To their apartment. She said that they needed her to baby-sit tonight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She must have found out that I took Harris in for questioning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>If she talked to his wife, she'd know he'd been released. And we both know what she does to people she doesn't like.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She's going after Ian Harris. We'd better find her before she finds him.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No answer from the apartment when the doorman called upstairs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>But he's sure Chloe is there. Says Ian Harris is up there too, came home about an hour ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Which means Chloe would have been there waiting for him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>All right, we don't have time to wait for emergency services. We're going to have to go in on our own.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Whoa, what about him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He stays here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Whoa, no, come on, I already signed my life away, what more can you want?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>OK, Castle. but it's 'accompany and observe,' not 'participate and annoy.' Got it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>'Participate and annoy' is much more fun, but all right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Stay behind us in the hallway and don't move unless I tell you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hope to die.  You know what I mean.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Open door.  I've got a victim down, guys, stack 'em up. Police, New York City police.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>MRS HARRIS</speaker><content/></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mrs. Harris?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>MRS HARRIS</speaker><content>In here, I've locked us in the bathroom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Room's all clear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Check him. Mrs. Harris, are you OK? Is your daughter with you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>MRS HARRIS</speaker><content>Yes, we're OK.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>He's still alive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mrs. Harris. is Chloe there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>MRS HARRIS</speaker><content>No, no, it's just me and Becca.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Apartment's all clear. Chloe's not here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You can come out now. Mrs Harris. Where's Chloe, Mrs. Harris?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-13"><speaker>MRS HARRIS</speaker><content>I don't know, she must have used her key. I was giving Becca a bath. I didn't even know she was here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-14"><speaker>MRS HARRIS</speaker><content>That's the doorman from downstairs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content/></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hello. Thank you, I'll tell her. Doorman says a tenant called, there's a girl in the laundry room and she's got a knife.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Where's the girl?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>MAN</speaker><content>She's inside, just sitting there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Esposito, get these people out of here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Let's go, everybody up the stairs. Come on, let's go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So what's the plan?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>To get everyone out of this alive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Good plan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You don't go in, do you understand?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content/></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>CHLOE</speaker><content>Please just go away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I'm sorry, Chloe, but I can't do that. Look, Chloe, you're hurt. Why don't you put the knife away and let me help you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-13"><speaker>CHLOE</speaker><content>Why don't you just shoot me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey, look at me, look. No one's going to shoot anyone, OK? Unless it's you, if you take another step inside, Castle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-15"><speaker>CHLOE</speaker><content>He was sleeping with Sarah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-17"><speaker>CHLOE</speaker><content>Only the whole time he was sleeping with me. He was telling me that he loved me and that he was going to leave his wife for me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Guys can be like that sometimes, Chloe. They can lie, and I know when you find out, how much it can break your heart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-19"><speaker>CHLOE</speaker><content>I'm pregnant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, that's even more reason for us to get you some help. Right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-21"><speaker>CHLOE</speaker><content>I just wanted to talk to her, that's all. I just wanted to tell her that Ian and I were in love.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-22"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I know what happened to Sarah was an accident, Chloe. I know that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-23"><speaker>CHLOE</speaker><content>I left Becca in the park and I went up to the apartment just to see if it was true. Cause I'd seen the way he was looking at her. As soon as I saw Ian's bed, I knew. He went to take a shower so I came down here, just to talk to Sarah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I know you didn't mean to kill her, Chloe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-25"><speaker>CHLOE</speaker><content>Sarah was my friend, you know? But she didn't get it. She didn't get how we felt about each other. So when she turned around I just grabbed the bleach and I hit her with it and she fell and I was so scared, I didn’t know what to do so I put her in the dryer. I was so angry. You know, so mad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-26"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Chloe, put the knife down, okay, and let me help you. Just put the knife down, come on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-27"><speaker>CHLOE</speaker><content/></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-28"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>It's OK.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-29"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So, looks like I made it through the case without getting injured, shot or killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-30"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah well, maybe tomorrow?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-31"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>By the way, I really like that whole sisterhood thing you ran back there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-32"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I wasn't running anything, Castle. What that guy did had consequences - only he'll just get to walk away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-33"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well not scot-free. I sense a pretty big divorce settlement in his future.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-34"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Whatever it is, it won't be enough.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>So did you guys get them?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>On the way up the river as we speak.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Cool. Was it who you thought?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Actually, it wasn't.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Wow. It must have been a pretty good story to surprise you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Uh huh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>You know you better be careful, or you'll turn into one of your readers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh. OK, you just ruined it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>You know it's OK to be surprised sometimes. That's the fun.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You surprise me, all the time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-11"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>I'll see you in the morning, Dad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Night, pumpkin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-13"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Dad, thanks for being my nanny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No sweat, kiddo.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>