<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>
<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>EPSIODE 3x23</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>ALEXIS CASTLE</speaker><content>Illinois? That’s like five hundred miles from Manhattan. No, I know Northwestern is closer than Stanford. I’m just saying that’s not where you want to go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>RICHARD CASTLE</speaker><content>Alexis?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Hold on Ash, my dad’s talking to me.  What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Don’t you have school?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Yes.  Look Ash, I know you and I think you need to get away from home. I mean, we all need to get away from home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>I gotta go. We’ll talk about this later. Love you too. ‘Bye.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>We all need to get away from home?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>No, I should never leave. We can be the father daughter version of ‘Grey Gardens’.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ew. You look like you didn’t get any sleep.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>I didn’t. I mean, Ashley got his college acceptances. He got in everywhere.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh that’s great!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s not great?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>I looked up statistics for high school sweethearts when one of them goes to college out of state and the other stays in high school. The odds are not in our favor. I mean, I want him to go where he wants but I don’t want him to leave. And he doesn’t want to leave but I don’t want him to resent me for not going where he wants and … I don’t know what to do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, do what I do.  Look at the odds as a challenge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Says the man who always loses in Vegas.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Relationships are hard. Odds are you’ll figure it out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Odds are someone’s dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Castle.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You’ve got to be kidding me. A murder in the theater of the V.B Tower Hotel? Victor Baron’s place? It’s not the Baron, is it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>KATE BECKETT</speaker><content>No. But you won’t be disappointed. This one’s right up your alley.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Why’s that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Because our victim is a contestant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>‘Death of a Beauty Queen’. Scandalous.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, I’m surprised it doesn’t happen more often.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Is that America’s Dad, Bobby Stark? What’s he doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He’s a pageant host. Oh please, don’t tell me you watch his sitcom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Family Foibles? Half of what I know about being a father I learned from watching that show.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>KEVIN RYAN</speaker><content>Hey, Beckett.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So what’s the story?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, according to Candace Ford, our pageant manager, our victim is twenty one year old Amber Middleberry. The contestants were rehearsing the production number. When they brought in the lighting truss Amber was tangled up inside of it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Must have been a show stopper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey there, Perlmutter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>PERLMUTTER</speaker><content>Detective. Writer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Cause of death?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>PERLMUTTER</speaker><content>Choked from behind with her own sash. Probably between eleven PM and one AM.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>How did she end up on the lighting truss?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Near as we can tell the lighting truss was left onstage after yesterday’s rehearsal. Killer probably thought he’d buy some time by dumping her on it and raising it up to the rafters.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So whoever it was must have known how to use the stage equipment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-21"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>No, the lift controls, they’re on touch screen. Pretty easy to operate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-22"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>When was she last seen alive?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-23"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Last night. Contestants, they all went to a dinner to honor Victor Baron. Ten thirty the party wrapped and they were all limoed back here to the hotel. Amber used her key card at ten forty three PM to get into her hotel room. After that she wound up here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-24"><speaker>PERLMUTTER</speaker><content>Detective, there’s something you should see.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-25"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>A black sequin?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-26"><speaker>PERLMUTTER</speaker><content>Part of one. I found it in her hair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-27"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, so the killer might have transferred it when he strangled her. Let’s find out who had access to this ballroom last night and let’s also talk to the pageant manager. I want to see if any of the girl’s outfits match with this sequin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-28"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Will do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-29"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So does Amber Middleberry have any family?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-30"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah. Just her …  dad.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>DAN</speaker><content>She started when she was nine. Little Miss Wholesome. I was against the idea at first but Amber’s mom had a bug about it and uh, right after her mother died … I think it just helped her feel closer to her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Did your daughter have any enemies you know of?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>DAN</speaker><content>No, of course not. Everybody loved her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, what about the other contestants? Were there any rivalries?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>DAN</speaker><content>She went way back with some of these girls. They … she … even after she made it to the semi-finals everybody was hugging her and they were calling her the front runner and … this pageant, this one, was her dream.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>When was the last time you talked with her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>DAN</speaker><content>Yesterday morning. I tried to call her last night. I knew that dinner thing was over. I wanted to wish her luck, you know, but she didn’t answer the phone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And what time was that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>DAN</speaker><content>A little before eleven. I uh … I thought she must have gone to sleep but she must have left her room and come down here for some reason.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>VICTOR BARON</speaker><content>Dan! I am so sorry. Gonna get the bastard that did this, you have my word.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>DAN</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>Detective? A word upstairs, if you don’t mind.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>This is a dark day. A sad chapter in Baron’s All American Beauty Pagent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>KAYLA BARON</speaker><content>Victor, this is just awful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>My wife, Kayla. You might recognize her as Baron’s All American Beauty 1995.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yes, of course.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Nice to meet you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>KAYLA</speaker><content>Nice to meet you, yes. This is just devastating. For us, and for the girls. We’re like family.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>How well did you know Amber?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>Um… she was a sweet girl. Hell of a violinist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>KAYLA</speaker><content>Yes, she was.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>Mark my words, I am putting the entire weight of the Baron empire behind this investigation. Anything you need, just say the word. Detective, I know you have to do your thing. I’m just hoping that since we’re airing the pageant live this Friday, if we could minimize the press, you know, to be fair to the other girls.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We’re going to have to be fair to our victim first. And speaking of press, can we get rid of the cameras? This is, after all, a murder investigation, not a reality show.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>We um, we film everything. The behind the scenes at the pageant. We like to catch the girls talking about each other. We let them confess their hopes and fears. You get the glamour but you also get the underbelly. People love the underbelly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>KAYLA</speaker><content>Yes, they do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>But maybe this isn’t the time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So were all the girls staying at the hotel?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>That’s right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, I’ll need access to Amber’s room. We’ll also need hotel security tapes. Now were those cameras recording last night’s dinner?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-18"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>Of course.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, we’ll need the footage. We’ll also need to interview all of the pageant contestants.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-20"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>I’ll have Candace give you anything you need.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Great. Thank you very much.  It was nice to meet you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-22"><speaker>KAYLA</speaker><content>Come again.  Oh no, we don’t –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-23"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>We don’t want them to come again.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Small town girl comes to New York for the fairy tale, ends up with a horror story.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Pageants aren’t fairy tales. They’re demanding, high pressure competitions that bring out the very best and the very worst in people.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That is the voice of experience. Oh my God, you were a beauty queen!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No. I had a roommate freshman year. Debbie Winaker. It was like living with Elle Woods on steroids.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well then, this ought to bring back some memories.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>PAGEANT MOM</speaker><content>You’re slouching. Winners don’t slouch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Castle, they’re everywhere!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It smells like a perfume counter at a department store.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>JAVIER ESPOSITO</speaker><content>It beats the usual lowlifes and nutjobs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I don’t know if you can say that nutjobs and beauty queens are mutually exclusive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, but none of them connect to the murder. I checked the sequin against all their dresses –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I bet you did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And none of them are a match.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, look at the footage from the dinner. Let’s make sure that the dresses we checked are the ones that they actually wore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hum. Watch a parade of beautiful women in evening attire? Yeah, I can do that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I bet you can.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey, so, I’ve been interviewing these ladies –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I bet you did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-19"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>About their alibis for last night. Anyway, there’s someone you should talk to.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Sascha, tell them what you told me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>SASCHA</speaker><content>When we got back to the hotel I wanted to work out a couple of my dance moves. I’m one of the semi finalists so I get to perform in the broadcast.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Congratulations.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>SASCHA</speaker><content>Thanks. I’m doing an interpretive dance to J-Lo’s "I'm Into You".</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And then what happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>SASCHA</speaker><content>I changed into sweats and went to the stage and … that’s when I heard it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You heard what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>SASCHA</speaker><content>Uh … a fight? It was coming from the dressing room. It was Amber and some guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Did you see the guy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>SASCHA</speaker><content>The door was closed. It started getting loud, so I bolted. But now I wish I had done something. I mean, maybe he’s the one who killed her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>His voice. Did you recognize it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>SASCHA</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What were they arguing about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>SASCHA</speaker><content>"How could you do this to me? You have no right. Who do you think you are?" Stuff like that. It kind of sounded like he was her boyfriend.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> That was Amber’s dad. He said he didn’t know anything about a boyfriend. Neither did any of the other girls.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Maybe she was keeping it a secret.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>They said if anyone knew what was going on in Amber’s life it was Justin Hankel, Amber’s pageant consultant.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>JUSTIN HANKEL</speaker><content>I coached her on her routine, interviews, oversaw stylists, makeup, clothing, violin lessons, glamour shots. Everything she needed to win.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The two of you must have spent a lot of time together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>JUSTIN</speaker><content>That’s what it takes. Today’s pageants are not just about beauty, they’re about brains, talent, social issues, and what with the money and the exposure at stake … winning one of the majors can launch a career.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What about a boyfriend? Was she in a relationship?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>JUSTIN</speaker><content>No boyfriends. That is a rule for my clients and Amber was no exception. She knew that she needed to focus one hundred percent of her energy on the pageant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know, the night that she died, she got into an argument. Any idea with whom?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>JUSTIN</speaker><content>No. The last time I saw her was before her dinner. But like I told that other detective, something was going on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>How so?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>JUSTIN</speaker><content>She’d been off the last couple of days. Upset. And I went to pick her up for a costume fitting and it looked like she</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Did you ask why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>JUSTIN</speaker><content>She said that someone was trying to take advantage of her. I asked her who but she said she would handle it. It wasn’t like her not to confide in me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Could it have been one of the other contestants?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>JUSTIN</speaker><content> There’s a lot of pressure on these girls to win. I mean, it can get really … political between them.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Do you think it’s possible political turned deadly?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I don’t know. Winning means fame and fortune. No one remembers the runner up. Besides, people have killed for less.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That still doesn’t explain who she was arguing with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Guys? I got something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>One of the girls?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Just watch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>This is from Baron’s dinner last night. That’s our victim, Amber. She’s laying it on thick for Victor Baron, but that’s not the interesting part. Now watch this. That. There. See that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Look at her face.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Looks like whatever good guy sitcom star Bobby Stark said, she didn’t like it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Don’t just look at her face. Look at his tux.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Black sequins.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yo. Bobby Stark’s blazer, courtesy of the costume lady at the pageant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And the broken black sequin?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Perfect match.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Bam, said the costume lady.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Ooh … she’s not the only lady saying bam when it comes to Bobby Stark.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Does he have a record?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Ah, no criminal charges, but Mr. Stark has quite the reputation. Three women filed restraining orders against Bobby Stark in the last year. All for unwanted advances.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>How come I didn’t hear about this on TMZ?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Oh, word is Stark paid quite a bit of cash to make it all go away. Oh, it gets better. I was talking to Candace Ford and a couple of the other girls – they said that Bobby Stark had started paying quite a lot of attention to Amber.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Maybe it was unwanted attention.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Maybe Bobby didn’t know how to take no for an answer.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>BOBBY</speaker><content>You lookin’ at me? Huh? You lookin’ at me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mr. Stark, I’m Detective –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>BOBBY</speaker><content>There’s nobody else around. You must be lookin’ at me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mr. Stark?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Have a seat, please.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>BOBBY</speaker><content>Yeah. You like that bit? It’s my Bobby De Niro.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Playing a homicidal maniac.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>BOBBY</speaker><content>Sold it though, right? See, I got this range as an actor but you probably don’t know about that because I’m always typecast as mister-nice-guy dad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah well, I don’t think you’ll have that problem now that you’re a murder suspect.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>BOBBY</speaker><content>Murder suspect? Is she joking? Are you joking?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What was your relationship with Amber Middleberry?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>BOBBY</speaker><content>Oh, c’mon. I didn’t kill her. If anything I was trying to recruit her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Recruit her? For what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>BOBBY</speaker><content>For my, uh, goddess train.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The goddess train?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-16"><speaker>BOBBY</speaker><content>Yeah, it’s my own little private pageant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And how did Amber respond to this oh so enticing offer?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-18"><speaker>BOBBY</speaker><content>You know what? She hadn’t seen the light yet. She was coming around. I could always tell the innocent act when I see it. Besides, who wouldn’t want to ride the Bobby Rocket?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Everyone, from what we hear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mr. Stark, here’s what I think happened. After dinner you invited Amber back to your dressing room and she had the bad sense to agree. And that’s when you decided to make another pitch to get her on board your goddess train.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>When she shot you down, you flew into a rage and strangled her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-22"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You were rehearsing on that stage all week. You knew all of the equipment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-23"><speaker>BOBBY</speaker><content>Stop. Will you … just stop. You guys are crazy, you know that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay well, maybe you can explain why we found this broken sequin from your jacket on her body. Where were you between eleven and one AM last night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-25"><speaker>BOBBY</speaker><content>Uh … I don’t know. I’m a little foggy on that, actually. I was … uh… partying pretty hard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-26"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Who were you with?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-27"><speaker>BOBBY</speaker><content>Um … not sure, but  whoever it was was definitely using strawberry oil.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-28"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, so let me get this straight. You don’t remember where you were or what you were doing last night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-29"><speaker>BOBBY</speaker><content>That’s bad, right?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That guy’s dropped more pills than a three fingered pharmacist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I just can’t believe that someone that’s given so much great fatherly advice on TV could be guilty of murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, he’s a drug addled predator who left physical evidence on the body.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, when you put it that way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey, Esposito.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We need to reconstruct Stark’s evening. Check his phone records, double check security cameras at the hotel. We need hard evidence to place him at the crime scene.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I got something that might help.  Amber had her violin with her at dinner, but it wasn’t with her body or anywhere at the crime scene.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So where did it go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, we know Amber went to the hotel so maybe she dropped it off there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Except uniforms inventoried the room. It wasn’t there and her dad and consultant didn’t see it either.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So maybe she had it when she was killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And Bobby Stark disposed of it. Check trash cans, dumpsters, and sewer drains around the hotel. If someone saw him ditch the violin we can connect him to the murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Right on.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>MARTHA RODGERS</speaker><content>Oh, beauty pageant intrigue. Some things never change. Ah, here it is!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ahaha … I didn’t know you competed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Well, that’s because I didn’t win.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>But I can tell you, the women I competed against? Just as cutthroat as they are now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What was your talent?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>The way I wore a sweater.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Hey honey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hey, Alexis. What’s wrong?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Ashley made his decision.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-11"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Uh oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Stanford?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-13"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>No. He decided to go to school here.  In New York.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-14"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Well, what’s not good about that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-15"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Stanford was his dream. I don’t want to stand in the way of that. He’ll just end up hating me for it, and this could be the most important decision of his life, so I made a decision, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-16"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>I broke up with him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-17"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Oh, baby. It’s okay.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, she’s right, you know. I mean, odds are it won’t work out. She’s just being practical.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Relationships aren’t math problems. You don’t solve them by being practical. I mean, what happens when she meets her soul mate and she doesn’t risk it because it’s not practical?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Okay then, what about Hawaii? Earrings? Oh! Lingerie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Things you buy a woman!  Used to kill in Pyramid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>It’s my thirtieth anniversary.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh sir, congratulations.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Thirty years of marriage and you don’t know what to buy her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>If you stayed married long enough you’d know it’s hard to stay original after the first ten.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s fair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So what’s the secret to your success?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-11"><speaker>MONTOMGERY</speaker><content>There’s no secret. Just keep … showing up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Any luck on Bobby Stark?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, but you’re not going to like it. Paparazzi snapped photos of him going into the Tribeca Grand Hotel at eleven thirty with a brunette wearing Jackie O glasses. At one AM he left, at which point he relocated to a gentleman’s club to watch mud wrestling.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Amber left her room at eleven. Where was he between eleven and eleven thirty?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-15"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>In a cab, on his way to Tribeca.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And … we know this for a fact?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-17"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, he was tweeting photos of his manhood along the way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And that’s how you trend on Twitter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So the sequin must have broken off onto Amber after he bumped up against her. Cut him loose. He’s not our guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-20"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Which means we are dead in the water.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-22"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Uh… wouldn’t go that far. Her stolen violin? We found it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Where?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-24"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Dumped in a garbage bin behind the hotel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-25"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Disposed of by our killer, just not we killer we thought.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-26"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Did we get prints?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-27"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah. Amber Middleberry’s and one other set belonging to the lovely, the talented contestant from Georgia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-28"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Which one was … oh!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>JOY</speaker><content>Amber and I have been friends since Little Miss Spangles. Why would you think I killed her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Because your prints were all over the violin case, Joy. And she had it with her when she came back from dinner last night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>JOY</speaker><content>I held it for her while she fixed her tights.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>They’re on the violin, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>JOY</speaker><content>She wasn’t even supposed to be a semi-finalist. And then she nailed all her pageant questions. It was supposed to be her weakness, but she blew everyone away. She was going to win.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So then you killed her and you dumped her violin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>JOY</speaker><content>No! That is not what happened. Last night when we went back to the hotel I saw her go into her room, drop off her stuff, and then leave again. But she left so fast her door didn’t close all the way, so I went to shut it. That’s when I saw her violin. She just left it there. It was like a sign. I thought, ‘Joy Jones, how badly do you want this?’</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>How … badly did you want it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>JOY</speaker><content>More than anything. I’m twenty five. I’m old. This is the last year I can qualify. I thought that if I took her violin it might throw her off enough in the talent finals that I could beat her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>But that wasn’t enough for you, was it? You thought, why not just take her out of the competition completely?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-11"><speaker>JOY</speaker><content>No! All I did was take her violin. When I found out she was dead, I panicked. I thought someone might find out so I threw it away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s a pretty good act, Joy, but the judges just aren’t buying it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-13"><speaker>JOY</speaker><content>I swear! I didn’t have to kill Amber to get her out of that pageant. I found something in her violin case. Something awful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And what did you find?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-15"><speaker>JOY</speaker><content>The reason she was murdered.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>JOY</speaker><content>If these got out, it would have ruined her. She would have been kicked off the circuit for good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh my God. She is absolutely, totally -</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Naked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>JOY</speaker><content>There’s a note on the back of that one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> ‘You know my price. Pay up or I will destroy you.’ So she was being blackmailed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Looks like somebody made good on their threat.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Beauty queens and naked pictures. It’s as American as socialites and sex tapes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Amber dreamt of winning this pageant. Why would she take those naked photos? I mean, she knew the chance she was taking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Just because you’re smart and beautiful doesn’t mean you have good judgment.  I didn’t mean me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Just got off with Amber’s father. That was a tough conversation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You mean he didn’t know about the photos?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content> And Amber didn’t tell him about the blackmailer, either. Or try to borrow money.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, maybe she paid off the blackmailer on her own?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Not an option. Any money Amber did have went to paying for shoes, gowns, and spray tans. She only had fifty bucks in the bank. And she didn’t have any recent withdraws, either.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Justin said she was upset. Maybe that’s because she didn’t have the money to make it go away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, but then why kill her? A smart blackmailer would give her the time to get the cash.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Not if she threatened to go to the police, forcing him to take deadly action. Deadly Action. That’s a good title.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I rechecked her phone. There’s no record of any unusual calls. I figure the blackmailer contacted her through the hotel phone - that way he couldn’t be traced.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, have you taken a look at these photos?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Only insofar as it pertains to the investigation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Look at the lighting and the composition. Whoever took these knew something about photography.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>A professional?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I mean, it happens all the time. Girl gets a session with the pro, they finish, he offers to take a few art shots, she’s desperate for the cash, he promises he’ll never show it to anybody …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Until she makes it big, in which case they suddenly surface.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Esposito, let’s get a hold of the pageant consultant. Let’s get a list of all the photographers that Amber’s had sessions with. One of them might be our blackmailer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-20"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>All right.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>JUSTIN</speaker><content>This must have been what she was so upset about. She knew that if the pageant found out, it would have all been over.  It is all over. Why didn’t she just tell me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Do you have any idea who might have taken these photographs?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>JUSTIN</speaker><content>With that hairstyle, it must have been six months ago. I’ll have to check my calendar.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So uniforms talked to the pageant girls that Amber was closest to. She didn’t tell them about the photos, either.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, she probably thought they’d use it against her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>Beckett, you’re a woman, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Sir, I have no idea what to get your wife.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Still no luck on the gift?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>Keep coming up empty.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The best thing to give a woman is something she said she wanted when she didn’t think you were listening.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>What if I wasn’t listening?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Gift certificate?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Beckett.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So according to her pageant consultant, Amber was in the city six months ago for a photo shoot. He thinks they were taken about the same time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And who was the shoot with?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>A photographer named Dax Lattimer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Does he have a record?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Negative. But I asked around and the guy is no stranger to dirty pictures. On top of headshots he also freelances for adult magazines.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, sounds like our guy. Where is he now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>He’s got a studio in the East Village. I’m heading there now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay. I’ll have Ryan meet you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>LATTIMER</speaker><content>Yeah, I remember Amber. Very sweet gal. I took some headshots for her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You take anything else while you were at it? Maybe some snaps of her wearing nothing but a smile?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>LATTIMER</speaker><content>Amber wasn’t the type. She was all about the glamour. So what’s this about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>She was murdered.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And we think whoever killed her took this picture right here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>LATTIMER</speaker><content>Yeah well, I didn’t take this. I’m not that mediocre.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Really?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>These were shot around the time you worked with Amber. We all know you do more than just pets and families.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>LATTIMER</speaker><content>Hey, we all have to pay the bills.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And with Amber’s star on the rise, that photo is worth some serious coin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Pretty girl like that? Alone here in the studio …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-12"><speaker>LATTIMER</speaker><content>Hey, you have to believe me. I didn’t take this photograph. Besides, we weren’t alone. She was with someone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-13"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Who?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-14"><speaker>LATTIMER</speaker><content>Some boyfriend. Guy was a real creep, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-15"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Amber didn’t have a boyfriend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-16"><speaker>LATTIMER</speaker><content>Well, she did when she was here. In fact, he fancied himself a photographer. Kept telling me I should shoot Amber in natural light.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-17"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>This boyfriend have a name?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-18"><speaker>LATTIMER</speaker><content>Jerry … Jeremy… something like that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-19"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Mr. Lattimer, where were you the night before last between eleven PM and one AM?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-20"><speaker>LATTIMER</speaker><content>At home with my wife. Trying to rock my colicky son to sleep. It’s a doorman building, so you can check.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, thanks.  Amber’s dad said she used to have a boyfriend. Jeremy Keiper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Keiper? Was he creepy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah well, her dad thought so. As far as he knows, they broke up late last year because she realized he was holding her back. The dad thinks that the boyfriend is still in Illinois.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, that’s the beauty of blackmail. You can do it from anywhere.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Blackmail maybe, but not murder.  Why don’t we find out if Keiper paid her a visit lately.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>On it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Bad boyfriends and pageant queens? This is like Debbie Winaker all over again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You having flashbacks?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>It was my own private Vietnam. Our place smelled of hairspray, perfume, and cigarettes. I’m surprised that we didn’t spontaneously combust.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I love the smell of hairspray in the morning. It smells like … victory.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-11"><speaker>ASHLEY</speaker><content>Excuse me, Mr. Castle?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ashley?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>ASHLEY</speaker><content>I’m sorry to bug you at work, but Alexis established a no calls, no contact policy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>She told me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>ASHLEY</speaker><content>Look, I made a big mistake. I thought if I chose Stanford Alexis would think that I was blowing her off. Instead she’s mad at me because I chose her over where I want to go to school. So now I’m going to Stanford, which is where I wanted to go in the first place, but –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>But if you call her and tell her that, she’ll be even angrier with you for ignoring her boundaries.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>ASHLEY</speaker><content>Exactly! Look, I think Alexis and I can make the whole long distance thing work, I really do. Would you tell her that? Would you talk to her for me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ashley, I appreciate that it was probably very hard for you to come down and talk to me today, but … I just don’t think it’s very appropriate for me to –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>ASHLEY</speaker><content>Mr. Castle, have you ever been crazy about someone who is determined to push you away?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey, Castle – oh, sorry guys.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No … uh … It’s okay. Um… Ashley, I’m sorry, I do have to go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-10"><speaker>ASHLEY</speaker><content>Please just … think about it, okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What was that about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He wants me to advocate for him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh. Well, that’s sweet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And awkward.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Mostly awkward.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-18"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yo Beckett! Just got off the phone with Jeremy Keiper’s mom. Turns out, Jeremy moved to New York last month. Said he was going to make something of himself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Looks like he made himself into a blackmailer and a killer.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Jeremy Keiper! NYPD! Open up!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mr. Keiper? Anyone here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Beckett?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Looks like someone had a hard time letting go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Castle!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>This is a classic murder suicide. Jeremy blackmails his ex-girlfriend, not because he needs the money but because clearly, he’s obsessed with her. Amber rejects him and his sleazy schemes and he flips. He snaps and kills her and then, faced with the reality of what he’s done, hangs himself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>PERLMUTTER</speaker><content>Only one problem with your theory, Castle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Which is?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>PERLMUTTER</speaker><content>This wasn’t a suicide.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>This wasn’t?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>PERLMUTTER</speaker><content>If he had hanged himself the marks on his neck would angle upwards.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Which they do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>PERLMUTTER</speaker><content>Yes! But if he was strangled the marks would go straight across. This guy’s got both.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So the hanging was a cover-up for the strangulation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-10"><speaker>PERLMUTTER</speaker><content>Well, there’s also perimortem bruising on the arms and across the ribs. I’m guessing there was a struggle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Estimated time of death?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-12"><speaker>PERLMUTTER</speaker><content>Ah, judging by temperature and lividity he was killed half a day before Amber Middleberry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Before Amber?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-14"><speaker>PERLMUTTER</speaker><content>Yes! Before! Now can you please move? You’re in my light.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, this doesn’t make any sense. If he didn’t kill Amber – How do a blackmailer and his victim both end up dead?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-16"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yo, check this out. His hard drive’s been wiped.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s our connection, Castle. It’s the one thing that Amber and Jeremy had in common – those photos. Someone didn’t want them to see the light of day.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Amber’s dad had no idea this was going on with his daughter. She didn’t even mention Jeremy’s name in the last six months.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Is there anything else Jeremy and Amber could have been involved in while there were together?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, not that he can recall.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>These pictures, by today’s standards, are downright tasteful. How do these get you killed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>It can’t be about naked pictures. Something else must have been going on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Unless …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Unless what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Unless Jeremy wasn’t the only blackmailer. What if he had a partner? I mean, we know Amber was arguing with someone the night she was killed. We know It couldn’t have been Jeremy because he was already dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why would the partner kill Jeremy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Maybe they had a falling out. Maybe Jeremy decided he couldn’t hurt Amber, but the partner still wanted his payday.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So he takes out Jeremy and decides to go after Amber himself?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>But Amber decides to call his bluff. She says she’s going to contact the police. Now the blackmailer has no choice. He has to kill her and get rid of all the evidence of blackmail.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ryan? Get me everything you got on Jeremy Keiper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-14"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> Sorry, baby.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, it’s late. I’ll see you two later.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What’cha looking at?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You really miss him, don’t you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You know I hate to interfere –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Since when?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Point taken. … Ashley dropped by the precinct to see me today.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>He did? Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He wanted me to intercede on his behalf.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-10"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>What did he say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, he looked about as happy as you do. And he wanted me to tell you that he’s decided to go to Stanford.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-12"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And, he wants to give a long distance relationship a shot. He thinks it could work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-14"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>What do you think?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I think that nothing is certain. And you could be ending something that could have worked, if you had just given it a little more time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-16"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>What if I’m just cutting my losses on something that was never meant to be?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well then, we can be the father daughter version of 'Grey Gardens'. But life is a journey and there is no predicting the outcome. Only thing you can control are your choices and know that they’ll define who you are. I would just hate to see you so focused on the problem right in front of you that you completely miss the entire picture.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-18"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>That’s pretty good advice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah.  Yeah, actually it is, isn’t it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-20"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Remind me to get you a subscription to a girly magazine for Christmas.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, that is so thoughtful. But I’m not looking at the naked girl.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What are you looking at?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Everything but the naked girl. We were so focused on Amber, we almost missed the entire picture. What if Amber and Jeremy were killed, not because of who was in this photo, but because of where this photo was taken?  Anything look familiar?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Sure does.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You can thank me later.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Talk about a motive for murder, if these photos got out to the tabloids…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, it’d destroy everything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> NYPD.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>PAGEANT COORDINATOR</speaker><content>They’re inside.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>KAYLA</speaker><content>The memorial for Amber should be simple. Peaceful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-6"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>And very, very classy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-7"><speaker>KAYLA</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-8"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>Detective! Is there something I can help you with?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yes, we need to ask you a few questions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-10"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>Ask away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Fine. Tell us about the blackmail and the murder of Amber MIddleberry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-12"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>Shut the cameras off! Go! Now!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I thought you said that everybody loves the underbelly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-14"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>This … this …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-15"><speaker>KAYLA</speaker><content>What’s going on, Victor?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What’s going on is we finally figured out who, aside from Amber, would be nervous about these photos.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-17"><speaker>KAYLA</speaker><content>What photos?  Oh my God! Oh my God, Victor! Oh my God!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-18"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>It’s not what it looks like.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-19"><speaker>KAYLA</speaker><content>It’s not what it looks like? This is …  … this is our house in the Hamptons. This is our bed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-20"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>It’s our vacation bed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Right underneath the two million dollar Picard that you purchased at the auction, which happens to be the companion to this painting here in your office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>We read all about it in the spread they did on you in Today’s Architect.  Looks as though you were hoisted on your own Picard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-23"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>I can explain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-24"><speaker>KAYLA</speaker><content>We agreed, Victor. Never again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-25"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>It was just the weekend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-26"><speaker>KAYLA</speaker><content>Just a weekend? I have friends in the Hamptons. What if somebody saw? I won’t be humiliated because you can’t keep it in your pants.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-27"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>No one saw!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-28"><speaker>KAYLA</speaker><content>No one saw? No, you took photos so everyone could see!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-29"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>I didn’t take those pictures.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-30"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Here’s what I think happened. Amber was being blackmailed, she couldn’t pay, so she came to you for help.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-31"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Only you had a lot to lose. Those pictures, they have a way of getting out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-32"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So instead of paying off her blackmailer, you killed him. And you came back here and took care of her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-33"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>It’s not what happened!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-34"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The cameras aren’t rolling anymore, Mr. Baron. You can drop the act.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-35"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>It’s not an act. Amber wasn’t being blackmailed. The conniving ***** was blackmailing me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-36"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She was blackmailing you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-37"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>She showed me the pictures. She said she had her boyfriend come and take them while I was away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-38"><speaker>KAYLA</speaker><content>Wait, you left her alone in my house?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-39"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>I had a meeting in the city. I was coming right back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-40"><speaker>KAYLA</speaker><content>How could you be so stupid, Victor?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-41"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>She said that If I helped her win the pageant the photos would never see the light of day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-42"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>"You know the price, pay up or I’ll destroy you." It wasn’t to Amber, it was from Amber. She was still with her boyfriend. They were in it together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-43"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So then what did you do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-44"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>I slipped her the pageant questions. Why do you think she was doing so well?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-45"><speaker>KAYLA</speaker><content>You ass!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-46"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh! Hey! Hey! Mr. Baron, where were you between eleven and one AM the night of the murder?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-47"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>After the reception I had drinks with Councilman Bollinger, uh … I got home at one AM. Kayla was with me. Weren’t you, babe?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-48"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Kayla? Is this true? Were you with him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-49"><speaker>KAYLA</speaker><content>Yes. Who else knew, Victor? Who do I need to be ashamed in front of?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-50"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>No one else knew.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-51"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, someone else must have, otherwise two people wouldn’t be dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-52"><speaker>BARON</speaker><content>The only other person I told was Candace. I told her what Amber was trying to do, to me, to the pageant. I … I told her to take care of it, make the problem go away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-53"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Maybe she did.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>CANDACE</speaker><content>I don’t want to see any fingerprints on those glasses.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Being careful of fingerprints, are we Candace?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>CANDACE</speaker><content>We want everything to be perfect.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>This pageant really is your baby.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>CANDACE</speaker><content>You noticed? Seventeen flawless years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So then you would do anything to protect it.  We know that Mr. Baron told you about the blackmail. And we know he asked you to handle it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>CANDACE</speaker><content>Kill her? I wanted to kill Baron. Seventeen flawless years and he wants me to give her the answers so his little fling can wear the crown? But it was either that or that snake destroys everything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Where were you the night Amber was killed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-3"><speaker>CANDACE</speaker><content>Please don’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ms. Ford –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-5"><speaker>CANDACE</speaker><content>I was with someone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Who?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-7"><speaker>CANDACE</speaker><content> I can’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Candace, if you have an alibi –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-9"><speaker>CANDACE</speaker><content>Bobby Stark. I was with him at the Tribeca Grand. And the worst part is he doesn’t even remember.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Tribeca Grand confirms that Stark was with Candace at the time of the murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>She did smell a little bit like strawberry oil.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Baron’s alibi checks out, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Which leaves us without a suspect. Okay, get into it with Baron’s lawyers. Just because Candace didn’t kill them doesn’t mean he didn’t hire someone else to do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Blind naked ambition. I think even your Debbie Winaker would be appalled.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, she would’ve. Debbie wanted to be a beauty queen because she believed in the ideals of beauty. She wanted to be beautiful on the inside and outside.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I thought you didn’t like her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, deep down, behind all the makeup and the hair, she wasn’t terrible. She was just a miserable person to live with. Unlike Amber, winning wouldn’t have meant a thing to her if she had to cheat to do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, talk about choices that change your life. When do you make that choice? When does winning become more important than your soul?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I don’t know. You have to be pretty cold and calculating to make some of the choices Amber did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Cold and calculating.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Amber was cold and calculating.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah. So?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So … all of those people we talked to about her? One of them was lying.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="34"><utterance uid="34-1"><speaker>JUSTIN</speaker><content>Tragedy struck the Baron’s All American Pageant with the untimely passing of our Illinois All American, Miss Amber Middleberry. I was fortunate to work closely with Amber. She meant the world to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well then, why did you kill her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-3"><speaker>JUSTIN</speaker><content>What? I didn’t kill Amber.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You’re lying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You’ve been lying to us the whole time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You told us that she was upset that she was feeling like she was being taken advantage of and threatened.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>But she was the one doing the threatening. There was no reason for her to be upset.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-8"><speaker>JUSTIN</speaker><content>You know, you’re interrupting a dress rehearsal. I don’t even know what you two are talking about.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh, yes you do. You got on to the blackmail.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You thought the old boyfriend was taking advantage of your prized client, so you confronted him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We ran your credit cards.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>We know about the cab ride you took to Jeremy’s apartment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So tell us, when you killed Amber’s boyfriend, did you know Amber was in on the scheme?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Justin. Justin, stop!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>A word of advice, Justin? When the lady says stop, stop.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="35"><utterance uid="35-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Justin confessed to everything. His last three clients were losers. Amber was supposed to be his comeback and if she didn’t win he was through. And apparently he found the same naked photos that we did and thought that her ex-boyfriend was trying to exploit her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He was worried if they called the cops that their secret would get out and they would be ruined, so he decided to handle it on his own. Unfortunately Jeremy was drunk, he got violent, and Justin ended up killing him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And he staged it like it was a suicide. Once Amber found out she threatened to turn him in and he killed her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-4"><speaker>MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>That’s a whole pageant of bad choices. Good work, you two.  Uh, good work, you all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ah… I see a beauty queen worthy of a crown.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-7"><speaker>EVELYN MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>Always the charmer, Rick.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-8"><speaker>MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>Hey, what’cha doing here? You know I was just coming to swoop you up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-9"><speaker>EVELYN</speaker><content>Yeah well, I know how you lose all sense of time when you’re working. I figured I’d meet you here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-10"><speaker>MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>Mmhmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you guys have any big plans?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-12"><speaker>EVELYN</speaker><content>Dinner and dancing with the best husband in Manhattan. Especially since he gave me that gift this morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, what did you end up giving her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-14"><speaker>MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>I followed your advice, Castle. I thought about some of the things Evelyn said she wanted the past couple of years. And my gift to her is - next year I’m retiring from the force.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-15"><speaker>EVELYN</speaker><content>We’re going to go traveling. We’re going to go to all of the romantic places.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-16"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Wait, are you serious, boss?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-17"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You really want to retire?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-18"><speaker>MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>I haven’t accomplished everything I want to on the job, but I’ve done enough. It’s time for me to move on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-19"><speaker>EVELYN</speaker><content>Best gift ever. More Roy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-20"><speaker>MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>Look, I’ve taught you guys everything I know about doing this job, all right? You’re going to be fine without me. For crying out loud, lose the long faces. Smile, please. That’s an order.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-21"><speaker>MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>You kids take care, all right? You guys behave now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-22"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Have a good time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Congratulations, you guys. Good night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-24"><speaker>MONTGOMERY</speaker><content>Night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-25"><speaker>EVELYN</speaker><content>‘Bye.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-26"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Happy anniversary.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-27"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Goodnight, Captain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-28"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> What the hell did you say to him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-29"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Nothing. No, I just told him to listen to what his wife wanted.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-30"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Damn Castle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-31"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>How can you … I didn’t… there’s no way …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-32"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, let me let you in on a little secret. Captain Montgomery retires all the time, just give it a week or two. He’s like the Brett Favre of the NYPD. Trust me. He’s not going anywhere.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-33"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Not going anywhere.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="36"><utterance uid="36-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey so, I’ve been meaning to ask you. Did Alexis make a decision about Ashley?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, she did, actually. She decided it was worth the risk and she’s going to just keep showing up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>It’s a good choice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>See you tomorrow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>See you tomorrow.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="37"><utterance uid="37-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ashley! What are you doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-2"><speaker>ASHLEY</speaker><content>Hey, Mr. Castle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-3"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Hey, Dad. Guess what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-5"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>I’m going to Stanford.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-7"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>I’m applying for early admission. And since I’ve been taking extra classes each semester since my freshman year, I have enough credits to graduate in the fall.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-9"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Yeah. This way Ash and I will be together in January. In college.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-11"><speaker>ASHLEY</speaker><content>That was actually her idea, sir.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-13"><speaker>THE END</speaker><content>CASTLE</content></utterance>
</scene>

</script>