<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>JOE</speaker><content>Keep it comin’, pal. You’re doing great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>JOE</speaker><content>Say, maybe you can help me. I’m looking for a dame.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>BARTENDER</speaker><content>Aren’t we all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>JOE</speaker><content>This one’s special.  You know her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>BARTENDER</speaker><content>Know her? I’m looking at her.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Talk about a slice of history. The Pennybaker Club. You know, back in the 40s all the greats played here. If these walls could talk, man, the stories they would tell.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, but the only story we need to hear is about –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>LANIE PARISH</speaker><content>Stan Banks, single GSW to the sternum. I’m calling the time of death between 6 and 8 this morning. Looks like he tried to defend himself with this ; obviously it didn’t work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So robbery gone wrong?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>JAVIER ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, still had his wallet, cell, and a room key from the Parksville Lawns, so…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>KEVIN RYAN</speaker><content>Pockets were pulled out indicating the killer searched the body. For what, we have no idea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s weird. He’s got an SRO key but his driver’s license has him living on 34th Street.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>We’ll hit the SRO. See if there’s anything we can find out about him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Thanks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You looking for a drink, Castle? ‘Cause I’m pretty sure the bar is closed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Actually, I was looking for a clue.  I think I found one. Some homeless guy’s squat and today’s Ledger. He was here this morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, whoever he is, maybe he saw something. I’ll get patrol units to canvass the area.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>MANAGER</speaker><content>Stan’s dead? Well, that’s just great. What am I supposed to do with all his ... crap?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>We’ll be taking … some of it off your hands for our investigation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You know of anyone that’s been threatening Stan lately?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>MANAGER</speaker><content>I’m the manager here, not the den mother.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Okay then. When was the last time you saw him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>MANAGER</speaker><content>Uh, this morning. Stan was all smiles. Gave notice that he was moving out ‘cause his ship was coming in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>What ship?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>MANAGER</speaker><content>Oh, I don’t know. The Titanic by the looks of things.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, if you can remember anything else can you please give me a call?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>MANAGER</speaker><content>Don’t hold your breath, hot shot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I think she likes you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And when was the last time you spoke with him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Doubloon? As in, old Spanish coin?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah. That’s the fella that found that sunken Confederate ship ten years ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>A blue – like an insect?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Was he having problems with anyone that you know of?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Nothing in Stan’s personal effects about butterflies, blue or otherwise.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Just a bunch of books about mobsters in Manhattan in the 40s.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s all right. Because I got a hit on that threatening money call to Stan’s wife and it turns out it came from a dry cleaners.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Maybe clothes aren’t the only thing they’re laundering.  I’ll check it out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Thanks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Uh, this diary in Stan’s stuff. It’s also from the 40s. It sounds like it belonged to a private eye. Listen to this.  “Usually the wives turn on the waterworks when shown pictures of their husbands stepping out, but not this dame. She wanted payback. So what’s worse? That I pitched woo with a client, or that I billed her for services rendered after?”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Cute.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Cute? I mean, this guy sounds like a hard boiled PI right out of a Raymond Chandler novel. I wonder why Stan had this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hey yo, Beckett. Still got no word on that homeless guy, but a bodega owner saw a white Mustang parked in the loading zone right outside the club for the past three days.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>‘kay. See if anyone saw those license plates.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Right on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Um … Beckett? Can I take this home for the night? I mean, It might be the key to what Stan was looking for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You just want to read it because you think it’s cool.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah well, that too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, just so long as you …  … bring it back … in the morning.</content></utterance>
</scene>



<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>BARTENDER</speaker><content>Aren’t we all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>BARTENDER</speaker><content>Know her? I’m looking at her.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>TOM DEMPSEY</speaker><content>You know who I am?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>DEMPSEY</speaker><content>A wise guy.  I like wise guys about as much as I like crumbs eyeballin’ my girl. It’s rude. Uncivil.  That’s okay, Fred. The boys here are going to teach you some lessons.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The Blue Butterfly! It’s a necklace!  That’s why Stan Banks was killed.  Why am I narrating?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So anything on that threatening call to the dry cleaners?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah, the owner claims he doesn’t know anything about Stan or blue butterflies. However, a guy named Ray Horton rents out a back room. Turns out, Ray is a bookie on parole.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, so maybe Stan was trying to meet Ray at the Pennybaker so he could pay off some debts?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Uh, Ray was not there because of his debt. He was not even there about a blue butterfly. He was there about the Blue Butterfly. It’s a necklace. A butterfly shaped centerpiece made entirely out of blue diamonds  worth about a million dollars, easy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Where are you getting all of this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>From the PI’s diary.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>So Stan was on a treasure hunt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Exactly. Did a little research. Turns out the Blue Butterfly disappeared some time in the 40s. And, rumor has it, it’s hidden somewhere in the Pennybaker Club. If he found it, a million dollar necklace? Talk about a motive for murder.  By the way, Ryan, say "boyo".</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Boy o.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>BOY-o.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Boy-o.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>BOY-o.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Boy oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>BOY-o.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Boy yo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Anyway.  Did some searching on the net, there wasn’t a lot there, but I found it’s supposedly cursed and at one time belonged to an SS officer’s mistress. After the war, made its way stateside, and into the hands of mob boss Tom Dempsey,  who owned the club. Which is why we need to go back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah. You remember the green rod we found in Stan’s hand?  Apparently Dempsey’s downstairs office was painted shamrock green. Stan had to have gone down there. Also according to the diary, the Blue Butterfly was kept in the secret safe in Dempsey’s office. It’s very possible we missed something. We never really looked down there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, Ryan, you see if you can get a hold of the bookie. Castle and I’ll go back to the crime scene.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-20"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Boy-o.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-22"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Boy-o.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-23"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>BOY-o.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-24"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Boy-o.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-25"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Like a leprechaun.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-26"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Castle!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-27"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Sorry.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So the PI tells Sally that he found her sister here, at the Pennybaker Club.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And did Sally go talk to her sister?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, no. Joe could tell that Sally, being an innocent girl from the country, she was a little bit nervous about dealing with mobsters, so he offered to go back and make contact with Vera.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Out of the goodness of his heart, I’m sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Can you blame the guy? I mean, she was gorgeous. So anyway, Joe tells Sally he’s going to go arrange a meeting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Sally agreed, but again, insisted that Joe not tell Vera that she was looking for her because of all the animosity back home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ah!  I was right. I bet that’s where he got the steel rod, which is probably what he used to pry open the secret safe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hate to burst bubbles, Castle, but this hasn’t held anything in years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Looks like Stan was disappointed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, he probably would have been. If that was the secret safe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s not the secret safe?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Here’s a fun fact – people often kept two safes. One that was easy to find, for minor valuables, and a second safe that was much harder to locate, for the extra specials. Like Blue Butterflies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, where’s the secret safe?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’m coming to that. So it’s five days since Joe and Vera met. And they were very much in love.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>After only five days? C’mon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, people didn’t waste time back in the 40s. Matter of fact, they were so much in love  they risked it all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So what does that have to do with our secret safe?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It happened backstage.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Right upstairs. They were stealing a moment together, which was dangerous because she was Dempsey’s girl. As they stared into each others eyes, Kate’s heart quickened.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Did you just say Kate?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Are you picturing the PI as you and me as the gangster’s moll?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What?  No. And I didn’t say Kate, I said fate. Fate’s heart quickened. I was being poetic.  Anyway, as I was saying… They were just about to kiss when –</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And … that’s it. That was the last entry in the diary.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What do you mean that’s it? What happened to Joe? What happened to Vera?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> I don’t know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, why would you tell a story when you don’t know the ending?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>If you wanted a beginning, a middle, and an end I have 27 novels you can choose from.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, so where is the secret safe?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I don’t know. I think Stan must have found it. Maybe that’s why he needed that rod. Pry open a wall or something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, look at the molding.  What?  It’s unlocked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Stan found it. That’s why he was killed. But by whom?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Ray Horton. Assault, battery, and now you’re using a dry cleaners to front your bookmaking operation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>RAY HORTON</speaker><content>Whoa, slow your roll. A man on parole like myself can’t be mixed up in bookmaking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>How about murder, Ray? Is it okay to get mixed up in that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>RAY</speaker><content>Stan? Who – who killed him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>RAY</speaker><content>Me? Why would I kill my business partner?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Your business partner? C’mon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>RAY</speaker><content>It’s true, man. One of my clients hooked us up. He knew that I was looking to diversify and that Stan needed financing to find this lost necklace. Stan told me he needed 10 Gs for expenses to buy this old private detective’s diary, so I agreed to back him for half the profits.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>If all that’s true, then why did you threaten Stan’s wife?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>RAY</speaker><content>‘Cause Stan was ducking me. I thought I got played. But then he came up to me two days ago and he told me what’s up. He said he found the man with the missing piece of the puzzle to the Blue Butterfly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>And who’s this man?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-11"><speaker>RAY</speaker><content>I don’t know. But if Stan found the Blue Butterfly that’s probably who killed him.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So I traced the diary. Stan did his research. He purchased it from the daughter of Joe’s old secretary. A woman by the name of Ruth Huntsacker.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So I spoke to Ms. Huntsacker. She said she still might have some of the PI’s old papers and they might be able to tell us what happened. She’s going to have her son look for them and then call me back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Look Castle, I admit that Joe and Vera’s story is fun and romantic, but whatever happened back in 1947 has nothing to do with who murdered Stan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Ah,  I’m not so sure about that. Our bookie alibied out, but ballistics came in and we got a match.  The .38 caliber revolver that killed Stan was used in an unsolved double homicide … in 1947.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I knew there was a connection.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Who were the victims?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Uh … some lady named Vera Mulqueen and a private detective named Joe Flynn.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Murdered. That’s too bad. I really thought those two crazy kids were going to make it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, not exactly the ending I was hoping for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I didn’t even know ballistics went back that far.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh yeah, since the 20s.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Being that it’s an old case, there’s not much in the system. Remains of Joe Flynn and Vera Mulqueen were found in Flynn’s car. It was parked in the alley of the Pennybaker Club. Both victims we shot with a .38 revolver and the car was set on fire.  The only suspect was Tom Dempsey but there was never enough evidence to arrest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know, I bet you Dempsey caught the two of them trying to run away together and he killed them. But how does Stan’s killer get Dempsey’s gun 60 years later?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Unless … Dempsey killed Stan. He’d be what, like 90 years old, but it’s still possible.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Couldn’t have been Dempsey. He died of a heart attack 4 months after Joe and Vera were killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Ah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Still… we should dig up that 1947 police report. There could be something in there about the gun that could shed light on Stan’s murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> All right. I’ll go to the warehouse and pull up the old case files.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, oh! Ah… I want to go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-13"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Uh… okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Can I drive?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-15"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I don’t care.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-16"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hey. So, I’ve been searching guns that Dempsey used to own. Turns out there was an estate sale where a treasure hunter named Clyde Belasco bought all of Dempsey’s firearms, including two .38s.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Wait, Clyde Belasco? Stan’s wife said that the two of them watched a documentary about him and that inspired Stan to become a treasure hunter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-18"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, the connections don’t stop there. Belasco just flew in from France a week ago and I just found an article that said he searched for the Blue Butterfly for 15 years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That bookie said that Stan found someone that had the missing piece of the puzzle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-20"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Maybe Belasco is that someone.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Here it is. This has been dusted off recently.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Looks like we’re not the only ones interested in this case.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Stan was here. It had to be. Think about it. The diary, the murders. All we’re doing is walking in his footsteps. This is the next piece of the puzzle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Huh. Crime scene photo of Vera and the PI.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Damn it, Joe. You old sap. Dizzy with a dame and got yourself cooked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>So Mr. Bogart, what exactly are we looking for here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Our 1947 murders and our present day murder have to be connected by more than just a gun. Somewhere in here is that connection.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>CLYDE BELASCO</speaker><content>Yes, I bought several of Tom Dempsey’s revolvers. And by all means, test fire every last one of them as you wish.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>We will. Now, how do you know Stan?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>CLYDE</speaker><content>You have to understand, I’m on television. Articles are written about me. Because of this, the amateurs come knocking. It’s a … occupational hazard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And what was the purpose of Stan’s visit?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>CLYDE</speaker><content>Why, the Blue Butterfly, of course. He must have read of my exploits searching for it and decided to burden me with his preposterous story.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And what story was that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>CLYDE</speaker><content>That he had found an old private investigator's diary which held missing clues.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You didn’t believe him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>CLYDE</speaker><content>Of course not. When I asked to see the alleged diary, he refused. And yet, he wanted access to all my research on the Pennybaker Club. I mean really, the whole thing was absurd. He even asked to exit out the back door, said a car was following him. Was a white Mustang.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>CLYDE</speaker><content>I guess someone else was interested in the Blue Butterfly, too.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>It’s like we’re looking for a needle in a haystack, except for we can’t find the haystack.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Who needs a haystack when the needle is right here? This is a statement from Joe’s secretary, Mrs. Cunard, that was taken right after his death.  “Mrs. Florence Cunard, secretary to the victim, Joe Flynn, attested to bearing witness to the following conversation between both victims on the morning of June 24th, 1947.”</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>What happens next?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I don’t know. That’s the end of the statement.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>But if Sally wasn’t Vera’s sister then who was she?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Sally set up the PI. It’s a classic film noir twist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>But why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I don’t know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>What was Sally up to?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I don’t know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Do you think she was connected to Dempsey?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I don’t know! Isn’t this great?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yo Beckett.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So our uniforms got a line on that homeless guy who was squatting in the Pennybaker. A hotdog vendor ID’d him. Said the guy goes by the name of Westside Wally. I put a want out on the guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Great. That might be the break we need to catch Stan’s killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Excuse me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mmhmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hello.  What? When?  All right, I’m on my way. Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>That was the manager of Stan’s residency hotel. A guy driving a white Mustang just forced his way into Stan’s room. He’s still there.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>NYPD, show us your hands!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Show us your hands, now!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Turn around slowly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You’re Tom Dempsey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>TOM DEMPSEY</speaker><content> Yeah, that’s me.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Tom Dempsey the Third.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Dead ringer. Complete doppelgänger.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>TOM</speaker><content>It’s DNA, guys. It’s not a magic trick. I’m his grandson. All right, look. I’m sorry I broke in a door. I’ll pay for the damages. It’s no big deal. Why am I still here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, we were just curious to see if you inherited anything else from your grandfather, aside from his looks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, like one of his .38 revolvers that you used to kill Stan Banks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>TOM</speaker><content>Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. That didn’t happen. Look, Stan came to me, only he told me his name was Nathaniel Jenkins. He said he was a biographer, said he wanted to do a story about my grandfather. He promised not to focus on his underworld dealings, just on the good stuff. Like how my granddad was a pillar of the community.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> More like a killer of the community.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And so when he made his pitch, you, wanting to rehabilitate your family name, cooperated.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>TOM</speaker><content>Yeah. I gave him access to all granddad’s old papers and everything was cool. ‘Til I found out everything was a lie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And how’d you do that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-11"><speaker>TOM</speaker><content>There’s this singer that used to headline at my granddad’s club. Betsy Sinclair. A couple weeks ago she passed away. Well, I went there to pay my respects and who do I see there but Nathaniel chatting up this old guy. He sees me, jets out the back. I’m like, what the hell is this all about, right? So I look in the guest book and I figured it out. He signed his real name. Stan Banks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Which is when you figured out he wasn’t really a biographer?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-13"><speaker>TOM</speaker><content>He was just another lowlife treasure hunter looking for the Blue Butterfly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And if anyone deserved the Blue Butterfly, it was you, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So you followed Stan. And when Stan found it, you shot him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-16"><speaker>TOM</speaker><content> I didn’t – I did not shoot him. Stan – wait – Stan did find it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>C’mon. You tell us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-18"><speaker>TOM</speaker><content>I don’t know. I was not there. I read in the newspaper that the guy was dead. I went to his apartment to see what I could find. And I didn’t kill the guy.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Dempsey’s alibi holds up. He didn’t kill Stan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, that’s all right. Because we caught a break. Unis finally tracked down Westside Wally. They’re bringing him in now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Great. Maybe that can shed some light as to what happened to Stan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And if he can’t, maybe Jerry Maddox can.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Jerry Maddox?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You remember how Tom the Third told us that Stan went to Betsy Sinclair’s funeral? I started thinking, why would he go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>To do research.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Right. But research on whom? So I stopped by the funeral parlor. Turns out that Stan spent an awful lot of time with a friend of the deceased named Jerry Maddox. And get this. Jerry was the old bartender at the Pennybaker Club. And probably the last living link to the Blue Butterfly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Good job, Castle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>FRANKIE</speaker><content>Jerry? This is Detective Beckett and Mr. Castle. They wanted a word?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>JERRY MADDOX</speaker><content>Oh yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>VIOLA MADDOX</speaker><content>You want some soup? It’s homemade.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, I don’t mind if I do. That smells delicious.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Uh, no thank you. Actually, we’re all right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Am I hearing “I Can’t Give You Anything But Love”?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>JERRY</speaker><content> That’s right, kid. That’s the best version of that song, too. Come here to talk music, did ya?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Actually, we’re here to investigate Stan Banks’ murder, and we were wondering if you met him at Betsy Sinclair’s funeral.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-9"><speaker>JERRY</speaker><content>He … uh… he was murdered?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mmhmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-11"><speaker>JERRY</speaker><content>Poor kid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Did he mention a necklace called the Blue Butterfly?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-13"><speaker>JERRY</speaker><content>Oh, sure. Asked me all kinds of questions, where it might be, stuff like that. But I was just a bartender back then. I wasn’t much help.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Now this might seem an odd question, but in 1947 do you remember when Vera Mulqueen and Joe Flynn were murdered?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-16"><speaker>JERRY</speaker><content>‘Course. It was a big deal back then. Dempsey, the fella that owned the club, shot them in cold blood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Same year, do you remember a woman named Sally Scofield? She was a redhead. In 1947 she would have been about 18.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-18"><speaker>JERRY</speaker><content>Oh! I think I know who you’re talking about. That was back in ’46. I had just got hired at the Pennybaker.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>JERRY</speaker><content>Dempsey wasn’t dating Vera back then. He was going with a girl named Priscilla Campbell. Priscilla had a daughter, a redhead named Sally. Sounds like she’s the one you mean. Sad story, what happened. Not long after Vera caught Dempsey’s eye he dropped Priscilla and cut her and Sally off cold. They said it was the curse of the Blue Butterfly. Priscilla killed herself with a handful of pills.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And Sally?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>JERRY</speaker><content>Couple months after Vera and that PI got whacked, Dempsey died of a heart attack. The evening of his funeral in walks Sally, all dressed up. Ordered a whiskey neat, slammed it back, gave me a big old crocodile grin, said she was free. And she strutted on out the door and that’s the last time I ever saw her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s a revenge story.  Sally blamed Vera for the death of her mother, so she plotted to take her down. Somehow she used the PI to do it. She must have been setting them up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, but how does any of this help us figure out who shot Stan?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>So, Westside Wally. May I call you Wally?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>WALLY</speaker><content>I prefer Westside.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>‘Course. Westside, we know you were at the Pennybaker Club two days ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, we found your squat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>WALLY</speaker><content>Whoa, Cagney and Lacey. You can stop right there. I wasn’t living in the club two days ago. I had already gotten bought out by the other guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Bought out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>By the other guy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>WALLY</speaker><content>A few days ago the other guy comes in, starts setting up a squat by the door, but Westside Wally doesn’t do neighbors. So I said, hey professor, kick rocks. He wouldn’t take no for an answer. Ended up paying me $400 dollars to relocate. So again, for the record this time, I wasn’t there!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Easy. Easy, okay? Did you get this guy’s name?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-10"><speaker>WALLY</speaker><content>I didn’t ask, he didn’t say.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Can you describe him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-12"><speaker>WALLY</speaker><content>Medium height, medium build, white, 50s. I called him the professor. Because he spoke like a pretentious jerk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-13"><speaker>WALLY</speaker><content>Hey… it’s the professor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Clyde Belasco.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We know you were at the Pennybaker Club, Mr. Belasco. You paid off a homeless man so that you could have the place to yourself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>CLYDE</speaker><content>I have a condo on the Upper East Side, a chateau in Bordeaux, a chalet in Gstaad, and yet on the word of some vagrant you believe that I paid to squat in an abandoned building? Me? Clyde Belasco?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Pretty much.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>CLYDE</speaker><content>I’d like you see you prove it, sir.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>All right. Have it your way, professor. We will see you at the sentencing hearing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You can do your TV show from prison.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-7"><speaker>CLYDE</speaker><content>Wait.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-8"><speaker>CLYDE</speaker><content>Okay, I was there. I admit it. I was at the Pennybaker Club when Stan was killed. But I didn’t kill him. Like I said before, Stan came to me and asked for my research on the Blue Butterfly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And you said no?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-10"><speaker>CLYDE</speaker><content>Of course I said no. I searched for the necklace for 15 years and now I’m just supposed to help him? The glory was to be mine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>But you knew he was on to something, didn’t you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-12"><speaker>CLYDE</speaker><content>Oh yes. I could tell he was close, so very close. Stan knew things about the club, about the necklace, that I had never heard before.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So you staked out the club and when Stan showed you shot him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-14"><speaker>CLYDE</speaker><content>I didn’t shoot him, Detective. Yes, I had a pistol with me. And a bullwhip. They’re my trademarks. Everyone knows that. But I brought a mask and gloves as well because I was simply going to threaten him and take the prize.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So then what happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-16"><speaker>CLYDE</speaker><content>I was lying in wait. Stan went downstairs and when he returned, he was holding the Blue Butterfly. Oh, you should have seen how it sparkled. Magnificent. I was about to pounce when suddenly there was a rag put over my mouth. It had a sweet smell, like it was doused with chloroform.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Chloroform? Really?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-18"><speaker>CLYDE</speaker><content>It had to be. Everything went dark and when I came to, Stan was dead. I searched his body but whoever knocked me out took the Blue Butterfly with them.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>God, I hope it’s him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, but without a confession our case is purely circumstantial. I’m gonna see if I can get a warrant for Belasco’s place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Which place? The condo, the chateau, or the chalet?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Hi, this is Detective Kate Beckett, 12th Precinct. I’m calling for the writing ADA.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Mmhmm. Yeah okay, I’ll hold.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, it’s kind of disappointing. I was really hoping that solving Stan’s murder would give us some answers to what really happened to Joe and Vera.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, but we already know what happened. Dempsey killed them both.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, that’s the obvious version. But what about Sally? What’s her part in all this and why would she hire Joe?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, I guess we’ll never know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No, something else was going on. Something we’re missing. “Wearing T-strap shoes and a country suit, I could tell that redhead was a hick off the cob.”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Wait, what did you just say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, that’s just how Joe described her in his diary.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, the part about the shoes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>T-strap. It’s when the strap comes over the –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Yeah. Can I just call you back?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, take a look at this photo. There’s a shoe next to the car. And look at what kind of shoe it is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s a T-strap. You don’t think -</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>If Vera was at the club that night she’d be dressed in an elegant dress and –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And heels. This isn’t Vera. This is Sally.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, but it can’t be Sally. The bartender said that he saw her months after the murders. Unless –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-21"><speaker>CASTLE_BECKETT</speaker><content> He lied.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-22"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>But that was over half a century ago. Why would he lie about that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-23"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Beckett, I just realized something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Huh?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-25"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>“I Can’t Give You Anything But Love”.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-26"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>W – what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-27"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s what was playing when we interviewed the bartender.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-28"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Right. Right … he said that that was the best version of the song.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-29"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It was Louis Armstrong’s version. In Joe’s diary he says his favorite performer is Satchmo. What’s Satchmo’s real name?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-30"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Louis Armstrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-31"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Put it all together, the answer is clear.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>VIOLA</speaker><content>Oh… hello again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hello, Vera.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And hello, Joe.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>If it isn’t Vera Mulqueen and Joe Flynn, back from the dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>FRANKIE</speaker><content>Everything all right, guys?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-3"><speaker>VIOLA</speaker><content>Everything’s peachy, thanks, Frankie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What happened? Stan figured out the truth? That you two were alive? That you murdered two people so you could disappear with the Blue Butterfly? So you lured him to the club and then you shot him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-5"><speaker>JERRY</speaker><content>Lady, you got it all wrong. Stan cornered me at Betsy’s funeral, wanted to know how I knew her. So I lied, told him I was the bartender.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-6"><speaker>VIOLA</speaker><content>He – Stan was clever. He was too clever. He figured us out. He came here demanding to know where the Blue Butterfly was. He threatened to expose us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-7"><speaker>JERRY</speaker><content>He was like a dog after a bone. So we told him what he needed to know. We told him where it was. But we didn’t kill him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh c’mon, you guys. We know it’s you. You used the same gun from the ’47 murders to kill Stan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-9"><speaker>VIOLA</speaker><content>Same gun? We keep that gun in the –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-10"><speaker>JERRY</speaker><content>China cabinet!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Don’t even think about it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Put the gun down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-13"><speaker>VIOLA</speaker><content>Francis Benjamin Huntsacker, what have you done?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Wait a minute. Huntsacker?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It was your mother who sold the diary to Stan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-16"><speaker>JERRY</speaker><content>What diary?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Your diary.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So you read it. And all this time you were looking for the necklace, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-19"><speaker>FRANKIE</speaker><content>That’s why I got this crap job. And for six months I built trust, gently acquired information, and that jerk just waltzes in here and bullies the location of the Blue Butterfly from you? C’mon!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-20"><speaker>JERRY</speaker><content>So when you realized it was now or never, you bushwhacked Stan and took the Blue Butterfly for yourself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-21"><speaker>FRANKIE</speaker><content>I brought their old .38 only as a precaution. I was just gonna chloroform Stan and steal it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-22"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>But you found Clyde Belasco hiding behind the bar.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-23"><speaker>FRANKIE</speaker><content>I pulled the gun, Stan grabbed for it. I didn’t mean to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Let’s go, Frankie. You’re under arrest.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey Castle, guess what we found at Frankie’s apartment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Oh my. Oh my God. It’s beautiful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>It’s fake.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We confirmed it with an appraiser. It’s well-crafted costume jewelry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>All this time, and it’s paste? That’s – or maybe it’s a twist on a twist. Maybe the real Blue Butterfly was switched out for this one years ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, whatever happened, it doesn’t change the facts. We still have one more case to close.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="34"><utterance uid="34-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, so now we know that Frankie killed Stan, but there are two murders that need to be solved. Sally Campbell and whoever else you put in that car.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s time you come clean on what happened the evening of June 24th, 1947. The night you disappeared.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-3"><speaker>JERRY</speaker><content>Tell ‘em, Vera.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-4"><speaker>VIOLA</speaker><content>We were all huddled around the radio, listening to the Sugar Ray Robinson, Jimmy Doyle prize fight.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="35"><utterance uid="35-1"><speaker>VIOLA</speaker><content>I was building up nerve to make my escape.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-2"><speaker>TOM</speaker><content>Yeah, yeah, yeah … make it quick.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="36"><utterance uid="36-1"><speaker>LENNY</speaker><content>Well. Aren’t you a picture.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-2"><speaker>LENNY</speaker><content>I’m with her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-3"><speaker>VIOLA</speaker><content>The guy was Sally’s husband. She’d only hired Joe to get me away from Dempsey so she could exact her revenge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-4"><speaker>LENNY</speaker><content>Wait, Sal. Let me get the ice first.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="37"><utterance uid="37-1"><speaker>VIOLA</speaker><content>We were hot as a pistol and – and – and we had two bodies on our hands and we had to do something.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="38"><utterance uid="38-1"><speaker>VIOLA</speaker><content>Joe had the plan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-2"><speaker>VIOLA</speaker><content>No one would be looking for those two. We needed to disappear.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="39"><utterance uid="39-1"><speaker>VIOLA</speaker><content>Obviously we didn’t disappear far enough.  So. Are you going to arrest us?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why would I do that? Sounds like self-defense. Besides, we’re looking for a woman named Vera, not Viola. And a PI named Joe, not a former bartender named Jerry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-3"><speaker>JERRY</speaker><content>We don’t know how to thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I do.  Answer two questions. One, if you had the Blue Butterfly, why didn’t you take it? And two, where has it been all this time?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-5"><speaker>JERRY</speaker><content>Well, we were home free until doll face here had herself an epiphany.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="40"><utterance uid="40-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Cursed or not, did you ever consider going back for it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-2"><speaker>VIOLA</speaker><content>They don’t get it, Joe. I –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-3"><speaker>JERRY</speaker><content>We got four children, seven grandchildren, two great grandchildren. And each other. What do we need a Blue Butterfly for?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="41"><utterance uid="41-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you think we should have told Joe and Vera about the Blue Butterfly?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, no. Why ruin it for them? Now that’s the stuff that dreams are made of.</content></utterance>
</scene>

</script>