<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>ANNOUNCER</speaker><content>Welcome to A Night of Dance, America’s favorite dance competition. With your host, Brad Melville!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>BRAD MELVILLE</speaker><content>Hey, hey, hey! Good evening America! It’s dance off time and tonight’s theme is latin. As always, tonight’s challengers were handpicked by the judges.  Max, are you looking forward to watching these two rumba?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>MAX</speaker><content>I’m looking forward to Santino redeeming himself for his samba inspired solo dance last week. Pathetic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>PIERRE DUBOIS</speaker><content>It was like a terrible dream my dog would have after eating the leftovers of my Brazilian dinner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>BRAD</speaker><content>Well then. You know our semifinalists. Our matchup is Santino versus Odette. Can the arrogant bad boy best America’s sweetheart? Let’s get right to it. Tonight’s elimination dance between Santino and Odette will mean the end of the road for one of them. One will be eliminated on Monday’s results show. The other will be garunteed a spot in the final 2. Ladies and gentlemen, Santino and Odette!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>ASSISTANT</speaker><content>Odette, are you in there?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>MARTHA RODGERS</speaker><content>Guess who I ran into at the beauty parlor today?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>RICHARD CASTLE</speaker><content>Mother, I’m at a critical juncture and –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Oona Marconi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oona Marconi the theater critic?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>I thought I might invite her to dinner, ask her to give a little mention to my acting school, put it into one of her columns. It would be invaluable publicity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yes well, that would depend on the mention. You aren’t forgetting her blistering review of your performance of Maggie in Cat on a Hot Tin Roof, are you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>That was 1983. I think I’m over it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>“Martha Rodgers, as Maggie the Cat, is more of a helpless kitten, mewing and flapping her hands when she doesn’t get her way.”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>You memorized it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I couldn’t help it! You walked around the apartment quoting it for months!  Mother, I’m just saying. Maybe it’s not a good idea to ask an important favor of someone who’s been … so unkind to you in the past.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>The operative word here is ‘past’. I think I can rise above. Besides, my acting school is more important to me than some old grudge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, that’s very mature of you, Mother.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>“If Tennessee Williams knew what kind of crimes Martha Rodgers had committed against the audience in his name, he would have her arrested for assault.”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Rising above.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>KATE BECKETT</speaker><content>C’mon, Castle. How mean can this critic be?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’m just afraid that she’s going to get her heart broken, you know? I mean, you know my mother. On the exterior she’s a tough cookie, but … underneath all that bravado, gooey center.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey Lanie. So who’s our victim?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>LANIE PARISH</speaker><content>Odette Morton. Cause of death is a single GSW to the heart. Probably a 9 milimeter. She died instantly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>RICHARD CASTLE</speaker><content>That bullet went right through her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, unless our killer used a silencer, someone must have heard the shot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>JAVIER ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Not necessarily. According to the stage manager, this area clears out once taping starts. Plus the opening pyrotechnics could have covered a gunshot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, that’s assuming she was shot just as the show started.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>It looks like she was.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, the makeup girl finished with Odette at 2:45, taping starts at 3, and she was discovered at 3:04.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>19 minutes. That’s not a very big window.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>All right, see if the crew saw anyone near this room at that time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You got it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey Ryan? Can I get a list of the guests that were invited to tonight’s taping along with anyone that checked in at security?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>KEVIN RYAN</speaker><content>Already on it. But that’s not the only way in here. There’s an exit door to the alley down the hall. The crew guys like to prop it open so they can go out for a smoke.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So either our killer got lucky and found an unlocked door –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Or this was an inside job.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>That gets my vote.  Odette was a lock to win this thing. I bet it was one of her backstabbing rivals that did this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>What? I watch the show. Odette was my favorite contestant. She was an heiress raised by her rich grandpa, a party girl headed down the wrong path, then a brush with death made her wake up and change her bad girl ways.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s a great story.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-19"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Except for the ending.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-20"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I gotta say Dr. Parish, I never figured you for a fan of A Night of Dance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-21"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>I’m not … exactly. It’s just … when I was young, more than anything I wanted to be a prima ballerina.  If I wasn’t dancing I was thinking about dancing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So what happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-23"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>The girls came around when I was 13.  Not that many top heavy ballerinas out there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-24"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, I think there should be.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-25"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Of course you do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-26"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s not what I meant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-27"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Although …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-28"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Does Odette have any next of kin?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-29"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Um… Paul Morton. Her brother.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-30"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, great. Bring him down here. And talk to the rest of the contestants. I want to see if anyone was taking this competition just a little too seriously.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>We understand that you and Odette were rehearsing your dance most of the day? How did she seem?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>SANTINO</speaker><content>On edge. We both were. I mean, one of us was about to be eliminated, which is why I can’t believe she just left rehearsal at 11 and took off for a half an hour.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>To do what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>SANTINO</speaker><content>She wouldn’t say. But everything was riding on this dance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>JEANINE</speaker><content>She told me she had to meet a friend. She told me to cover if anyone was looking for her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Um… do you have any idea why she was being so secretive?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>JEANINE</speaker><content>The producers don’t like us to leave the stupid on show day, so if must have been important.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, the NYPD thanks you for your cooperation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> You too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Damn. Did you see that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Mmhmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>She acted like I didn’t even exist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You don’t. Not since you put that ring on your finger.  Get used to being invisible to single women.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>PAUL MORTON</speaker><content>I’ve never seen her happier than these past couple months. I can’t believe that my sister’s dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>We understand that she had some … difficulties in the past.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>PAUL</speaker><content>A few years ago our grandfather passed away and Odette took it hard. She quit school, she broke off her relationship with a nice guy, started hanging out with a bad crowd.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What kind of bad crowd?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>PAUL</speaker><content>Partiers … druggies. She was arrested several times, but after the accident she left all of that behind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That was her brush with death?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>PAUL</speaker><content>It was a train derailment last year. Odette was on board. She made it out alive, but it scared the hell out of her. She turned her life around. Six months of dance training and the next thing that I know she’s auditioned for A Night of Dance and been accepted. She finally found a direction in life. She was so close to realizing her dream.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Was there anyone in Odette’s old life that could have come back to cause trouble for her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>PAUL</speaker><content>Not that I’m aware of.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What about on the show? Anyone she didn’t get along with?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>PAUL</speaker><content> Uh … she did mention someone. Another contestant. I think she said his name was Eddie.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>JASMINE</speaker><content>Detective Beckett, they’re waiting for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>MAX</speaker><content>Detective Beckett. As co-creator and executive producer of A Night of Dance I’ve instructed my staff to provide you with anything and everything you need to help solve this terrible murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>PAM FRANCIS</speaker><content>Anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>PIERRE</speaker><content>Absolutely anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Thanks. Now, Odette told her brother that there was someone on the show that she didn’t get along with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>MAX</speaker><content>Eddie Gordon. But he’s not here anymore. Last week Eddie and Odette performed a Bob Fosse inspired number for the elimination dance off. We voted and sent Eddie home. He was upset.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>How upset?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>MAX</speaker><content>Well you have to understand. All the contestants are cast on this show to tell their unique, yet familiar stories. Odette was the poor little rich girl and Eddie was the kid from the wrong side of the tracks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>MAX</speaker><content>We cast Eddie to bring the drama. Eddie brought the drama, and not just for the cameras. He was furious when we sent him packing and we all got an earful about it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>PAM</speaker><content>Oh, he was so rude.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>PIERRE</speaker><content>I had to call security.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Was he threatening?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>MAX</speaker><content>Let’s just say that I was relieved when we was gone. Ironic really.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>How so?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>MAX</speaker><content>Well, according to the rules, when a contestant is unable to continue the last eliminated dancer returns to take his or her place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And that dancer is Eddie Gordon.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>EDDIE</speaker><content>Let me tell you something about Miss sweet and innocent Odette. She threw me under the bus tonight. She blew off rehearsals all week, then messed up her footwork, and blames it on me. Well where I’m from we know what to do with lying b*itches like that. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>That was Eddie’s exit interview. Contestants are encouraged by producers to speak freely.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He certainly took their advice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Eddie’s got a record back home in Rochester. And one of the assistants at A Night of Dance says they remember seeing him in the studio the afternoon Odette was murdered.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, so Eddie was eliminated but he knew that if Odette was out of the running he’d be asked to return and take her slot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So he went back and eliminated Odette.  Permanently.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>B and E, robbery … you’re pretty busy up in Rochester, Eddie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>EDDIE GORDON</speaker><content>Yeah, but that was a long time ago. When I started dancing I gave up thug life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, well that didn’t stop you from going off on the judges when you were eliminated.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>EDDIE</speaker><content> Me going home was the wrong call. And I said so. Maybe I said it loud, but that don’t make me no killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Now that Odette can’t finish the competition, the last eliminated contestant would be asked to return. And that’s you, Eddie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>EDDIE</speaker><content>Like my Daddy used to say, the universe works in mysterious ways.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And maybe you decided to give the universe just a little shove.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So what were you doing at the studio on show day?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>EDDIE</speaker><content>I went by early to see my boy Santino. Give him support on his big day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You’ve got an answer for everything, don’t you Eddie? You know what else you’ve got? You’ve got motive and opportunity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>EDDIE</speaker><content>Man, I was across town when that mess happened! Meeting my agent. But last week something was going on with Odette.  Something that didn’t have nothing to do with dancing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What do you mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>EDDIE</speaker><content>She was out of it. Missing easy steps. She said she was going to the ladies room then be gone for a half an hour.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What do you think she was doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>EDDIE</speaker><content>I know what she was doing. I saw her go out the back door. Meet some guy in the alley. Talk real serious for a minute. Then she’d hand him a roll of bills. Looked like 3 grand, easy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You get a good enough look at this guy? You think you can provide us with a sketch?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-17"><speaker>EDDIE</speaker><content>Yeah, I can do that.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey. So Eddie Gordon spoke the truth. He was meeting with his agent when Odette was shot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So maybe he was also telling the truth about the guy he saw Odette with in the alley.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, he gave us a sketch.  Pretty generic, though. Handosme, Caucasian, dark hair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You know, that missing half hour when Odette left rehearsal the day she was shot, maybe she was with him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hmm. I’ll have uniforms circulate the sketch through the studio. See if anybody recognizes him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay, so if Odette had straightened up after the train accident, what was she doing behind the stage door secretly giving some guy a roll of bills?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Could be a drug deal. Maybe Odette was falling back in to old habits. Any recent withdrawals in her bank statement?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, not for that amount of money. But check out these credit card payments.  For the last 6 months Odette’s credit card spending was pretty much steady and then about a month ago it suddenly shot up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No kidding. The cards were maxed out. Over a hundred grand in charges? What was she spending all that money on?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Thank you for coming in, Mr. Lynchberg. You were Odette’s business manager as well as the executor of her grandfather’s estate?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>SAMUEL LYNCHBERG</speaker><content>And now I have the unfortunate task of handling Odette’s estate as well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And who inherits her share of the family trust?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>LYNCHBERG</speaker><content>Per Odette’s wishes it goes to the Graham Morton Foundation. It’s a charitable organization.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know, I noticed a pretty big spike in her spending over the last month. Do you have an idea what that was about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>LYNCHBERG</speaker><content>I’m sure you know that after Odette’s grandfather passed away three years ago she … went through a bad period.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, her brother filled us in. Parties, drugs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>LYNCHBERG</speaker><content>Of particular concern to me during that time was her spending. Odette would get drunk and … spontaneously buy a car. Or put a bid down on a new apartment. She paid for her friend’s nose job. Just, whatever struck her fancy. But then after the train accident last year, all that stopped. It was refreshing to those of us who cared about her. I was worried that last month’s credit card charges indicated that she might have been backsliding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What was she buying?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>LYNCHBERG</speaker><content>Clothing, mostly. The bulk of the charges were over two days at one particular 5th Avenue department store.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I’d like to see the original receipts.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>LYNCHBERG</speaker><content>Of course.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>This is the weirdest spending spree I have ever seen. Odette spent tens of thousands of dollars on clothes, but nothing in her size, according to these receipts. Everything’s a size 4.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I went through her apartment. I didn’t see a hundred grand worth of new clothes. Maybe she hid ‘em.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Sounds to me like the old gas card scam.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What do you mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, your parents put you on a strict allowance, but they give you a gas card so you can fill your car. Well, you fill your friend’s cars and they give you cash. Some of my buddies in boarding school nearly doubled their allowance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Uh huh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Not me, of course.  That –  Don’t tell my mother.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So Odette needed cash in a hurry, to say maybe … pay off some guy in an alley?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>But the monthly stipend from her family trust wasn’t enough to cover it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So she charges the clothes, sells them to her friends. Instant cash flow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Which is still not enough. The cards max out, the money train stops, and she can’t make payment to whoever she owes. She ends up dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, but do you guys think that Odette had one size 4 friend willing to pay a hundred grand for a bunch of Peg jeans and a faux rabbit purse?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Did you say rabbit?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Jasmine?  We need to talk.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Where’d you get the bag?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>JASMINE</speaker><content>A friend gave it to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Your friend Odette Morton?  We talked to the salesperson, Jasmine. She said that you were with Odette when she dropped a hundred grand on clothes for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>JASMINE</speaker><content>Odette was very generous.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She’s also very dead and I know a blackmail scheme when I hear one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Maybe Odette had something going on in her personal life she wanted to keep secret. You found out about it but told her the price for your silence was a closet full of fancy duds.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>JASMINE</speaker><content>But why would I kill her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Maybe she couldn’t give any more. You got frustrated, you killed her. Maybe she decided to come forward herself, accuse you of blackmail. You killed her. Jasmine, these are just off the top of my head.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We can finish off this conversation in the precinct.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-10"><speaker>JASMINE</speaker><content>Wait.  Last month I was here working late. And I happened to see Odette walk by my desk real fast, like she was upset. Next thing I know here comes Brad Melville like he’s looking for her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Brad Melville, the show’s host? Why would the host of A Night of Dance be looking for a contestant. Aren’t they not supposed to fraternize?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-12"><speaker>JASMINE</speaker><content>That’s why I followed him. Brad and Odette were in the stairwell having a fight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>About what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-14"><speaker>JASMINE</speaker><content>I’m not completely sure. But when I bluffed Odette that I was going to tell Max about her and Brad she got really nervous. She offered to buy me some stuff I wanted if I’d keep quiet. And I thought that sounded like a good deal. But that’s it. I would have never hurt Odette.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You’ll have to pardon me if I don’t take you at your word.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-16"><speaker>JASMINE</speaker><content>Look, if anyone had a reason to murder Odette it was Brad.  Just listen. I recorded the two of them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-17"><speaker>BRAD</speaker><content>We had a deal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-18"><speaker>ODETTE</speaker><content>And I’m willing to stand by it if you are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-19"><speaker>BRAD</speaker><content>I have worked too hard to get where I am. If anyone finds out about this, Odette, I swear I’ll kill you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>If Max Renfro found out that Brad Melville was in a relationship with one of the contestants, what would happen?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-21"><speaker>JASMINE</speaker><content>She’d be thrown off the show and he’d be fired.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Motive for murder, anyone?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>BRAD</speaker><content>If anyone finds out about this, Odette, I swear I’ll kill you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>BRAD</speaker><content>That is completely not what it sounds like.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What it sounds like, Brad, is you threatening Odette Morton’s life a few weeks before she was murdered.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>BRAD</speaker><content>But I was trying to protect her!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Protect her how?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>BRAD</speaker><content>I knew about Odette’s troubled past. The drugs, the DUIs. But I also believed her when she said that she was clean now and that dancing was all she cared about.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Are you trying to say that that wasn’t true?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>BRAD</speaker><content>What I’m trying to say is two months ago I walked into makeup early and found Odette shooting up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Are you sure about this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-10"><speaker>BRAD</speaker><content>100% positive. If Max knew she was using she would have been eliminated on the spot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>But you never told Max.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-12"><speaker>BRAD</speaker><content>Odette promised she would clean up. I gave her a second chance. But I also kept an eye on her. Then a month ago I caught her again. I told her I was going to Max, that she was on her own.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And did you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-14"><speaker>BRAD</speaker><content>No. Because Odette threatened me. She said that if I went to Max and told him what I’d seen, that she’d go to him and tell him that I was the one that let her off the first time. Max would have fired me for keeping a secret that big from him. I’d be off the show! I’d be Brian Dunkleman!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Who’s Brian Dunkleman?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-16"><speaker>BRAD</speaker><content>Exactly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So if Odette went down she was taking you with her.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Brad was right about her shooting up. Found these hidden under a false bottom in her jewelry box. No wonder CSU missed it when they went through her apartment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Could be speed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, except I just got off the phone with Lanie. She said that preliminary tox screen results show that Odette wasn’t using drugs. A least, none of the usual ones.  So what the hell is in this bottle?</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>OONA MARCONI</speaker><content>And so, I said to Sir Lawrence, “Larry, that is the second best performance of Othello that I have ever seen. But I’m afraid no one can improve the Orson Welles interpretation. Larry,” I said, “you simply have been outdone.”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Oh!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>ALEXIS CASTLE</speaker><content>What did Olivier say to that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>OONA</speaker><content>He said, “My dear girl, you have the makings of a theater critic.”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>OONA</speaker><content>So here I am.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Yes indeed you are.  Oh, by the way. I don’t know if I told you that recently I opened my own acting school.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>OONA</speaker><content>Martha! How wonderful!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>OONA</speaker><content>How good of you to share your years and … years of experience with a new generation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yes, we are very proud.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-11"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>And I was wondering. Perhaps you might consider stopping by and sitting in on a class or two and then, if you felt so inclined, mentioning our little school in one of your columns.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-12"><speaker>OONA</speaker><content>I’d be happy to do that. You just tell me when and where.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-13"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Well, that’s lovely.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-14"><speaker>OONA</speaker><content>I just hope you’re not teaching your students your little trick of tilting your head before delivering an important line of dialogue.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-15"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>I don’t do that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-16"><speaker>OONA</speaker><content>Well, you did it when you played Maggie the Cat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-17"><speaker>OONA</speaker><content>Oh, and you fluttered your hands like little bird wings. I kept waiting for you to take off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Who wants pie? Alexis, would you? Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-19"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>I believe that was the year that I was nominated for a Tony.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-20"><speaker>OONA</speaker><content>Well, perhaps the American theater wing is more tolerant of head tilting and hand fluttering than I am.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-21"><speaker>OONA</speaker><content>Oh Martha, I’m just teasing.  You can’t possibly still be upset about that old review.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Let’s not say anything that we’ll regret.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-23"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>That was no review. That was a hatchet job. It was vicious and it was uncalled for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-24"><speaker>OONA</speaker><content>And it was also accurate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-25"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Rise above. Rise above.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-26"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>You know what, Oona? I rescind my request. There is no way that I would accept your endorsement of my school now if you begged me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-27"><speaker>OONA</speaker><content>Fat chance of that!  Just remember, Martha. Those who can’t do, teach.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-28"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>And those who can’t teach become theater critics!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-29"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Gram…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-30"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Could have been worse.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It couldn’t have been worse. My mother exposed her gooey center and Oona Marconi drove a stake through it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, tell her I feel her pain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Thanks. I will. Anything new on the case?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, unis found the café that Odette went to the day that she was killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Scoring drugs off her mystery man?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>More like scoring a fat free latte. She met up with a friend for a coffee.  Suzanne Steiner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>A friend. Leaving the studio on show day was a very big deal. What was so important that it couldn’t wait?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>According to Suzanne, she just wanted to talk about old times.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey. We got a fax from the lab.  That clear vial of liquid that we found at Odette’s apartment? It wasn’t illegal drugs. It’s insulin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Odette was diabetic?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Not according to her doctor. He says he hasn’t seen her in over a year.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well maybe she developed it recently. Or maybe she went to a new doctor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Then why not just tell Brad Melville the truth? That it wasn’t speed. It was insulin. And why bother buying Jasmine half of 5th Avenue to keep it quiet?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, I think I can help with that. CSU report is back in Odette’s place. They only found one set of prints and they were not Odette’s. They belong to a woman named Barbra Landau.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Who the hell is Barbra Landau?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-16"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Not someone who would run in Odette’s circles. She was raised in foster care and was a high school dropout.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So she was staying with Odette?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We need to talk to her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-19"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>That’s gonna be tough.  Officially Barbra Landau’s been dead for over a year. Here’s her death certificate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She died of blunt force trauma from injuries suffered in a train collision.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-21"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>That’s right. The same train collision that Odette survived.  Or did she? You see that picture of Odette? Well, this is Barbra.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>They’re identical.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>But that’s impossible.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-24"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Impossible? Or the explanation to everything? The dramatic change in Odette after the accident. The need to hide being a diabetic, because Odette was not a diabetic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-25"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Odette Morton didn’t survive that train crash. Barbra did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-26"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And like a phoenix rising from the ashes Barbra Landau walked away from the wreckage of that train and stole Odette Morton’s life.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Twin girls are born and put up for adoption. Odette goes to a wealthy, loving family. Barbra, not so lucky. She gets bounced around from one foster home to the next, always knowing deep inside that she was meant for something better. Then, one day, the two of them meet on a train bound for Miami. The connection is instantaneous. In two days, they learn everything there is to know about each other and Barbra can’t help but think, if only I had landed in the lap of luxury like Odette, I could have been anything I wanted to be.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Are you suggesting that Barbra purposefully caused the derailment to take over Odette’s life? With what, her crazy Wiccan powers?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh.  Wow, that would be an incredible twist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>But no. No. The accident happens. Odette is killed. Barbra survives. And in the midst of all the chaos and rubble, she sees her chance. She switches identification with Odette and she changes her destiny. In one move Barbra builds herself a better future. A perfect life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Until she was murdered a year later.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah well, separated twin stories never end happily.  Except The Parent Trap.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Blood tests are back.  Odette and Barbra were not biologically related.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Barbra has no living family that we could find.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well if they’re not related how can Barbra look so much like Odette?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I don’t know. But we do have an address for her former place of employment. A strip club in Midtown.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>See we’ve been operating under the theory that Odette was killed because she was Odette. But what if she was murdered because she was really Barbra?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Find out everything you can about Barbra. In the meantime, I’m going to reinterview Odette’s brother, Paul.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Is he a person of interest now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I’m just having trouble believing that Barbra managed to fool Odette’s own brother for over a year. He’s going to have to convince me that he didn’t know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well that sounds like something better done one on one, mano-a-mano.  I’m going to take a ride downtown with the boys, check out that strip club –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-16"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Sorry, Castle. Three’s a crowd.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-17"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What’s up? Why’re you freezing out our boy like that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-18"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I want to try an experiment. Having Castle along would mess things up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-19"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Here.  Wear my wedding ring.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-20"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What?  Get that thing away from me, man. It’s a mood killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-21"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Just wear it when we’re at the club.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-22"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What for?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-23"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>See, I’ve been talking to all my married guy friends. They say that your theory is way off. Wearing a wedding ring gets them more attention from women, not less.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-24"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-25"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>So, wear the ring.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-26"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I want to see if women still flirt with you and ignore me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-27"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So you didn’t want Castle to come because –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-28"><speaker>RYAN_ESPOSITO</speaker><content>All the women would flirt with him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-29"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I want to know if it’s just the ring that’s repelling members of the fairer sex.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-30"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>It’s not the ring, bro. It’s you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-31"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>See, once you’ve been married for a little while and you’re feeling a little bored and unsatisfied the ring will get you love from the ladies. They’ll want to take you away from all that so you can be bored and unsatisfied with them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-32"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Why not now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-33"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content> Because now you’re all blissfully happy with your wife and whatnot. You have the stink of honeymoon phase all over you. No woman wants to be around that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-34"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>How long does it last?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-35"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content> It’s hard to say.  But knowing you and Jenny, probably forever.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>CHANTAL</speaker><content>Oh yeah, Barbie. All she wanted to do was be a dancer on Broadway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>She used to talk about it a lot, huh?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>CHANTAL</speaker><content>More than that. She got a makeover, changed her hair. And then two years ago she got her nose done, even though her nose looked fine before.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Back in the day did Barbra have trouble with anybody? Say a customer? Maybe a boyfriend?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>CHANTAL</speaker><content>Boyfriend, yeah. Jason.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Can this be him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>CHANTAL</speaker><content>That’s him. Jason Bagwell.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Do you know where we can find Jason?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>CHANTAL</speaker><content>He lived over in Alphabet City. He was always running some scam. Borrowing money from Barbra for some business venture, never paying her back. But she loved him. Crazy love, you know?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content> Oh yeah. I do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, you’ve been very helpful, Chantal. Thank you for your time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-12"><speaker>CHANTAL</speaker><content>If you wanted, you could come back later. My show starts at 8.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I could probably get –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-14"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>He’s gotta get home to the little woman, Chantal, but we do thank you for your time and your cooperation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-15"><speaker>CHANTAL</speaker><content>All right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-16"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What’s wrong with you, man? Why’d you have to assault my game like that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-17"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>You can’t pick up on honeys while wearing the eternal symbol of my love and commitment to Jenny.  Did I just say that out loud?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-18"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Mmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-19"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>No wonder women won’t flirt with me. I’m a lost cause. A man in love with his wife.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-20"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Enjoy it, my friend. A lot of men would switch places with you.  Not me. Uh uh. Other men. Guys. Unhappy single guys.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-21"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah yeah yeah. Just give me my ring back and you can go get Chantal’s phone number.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-22"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What the –  Ow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-23"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-24"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>It’s stuck.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The guys are out picking up Barbra’s ex-boyfriend, I thought I’d use the time to follow up on what they learned at the club. Starting with the fact that Barbra Landau did get plastic surgery.  Here is her old DMV photo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She’s a pretty girl.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Exactly. Plastic surgery didn’t make her look more beautiful, it just made her look more like Odette Morton.  You remember her accountant? Samuel Lynchberg told you that Odette paid for her friend’s nose job.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And you think Barbra’s that friend? You think they knew each other?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I know it. Lynchberg’s assistant confirmed it. Odette paid for Barbra’s surgery, plus expenses.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And I’m guessing you have a theory as to why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You know Odette loved to party. Speaking from personal experience I can tell you that all that constant carousing does not come without consequences, like arrests, community service hours,  waking up in a strange hotel room with some girl’s panties on your head…  … that’s … forget that part.  Here is Odette doing community service hours for her second DUI in 2010.  Here’s Odette at a bridal shower with friends.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So according to the time stamps, these photos were taken on the same day within 20 minutes of each other.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So it was really Barbra at the soup kitchen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Odette would do the time, but she didn’t want to do the time. So she created a Faux-dette to do her dirty work for her. A job that I bet paid very well. Maybe a wild night on the town brings Odette to the strip club where she sees Barbra. All of Barbra. And she realizes that with a little work, Barbra could be the perfect double for her, doing all the dirty jobs that Odette simply couldn’t be bothered to do. Community service hours, drug tests …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And with a little training and some surgical tweaks, Barbra could do even more. Like meetings with Odette’s business manager or … boring luncheons with her Aunt Margaret.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Nobody in Odette’s inner circle could have known about the ruse, so that when the train crashed, Barbra saw her chance to go from understudy to leading lady and she took it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, so that explains the transition, but we still don’t know who killed her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Maybe we do. It would have to be someone that knew that Odette was actually Barbra when he saw her on TV. Someone who was looking to cash in on her new life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Someone like Barbra’s boyfriend Jason.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-17"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content>I’m telling you, this is crazy. I didn’t kill anybody.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Here’s what I think happened. You realized that Barbra didn’t die in that train accident. She was alive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And living as Odette Morton, which meant that she was very rich.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You knew her secret and you wanted to be rich, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>But Barbra wasn’t the kind of girl to claw her way into the good life and then be taken advantage of by the likes of you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She rejected you. And so you shot her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content>See, this is why I didn’t come forward. I knew you’d suspect me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We suspect people with motive, Jason.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content>You’ve got it wrong. Barbra came to me. Two weeks ago she showed up on my doorstep and told me the whole story.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Barbra had everything she could want. A perfect life. Why would she risk it all by getting in touch with you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-10"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content>Because she missed me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-11"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content>And Odette’s life wasn’t as perfect as Barbra thought. Barbra was lonely and she wanted to get back together. She told me that she had found out some stuff about Odette… um… secrets from her past.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What kind of secrets?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-13"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content>I don’t know. But she said if anyone found out it would all be over for her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You think this secret got her killed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-15"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content>She said she could use it to her advantage. She just needed more information. Information was leverage. It would protect her. But she had to move fast.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And she didn’t move fast enough.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-17"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content>Barbra had been dancing since she was a little kid and all she ever wanted was to be a star on Broadway.  And she was so close.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So it wasn’t something from her own past that got Barbra killed. It was something from Odette’s.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, so a week before her death, Barbra as Odette is acting odd, she’s missing rehearsals –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>She seeks out her ex, tells him that Odette’s perfect life isn’t so perfect and that there’s something in Odette’s past that’s a problem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Right. So she needs information. So where does she go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Suzanne Steiner. Remember Barbra met her for coffee the day she died. She wanted to talk to Suzanne about old times.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>SUZANNE STEINER</speaker><content>I’m not sure what help I can be. Odette seemed fine the day that I saw her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mmhmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>SUZANNE</speaker><content>Oh, I keep forgetting that she wasn’t Odette. The resemblance was remarkable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You said that she wanted to reminisce. How close were the two of you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>SUZANNE</speaker><content>My dad was the butler in her grandfather’s home for 20 years, so we practically grew up together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And what did she want to talk about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>SUZANNE</speaker><content>Well she asked about her grandfather. Well, Odette’s grandfather.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mmhmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-9"><speaker>SUZANNE</speaker><content>She talked about how close they had been.  And then she asked about the day that he died.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He died in his sleep, didn’t he?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-11"><speaker>SUZANNE</speaker><content>Yeah. Yeah, he was 98. It was odd that she asked, because I wasn’t there. But she was. Odette was. Along with my father and … when I reminded her of that, she asked about my dad. She said she wanted to catch up with him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you know if they two of them ever spoke?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-13"><speaker>SUZANNE</speaker><content>Well I gave her his number, but I’m not sure what happened.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hmm.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>It’s not coming off. It’s like it’s soldered itself to my hand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Maybe it’s possessed. You know, like some sort of cursed object in a Stephen King story.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>How can I tell my wife that I’m not wearing my wedding ring because I lent it to Esposito as an experiment to see if strippers would flirt with me?  Maybe she’ll see the humor in it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Not a chance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You’re a dead man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So, Charles Carson, former butler to Odette’s late grandfather.  No record, but get this. His name rang a bell so I looked up the guest list from Wednesdays taping and he’s on it. Odette called in a last minute ticket request for Mr. Carson.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So he was at the show?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yes. Security has him going through at 2:15, but after that no one remembers seeing him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay, so Suzanne said that Faux-dette wanted to talk about the day her grandfather died. What if this was the secret that Barbra was on to? What if Graham Morton didn’t die of natural causes and she felt somehow that Charles Carson here had something to do with it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We need to see Graham Morton’s autopsy report.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Based on my reading of the coroner’s report, I can see why Graham Morton’s death was ruled natural causes. However –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ooh… there’s a however.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>A very big however.  Tell ‘em.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>There were some anomalies that I found suspicious. Evidence of petechiae in both eyes, fresh bruising on the right side of Mr. Morton’s nose, which could have happened if say … someone was holding a pillow over his face. All in all, I think there’s ample evidence that Mr. Morton was murdered.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Ample?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Murdered.  I am just so proud –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content> Dad? Work. Boundaries.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-9"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>One more thing. When I requested the file be sent over, the clerk told me that I was the second person this week to ask for it. Odette Morton was there on Tuesday.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So Barbra realized Odette’s grandfather was murdered and must have thought Carson the butler had something to do with it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And then when Carson figured out that Barbra knew too much he killed her. We’re gonna bring him in first thing in the morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And arrest him for a double murder.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Good morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Speak for yourself. Oh Richard, I really messed up. I just let my ego get the better of me.  Now Oona Marconi is never going to endorse my school. She’ll probably write something negative just out of spite.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, there is a chance that you can still turn this around, but … are you willing to apologize to someone who doesn’t really deserve it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Darling, I don’t think a simple apology is going to get me out of this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Then in the wise words of Don Vito Corleone,  you need to make her an offer she can’t refuse.  And if there’s anything  … and if there’s anything I can do to help, you let me know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>I will.  I will.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mr. Carson, you worked for Graham Morton for over 25 years. I understand that you were very close with his grandkids.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>CHARLES CARSON</speaker><content>Well, as close as one could be while still maintaining the employer servant relationship.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So when the victim called you and invited you to the A Night of Dance taping on Wednesday, you said yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>CHARLES</speaker><content>I was delighted. She asked me to meet her afterwards, said she had a question for me, but of course as you know, they cancelled the show and I didn’t find out until the next day what had happened.  I had no idea that that girl wasn’t Odette. And no idea why she wanted to talk to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She wanted to talk to you about the day that Graham Morton died.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>CHARLES</speaker><content>Why would she care about that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It seems she had some evidence that Mr. Morton didn’t die of natural causes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-8"><speaker>CHARLES</speaker><content>I don’t understand. Are you saying that he was murdered?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You were at the house that day, weren’t you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-10"><speaker>CHARLES</speaker><content>Oh good lord. You don’t think that I had anything –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You were the person closest to him. You had ample opportunity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>We’ve seen the will. He left you an ample bequest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-13"><speaker>CHARLES</speaker><content>I would never have hurt Mr. Morton.  But that woman – the woman who pretended to be Odette – she might be right about his death. In fact, it’s possible that she believed that I knew something. Tell me, how did Mr. Morton die? Was he smothered?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why would you ask that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-15"><speaker>CHARLES</speaker><content>The month he died there was tension in the household. Odette was seeing someone, of whom Mr. Morton did not approve.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you know who?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-17"><speaker>CHARLES</speaker><content>No, but he ordered her to break it off. And of course that day Odette was crying, she spent most of the morning in her room. And about 1 o’clock Mr. Morton said that he wanted to take a nap. So I cleared the bed of all the pillows. He preferred a flat surface. Now a few moments later there was a commotion down in the kitchen. Odette had put a sandwich in the toaster oven too long and it had caused a small fire. We put it out and then I went back upstairs to check on Mr. Morton and he was dead. And that’s when I noticed it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Noticed what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-19"><speaker>CHARLES</speaker><content>A pillow. On the bed. And I was sure that I had taken them all off. So I told Odette about it, but she said my mind was playing tricks on me. So I let it go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mr. Carson, when you were in the kitchen was there ever a moment that Odette was out of your sight?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-21"><speaker>CHARLES</speaker><content>No.  I knew she was innocent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>She wasn’t innocent. She was a distraction. Odette got you down to the kitchen while her accomplice went and murdered her grandfather.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And then when Barbra Landau figured out the truth the accomplice murdered her, too.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Thank you again for coming, Mr. Lynchberg.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Mr. Lynchberg, being the Morton family financial adviser, that must give you pretty good insight into their personal lives, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>LYNCHBERG</speaker><content>Well, looking at what people spend their money on … you get to know folks pretty well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And how well did you know Odette?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>LYNCHBERG</speaker><content> As well as any of my clients. Given the lectures I’d given her about her lifestyle maybe more so.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>We understand about the time her grandfather died Odette was dating someone. Someone her grandfather didn’t approve of.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-7"><speaker>LYNCHBERG</speaker><content>Oh well… that’s not surprising. The two of them rarely saw eye to eye.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>This boyfriend, do you remember who he was?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-9"><speaker>LYNCHBERG</speaker><content> No. Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well because we think he conspired with Odette to kill her grandfather and that he killed Barbra when she was on the verge of figuring it all out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You’re sure you don’t remember?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-12"><speaker>LYNCHBERG</speaker><content> No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well we just spoke with Odette’s brother and he remembers. In fact, he remembers it being you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He said that they two of you wanted to get married but Odette’s grandfather threatened to cut her off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Now, a girl like Odette, she could never be happy living off a meager six figure salary like yours. She needed to inherit. But that old man refused to die.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So she convinced you to go upstairs and smother him to death with a pillow while she created a distraction in the kitchen. Problem solved.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Except once she had her money, she left you. Went back to her partying lifestyle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She used you. But there wasn’t anything you could do about it. At least, not without admitting to the murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-19"><speaker>LYNCHBERG</speaker><content>You can’t prove that. His death wasn’t even ruled a homicide.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, but Barbra Landau’s was.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Uniforms found this 9 millimeter in a dumpster behind your offices. Ballistics match. This is the same gun that was used to kill Barbra Landau and it’s got your fingerprints all over it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-22"><speaker>LYNCHBERG</speaker><content>Last month her credit card bills were so high, I thought she was slipping back into her old ways. I said to her, ‘we didn’t risk everything to get this money so you could let it ruin your life’. And she looked at me and I could tell she had no idea what I was talking about. In that moment I knew she wasn’t my Odette.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-23"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And that’s how she got on to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-24"><speaker>LYNCHBERG</speaker><content>So this Barbra told me that if I kept her secret she would keep mine. She thought we were even. She thought that she could just take the place of Odette. What – what was I supposed to do? Just let some dirty stripper live in her house and wear her clothes and – and blackmail me? Odette deserved better.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What’s going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I was just thinking about how we rely on dreams to keep us going in life and how sad it is when they become the things that tear us down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah well, that might be the case for Barbra Landau, but not for everyone with dreams that didn’t come true.  I mean, take Lanie for instance. She wanted to be a dancer. She became a doctor. That’s not so bad, is it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hum.  What about you? I mean, we know you became a cop because your mother was murdered, but there had to be something before that. What did little Kate Beckett want to be when she grew up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>At Stanford I was pre-law.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So your dream was to argue a case in front of the Supreme Court.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mmhmm. Yep. I was on my way to becoming the first female Chief Justice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Wow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mmhmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Not bad.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Argh! It won’t – you know what?  Ooh! I’m late for my stripper date.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Whoa whoa whoa … no, no. I – I cannot go home again without that ring on my finger tonight. My couch has a loose spring, my back –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey, did you try soap?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah, it was like the first thing we did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Cooking spray?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I didn’t think about cooking spray.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>It’s like silk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>That might work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Oh yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I think it’s coming.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>At least it’s off my finger.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Oona, thank you so much for stopping by.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>OONA</speaker><content>Thank you. Martha. And I’ll be sure to find a few inches of column space to mention your little school.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Oh, good. Thank you. I really appreciate that, dear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-4"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Oh Richard, you’re just in time to say goodbye to Oona.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, how nice to see you again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-6"><speaker>OONA</speaker><content>It’s lovely see you as well.  And I … look forward to hearing from you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hearing from – </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-8"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Well, I know you’re in a hurry, dear.  And um, I’ll call you. We will have lunch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-9"><speaker>OONA</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-10"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Yes. Bye-bye.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-11"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Aaaahhh! All's well that ends well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Mother, why would Oona Marconi be looking forward to hearing from me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-13"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Well, you did say if there was any way you could help …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That you should let me know. Exactly what did you promise her without asking me first?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-15"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>That you would read her novel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, Mother.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-17"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>And critique it and give it to your publisher.  It is the inspiring story of a young woman’s journey from a department store clerk to world renowned Broadway star.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Chick lit? Mother, this is really not my -</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-19"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Oh, and darling? When you give her your thoughts, do be kind. Because it’s always been her dream to be a novelist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Be kind. For you, Mother …  I can be kind.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>