<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>


<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>EMCEE</speaker><content>Ladies and gentlemen, the moment is almost upon us. As world-renowned trainer Francisco Pilar takes one last look at the finalists, only one question remains: Who will be this year’s Best in Show?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>REPORTER</speaker><content>I’m here in the audience with reality star Kay Cappuccio and her manager and boyfriend Reggie Star. Kay, when are you and Reggie getting married?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>KAY CAPPUCCIO</speaker><content>Oh …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>REGGIE</speaker><content>Um…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>REPORTER</speaker><content>Will it happen on the show?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>I just want to say hi to all my fans out there and remind them that next month my new scent hits stores. Kay Cappuccio’s Guilty Pleasure.  Make sure he’s guilty - of wanting you. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>EMCEE</speaker><content>Francisco is ready to reveal his decision.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>FRANCISCO</speaker><content> One.  Two.  Three.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>EMCEE</speaker><content>And there you have it, folks. This year’s Sunfair Kennel Best in Show is the one, the only –</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>RICHARD CASTLE</speaker><content>Buttons?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You have a friend named Buttons? A human friend?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>ALEXIS CASTLE</speaker><content> Her mom called her that when she was little and it stuck.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> And now so is she.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Buttons and I bonded over being rejected from Stanford. In fact, we applied to a lot of the same schools, so we were planning on visiting a few campuses together this weekend. Make a road trip out of it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Whoa. Okay, whoa. Where are you staying, who’s driving, who’s chaperoning?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>We were going to take your Ferrari and hook up with some boys we met on Craigslist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Not cool.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>MARTHA RODGERS</speaker><content>Honey, don’t be suck a killjoy. I’m sure Buttons’ mother is going along.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>She is. And she’s very responsible.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, except when it comes to picking nicknames.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Look, if you want, I can have Mrs. Dutton stop by to meet you when she picks me up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, I think that’d be ok-  Her last name is Dutton?  Her name is Buttons Dutton?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>That is unfortunate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>What’s so wrong with that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, c’mon. That’d be like calling me Wrassel. Or Tassel  or No Hassle Castle. Hey.  No, I was just making a point.  Please don’t call me that.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>JAVIER ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Victim is Francisco Pilar. We found him here in his dressing room. He still had cash on him, plus his wallet, phone, and key card of some kind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>KATE BECKETT</speaker><content>Is the cause of death what it looks like?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>LANIE PARISH</speaker><content>Yep. Someone put a leash around his neck and pulled.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you guys have an estimated time of death?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>We put together a window –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Excuse me. You’re doing my job now? I didn’t know you went to medical school.  But go ahead, Dr. Esposito.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content> Okay. Last guy to see Francisco alive left this room at 5:15, to go get him some dinner. And Mr. Green found him like this 20 minutes later.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay. Thanks.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>ADAM GREEN</speaker><content>Hi. Adam Green. I’m the Sunfair Show organizer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mr. Green, how well did you know our victim Francisco?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>GREEN</speaker><content>Uh, Francisco’s been our judge for almost two decades. No one cared about dogs more than he did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Did he have any family that we could talk to?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>GREEN</speaker><content>Royal was his family.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, that’s a handsome pooch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>GREEN</speaker><content>Francisco loved him very much. Truth is, he got along better with dogs than their owners.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So dog whisperer, check. People whisperer, not so much.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Uh, did he have any problems with any of the owners?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>GREEN</speaker><content>What are you suggesting?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Just that he was killed about a half an hour after he gave out Best In Show.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>GREEN</speaker><content>I’ll admit that show dog owners can be passionate people. But not to this extent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Somebody wrapped that leash around his neck.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We’ll need a list of the names of all of the contestants, along with anyone that might have had access to this room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>GREEN</speaker><content>Of course.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Is this Francisco Pilar’s dog?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>GREEN</speaker><content>Yes, that’s Royal. We thought it best to keep him out of the room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Why is he doing that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>GREEN</speaker><content>He was doing the same thing by the body when we found him. Maybe some sort of grieving process? I’ll get you that list of names.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So, the dog was at the crime scene at the time of the murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What do you want us to do, bring him in for questioning?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’m just saying – would man’s best friend just stand idly by while his master was attacked?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And if he did intervene, maybe he got DNA or trace evidence on him that could lead to our killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>KEVIN RYAN</speaker><content>May have a lead of my own.  One of the losing contestants just filed this appeal of Francisco’s decision. A guy named David Hernand. Said he was so angry the vein in his forehead was visibly throbbing. Apparently dog shows are this guy’s whole life.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>DAVID HERNAND</speaker><content>Was I upset about Francisco’s death? Sure. I was more upset about his choice for Best In Show. Hey, that ribbon belonged to my Max.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mr. Hernand, can you account for your whereabouts between 5:15 and 5:35?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>HERNAND</speaker><content>Yeah, I was right here at my grooming station filing my appeal – oh look, I didn’t kill him, okay? Given everything he was into, I’d say he brought it on himself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And what exactly was he into?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>HERNAND</speaker><content> Well, rumor has it he was on the take.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Are you saying he was taking bribes to fix dog shows?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>HERNAND</speaker><content>Betting on dog shows? It’s a big business. And he was seeing some pretty shady characters. People with ties to Vegas.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s a serious allegation. Do you have any proof to back it up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>HERNAND</speaker><content>You want proof? That’s who Francisco selected Best In Show.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>HERNAND</speaker><content>Just look at that mutt. Now back to my Max. Now the mutt. That’s all the proof I need.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Really? There’s big money riding on dog shows?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s actually kind of ingenious. You know, everyone’s got football, basketball, horse racing under a microscope looking for the slightest hint of impropriety. Who’s looking at dog shows?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I’m going to have Ryan look into it, along with Hernand’s alibi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Whatever you’re talking about, it can wait. Ma’am, please tell Detective Beckett what you told me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>KELLY GUNTHER</speaker><content>I was backstage after the show when I saw a woman leave Francisco’s dressing room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Can you describe her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>KELLY</speaker><content>Even better. I took a video with my phone. She was wearing a hood and sunglasses, but I recognized her instantly.  It was Kay Cappuccio.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The reality television star?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Check the time stamp. Right in the middle of our time of death window.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Here’s what I don’t get. Why would Kay Cappuccio want to kill Francisco Pilar?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Here’s what I don’t get. How does this woman have her own perfume line, an army of paparazzi outside her apartment, millions of Twitter followers, dozens of magazine covers, all with no discernable talent to account for it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Even more perplexing? Why in almost every photo is she posed like this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh guys, sorry. No time for photos.  Okay, maybe just one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>PAPARAZZO</speaker><content>Hey, that’s not Jason Bateman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s getting old.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>REGGIE</speaker><content>Oh, you two must be the softer people, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Actually, no. We are NYPD. We are here to speak with Kay Cappuccio.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>REGGIE</speaker><content>Oh, my bad. Uh, why don’t you just grab a squat right over there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Excuse me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>REGGIE</speaker><content>Phoebe will bring you a goji berry juice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know what? I think I have a better idea.  Everybody, take five.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>REGGIE</speaker><content>Whoa, hold on a second. Kay Cappuccio doesn’t have five to spare.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>How about 15 to 20?  And that goji berry juice sounds delightful.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>Sure, I knew Francisco. I hired him to do two weeks of behavior training with my dog. Our show is going to start shooting again soon and Lolita has some minor aggression issues I wanted taken care of.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>This little charmer? I find it hard to believe –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I assume you asked for your money back?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>I never paid him. He brought her back yesterday morning after just a few days. Said he didn’t want to work with me. So are we done here? Because I have fittings, a couple endorsement meetings, like … three red carpets I have to show up at…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And I’ve got a witness that places you at the murder scene. So sit down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content> Sure. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Now why did you go to see Francisco after the dog show last night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>I wanted an explanation as to why he wouldn’t train Lolita.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And what did he tell you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>I would so much rather not go into it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We’ve got a video of you leaving Francisco’s dressing room right around the time of the murder. So not going into it is not an option.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>Fine. We didn’t talk about anything because he was already dead. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You found the body?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And you didn’t call 911?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>No, I did. As soon as I got into the limo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-17"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>No harm no foul, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You fled a crime scene.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-19"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>All right.  Have you heard the phrase ‘there’s no such thing as bad press’? Having your picture taken with a dead guy is the exception. I have to be so careful with my image. My image is all that I have.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, no. We were just talking about that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ms. Cappuccio, when Francisco brought your dog back, was he acting unusual at all?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-22"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>Oh, I didn’t see him. He showed up in the middle of my 10AM workout.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-23"><speaker>PHOEBE</speaker><content>I was here, so I took Lolita. But you’re right. The guy was acting weird. He kept saying ‘who is she working for? I know she’s working for somebody.’. He seemed really paranoid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-24"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Do you have any idea what he was talking about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-25"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>No clue. That’s why I went to go talk with him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-26"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay. I guess then we are done.  For now. Just uh … stay available for questioning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-27"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>Oh my God, like I’m gonna go anywhere? I can’t take one step without a million people taking my picture.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, it’s no mystery why someone wouldn’t want to be in business with Kay, but why did Francisco think she was working for someone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Especially since her whole life is about not working. And what made him so paranoid about her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Maybe he had something to hide. Looks like there might be some truth to those rumors that the fix was in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, I’ve been going to Francisco’s financials. He made a bunch of cash deposits over the last year. Ten grand a pop. So we went back and looked at the last few shows he judged. Our boy had a thing for long shots.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>The line in Vegas on yesterday’s Sunfair winner was 50 to 1. A real underdog.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What doesn’t make any sense is if he was taking the bribes, why would they kill him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Maybe he wanted out. Or more money.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>His calendar said he had weekly appointments with a therapist, Dr. Patty Barker. They had a session the day he died. Maybe she can fill in some gaps.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay. Let’s bring her in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>All right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Brought you guys a little visitor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, look who it is!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Okay, adorable. We swabbed his mouth for human DNA but I don’t have high hopes. Even if there were some, all that slobbering - it’s probably long gone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hey, what are we going to do with Royal? I mean, Francisco didn’t have any family.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>I didn’t have the heart to call Animal Control.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-16"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Jenny’s friend runs a rescue.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Or … we could keep him here at the precinct. I mean, we could use a mascot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-18"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I thought that’s what you were.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That -  What’s that? What’s that, buddy? Esposito’s sense of humor fell down a well and can’t get out?  Please?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, fine. But only until we find him a suitable home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-21"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Then you better find out what kind of food he eats, because he’s not touching the stuff I put out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-22"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, there’s gotta be some food for him at Francisco’s place. Who wants to make a run for it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-23"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>To go get dog food?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-24"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Castle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-25"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ryan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-26"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Esposito.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-27"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well. Shall we settle this like men?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-28"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>All right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-29"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Mmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-30"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Two out of three?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-31"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Snip.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Dr. Barker, what kind of issues was he dealing with? Did he ever exhibit signs of paranoia?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>BARKER</speaker><content>No. The occasional bout of depression, which then led to low self-esteem, which lead to binge eating. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>An eating problem? You wouldn’t know it to look at him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>BARKER</speaker><content>Oh, his diet was horrible. Oh, scraps from the garbage, dead birds, even his own feces.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>We’re not talking about Francisco, are we?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>BARKER</speaker><content>Oh … you – you thought I was Francisco’s therapist?  My patient is Royal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>BARKER</speaker><content>Well, I am a canine therapist. It’d be pretty crazy for me to treat people.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>People. That would be crazy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Uh, Dr. Bark- Mrs. Barker, how did Francisco seem to you at Royal’s last appointment?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>BARKER</speaker><content>Actually, he canceled it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Did he say why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>BARKER</speaker><content>Just that something had come up, then he had to be somewhere in a hurry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, that’s … actually helpful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, um… thank you. We’ll contact you if we need anything further.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-16"><speaker>BARKER</speaker><content>How is Royal doing? Is it true that he was at the crime scene? That he witnessed the murder?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>We think so, yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-18"><speaker>BARKER</speaker><content>There may be things he saw. Things he is trying to communicate about the crime. If you let me see him, I can try to find out what he knows.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You know, Francisco had a lot of faith in her. It might be worth a few minutes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Of your time, sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’ll get him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-22"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Beckett.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-23"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I found enough dog food to keep Royal fat and happy for a while. Found something else tasty, too. Electronic bug sweeper. Looks new.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>To detect eavesdropping devices?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-25"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Uh huh. Paranoia or not, Francisco thought he was under surveillance.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, Francisco was worried that he was being bugged. Then yesterday, somewhere around 11AM, he runs off right around the time that Kay’s assistant said he started acting paranoid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And then a few hours later he’s murdered.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So then where the hell did he go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You know, we’ve got Francisco’s cell phone in evidence. If the GPS was turned on it might tell us exactly where he went.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>BARKER</speaker><content>Yes, that’s right. I know. I know you are. Oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>BARKER</speaker><content>The poor thing is just traumatized. How was he when you found him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Uh, they said he was pawing at the ground. The man from Sunfair said that was a sign of bereavement?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>BARKER</speaker><content>Royal. Royal, look at what I’m doing. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>BARKER</speaker><content>That’s right. I know it is.  He was trying to tell you something. Something important.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Really? You can tell all that from-</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>BARKER</speaker><content>Royal, look at me. I know. I know you’re hurt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>BARKER</speaker><content>You’re confused. You’re dealing with abandonment issues.  There’s a lot to break through here. This could take some time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Tell me, did Francisco ever observe you during your sessions?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>BARKER</speaker><content>No. He waited outside. Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No reason.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>According to his phone, this is the place Francisco went yesterday before the dog show. Maybe it was to meet his gambling contacts.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Couldn’t he just do this over the phone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Not if he was being bugged.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Remember what else Francisco had in his pocket?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What is this place?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>It looks like some kind of a kennel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, I see the cages, but where are the …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Shepherds.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Okay, listen. A friend of mine had one of these. They smell fear, so don’t flinch. Whatever you do, don’t –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Run!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ahhh!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Go!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Okay, okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>JACK PATTERSON</speaker><content>What the hell are you doing in my warehouse?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Detectives Beckett and Esposito, NYPD.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>PATTERSON</speaker><content>You got a warrant?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Who are you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>PATTERSON</speaker><content>Jack Patterson. I work for Francisco Pilar. Did anyway. What do you want?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We’re investigating his murder. What the hell is this place?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>PATTERSON</speaker><content>Francisco was breeding a new type of dog. The Pilar Retriever. I managed the operation when he was travelling. It was a real tragedy. Guy spends his entire life developing a dog. He was almost ready to unveil it, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>How well did you know Francisco?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, did he have a gambling hobby? Possibly took some bribes from the wrong people?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>PATTERSON</speaker><content>Francisco didn’t have hobbies. His whole life was his work. And it was honest work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, well the thing is, Francisco made a bunch of major cash deposits into an account.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>PATTERSON</speaker><content>Let me guess. Ten grand each, right? Word was leaking out about the Pilar Retriever. People were stopping Francisco at dog shows, giving him cash just to reserve a pup from the first litter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Any idea why he rushed over here yesterday?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>PATTERSON</speaker><content>Actually, yeah. He showed up with a bug detector, started sweeping the place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why would anyone want to put a kennel under surveillance?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I don’t know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-11"><speaker>PATTERSON</speaker><content>Well, his breeding and training methods were closely guarded secrets. And the Pilar Retriever was making his competitors very nervous.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Anyone specific?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-13"><speaker>PATTERSON</speaker><content>It sounded crazy at the time. He thought one of his dog training clients was in business with someone who was trying to infiltrate our operation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And did he tell you which client?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Kay Cappuccio? Why would she steal Francisco’s secrets?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We don’t know for sure that she did. In fact, we don’t actually know that he was bugged by anyone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, we do now.  Francisco’s sweeper has a memory and it tripped to a listening device yesterday morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The same time he confronted Kay’s people and asked who she was working for. This can’t be a coincidence that all happened on the day he was killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know, I’ve got a feeling that Kay Cappuccio knows a lot more than she’s letting on. We’re going to have to talk to her again. And this time, she’s coming to us.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Right this way, Ms. Cappuccio.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Just her.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I don’t really watch reality television, Ms. Cappuccio. Would you like to know why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>Kisses. Kisses.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Because I usually find that it’s not all that real. And I don’t like things or people that present fiction as truth. In fact, I find it to be a waste of time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>Okay, is this why you brought me down here? To insult my show?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>This isn’t about your show. I want to know what really happened to Francisco, this time the truth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>I told you the truth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, according to your assistant, Francisco asked you who you were working for. What does that mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>I told you, I have no idea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Really. No idea that he was starting a breeding venture that his competitors were just dying to know about. Tell me, does the phrase ‘corporate espionage’ mean anything to you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-11"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>No, seriously. I have no idea what it means.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Could I, uh, see you guys for a minute?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>She set off the sweeper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>The bug sweeper was on my desk when she walked by. It went off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You think she’s wearing a wire?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Dude. Look at that outfit. Where is she going to put a wire?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, if I’d have to be creative I’d guess  ... that that was rhetorical.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>We went into the tech room to isolate the frequency that the bug was transmitting on and we found … well …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Show ‘em.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content> Oh sweet baby, mommy’s going to get you home so soon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Boobs?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Not just any boobs. Her boobs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s in the collar. There’s a camera in one of the jewels on the dog’s collar.  You said she takes that dog with her wherever she goes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Mmhmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Which means that Francisco probably wasn’t the intended target of the surveillance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Kay Cappuccio is.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>I cannot believe that someone has been watching me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ms. Cappuccio, when you say that your dog goes with you everywhere –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>Oh my God! He could have seen me in the shower. He could have seen me and Reggie in bed together.  He could have seen me without my makeup.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>I feel so violated.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Look, the paparazzi are aggressive. But wiring a dog collar, that’s a lot of effort to go through just to get some celebrity video.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>Oh, well, I mean, it’s not just any celebrity video. I mean, TMZ’s offered like, a million bucks for the first naked picture of me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You ask me, that number’s on the low side.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>You are too sweet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>A million dollars is a pretty powerful incentive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-11"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>When did you get that collar?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-13"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>Um … a few weeks ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The camera would have to be installed since then, which would mean they would need access to your dog.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-15"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>Lolita is barely even out of my sight. Only when she goes on her walk or to the groomers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>‘Kay, we’re going to need the names of all of those people, along with your house staff. We’re going to want to run background checks on all of them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-17"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>In the meantime, we should keep the collar cam active. We don’t want whoever’s behind this to know that we’re on to them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Right. Which means, just go on about your regular routine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Just try to keep your private moments … more private.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>If Kay was the actual target of the surveillance, what does any of this have to do with Francisco’s murder?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What if Francisco discovers the collar is rigged? He returns the dog to Kay but doesn’t get the chance to confront her about it at the time. But whoever is monitoring the feed, hoping to see her naked, hears Kay say that she intends to talk to Francisco after the show.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So they killed him to keep him quiet?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>This is paparazzi we’re talking about. I could see one of those scum killing for a fat paycheck.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So if we find whoever bugged that collar then we might be able to find our killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, we could go through recent photos of Kay, you know, from tabloids, gossip websites, and see if she can identify any of them as being from the collar cam.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And then there might be a trail that leads back to the guilty party. So we’re going to have to find somebody to pull all those photos.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content> I’ll do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Got a little case of puppy love there, Esposito?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You do realize that she’s got a serious boyfriend, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Who? Reggie?  He’s a backup dancer in a fitness video. I mean, I don’t even know what she’s doing with that knucklehead. I –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, it looks like Esposito isn’t the only frustrated dog in the precinct. Who closed him up in there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh, he had to take a nap, but he can’t stay there overnight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I could take him home with me. Alexis is gone for the weekend and I could use the company.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Or … I could take him home. I mean, I’ve been thinking about getting a dog, this might be a great chance at a trial run.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh. Yeah. All right. I guess you can take him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I mean – I – I don’t want you to feel lonely.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, I could flip you for it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No Rochambeau?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, I mean, that would put you at an unfair disadvantage. I’m pretty good at it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh, c’mon, Castle. Let’s go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>All right. Just so you know, there’s strategy to this game that uh-</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-23"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Two out of three?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mmhmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-25"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Three out of five.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-26"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-27"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know, there is another way that we can go about this.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, you were supposed to be here over an hour ago, you know. It’s called shared custody, not show up when you want custody.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, I thought I had everything together but at the last minute I could not find Mr. Squeaky.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So. Don’t worry about feeding him – I had a rib eye I couldn’t finish.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You fed him a steak?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah. Don’t worry, we worked it off. He played fetch in the hall and then we watched some Beverly Hills Chihuahua. Boy, this guy – this guy is a snuggler.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And I bet you let him sit on your couch, didn’t you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Um…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, it’s okay. You can be the fun one. I’ll just be the bad guy  because there is no way that you are shedding all over my couch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh no, he’s perfectly happy right there. Oh, and he loves it when you rub him right between the eyes. Just little circles with your thumb, not too hard, just …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle -</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah. You get it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Um, all right. You guys have fun.  Don’t miss me too much. . The dog, not you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay. C’mon. Right here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You’re so cute!</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>I’m so sick of looking at myself right now. I can’t even imagine how you must feel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Don’t worry about me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What about that one?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>Um … that is what I wore on Thursday. So that means Lolita was off at the groomers, so no. The collar couldn’t have taken this picture.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I can’t believe you can identity what day of the year it is just by what you’re wearing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>And people say I’m talentless.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Don’t listen to those haters. How many of them can say they’ve got their own cosmetics line, huh?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>How about this one?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>No, God, I remember that day. There was this creep photographer hidden down between two cars.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-10"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>This is depressing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Don’t worry, we’ll catch the guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-12"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>No, I mean my life. It’s … shopping. And partying. And more shopping. And it is bad enough that people fight to take pictures of me doing all this dumb stuff, but –  Do you really think that Francisco was murdered because of it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, if he was, it doesn’t make it your fault.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-14"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>Did he have a family?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-15"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No. It was just him and his dog.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-16"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>Oh, well, I guess we weren’t so different then.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-17"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What are you talking about? You uh … well, you have Reggie. Phoebe. All your friends. Look at all these pictures. You’re never alone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-18"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>Pictures can be really deceiving.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-19"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>Wait. This one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-20"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>This one? This is from a high angle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-21"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>No, no. This is from last week. This is the day that Lolita got off her leash and she climbed up this hill and it would have been her exact vantage point.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-22"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Now all I gotta do is call Celebrity Report and they ought to lead me right to –</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Marcus Hiatt. All the pictures IDed from the collar cam can be traced back to him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He was outside of Kay’s place with the rest of the paparazzi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>The guy’s a full on stalkerazzi. Harassment, trespassing, even B and E. Seems like there’s nothing this guy won’t do to get that big money shot. And we know he had opportunity for the murder because he was issued credentials to that dog show.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Wonder where he might be now.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Who is your cable service provider? Because I do not get this channel.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You recognize your work, Marcus?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Kay Cappuccio did, and so did that scandal rag you sold it to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>BECKET</speaker><content>How did you get access to the dog? Did you pay someone off?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>MARCUS</speaker><content>You guys are way off base here, all right? Look, it’s not what you think.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No? Because I think you knew that if Francisco told Kay about the collar, she’d go straight to the FBI and you saw your whole world crashing down around you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>MARCUS</speaker><content>I did not kill that Francisco guy. I didn’t wire the dog collar, either.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Marcus, we just caught you watching the feed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Who’s a good boy, huh? Who’s a good boy? Is Marcus a good boy?  No, he’s not a good boy. He’s a bad boy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>MARCUS</speaker><content>… maybe hack into her cell phone, maybe find some nude pictures of her or something.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>MARCUS</speaker><content>But then out of nowhere, I picked up that video feed. Kay Cappuccio dropping her bathrobe and jumping into the shower. Look, I know they say she’s got no talent, but let me tell you something, brother. That girl’s got more talent than a thoroughbred.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hey! Watch your mouth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you actually expect us to believe that you accidently came across that feed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>MARCUS</speaker><content>Look, I don’t know where it was coming from and really, I didn’t care. I was sitting on a gold mine. Only I didn’t have the equipment to record it at first, so I scrambled to get it set up, but later that day they shipped the dog off to that damn trainer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, that’s a great story, Marcus.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>MARCUS</speaker><content>Look. If you want to find who killed him, find who he’s doing business with. And I’m not talking about his dog training business, either.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Then what are you talking about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-8"><speaker>MARCUS</speaker><content>I drove back there to check on the signal, right? Thought maybe I could find out when the dog was going back to Kay. The things I heard that Francisco guy talking about? Yeah, he was into some sketchy stuff.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Really, bro? You’re going to sit here and call someone else sketchy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-10"><speaker>MARCUS</speaker><content>Listen to what I’m saying, all right? The guy was talking about shipments from Argentina. Getting past customs. Street values?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Drugs?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah, it seems to fit his travel. In addition to his international trips, he had a lot of flights to Boston, New Orleans, Seattle, Long Beach, Miami.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>All port cities.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Exactly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The international travel to judge dog shows. That’s a perfect cover.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So our dog trainer is a drug courier. No wonder he was so paranoid about being bugged.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Then that warehouse that we saw –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Breeding facility my ass.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The Pilar Retriever?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>PATTERSON</speaker><content>Pretty good story, right? Hey, I had to get you out of there somehow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mr. Patterson, I don’t think you understand how serious this is. We’re in the process of obtaining a warrant. We’re going to search that warehouse from top to bottom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And we’ve got a pretty good idea of what we’re going to find in there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-5"><speaker>PATTERSON</speaker><content>I’ll tell you exactly what you’ll find. Suitcases with false bottoms for smuggling drugs through customs. About two kilos of pure Argentinian heroin. Best drug sniffing dogs we’ve ever had.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-6"><speaker>PATTERSON</speaker><content>My name’s not Jack Patterson. Kenny Wiser, US Customs Agent. You got any coffee?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hum.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="34"><utterance uid="34-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So Francisco was training drug sniffing dogs?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-2"><speaker>WISER</speaker><content>His methods were amazing. Personally handled deployment wherever we thought the shipment was coming in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Which explains all that travel to those port cities. And payments. And secrecy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-4"><speaker>WISER</speaker><content>Yeah, sorry about giving you the runaround at the warehouse, but when you’re dealing with the cartels you can’t be too careful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ah, so that’s why you gave us Kay Cappuccio’s name. ‘Cause you thought she bugged Francisco.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-6"><speaker>WISER</speaker><content>Yeah, we couldn’t really launch an investigation without tipping our hand to the Vasquez operation, so I figured I’d tell you what I know, see where you could get.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Vasquez? That’s out of Argentina, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-8"><speaker>WISER</speaker><content>Mmhmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> It’s a huge heroin smuggling family.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hey, Wiser. What are Francisco’s dogs trained to do when they smell drugs?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-11"><speaker>WISER</speaker><content>They paw at the ground.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-12"><speaker>WISER</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Because that’s what Royal was doing. So I guess that dog therapist was right. He was trying to tell us something. He smelled drugs on our killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-14"><speaker>WISER</speaker><content>Well, that makes sense. The Vasquez cartel had a hell of a lot to gain from Francisco’s death. His program was costing them a fortune in intercepted shipments.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Which is why they wanted eyes and ears on Francisco. They wanted to figure out how the customs operation worked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>But once Francisco realized he was under surveillance they knew he was onto them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-17"><speaker>WISER</speaker><content>So they got someone to finish him off. Probably the same person who wired Kay Cappuccio’s dog collar.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="35"><utterance uid="35-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Whoever wired up that dog collar had to have three things. One, access to the dog. Two, knowledge that Francisco would be training that dog. Three, some connection to the Vasquez cartel. The intersection of these three circles holds the identity of our killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He’s doing that thing again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, but I don’t have any heroin on me, Castle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Why would he react like that? Unless  Beckett, are you wearing perfume? And just for future reference, I’m partial to Fracas.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Listen, don’t flatter yourself, okay?  I just spritzed some of this stuff that Kay sent over in the gift basket.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Why would he react to that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Because the main ingredient is essence of poppy flower.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And heroin is made from morphine, which comes from the opium poppy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Guys, what if at the crime scene he was pawing, not at drugs, but at the scent of that perfume?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, but this perfume hasn’t even come out yet. I mean, who would be wearing it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Only one person.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Not Kay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, she was at the crime scene.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Castle, we’re not talking about paparazzi and celebrities. We’re talking about dealing with a drug cartel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay, let’s remember what we’re looking for. One, access to the dog, check. Two, knowledge that Francisco was training the dog, check. Only thing we’re missing is connection to the cartel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-16"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Ah, guys. I think I might have our link. Kay Cappuccio shot a commercial in Argentina six months ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-17"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So? Argentina is a big country. It doesn’t mean that she’s connected to the Vasquez family.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-18"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>But this does. She stayed at the compound of Junior Vasquez, first lieutenant of the cartel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She’s the one.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="36"><utterance uid="36-1"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>… and I want to remind you all that my new scent hits stores next month. Kay Cappuccio’s Guilty Pleasure. Make sure he’s guilty - of wanting you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Guilty pleasure or just guilty?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-3"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>What does this video have to do with anything?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>This is about 15 minutes before you went backstage to Francisco Pilar’s dressing room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-5"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>So?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So we have reason to suspect that our killer was wearing your perfume.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-7"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>Well that’s impossible. It wasn’t even out yet. I’m the only person that had it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="37"><utterance uid="37-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Does she realize she just incriminated herself?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I said she was nice. Didn’t say anything about smart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-3"><speaker>UNIFORM</speaker><content>Customs Agent Wiser is on the phone for Detective Esposito.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Thanks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>What was that about?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="38"><utterance uid="38-1"><speaker>REGGIE</speaker><content>Hey.  You know when they’re going to be done in there? We’ve got a reporter from Vanity Fair coming by the house later. They’re giving her the cover.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I don’t know, bro. But uh, good luck with that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Esposito.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="39"><utterance uid="39-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What’s your relationship with Junior Vasquez?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-2"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>Junior?  He’s such a sweetheart. Um, they have Keeping Up With Cappuccio in Argentina, so he’s kind of a big fan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you realize that the Vasquez family is the number one heroin exporter in South America?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-4"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>What? Oh my God, you guys. I did not know that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Excuse me.  Give me a minute, Castle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-6"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>This is a nightmare. Heroin, murder … I just wish I never even heard of Francisco.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Kay, how – how did you hear about him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-8"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>Reggie. He read about him in a magazine or something. He said he was the best, so he insisted I use him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So it was Reggie’s idea that Lolita go to Francisco for training.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-10"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-11"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>… Make sure he’s guilty - of wanting you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="40"><utterance uid="40-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Are you sure about this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Positive. Customs connected Kay to the Vasquez family, all right. Through Reggie. Turns out he went to school with one of the Vasquez kids. He’s the connection, not Kay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Get ‘im Royal.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="41"><utterance uid="41-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So he confessed to the whole thing. The Vasquez cartel suspected that Francisco was training dogs for customs. And then when Kay needed Lolita trained, Reggie steered her toward Francisco and then wired the dog collar.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>But then Francisco caught on and Reggie panicked. He felt he had to protect the cartel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, and Reggie wanted to get in good with the cartel. He knew that his days of mooching off of Kay were almost over, in spite of all the reports that the two of them were getting married.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Whoa, whoa. You mean, the tabloids were wrong?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, and um… you know, I was wrong about something, too. Turns out having a mascot in the precinct can be pretty useful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So I was thinking that for tonight maybe you take him home and then I’ll swing by and pick him up maybe 9:30?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ah, I don’t know, Castle. I don’t know if this whole splitting time thing is a good long term solution.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well what, then? Alternating nights? Weekends/weekdays?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I think it’ll just confuse the poor guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>God knows he’s had enough therapy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I think he deserves one home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ah, I see where this is going.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, no. No Rochambeau.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You got a better idea?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I think we should let Royal decide. We go to opposite ends of the room and wherever he goes, that’s home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Let’s do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Sit down. C’mon, sit down. Stay there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>All right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ready?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ready.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>C’mere boy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-22"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Come over here, Royal. Come on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Come over here, boy. C’mon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-24"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s your decision. But I know you’ll make the right one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-25"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>C’mon, Royal. C’mon! My couch is super comfortable, Royal. Come right over here, babe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-26"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No. You know, in your heart. Man’s best friend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-27"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Come over here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-28"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Man’s!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-29"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>Looks like he’s made his choice and it’s me.  Such good taste, Royal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-30"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>Hi, buddy. You have very good taste. Hey, buddy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-31"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Are you sure you want to take him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-32"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, maybe we should do two out of three.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-33"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>Oh, yes. Lolita and I need a big strong man around the house.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-34"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>Especially one as loyal as this, right bud? Royal, you are officially a Cappuccio now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-35"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content> And you have been so sweet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-36"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>If – you know, I know that the paparazzi can be very vicious sometimes, so if you ever need anything, I mean anything at all, you know where to find me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-37"><speaker>KAY</speaker><content>I might just take you up on that one day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-38"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, you know, I mean, I’m sure it’s for the best. He’d of been lonely at my place. There’s nobody to play with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-39"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, mine too.  They do look like they enjoy each other.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-40"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hmm.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="42"><utterance uid="42-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hey, sweetheart. How was your trip?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-2"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>We had fun. Miss me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ah, terribly. But, I did manage to have a good time without you. With my new friend Royal the dog.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-4"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>You got a dog?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No. But I was looking after him for a while. But it made me think. All those times when you were little, how you begged me for a dog and I refused because –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-6"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>You said you’d be the one who’d wind up having to feed it, and it was hard enough remembering to feed me every day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, I –  I don’t remember that last part.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-8"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>It was subtext. Barely.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Anyway … I want to make it up to you. I want to get you a dog. Only question is, what kind of dog do we get? What are we going to name it? Whose room is it going to sleep in?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-10"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Whoa Dad, slow down. I’m leaving for college soon, remember? You can’t have a dog in your dorm room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Right.  I know. I’ll just take care of him here. You can come visit him whenever you can.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-12"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>So, this dog you want to get. You know, for me? This wouldn’t be an enticement to come home from college more often, would it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Don’t pretend like you’re smarter than me. I taught you subtext, young lady.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-14"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Don’t worry. I’ll come back and visit so much you’ll be sick of me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Promise?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-16"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Yeah. Someone has to leave food out for you once in awhile.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Speaking of, I’m kind of hungry right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-18"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Kibbles ‘n’ Bits?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Peanut butter on a spoon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-20"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Chinese.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Turkey sandwich. Welcome home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-22"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>