<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>MARTHA RODGERS</speaker><content>Blow winds and crack your cheeks! Rage! Blow you cataracts and hurricanes. Spout ‘til you have drenched our steeples, drowned our -</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>ALEXIS CASTLE</speaker><content>Dad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>RICHARD CASTLE</speaker><content>I know what you’re asking and the answer is yes. Yes, you can take your grandmother and her entire production of King Lear to college with you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>I’m going crazy!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Earplugs?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Not that. I need something to do. I planned to be at Stanford, but now I’m here … just waiting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What about school?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>I finished all my credits. All I’m taking this semester is theoretical physics.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, maybe this is exactly what you need. A little time off to discover yourself. Travel. Adventure.  Go for a little life experience.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>That’s a great idea. I could get an internship.  Practical experience in the job market. You know, test the waters?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well … that’s not exactly what I was thinking –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Thank you!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>… wind, thunder, fire are my daughters!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Daughters. That’s why King Lear went mad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hello?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Your timing was perfect. My mother was teaching three acting classes today. In my living room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>KATE BECKETT</speaker><content>Wait a minute. What about her studio?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Flooded. They’re doing the storm from King Lear and things got … out of hand.  Remind me to check my insurance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>SIRI</speaker><content>Got you covered.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey Lanie, what do you got?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>LANIE PARISH</speaker><content>This is Laura Cambridge, 28. Traffic found her in the passenger seat of the car.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Cause of death?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>She was strangled between the hours of 8 and 10 last night.  This bruising here indicates a choke hold. He probably grabbed her from behind with enough force to crush her hyoid bone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He? So there was a witness.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>No. But to kill her in one swift move like that the perp had to be taller and heavier than the victim. No signs of sexual assault, though.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Was she strangled in the car?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>CSU didn’t find any signs of any struggle. Looks like her body was dumped here postmortem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Whose car is it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>JAVIER ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Not hers.  She had a non-driver ID card. Ryan’s running the plates to see if we can find the owner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And what about the purse?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>It was tossed in the dumpster. Still has cash in it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Cell phone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Didn’t find one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What girl in her 20s doesn’t have a cell phone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Maybe she’s Amish.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>KEVIN RYAN</speaker><content>Hey. So I … um… ran those plates off the sedan and uh …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-22"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-23"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>It’s from the motor pool at City Hall.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-24"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>City Hall?  Who used it last?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-25"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Mayor Robert Weldon.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>MAYOR ROBERT WELDON</speaker><content>We’re all still a little stunned to hear that one of our cars is mixed up in this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Trust me, we’re going to get this all sorted out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>WELDON</speaker><content>Is that the victim?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yes. Laura Cambridge. Do you recognize her, Your Honor?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>WELDON</speaker><content>Uh, my staff would know better, but I don’t believe she’s connected to this office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Sir, I’m sorry to have to ask you this, but where were you last night between 8 and 10PM?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>WELDON</speaker><content> She's one of New York’s finest, huh, Ricky?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> She’s the best.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>WELDON</speaker><content> So you keep telling me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>WELDON</speaker><content>I was at a small fundraiser last night with about 50 other people. I’ll – I’ll get you their names.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, I appreciate that. And what about the car?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>WELDON</speaker><content>That was one of several used by my office for the event. Uh, apparently one of my staffers reported it stolen later that night.  Off the record? People I was with last night were part of my inner circle. We’re forming an exploratory committee for a possible run at governor. But I’m not anxious to make that public yet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I’ll do my best to keep the nature of your business private.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>WELDON</speaker><content>Thanks.  I’d hoped you be there, Rick.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Fondue night with Alexis. But I did send a check.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>WELDON</speaker><content>Thank you for that.  I know that you have a lot more questions, Detective. My chief of staff, Brian Shay, will answer anything else you want to know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>BRIAN SHAY</speaker><content>Listen, listen – listen to me, Jack. You’re swinging in the wind on this. But you get me three more votes in the council and I’ll send you a helicopter.  You’re the Detective, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>SHAY</speaker><content>Have a seat. Jordan, we don’t need you in on this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-20"><speaker>WELDON</speaker><content>I’ll leave you guys to work through this. Rick, you want to take a look at our new library initiative? It wouldn’t hurt us to have your endorsement on that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>For the New York Public Library? My first love? Anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-22"><speaker>SHAY</speaker><content>I’ve already done your leg work, Detective. The car was checked out by Elizabeth Watson, senior director of communication here at the office. When she left last night’s event around midnight she discovered that it was missing.  Here’s her statement.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>With all due respect, Mr. Shay, police investigations are usually conducted by the police.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-24"><speaker>SHAY</speaker><content>Yeah. Well, unfortunately the 24 hour news cycle moves a hell of a lot faster than you do. And I have to get all my ducks in a row before this thing breaks. It’s my job.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-25"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And my job is to find Laura’s murderer, so if you don’t mind, and even if you do, I’m going to get my own statement from Ms. Watson about that car.  And I’m also going to need statements from all of your staff as to whether they recognize our victim.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-26"><speaker>SHAY</speaker><content>Knock yourself out. But trust me. You’re wasting your time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-27"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>It’s my time to waste. Now, I got a job to do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-28"><speaker>SHAY</speaker><content>So do I. Let me be clear – Mayor Weldon is my priority. And I’m not about to let this thing embolden his opponents and ruin everything that we’ve built.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He’s right, you know. If this thing gets out and they’re not ready with a response? That’s front page material for weeks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>It’s front page news either way. If his staff wants to minimize damage, they’ll step back and let me do my job.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Step back? These are politicians. They can’t order in a restaurant without two compromises and an ultimatum.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>VICTORIA GATES</speaker><content>Beckett? My office?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>What did you find out at City Hall?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The staffer that reported the car stolen is accounted for all last night and no one in the mayor’s office seems to recognize our victim.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>So her ties to that vehicle could be entirely coincidental.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s entirely possible.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Castle and the Mayor are friends, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Sir?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>These investigations are like juggling wet dynamite. One misstep and it’ll all blow up in your face.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I can handle myself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Well, that’s good, Detective. Because I won’t be the only one watching.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What was that about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Politics.  And your connection to the mayor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, what does it matter? We know he’s not involved.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She’s right. You are biased.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’m biased?  Do you know who Gates voted for in the last election? Because I’m betting it wasn’t Weldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Espo, where are we on that motor pool?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Verification. The vehicle was checked out at 5 and reported missing shortly after midnight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So it was stolen off the street.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-19"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Looks like.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Which means any connection to the City Hall is entirely coincidental.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey Ryan. What do our victim’s phone records show? Any phone calls to City Hall?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-22"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>No phone calls at all,  because Laura Cambridge didn’t own a cell phone. Credit cards haven’t been used in six months.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-23"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No cell phone and no credit cards? It’s like she’s from another century.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-24"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Amish theory is looking pretty good, bro.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-25"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>It would be nice if it were that easy, but I think something else was going on with her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-26"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What do you mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-27"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Laura was a Professor of Literature at Hudson University. She was a rising star in her department until six months ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-28"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What happened six months ago?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-29"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>She quit, for no apparent reason. According to her colleagues she also completely cut ties with them. Cancelled her cell phone, cut off her credit cards.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-30"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-31"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>No one knows. It’s like something happened to her. After that all I could find were pay stubs for fast food restaurants, a laundry service, and an office cleaning company.  It’s like she couldn’t keep a job.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-32"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>She went from professor to janitor? That’s … Good Will Hunting but in reverse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-33"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Maybe her family can shed some light.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-34"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, I tracked down her next of kin. She has a sister. She’s on her way in now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-35"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>All right, you guys dig into her life. See if we can find out where she was the night she died. Castle and I will go over to her apartment to find out who she was with.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>HARVEY</speaker><content>Honestly, she pretty much kept to herself. She paid on time. That’s what matters.  Unlike those two chuckleheads. Uh, excuse me please, Officer. And uh … gentleman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>HARVEY</speaker><content> Pipe down, for crying out loud!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>An officer and a gentleman? That could be the name of our crime blog.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Crime blog? The way you help me write police reports? I got a feeling I’ll be writing that one on my own.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Doesn’t really seem to be any signs of struggle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, no sign of a TV or a computer either. That’s weird, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>HARVEY</speaker><content>A bunch of deadbeat tenants in here. You ever get bored, I’m sure I could fill up a bunch of holding cells for ya.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mr. Harvey, when was the last time you saw Laura? Did you see her yesterday?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>HARVEY</speaker><content>During the day. She worked nights. I saw her head to work around … 5.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you know where she worked?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>HARVEY</speaker><content>Some place that paid, that’s all I know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Did you ever see Laura with any friends? Boyfriends?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>HARVEY</speaker><content>No. No. Uh, but I did see a guy leaving here last night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>When was that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>HARVEY</speaker><content>Around 9 … 30.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well that’s inside our 8 to 10 murder window.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you remember what he looked like?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-18"><speaker>HARVEY</speaker><content>Uh … six feet tall. Caucasian. Dark hair.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>ROBERTA CAMBRIDGE</speaker><content>She never mentioned anyone like that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>ROBERTA</speaker><content>She wasn’t dating anyone.  Thank you. I tried to set her up with a few guys, but she wasn’t interested.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Did your sister have any connection to City Hall, or local politics?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>ROBERTA</speaker><content>No, I don’t think so.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Were you and your sister close?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>ROBERTA</speaker><content>We used to be. She used to tell me everything, and then … six months ago she stopped calling. She just … dropped out of her life. She gave up her teaching position, she moved out of her apartment on the Upper West Side into that flophouse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Do you have any idea why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>When was the last time you spoke to her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>ROBERTA</speaker><content>Three days ago. She called for my birthday.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>From where? She didn’t have a phone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>ROBERTA</speaker><content>I don’t know. But she was upset. She said she was in trouble because of something that happened at work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Did she tell you what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>ROBERTA</speaker><content>No. She said it was too dangerous for me to know.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So Laura Cambridge left a tenure track position at a respected university for some flophouse and a mysterious night job that got her into so much trouble she ended up murdered? What the hell was she mixed up in?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The man that left her apartment? If he’s our killer he was looking for her. He probably went to her work to find her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Which means wherever that is it was probably the last place she was seen alive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I got it.  I found out where she works. Her bank statement says she was receiving recent direct deposits from a DAG Corp. Now, I had to dig deep within the city’s business registries, but I found one listing for a DAG Corp between 2nd and 3rd in the Bowery.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Let’s go.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>There it is. Suite 250.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What kind of business do you think this is? Shadowy import export? Money laundering? Sweat shop?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Shh … shh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you hear that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>NYPD, don’t -!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>It’s just an office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Where only women work?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What is this place?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’d say it’s about $4.99 a minute. It’s not a sweat shop.  It’s a sex shop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>ELDERLY WOMAN</speaker><content>Oh Murry. Yeah, yeah, yeah.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>MARILYN KANE</speaker><content>Laura was one of my favorites. Just a sweet, intelligent, funny girl. She had only been here a few months and already she was one of our most popular goddesses. I can’t believe that she’s dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Was she taking calls last night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>MARILYN</speaker><content>No. No, she took last night off. Said she had something to take care of.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Laura told her sister that she was in trouble at work. That something happened.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>MARILYN</speaker><content>Nothing happened that I know of. I mean, she did seem distracted the past few days, but that’s about all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, being the Chief …  Sexecutive Officer, did you notice any conflicts with her and her colleagues?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>MARILYN</speaker><content>Uh, she kept to herself, but she got along well with the other girls. There were no complaints about Laura.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Did she ever tell you why she was working here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>MARILYN</speaker><content>What do you mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I – I just find it odd. She’s a professor with a promising career ahead of her and then all of a sudden she decides to become a phone sex operator.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>MARILYN</speaker><content>Maybe she liked it. We get all types here, Detective. Students, actresses, moms.  I knew an accountant who did it because she liked the challenge. And it turned her on. It’s a powerful thing to make a client lust for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Any chance that one of her clients became obsessed with her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>MARILYN</speaker><content>Oh honey, obsession pays our bills.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Could they have found out her real identity and maybe contacted her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>MARILYN</speaker><content>Absolutely not. No, we keep all of our girls anonymous. Clients can’t be contacted directly. They call one central line and all our calls are routed to each girl by our dispatcher.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>SARAH MARX</speaker><content>Uh yeah, it’s my job to take the client’s name and credit card information and then route the calls to the girls.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s three o’clock in the afternoon. Is it always this busy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>SARAH</speaker><content>Sure. Some guys need a morning jolt, some guys need an afternoon pick-me-up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Someone should have told them coffee’s cheaper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>SARAH</speaker><content>It’s not just about the sex. That’s the part of this business most people don’t understand. Guys call, girls call … they’re looking for release. Sometimes that release is sexual, but sometimes –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s therapy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Or … so I’ve been told.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>SARAH</speaker><content>It’s true. Laura was a successful goddess, not just because of her sexy talk, but because she was a really good listener.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, that might have gotten her killed. Sarah, were there any clients that she asked to have blocked?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>SARAH</speaker><content> No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What about problems here at work? Was there anything that she couldn’t tell her boss about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>SARAH</speaker><content>No. She … um…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She what?  Sarah?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>SARAH</speaker><content>I’m sorry. Oh God, I’m so sorry. It’s my fault she’s dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>How?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Did a client find out who she was?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-17"><speaker>SARAH</speaker><content>No. It was the other way around. Laura came to me about a week ago. She um… she wanted a client’s contact information. I told her it was completely against policy, but she was desperate. She said it was a matter of life or death.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Okay, we’re going to need that client’s name.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Edgar Navarro?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>EDGAR</speaker><content>I didn’t do nothing. You had no right to drag me out in front of my moms.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No? Where were you last night between 8 and 10?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>EDGAR</speaker><content>What’s this about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you recognize this woman?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>EDGAR</speaker><content>Yeah, look, I don’t know what she told you, but all we did was talk. I didn’t do nothing illegal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Then how come she’s dead?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>EDGAR</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We know that she called you, Edgar, and that the two of you met up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>EDGAR</speaker><content>It’s not what you think. She just needed my help.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What kind of help could you have given her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>EDGAR</speaker><content>I learned how to fix computers in prison. And that’s why Laura called me. She needed me to copy some digital recordings for her, from their hard drive. But she didn’t know how to rip them. I told her I needed the file extensions. She said she’d get them and call me from her cell to walk her through it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Only she didn’t even own a cell, Edgar.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>EDGAR</speaker><content>Yes she did.  That’s her number right there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Did she tell you why she needed those files copied?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-16"><speaker>EDGAR</speaker><content>She said she’d heard something on a call. Something she wasn’t supposed to hear. Something bad. She said she needed a copy of it for evidence.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So Laura never mentioned a call that upset or concerned her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>MARILYN</speaker><content>She never said a word.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And she never asked for copies of recordings?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>MARILYN</speaker><content>No, and I’m the one to ask. This computer room is locked up tight and I’m the only one with a key.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>MARILYN</speaker><content>The lock’s broken.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>‘Kay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>MARILYN</speaker><content>The hard drive’s gone. All of our calls for the last two months were on that drive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>When was the last time you were in here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>MARILYN</speaker><content>This morning. Everything was fine. This must have just happened.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Has anyone visited the office today?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>MARILYN</speaker><content>Yeah, a …  a man from the gas company. He said there was a leak in the building because of the construction.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Can you describe him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-13"><speaker>MARILYN</speaker><content>Uh … about six feet tall, white, dark hair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Same guy that was at Laura’s apartment the night she died?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What the hell was on that recording?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Whatever it is, it’s worth killing for.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>So how’s the case of the phone sex gal who knew too much going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s more of a conspiracy thriller. Like The Conversation or uh … Blow Out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Ah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Everyone wants this recording and the secrets on it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Very mysterious.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, and that’s not the only mystery. Why would a woman, like Laura Cambridge, a highly educated professor, suddenly quit everything and drop out of her life for a series of menial jobs culminating in the wonderful world of phone sex?  None of the pieces fit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Huh. Who called her? I mean, you must be able to trace the call, even though you don’t have the recording, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Well, we have subpoenaed a list of all the incoming lists on Laura’s shifts, but that’s going to be like looking for a needle in a needle stack.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hello?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>MYSTERIOUS MAN</speaker><content>Mr. Castle. Do you remember me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-11"><speaker>MYSTERIOUS MAN</speaker><content>I called you before. About Detective Beckett’s safety.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I remember.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-13"><speaker>MYSTERIOUS MAN</speaker><content>Once again, Mr. Castle, it seems like we need to talk.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Are you sure it’s the same man who called you about Beckett?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s definitely him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Then the death of this young woman is somehow connected to Beckett’s mother?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It has to be. Otherwise why would he call?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>What did he say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He said there were greater forces at play. That more was at stake than we realized. Clearly this is not just about phone sex. Whatever Laura Cambridge overheard that night, it got someone’s attention. Someone big.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>What I don’t get is, what are you supposed to do about it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I don’t know. He gave me a number to contact him, if I needed help. He said I would know when it was time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Mmhmm. You plan to tell Beckett?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Tell her what? ‘Hey Kate, I’ve been taking calls from a shadowy figure who wants to keep you off your mother’s murder case, so they don’t kill you, too'?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Okay. … hold on, wait. What did you say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> No, I’m not eating. Okay, thanks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey. You’re just in time. Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What’s wrong?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So, what do we got?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Lanie just called. She said that she found fibers in Laura’s mouth and esophagus. Lab ID’d it as light brown cashmere, which was most likely from our killer’s coat sleeve.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Brown cashmere? So we can narrow our suspects down to rich men with impeccable taste.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Are you saying you’re a suspect?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Alexis is my alibi.  What about our gas company worker?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, surprise. He doesn’t work for the gas company. And uniforms said that there was no forensic evidence at the Dial-A-Goddess office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>But what we did get from Dial-A-Goddess was their copious call logs – about 200 pages worth. These ladies are busy. I’ve been going through them all morning trying to sort Laura’s calls from the other girls' lines.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Are there any calls in there from the Mayor’s office?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Thought you said you’re confident that he wasn’t involved.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’m just trying to be thorough.  And impartial.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-16"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Not yet. But the private sector is well represented. I’ve got calls from the Met, banks, several high profile brokerage houses – no wonder the economy collapsed, huh?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-17"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yo Beckett.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Excuse me. What do you got?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hey. If anything shows up in here as tied to Beckett’s shooting or Johanna Beckett’s murder, would you tell me right away?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-20"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Wait … you guys think this is connected –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No. Not you guys. Beckett doesn’t know and I don’t want her to know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-22"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Why do you think it’s connected?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-23"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I just – I just want to cover all my bases, okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-24"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-25"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Thanks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-26"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey guys? So uniforms canvassing around Laura’s apartment found a cab that recognized her pic. He said that he dropped her off at the Gotham 11 TV station downtown.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-27"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>A television station.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-28"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Why would she go to a television station?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-29"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Why would she go into the phone sex business? Why would she do any of these things that she did?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-30"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, hopefully I’ll get some answers. But first, I ran down that cell number we got from Edgar Navarro. It’s a pay as you go phone. Laura just activated it 6 days ago. She’s hardly used it. She made one call to Edgar and another on the day she died to an agent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-31"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>A federal agent?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-32"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No, a book agent. Trevor Hanes.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>TREVOR HANES</speaker><content>It’s just absurdly tragic. Laura was an incredibly talented writer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You were her agent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>HANES</speaker><content>Yeah, we signed her as a client about 6 months ago on the back of an astonishing book proposal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What’s the book about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>HANES</speaker><content>It’s a scathing indictment of societal inequity as seen through the lens of the working poor. A sort of contemporary take on how the other half lives. A privileged young woman gives up every comfort to experience life below the poverty line.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s why she took all those jobs. First hand research.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>HANES</speaker><content>Thing pitches itself, really.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So we’ll need to see a copy of that manuscript. Her investigations might have led to her death.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-9"><speaker>HANES</speaker><content>Well, there isn’t one. At least, not that I’ve seen anyway. Besides, I don’t think she was killed because of her anti-capitalist polemic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What do you mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-11"><speaker>HANES</speaker><content>Well, earlier this week she called my office. Said she stumbled across a much more explosive story. A scandal involving a very prominent, very powerful New Yorker. She said it would rock the city to its very foundations.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What – what prominent New Yorker?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-13"><speaker>HANES</speaker><content>She wouldn’t say. I just assumed that it was a pitch for her next book. We were going to discuss it this week.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Sorry. Excuse me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey Espo. What’s up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-16"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I’m at the Gotham 11 office. There’s something you need to see.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>This is Pat McConnell, Laura’s college buddy.  Tell them what you told me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>PAT</speaker><content>I – hadn’t seen Laura in years. Just a few days ago she calls me out of the blue. Says she needs to see some raw footages we shot for this research project she’s working on. So I set her up with this edit bay. She was here for over 8 hours. I mean, at one point she even fell asleep. I came by to check on her and she had her eyes closed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Raw footage of what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>It’s all B roll. Of Mayor Weldon.  City council meetings, playground openings, backstage at a press conference.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>A scandal about a prominent, powerful New Yorker.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Now check out this last tape she was watching.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s the Reading Train Foundation. I went to their gala last year.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Now look at the girl on the side of the screen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s Laura.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s impossible. He said he didn’t know her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, look what the Mayor’s wearing. It’s a light brown coat, and it looks like cashmere. That’s just the coat that our killer was wearing.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Beckett, I know this man. I’ve known him 12 years. He’s not a killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You don’t know that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yes, I do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, he lied about knowing our victim.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He was standing next to her. That doesn’t mean he knew her. Do you know how many people he meets in a day? Expecting him to remember them all, that’s like expecting me to remember everyone that comes to my book signings.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You’re biased.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You’re damn right I’m biased. Robert Weldon is a good man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Even good men make mistakes. He had access to that car. His aide said that he left the event at 9PM. That’s right inside our kill zone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Fine. What’s his motive?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I don’t know. At least not yet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Then give him a chance. Because the minute you move on him, his career is over.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-12"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>So … what’s the latest?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We’ve got a couple of promising leads. I’m hoping to find something concrete soon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-14"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Well, anything more on the victim? Anything connecting her back to City Hall?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, not yet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-16"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>All right, Detective. Anything pops, you let me know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Great. Now I’m a liar.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You know what I think? I think she’s hoping it’s him. Because if he’s gone, I’m gone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, you can’t make this one about you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Where are you going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You’re right. We have to figure out Weldon’s motive. There’s no way Gates is going to let me subpoena that coat without it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Really? That’s your takeaway?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What do you want me to do, Castle? I know that he’s your friend, but I’m sorry. If he killed that girl –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-24"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He didn’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-25"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Then let me prove it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-26"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ryan?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-27"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>All right, thanks for your help. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-28"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Anything else on that video?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-29"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Actually, yeah. When we first saw Laura, she was wearing a volunteer badge for the Reading Train Foundation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-30"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>She was on staff at the Mayor’s charity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-31"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That doesn’t mean he knew her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-32"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ryan? You’re with me. Castle, I’m sorry, but you can’t be objective on this one, so I’m going to have to pursue it on my own.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>CONNIE PARK</speaker><content>No, I don’t know if Mayor Weldon and Laura Cambridge were acquainted. I don’t know much about her at all. She wasn’t here very long.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What do you mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>CONNIE</speaker><content>Well, we hired Laura as a volunteer, about a week ago. A few days later, we had to fire her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>CONNIE</speaker><content>She was caught copying confidential files.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>What kind of files?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>CONNIE</speaker><content>Accounting files.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Any idea why she would be interested in those files?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ms. Park.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>CONNIE</speaker><content>It’s sensitive. I’m not supposed to talk about it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ms. Park, a woman was murdered and we are trying to figure out why. You can talk to us here or we can go downtown.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-12"><speaker>CONNIE</speaker><content>We recently discovered some discrepancies in our accounts. We found there was some money missing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-13"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>How much money?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-14"><speaker>CONNIE</speaker><content>$2.3 million dollars.  There’s an internal investigation going on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>This investigation. Does it have anything to do with Mayor Weldon?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Thank you.  Attorney General’s office confirms that Mayor Weldon is the subject of the investigation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You were looking for motive and here it is. $2.3 million dollars worth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Weldon embezzled from his own charity. Someone must have told Laura about it during one of her sessions and she decided to investigate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Once she found enough evidence to expose the Mayor, he killed her to shut her up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You going to tell her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> I have to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>This will destroy Weldon, you know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, I know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And when he’s gone the first thing she’ll do is get rid of Castle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> I know.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Are you sure about this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yes, sir. But the moment I file a warrant request for that coat it becomes public record.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>So?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So then everyone will know that Mayor Weldon is a person of interest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Isn’t he?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yes, but …  What if I’m wrong? It could ruin his career.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>We are tasked by the city of New York to protect its people. Sometimes that task comes with a cost. I know what they call me, Detective. ‘Iron Gates.’ I hear the whispers. ‘She’s from IA, she must hate cops.’ Well, the truth is, I love cops. My daddy was a cop. My uncles were cops. But the sergeant who assaulted my patrol partner under the cover of authority? Who holds him accountable? We do.  Go to the Mayor. Get him to voluntarily surrender his coat for fiber testing without a warrant. Tell him it’s the only way to keep it out of the media. But if he refuses – you get that warrant and you do your job. Whatever the cost.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You going to see Weldon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’d like to come with you. I think I can help.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I don’t think you can.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I heard what you said. I did. And I think I can be a valuable asset.  I play poker with the guy. I can tell when he’s bluffing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And what about if I have to force his hand? Can you be an asset then?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Look, I don’t think he did it. But if he did, I want to know. That makes me objective.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>BRIAN SHAY</speaker><content>Sir, you don’t have to talk to them. It’s my job!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>WELDON</speaker><content>It’s okay. I don’t need you to protect me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>SHAY</speaker><content>Sir.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>WELDON</speaker><content>I haven’t done anything wrong.  Please. Thank you. Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Your Honor, I appreciate you speaking with us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>WELDON</speaker><content>Well it sounded like I didn’t have a choice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The last time we spoke, you said you didn’t know Laura Cambridge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>WELDON</speaker><content>That’s right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And yet, here you are standing next to Laura, a volunteer, at Reading Train.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-10"><speaker>WELDON</speaker><content>I – I didn’t recognize her, but in context I remember her. This event was a few nights ago. She was trying to talk to me, but –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Did she? Talk to you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-12"><speaker>WELDON</speaker><content>No, I got pulled away. I had donors I had to speak with. I remember her saying that she wanted to talk to me, but circumstances prevented it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So you and Laura never actually spoke.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-14"><speaker>WELDON</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Not even on the phone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-16"><speaker>WELDON</speaker><content>No. Honestly, after that night I never gave her a second thought.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know, in this photo you’re wearing a light brown cashmere coat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We’d like you to turn it over to CSU for testing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-19"><speaker>WELDON</speaker><content>Respectfully, I’m going to have to decline.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Robert, give her the coat. It can only be good for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-22"><speaker>WELDON</speaker><content>I’m afraid I can’t do that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-24"><speaker>WELDON</speaker><content>I had nothing to do with Laura Cambridge’s murder. Or the theft of money from my charity or anything else I’ve been accused of in the last 48 hours. Do you think that any of this is a coincidence?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-25"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Robert –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-26"><speaker>WELDON</speaker><content>No, me here, talking to you? This is exactly what they wanted to have happen. So no, I will not give you my coat. Look, there is a conspiracy against me and I will not voluntarily feed it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-27"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What conspiracy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-28"><speaker>WELDON</speaker><content>Don’t you think it’s funny that all this is happening the moment I consider running for governor? Rick, I’m used to having enemies but this is an organized effort to destroy me. So right now, I don’t trust anyone.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, he has good reason to not turn over his coat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yes, guilt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The conspiracy. Is it so far-fetched? Maybe Laura found out about it and tried to warn him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Or maybe she and Weldon did talk. She confronted him with what she knew and he killed her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hmm. I believe the conspiracy. I mean, I know Weldon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And Weldon knows you. Conspiracies, intrigue – that’s your bread and butter. That’s exactly the kind of story that you would respond to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’m sorry, are you suggesting he’s playing me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I’m suggesting that you consider the possibility.  I have a procedure to follow. He didn’t submit his coat willingly, so I’m going to have to get a court order.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Whoa. Look, once word gets out that the NYPD subpoenaed his clothing in connection with embezzlement and murder? That man’s career will be over.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Not if he’s innocent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Are you kidding me? Kate, this is politics. Perception is reality. The truth won’t matter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What am I supposed to do, Rick? I can’t just stop being a cop because it’s inconvenient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No, no, no, just – you can wait. Right? For something else. For another lead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>For the coat to disappear? You think I don’t know what’s at stake here? Do you think I actually want to do this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Then don’t do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I don’t have a choice.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>WELDON</speaker><content> My office is cooperating fully with both investigations and I stand here with 100% confidence that a thorough and full investigation will reveal that I am completely innocent of any wrongdoing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>You still believe him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>You’ve been down this road before, with a friend. You believed Damian Westlake. He’s rotting in prison for murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Damian and I were kids together. Believing in him was sentiment. My experience tells me Weldon is innocent. My experience tells me there’s something very wrong with this whole situation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>In that case, maybe it’s time to phone a friend.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>MYSTERIOUS MAN</speaker><content>Right there, Mr. Castle.  That’ll be fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You know Weldon’s not behind this. That’s why you offered your help. He’s right about the conspiracy, isn’t he?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>MYSTERIOUS MAN</speaker><content>He isn’t wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So what do I do? How do I help him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>MYSTERIOUS MAN</speaker><content>Listen to the evidence. That’s what Laura did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No, I watched the video of Laura and the Mayor a hundred times. There’s nothing there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>MYSTERIOUS MAN</speaker><content>That’s not what I said, Mr. Castle.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I met Weldon a few times before this. I liked him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>You didn’t set his house on fire.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No. I just threw gasoline on it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Beckett.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Thanks for coming. I wasn’t sure that you would, given the way that we left things.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I can’t apologize for doing my job, Castle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And I would never ask you to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So. Why’d you call me here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Because I had an epiphany.  All this time we’ve been looking for evidence when we should have been listening instead. This all started when Laura told Edgar Navarro she heard something on a call, something she wasn’t supposed to hear. We writers call this the inciting incident. Whomever she spoke to, whatever she heard, is what lead to her murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well what does it matter? I mean, the hard drive is stolen, the recording is gone. We’ll never know what she head on that call.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No. But we might know who she heard it from. You remember how Laura fell asleep watching those B roll tapes at Gotham 11?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mmhmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>She was closing her eyes. She wasn’t watching the tapes. She was listening to them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So you’re saying she was trying to ID our caller’s voce?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I had Sarah, our goddess dispatcher, listen to those B roll tapes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-12"><speaker>SARAH</speaker><content>It’s him, I’m sure of it. He was one of Laura’s regulars.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Show her who.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The Mayor?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-15"><speaker>SARAH</speaker><content>That guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Jordan Norris. Deputy assistant to the Mayor’s chief of staff.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mr. Norris, you told us that you didn’t know Laura Cambridge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>NORRIS</speaker><content>That’s right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And yet your 80 year old grandmother Greta Markenson did.  According to the phone sex records, Laura received numerous phone calls from her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Which made Greta look pretty frisky, until we realized that you’d been housesitting at her apartment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>NORRIS</speaker><content>I – I may have called that service from time to time, but I – I never knew who I was talking to. I mean, how would I?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We’ll get to that in a minute. In the meantime, we checked your phone records and you sent this text to a burner cell about a month ago.  Now, to most people that would look like a random set of numbers, so we looked into it. Those are actually numbers to a bank account for Mayor Weldon and his charity. Numbers that someone could have used to make it look like the Mayor was embezzling money.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The man trusted you and you sold him out. So what’d they give you, Jordan? What’d they promise you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-8"><speaker>NORRIS</speaker><content>I – I thought this was just about the money. I - I didn’t know. I didn’t know they’d try to destroy him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And when you found out you betrayed the man you worked for, it ate you up. Didn’t it? So much so that one night, after too many shots of tequila, you called Laura and you let it all spill out. Oh, you didn’t mean to. But she was such a good listener.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-10"><speaker>NORRIS</speaker><content>It was anonymous. I was supposed to be safe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>But you weren’t. Because she was a writer and you gave her the story of her life. So she tracked you down. She confronted you. She was going to blow the whistle on you, on your friends. She had to be stopped.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We talked to your doorman, Jordan. We know that she visited you that night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-13"><speaker>NORRIS</speaker><content> Okay. She was there. She left after 20 minutes. I – I didn’t kill her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You didn’t have to. All you had to do was call that same burner phone and whoever answered sent a man. A man without a face who choked the life out of Laura Cambridge. And then he broke into her home and her work and he destroyed all of the evidence of everything she knew.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Whose phone was it, Jordan?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-16"><speaker>NORRIS</speaker><content>You don’t understand. These people, they’re more dangerous than you know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You are looking at 20 years in prison. I am offering you a way out. Now, who did you call?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I want a name. Who did you call?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-19"><speaker>NORRIS</speaker><content>Uh … I –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>A name, Jordan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Say it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-22"><speaker>NORRIS</speaker><content>Okay. … The person that I called was –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-23"><speaker>BILL MOSS</speaker><content>If it’s all the same to you, I’d prefer my client not be asked any more questions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-24"><speaker>NORRIS</speaker><content>Your client?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-25"><speaker>MOSS</speaker><content>Mr. Norris, I’m Bill Moss. From now on, please don’t speak to anybody outside my presence. I’ve been retained to represent you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-26"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>By whom?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-27"><speaker>MOSS</speaker><content>We’re done here.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>It seems our Mayor will live to fight another day. It seems justice has prevailed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Not for Laura Cambridge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>We charged Mr. Norris with criminal facilitation. That’s something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Jordan Norris is a pawn. I want the people controlling him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Oh, it’s a long game, Kate. Play it piece by piece.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>But why would you abandon all your plans? You’ve been cleared of all charges?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>WELDON</speaker><content>You know, for someone who kills off all his characters you have a strange, stubborn streak of optimism in you. But no. I can’t run for governor in 2 years and I can’t run for president in 6. That dream is done.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>There’s gotta be something we can do. You’re innocent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-4"><speaker>WELDON</speaker><content>A little too innocent. There are people out there - I realize it now – people that control what goes on in the city and beyond. I wouldn’t play ball so they took me out of the game. It’s been decided. This is as far as I get.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So what are you going to do now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-6"><speaker>WELDON</speaker><content>I am going to continue to be an outstanding mayor for the greatest city on Earth.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>MYSTERIOUS MAN</speaker><content>Why did you contact me, Mr. Castle? The case is resolved.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Resolved? How is it resolved? Someone tried to destroy this city’s mayor and I want to know who.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>MYSTERIOUS MAN</speaker><content>Trust me when I say it’s not your concern.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It is if it involves Beckett or her mother’s murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-5"><speaker>MYSTERIOUS MAN</speaker><content>You’re a writer. Finish this sentence. ‘If Weldon had been run out of office –‘</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’d be gone from the 12th Precinct.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-7"><speaker>MYSTERIOUS MAN</speaker><content>And then who’d keep Beckett from looking into things she shouldn’t? Who’d keep her out of harm’s way?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So you did this to protect her? Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-9"><speaker>MYSTERIOUS MAN</speaker><content>You play chess, Mr. Castle? There are times when a well-placed pawn is more powerful than a king.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I have your number if I have to reach you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-11"><speaker>MYSTERIOUS MAN</speaker><content>You don’t reach me, Mr. Castle. I reach you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>