<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>





<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>KATE BECKETT</speaker><content>I’m telling you. Something happened. Something changed. It’s been weird between us lately.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>LANIE PARISH</speaker><content>Lately?  Kate, it’s been weird for 4 years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, this is different. He’s different. It’s like he’s pulling away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Well, can you blame him? He’s probably tired of waiting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Waiting? Waiting for what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>What do you think? The guy is crazy about you. And despite your little act, you’re crazy about him.  Oh, what? Was that supposed to be some big secret?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Yes.  No.  Do you think he knows?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Do you remember how he used to be? Girl on either arm? You really don’t see that guy too much anymore. Why do you think that is?  He’s waiting for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, but Lanie –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>I know. You’re dealing with stuff. But you cannot ask him to wait forever.  Unless, of course, you’re okay with him pulling away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What if it doesn’t work? What if it ends up like you and Javi?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Well at least we gave it a shot. And so it didn’t work out. So what? Now we can move on, give or take the occasional booty call.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I just – I don’t want to lose what we have, you know?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Girl, please. What exactly do you have, really?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>A friendship.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>No. What you and I have is a friendship. What you and Castle have is a holding pattern. How long can you circle before the fuel runs out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Beckett.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Don’t think you were saved by the bell, Kate Beckett. As your friend, I’m not going to let drop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So, what? You think I should tell him how I feel?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Yes! You hunt murderers for a living. You can do this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay. Okay. I just, I – I have to find the right time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>No time like the present.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>What the… ?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>On second thought, maybe you should wait a bit.  What’s that? Ryan’s calling? I – gotta go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’ll call you in about an hour.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hey there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I feel like I just walked into a bad episode of Miami Vice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay, first, there are no bad episodes of Miami Vice. Second, who died?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You, from the looks of it. You look like you just got run over by a truck.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, a truck delivering a shipment of awesome. Nah, I just uh, flew into Vegas for the weekend. Just needed a little change of scenery.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And you won the blonde in a high stakes poker match?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No, I met her on the flight back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And you just gave her your car?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Jacinda happens to be a very trustworthy person. She’s a first class flight attendant. It’s not like I gave her my social security number.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle –  is everything okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Never better.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>JAVIER ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Our victim’s Naomi Allen, age 25. Her green card indicates she’s a British national. Ryan’s notifying the consulate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Her address is in SoHo. What was she doing all the way down here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Don’t know, but she checked in 2 hours before she was killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hope they prorated the room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Good news is we have a witness. The maid who discovered the body saw a guy run out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Did the maid get a good look?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>She’s with the sketch artist now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well then whoever he is he was looking for something.  This place has been searched.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>One thing we do know is that she was not robbed. Her wallet, watch, and cash were untouched.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey Lanie, how does it look?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Like you waited too long.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The vic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>She was strangled, but she went down with a fight. Prelim suggests signs of a struggle.  She took one to the face.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>A well dressed, attractive woman in a seedy motel and a guy who flees the crime scene. This might have been a one night stand gone wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Are we talking about the victim or Castle?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey Espo? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Can you contact the next of kin and canvass the area once the sketch is done?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, no problem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-20"><speaker>KEVIN RYAN</speaker><content>Hey Beckett.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-21"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Found the vic’s business card in the side pocket of her purse.  Looks like she works in Manhattan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Naomi Allen, Kittman Group.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>CLAIRE PANCHARD</speaker><content>Yes, I was her US booking agent. Naomi was one of our top models.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So she was in the city for work?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>CLAIRE</speaker><content>She split her time between here and London. The good ones usually end up spending half the year in New York.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Now do you have any idea why she was at the Alexandria Motel last night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>CLAIRE</speaker><content>Uh, no. I’ve never even heard of it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s one of those … um… pay by the hour places.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you recognize this man?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>CLAIRE</speaker><content>No. No I don’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>But you do have an idea of who he might be.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>CLAIRE</speaker><content>It’s just …  lately Naomi was making some choices.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What kind of choices?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>CLAIRE</speaker><content>Well, she seemed to have lost interest in standard modeling jobs. Recently she had been booking more uh … unconventional gigs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Like what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>CLAIRE</speaker><content>Well I heard the London office booked her to attend the birthday party of some foreign dignitary a few months ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She was hired to go to a party?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>CLAIRE</speaker><content>It’s common for models to get hired to pretty up an event. Some girls do it to pick up extra cash and other girls do it as a way of connecting with wealthy men.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Wait, are you saying Naomi was hiring herself out as an escort?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>CLAIRE</speaker><content>You just don’t see girls good as Naomi taking these party jobs. Not unless there’s a bigger payout involved somewhere.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you know if she took on any of these kinds of gigs recently?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-20"><speaker>CLAIRE</speaker><content>It’s not really what we do.  She did want me to try to get her into an event last night, though. An album launch party in Midtown. But I didn’t have any connections to it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Last night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-22"><speaker>CLAIRE</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Are you thinking what I’m thinking?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, that we should throw a party and hire a bunch of models.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No. That maybe Naomi somehow got into that party last night and that that’s where she met her killer.  That’s what I was thinking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Weird. We’re usually more in sync than that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey Ryan, did you find anything at Naomi’s apartment?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>No, but someone else might have. It’s been tossed. Not only that, but the neighbor said they saw a man leaving the apartment late last night. The neighbor ID’d him off the sketch. It’s the same guy who fled the murder scene.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He couldn’t find what he was looking for in the motel so he searched her place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah, but this time he left a footprint.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Meaning?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, unis canvassed around the apartment with the sketch. He bought a bottle of single malt with a credit card a couple of blocks away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Colin Hunt. What do we have on him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Nothing in the system but I ran a trace on the credit card. He checked in to the Mondaray in SoHo this morning.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>NYPD! Show me your hands.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>COLIN HUNT</speaker><content>You’re making a mistake.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, like I haven’t heard that before. Hands in the air, now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content> If you insist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Whoa!  Dude.  Whoa. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Allow me to introduce myself. Detective Inspector Colin Hunt, Scotland Yard.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You’re a long way from home, Detective Inspector Hunt. How did you end up in that dead girl’s hotel room?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>I was at a seminar last night in DC when Naomi called me, panicked. She said she was in trouble and needed my help.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So you knew her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Naomi was like a sister to me. Her dad, Terrence, was my first partner on the job. When he passed away I promised her family I’d look after her. After she called me I grabbed the next flight but by the time I arrived it was too late.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And your first instinct was to flee the crime scene?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>I didn’t flee. I left. She was dead. There was nothing else to do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah. Except to maybe hang around and give the police a statement.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>You and I both know that if I had stuck around it would be hours of questioning and then you’d send me off with a “cheers, we’ll keep you posted”.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>But I suppose you had something more important to do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>The room had been searched. And whoever killed her was looking for something. I thought they might try her apartment next. By the time I got there it had already been tossed. Look, I know I shouldn’t have been investigating. But if you were in a foreign country and someone you loved was killed what would you do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What were they looking for?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>When he was on the job, Naomi’s dad used to stash a gun in the lining of his Kevlar. When Naomi started modeling as a teenager he didn’t want her on the underground without any protection so he taught her to cut a tiny piece of lining in her jacket to stash pepper spray. That’s where I found it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You found what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>A message to me. About her killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What kind of message?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Not until I’m on the case.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Excuse me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Detective, please. I owe this to Naomi. I owe it to her family.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> You do realize that I could arrest you for withholding evidence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-20"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>And since you don’t know what that evidence is, I could deny it. And none of that will get us any closer to catching her killer.  Let me work this care with you. Because if you don’t I swear, I’ll go out there and catch the bastard on my own.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay. But I have to check in with my Captain first.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>What’s she like, your Captain?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You ever see that YouTube video of the grizzly bear that decapitates a moose with one swipe of its paw?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content> Comforting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s nothing personal. She just doesn’t like outsiders in her precinct.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>I don’t need her to like it. I just need her to allow it. This whole thing with Naomi doesn’t add up. Turning down conventional modeling jobs, booking sleazy jobs at private parties, that just doesn’t sound like the Naomi I know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Yeah well, sometimes it’s the people we think we know best that we really don’t know at all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well… you’re in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content> Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What?  Seriously?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, your supervisor at Scotland Yard said you’re one of the best. Even Captain Gates was impressed with your record.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well I guess it’s not outsiders she doesn’t like.  It’s just me. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Look, we had a deal. What did Naomi give you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>This.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>A key? You said she left a message.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>This is the message. She put it there for me to find. I guarantee it has something to do with her death.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>This looks commercial.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>It’s an Arco-Rifkin 1130R. Mostly used for lockers found at train stations or health clubs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>All right. Well, I’ll have Ryan canvass the area around her apartment and the hotel. We’ll see if any of the businesses have lockers that use this kind of key.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yo Beckett, I got something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey uh, Detective Esposito, this is Detective Inspector Colin Hunt. He’s from Scotland Yard. He’s going to be consulting on this case. He knows our victim.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-21"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hey, how’s it going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-22"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Pleasure, mate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So, what do you got?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-24"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, Naomi did make it to that album release party last night at a club in Midtown. But she was kicked out by security around 10 o’clock.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-25"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-26"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>She had an altercation with the host.  Female rapper and ex-felon Nicki J. And she wasn’t afraid to take a swing in front of paparazzi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-27"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Wow. What was the fight about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-28"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Unclear, but uniforms are bringing her up to interrogation now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-29"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Do you usually question them solo?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-30"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, Castle and I usually go in together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-31"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Actually, you know what? Why don’t you guys take this one?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-32"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Are you sure?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-33"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah. Absolutely. Besides, Colin’s got a personal interest. I really don’t, now do I?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-34"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Hah, all right. It’s settled then.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-35"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, I guess it is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-36"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah. Besides, my lunch date is here.  I’ll be back in a few hours. You guys call me if you find anything interesting.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>NICKI J</speaker><content>Hell yeah I clocked it. She was trying to make a move on my man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Your man Biggie Slim?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>NICKI J</speaker><content>That’s right. She had the nerve to say that he told her to put her digits in his phone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Did he?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>NICKI J</speaker><content>That ain’t the point. That skinny b*tch wasn’t even supposed to be there. When I got up in her face she said that Biggie Slim’s cousin Drew told her about the party. But I knew that was BS because Drew wasn’t even invited.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Must make you so bloody mad to know that your man has a wandering eye.  I had a girlfriend like that. Traveled for business. She’d ring from the airport to say that her flight was cancelled. I come to find out that she was seeing some other bloke.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>NICKI J</speaker><content>She sound like a ho.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>I’ll I’m saying is, I understand your instinct to lash out at the person you believe is responsible.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>NICKI J</speaker><content>I protect what’s mine. You should do the same.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Is that why you followed Naomi to the motel and strangled her with your bare hands?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>NICKI J</speaker><content>You must be high. That skank wasn’t worth another second of my time. I told security to give her the boot and that was that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Really? Can you prove it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>NICKI J</speaker><content>My driver brought us home.  I was with Biggie Slim the rest of the night.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>BIGGIE SLIM</speaker><content>Yeah, I went home with Nicki J. After the tussle she was all worked up. But I like it when she gets worked up. When she got something to prove.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She said that the fight started because you were spending time with this girl.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>BIGGIE SLIM</speaker><content>Oh yeah, that girl. What can I say? Women are powerless to my good looks and charm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Yes, it’s a curse. You and Naomi, what did you talk about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>BIGGIE SLIM</speaker><content>Ah, a little bit of this, a little bit of that. She wasn’t a bad chick. But a little off, you know what I’m talking about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>No, what are you talking about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>BIGGIE SLIM</speaker><content>She was acting paranoid, man. Said someone had followed her to the party. Figured she was just blowing smoke.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Why’s that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>BIGGIE SLIM</speaker><content>Look, I just don’t produce Nicki J, all right? I’m building my brand. I got Biggie Slim Records, Biggie Slim clothing.  Hell, I even got a Biggie Slim energy drink. So some filly comes up trying to make her time?  It’s just an everyday thing in my life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Did she tell you who she thought was following her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>BIGGIE SLIM</speaker><content>Sure didn’t.  I guess she wasn’t lying though, huh?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Naomi left that party and then 3 hours later she was dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Based on what she told Biggie Slim, Naomi knew someone was after her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>All right, let’s canvass the area around the party venue. See if she was being followed. And let’s track down Nicki J and Biggie Slim’s driver. I want to see if they went straight home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>On it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So… that story you told Nicki J about your girlfriend…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Total pants. I just wanted her to think I sympathized and, honestly, after meeting Biggie Slim I do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, well, maybe she’s hanging on hoping that he’ll change.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content> Guys like him never do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Our ME’s finished the autopsy.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Her larynx was crushed. Whoever did it was strong. Large hands. Probably a male.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s like half the city.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>You may be able to narrow it down a little further than that.  The pressure from the killer’s grip left a print on her neck.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Were you able to pull a print?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>We were able to pull a partial thanks to the body lotion she was wearing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Is it in the system?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Not enough to run if, but you bring me a print from a suspect and I can tell you if it’s a match.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Excuse me, I have to make a call.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Easy on the eyes.  Cute accent, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mmhmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>I just got one question.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Where’s Castle?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He took off. For a lunch date.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>In a Ferrari full of flight attendant?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He’s probably trying to rack up his frequent flyer miles.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-17"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>I’m sorry.  But you know she’s just a passing thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do I? I mean, the guy has been divorced twice and he’s still chasing bimbos.  Maybe that’s just who he is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-19"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Look, maybe’s it’s the wrong time. Or maybe he’s even the wrong guy. But if he is, how long are you going to wait to find out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-20"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Ten years I’ve been keeping them company  while they spend a night or two here on their way to where we’re all going. They all had plans, Kate. Things they were going to do when they got around to it. Go on a cruise, lose 10 pounds, fall in love. They thought they had all the time in the world. But nobody does.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Personal ones are tough.  No call.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>What’s my tell?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The brooding lean.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Ah, yes. Rookie move.  You know, even with a mouth full of braces she was the prettiest girl in her class. Although having a cop for a dad didn’t do much for her social life. Terry used to interrogate her dates when they used to drop her off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> I could see how that would weed out the lightweights.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>And when she was 22 she fell in love with a young doctor. Good guy. He died last year in Africa doing God’s work. I don’t think she ever really got over it because hearing what she was up to … it’s like she was a different person.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>People change when you’re not looking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Excuse me.  Hey Ryan, what’s up?  Are you sure?  Where? Okay, great. Call in a warrant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Found a gym near the hotel. Naomi bought a day pass there the night that she was killed and the clerk said she was in and out in 3 minutes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Just enough time to run in and hide something in one of their lockers.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>She bought the day pass at 10:24PM.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>That’s 20 minutes after she called me to say that she was in trouble.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>She was leaving me a message.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She did better than leave a message about the killer.  She left us a picture of him as well.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Anything on the number sequence?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>TECH GUY</speaker><content>We’re running it through every database but nothing so far.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>She wrote it on there for a reason.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What about the photo?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>TECH GUY</speaker><content>Well ,based on the light and background architecture, this photo was taken in Midtown New York.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hey. What’d I miss?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh, not much.  Oh, we did manage to find the mystery locker. And that guy in the photo, he’s probably our killer. So, how was your lunch?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, I loved the special.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> I’ll bet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-10"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Wait a minute. Can you blow up this one section?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-11"><speaker>TECH GUY</speaker><content>Yeah, sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Rounded and gold? It’s a plaque.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-13"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>It’s the British seal. This picture was taken right outside the British Consulate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Pull up a list of the Consulate employees.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-15"><speaker>TECH GUY</speaker><content>Here you go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-16"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Well he’s not on this page.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>There he is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Nigel Wyndham.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Deputy general of the British Consulate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-20"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Which means he’s just under the Consulate General in rank so he’s responsible for the daily operations in financial and logistical matters.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What the hell was Naomi doing mixed up with this guy?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content> That was my mate at Scotland Yard. He found out some intriguing details on Nigel Wyndham. Like the fact that a girlfriend in college died rather mysteriously while they were on holiday in Rome.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Well was he ever charged?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Nope. And after that he had a string of bad investments until he married Cynthia Woodlow. It was her prominent family that pulled strings and got him a position, first at the Ministry of Culture and then here at the Consulate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yo. So we’ve been reconstructing Naomi’s movements since she landed in New York a couple of weeks ago. Her financials indicate that she booked a car service last week that dropped her at Nobu. Now we showed the host Nigel’s picture and he confirmed that they met for dinner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Did the host notice anything?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, he noticed the c-note Nigel dropped to secure the romantic table in the back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey. I just called the Consulate. The day after the romantic Nobu dinner security removed Naomi from Nigel’s office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Well it sounds like a fight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Uh, security heard Naomi yell something about Cynthia as they escorted her out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, it makes perfect sense. Stuck in a marriage of convenience, Nigel meets the young and beautiful Naomi, finds her irresistible. A chance meeting turns to dinner, dinner to a tryst but then Naomi wants more. Nigel realizes that his affair has become a threat to his position, to his reputation, to the life he built on the backs of his wife and her family.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Sir, if Nigel’s wife found out about an affair it would kill his marriage and his career.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-12"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Detective Inspector Hunt, I take it by your silence that you don’t agree?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-13"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Well, the Naomi I knew would never fall for someone like Wyndham, but she wouldn’t have left his picture in that locker if he weren’t connected to her death somehow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-14"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Nigel Wyndham’s position at the Consulate includes diplomatic immunity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Which would be waived if he were a suspect in a murder case.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-16"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>If I pick up the phone to make that request I’m going to need something more concrete than just a theory.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Sir, Lanie pulled our killer’s prints off of our victim’s neck. And given everything that we know right now, I’m willing to bet that they’re a match to Nigel’s.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-18"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>A bet’s not enough. But if you can get those prints then this is a whole different conversation.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Here’s the problem, bro. Foreign dignitaries don’t register their fingerprints with local law enforcement.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>And if we put in a request to the Consulate they’ll box us out and alert Nigel that he’s a suspect.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, I thought Scotland Yard would be able to get them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Even with his connections across the pond we struck out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay, boys. Here it is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Here’s what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>My foolproof plan for getting Nigel’s fingerprint. Nigel lives in a high rise apartment here on Park Avenue.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, high security.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Exactly. Ryan, you’ll be here.  Front door, dressed as a flower delivery boy.  Esposito, you’ll be here  dressed as a hobo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Question. Why does the brown man gotta be the hobo?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You want the flowers?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hobo it is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You boys will cause a distraction whilst I rappel down the side of the building with Nicolai.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-14"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Who’s Nicolai?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He’s a Romanian gymnast I found on YouTube. He’s extremely flexible and fits in the duffel bag. Using a glass cutter –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-16"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Excuse me, gents. Has anyone seen Detective Beckett?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-17"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Wow.  Uh… you guys going out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-18"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>I pulled some strings and got us into a party at the British Consulate tonight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Nigel will be there. We’ll get his prints and he won’t even know it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-20"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Cheers lads.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-21"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Or they could do that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, if you want to do it the easy way.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So who is Sir Alfred Heath?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Tonight, I am. The lads back home said the real Sir Alfred is down as a no-show. Gout or some damned thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, but what if Nigel Wyndham doesn’t show, either?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>He’ll be here. And I expect he’ll skip the champagne and drink something posh and pretentious and leave his print on the glass.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What if he doesn’t drink?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>He’s British. Trust me, he drinks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>May I?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> I didn’t realize that dancing was part of the plan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Oh … well.  It offers the perfect vantage point.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Huh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you come to a lot of these events?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-13"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>No, thank God. Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You just seem very … confident.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-15"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Ah. Well, that’s because my companion is the most beautiful woman in this room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s clearly the champagne talking. I’m sure your just comfortable here because you’re amongst your own people.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-17"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>These aren’t my people.  My people are the ones carrying the trays. Yeah. I grew up in the East End. My mum cleaned flats, dad worked in a factory. They wanted something better, they just – couldn’t quite get it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And then?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-19"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>I was admitted to Eton on scholarship where I minored in blending in.  What about you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I grew up in the city and went to college in California.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-21"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Well, you could obviously do anything you put your mind to. Why be a cop?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-22"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I guess it was just my calling.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-23"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Ah… crusader. I know the type. It doesn’t leave a lot of time for personal life though, does it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> What about you? Are you the crusader type as well?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-25"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Married to the Bill, I’m afraid. The job comes first. Sometimes I wish it didn’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-26"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah. I know the feeling.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-27"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Wait a minute. Look over there by the bar. My 1 o’clock.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-28"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Let the games begin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-29"><speaker>NIGEL WYNDHAM</speaker><content>Good evening.  Nigel Wyndham, Deputy General.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-30"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Jean Harrington, bored.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-31"><speaker>WYNDHAM</speaker><content>Well we’ll have to remedy that, Miss Harrington.  Uh, one for the lady, please.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-32"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh, a ring. That’s discouraging.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-33"><speaker>WYNDHAM</speaker><content>Oh, well … needn’t be.  To new friendships.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-34"><speaker>WYNDHAM</speaker><content>Now tell me, Miss Harrington. Are you here alone? If so it would be a grave injustice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-35"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> My date’s more interested in networking than he is in me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-36"><speaker>WYNDHAM</speaker><content>In that case, he won’t object if I ask you for a dance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-37"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know what? I wouldn’t care even if he did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-38"><speaker>WYNDHAM</speaker><content>Shall we?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-39"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mmhmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-40"><speaker>WYNDHAM</speaker><content>So Miss Harrington, what should I know about you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-41"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, there’s more to me than meets the eye.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-42"><speaker>WYNDHAM</speaker><content>Well, what meets the eye is irresistible.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-43"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know, actions speak louder than words.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-44"><speaker>WYNDHAM</speaker><content>Meaning?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-45"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Meaning if I’m so irresistible, then why aren’t you using both your hands?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-46"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Excuse me Your Excellency.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-47"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Oh, excuse me. Pardon me. Coming through.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-48"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Sorry, sir. Excuse me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-49"><speaker>SECURITY MAN BRYSON</speaker><content>Sir Alfred Heath?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-50"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-51"><speaker>SECURITY MAN BRYSON</speaker><content>May I have a word, sir? There seems to be two of you here this evening.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-52"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-53"><speaker>WYNDHAM</speaker><content>I have to ask, are you as aggressive in your other activities as you are on the dance floor?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-54"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ah, you know, what can I say?  I like to lead. All the time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-55"><speaker>WYNDHAM</speaker><content>You –  Is everything all right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-56"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Um… yeah, you know, suddenly I feel very hungry. Excuse me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-57"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Would you like one of there? I hear they’re great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-58"><speaker>WYNDHAM</speaker><content>I’m not a caviar man myself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-59"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, but I hear they’re an aphrodisiac.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-60"><speaker>WYNDHAM</speaker><content>Mmm… not for me, I’m afraid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-61"><speaker>SECURITY GUY BRYSON</speaker><content>Sorry to intrude, Mr. Wyndham.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-62"><speaker>WYNDHAM</speaker><content>Yes, what is it, Bryson?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-63"><speaker>SECURITY GUY BRYSON</speaker><content>The young lady, I need her to come with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-64"><speaker>WYNDHAM</speaker><content>Well, for what purpose?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-65"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Don’t worry, darling.  I have no doubt that we’ll see each other again very soon.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content> Ugh, I had the waiter then I lost him. I bollixed up the whole plan and now we’ve got nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh, I wouldn’t say nothing.  I swiped Wyndham’s card case. It’s got his prints all over it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content> Look at you, you sneaky little thief. That’s bloody brilliant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Thank you. Now let’s go get this son of a b*tch.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Print’s not a match.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>CSU ran the fingerprints off the card case, compared them to the print Lanie pulled off of Naomi’s body. It wasn’t a match.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, that’s not possible. Run it again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Ryan already did that three times. Wyndham’s not our killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>He’s behind this, I know it. It’s why Naomi left us his photograph.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well maybe he hired somebody to do his dirty work for him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Like one of his security men.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Can you get Scotland Yard to run background checks on the security staff?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Or a better path might be to look into this mysterious number that Naomi wrote on the back of that photo.  Which is a mystery no longer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Is this lobster, bro?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Lucky for you, Jacinda’s a light eater. You heat that up, a little bit of melted butter –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-14"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Are you telling me she knew what that number means? How?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well as Jacinda and I were enjoying our succulent lobsters – from Maine – paired with an earthy yet elegant Pinot Noir from Sonoma Valley –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle. Numbers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Right. Well, we were going over the file. Turns out Jacinda’s quite a little crime solver.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You showed the stewardess the evidence file?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No.  I took picture of it with my phone. And the current nomenclature is ‘flight attendant’. Point is, this code refers to a diplomatic pouch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-20"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>How do you know that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Jacinda recognized the format. Furthermore, she told me these last three digits are a reference code for Royal Eastern Airlines.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-22"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Which means the pouch was delivered on an airline.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-23"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Exactly. The W4 refers to the size of the pouch, the 1949 indicates exactly which pouch it is in the consulate sequence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-24"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>As the Deputy General Nigel signs for all the pouches.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-25"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So then maybe this wasn’t about an affair gone wrong between Nigel and Naomi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-26"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>It’s about smuggling.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-27"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well that makes a lot of sense. Diplomatic pouches are sealed and their contents bypass TSA and customs inspections.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-28"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Naomi must have got on to what Wyndham was doing somehow. We need to know what was in that pouch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-29"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Consulate’s never going to release that information.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-30"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well we don’t have to worry about the Consulate. The airline keeps a copy of the waybill.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-31"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Get a hold of the airline. Let’s get that waybill down here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-32"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Ryan. Grab a pen.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, you can’t just share confidential police information with an outsider.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Even if it solves the case? I mean, she gave us a lead. That’s more than you got at the Consulate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And that’s supposed to make this all okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Jacinda just wanted to help. What’s the big deal?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You just don’t get it, do you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No, I guess I don’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No. No, I guess you don’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey. We found something you’re going to want to see.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Airline sent over the waybill. The pouch that matched our number was shipped from the British Consulate about a year ago. It flew from JFK to Kampala, Uganda.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Uganda. That can’t be a coincidence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What do you mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Naomi’s boyfriend, the one who died. He was killed in Uganda.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Any idea what was being shipped?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Uh… just that it weighed 200 pounds.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, that’s awfully heavy for a pouch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, a diplomatic pouch can be as small as an envelope or as large as a cargo container.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Whatever’s being shipped, it’s being sent out about once a month. I just combed through airline waybills from the last year. Ten other pouches, all the same weight, were flown from here to Uganda. In fact, one of them is listed as being in JFK’s secure baggage area.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>You mean to say one of those pouches is at the airport right now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Finding out what’s in that pouch could tell us who killed Naomi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, but we don’t have any jurisdiction here, Castle. If the NYPD tries to open up a British diplomatic pouch we could risk an international incident.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-13"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Well, then it’s a good thing I’m not NYPD.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>JFK GUARD MORGAN</speaker><content>Hey!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Oh, good evenin’ sir. I’m Agent Bauer, Homeland Security.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>I’m here for the inspection.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>JFK GUARD MORGAN</speaker><content>Nobody radioed me about any inspection.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content> Of course they didn’t. We conduct random checks to assess security. Telling you we were coming kind of defeats the purpose, am I right?  We’d be tippin’ our hand, showing our playbook, so to speak.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>JFK GUARD MORGAN</speaker><content>Two years I’ve worked this shift and I’ve never heard of any –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Look, Morgan, is it? I’m sure you run a tight ship here, so if everything checks out as secure I’ll be sure your bosses know about it, which will reflect well on you.  We’re all on the same team here, pal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>JFK GUARD MORGAN</speaker><content>I gotta verify this with my supervisor!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content> You do that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-10"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>I’m more adept at faking my way past people. Must be all the practice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You’re in the baggage area?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-12"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Yep. I don’t have much time. Maybe a minute before the guard gets his supervisor to check my story.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, so based on the shipping code the pouch that you’re looking for is about 5 feet long.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-14"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Does the waybill say if it’s a crate, a footlocker, a cardboard box? What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-15"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No. Sorry bro.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-16"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>But its 200 pounds so it’s gotta be something sturdy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-17"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Something sturdy. Right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-18"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Here we go. I found it. It’s a crate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-19"><speaker>JFK GUARD MORGAN</speaker><content>Agent Bauer? I need you to step out of there, please.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Okay, that didn’t sound good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Agent Bauer? What did he expect?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content> I heard that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content> Uh… I’m just about wrapped up here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>JFK GUARD MORGAN</speaker><content>My supervisor will be here in like –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>And he will be mighty pleased with your work. Mighty pleased.  It’s clear to me you’ve been working harder than a … one legged man at a mouse kicking contest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>JFK GUARD MORGAN</speaker><content>Step out of there now, sir. I will not tell you again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>JFK GUARD MORGAN</speaker><content>Hello? You there? Hello?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Bloody hell.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What’s in the crate?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-9"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Missiles.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Customs and Homeland Security have impounded the crate and Interpol is on their way to JFK.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>How did you explain opening the diplomatic pouch?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Well, everyone’s more interested in the missiles at the moment, but I expect I’ll be hot water at some point.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Where does this leave Wyndham?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Untouched.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What do you mean, untouched? He was smuggling weapons.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Well there’ll be an inquiry of course, but they can’t prove he knew what was in the crate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And since we opened the crate illegally we won’t be able to use it as evidence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>At least it all starts to make sense now. Naomi was trying to solve Aiden’s murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>That would be Naomi’s boyfriend, Aiden Miller. He worked for Doctors Without Borders in Uganda until his helicopter was shot down by guerrilla forces a year ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-11"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>The British government launched an investigation but was never able to determine how the rebels acquired a stinger missile.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Which we now know came to them courtesy of Nigel Wyndham.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Except Nigel’s not the type to get his hands dirty when it comes to missiles or murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Must have had a partner who had a line on those stingers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And if Naomi started looking into the smuggling operation –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-16"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Then perhaps it was the partner that got rid of her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-17"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>So then the question is who is his partner?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Everything is Naomi did was about finding out who supplied the weapon that killed her boyfriend. That’s why she stopped taking modeling gigs. That’s why she came to New York.  Maybe there’s someone on the list of attendees for that foreign dignitary party.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I mean, it all started when she booked that in London a few months ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-20"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Paulo Macuzzi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-21"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>And who is he?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-22"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Leader of the rebel army in Uganda.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Naomi must have heard something at the party. That’s what lead her to the Consulate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-24"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>That romantic dinner with Nigel was just part of her agenda to get the pouch number from his office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-25"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So then there’s just one piece that doesn’t fit in her investigation.  What was she doing with Biggie Slim?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I want you to take a close look at this photo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>BIGGIE SLIM</speaker><content>Yeah, I see. That’s when paparazzi caught me and Nicki J coming out of the studio a couple of weeks ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>In fact, that is Nicki J’s black SUV, isn’t it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>BIGGIE SLIM</speaker><content>Bought by Biggie Slim himself. Supply and demand. She demands, I gotta supply.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know, the thing that I find intriguing is that before you became Biggie Slim your name was Darrius Young. Best known for launching several failed internet startups.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>BIGGIE SLIM</speaker><content>But a man ahead of my time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Well the SEC thought you were a man trying to fleece investors.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-8"><speaker>BIGGIE SLIM</speaker><content>See I was never charged for that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>One of your ventures, a music sharing website based in the UK caught the attention of authorities and when they tried to shut it down and aide to the Minister of Culture lobbied on your behalf. And do you know who that aide was?  Nigel Wyndham.  In fact, this is Nigel stepping out of the very same black SUV.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-10"><speaker>BIGGIE SLIM</speaker><content>No … I don’t think so.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why don’t you take a closer look. Those are the same custom pinstripes on the door.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-12"><speaker>BIGGIE SLIM</speaker><content>It’s just somebody else's truck with those stripes on there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-13"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Your driver already admitted that he drove you to this meeting outside the Consulate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We also know that your cousin is in the service. Drew Harris?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-15"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>A staff sergeant. He works at an armory. He supplied the missiles.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You knew that Wyndham had access to the diplomatic pouch and you saw an opportunity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-17"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Supply and demand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-18"><speaker>BIGGIE SLIM</speaker><content>That’s a whole lot of speculation there, mate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, we weren’t the only ones to put together the pieces.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-20"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Naomi wasn’t giving you her phone number. She was looking for evidence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Once you realized that she was the same girl that Wyndham caught snooping you followed her to the motel and you killed her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-22"><speaker>BIGGIE SLIM</speaker><content> Well how’re ya’ll gonna prove that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-23"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>A partial fingerprint on Naomi’s body. And it’s a match to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know, the thing that I still can’t figure out is why Uganda? Why would you care?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-25"><speaker>BIGGIE SLIM</speaker><content>Man, it wasn’t about Uganda. It was just about the money. I didn’t even know where Wyndham was shippin’ the stuff to.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>WYNDHAM</speaker><content>Good. I will call my assistant. I’m wide open all week.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Actually, you’re not. Or the following week for that matter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Told you I’d see you soon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>WYNDHAM</speaker><content>What is this? Getting thrown out of here once wasn’t enough for you people? Security –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>They can’t help you, mate. Nobody can. Not even your well-funded Ugandan friends. Nigel Wyndham, you’re under arrest for international arms trafficking and</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Her dad would have been proud. How brave she was, taking on these men. I still wish she hadn’t done it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do what happens now? Do you go back to DC?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>London, I’m afraid. Face the music.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> You know, they should give you a commendation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Well, that is wildly improbable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Well, Detective Beckett. It’s been a true pleasure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> The pleasure was all mine, Detective Inspector Hunt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-8"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Please. Colin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Kate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-10"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>You know I have a few hours before my flight, Kate. Could I persuade you to let me buy you a drink?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Um –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I’m sorry. I have a bit of paperwork to do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-13"><speaker>HUNT</speaker><content>Another time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Where’s Scotland Yard off to?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh, he’s going back to London. Um…  Castle, do you have a second? Can we talk?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Actually, I don’t. Jacinda had the Ferrari double parked in a loading zone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Wow.  4 dates in 3 days. You like her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah.  Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She just … she doesn’t seem like your type.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, she’s fun and uncomplicated. I think that’s what my life needs right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hi. It’s uh … it’s Kate.  Do you still want to buy me that drink?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-22"><speaker>THE END</speaker><content>CASTLE</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>