<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>



<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>MARTHA RODGERS</speaker><content>She screamed as the pain ripped through her and in between each labored breath she thought “there is no way in hell I’m having this baby on a subway train in the Bronx”.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content> Did you get all that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>MARCUS</speaker><content>So you actually gave birth to your son on the Metro?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>RICHARD CASTLE</speaker><content>No … she didn’t. She also didn’t run a marathon the night before she had me or beat up a mugger while 9 months pregnant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>It’s called dramatic license, darling.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Actually, it’s called wild exaggeration. Dramatic license applies to writing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>And that’s what I’m doing. This is Marcus, the fabulous young playwright I told you about who’s helping me put together my one woman show.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>MARCUS</speaker><content>Mr. Castle, I’m a huge fan. Just being in this office is a dream come true.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>For me too. For me too. Only in my dreams, I’m usually by myself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>We just felt that this room had the best creative ju-ju.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, it does. It does. I wrote 20 best sellers in here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Oh, right. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’d like to write another one.  Now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Oh, can’t it wait dear? We’re putting the final touches on Act 1. You know, where I overcome the challenges of being a single working mother –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> You know you’re writing a work of fiction, right?  Castle.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>First Alexis is interning for Lanie.  Thank you.  Now my mother is taking over my office? I feel like my whole life is being invaded.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>KATE BECKETT</speaker><content>You’ll get used to it. I did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It is not the same thing.  ‘kay, it’s similar. Just much less invasive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey Lanie.  So what do we got here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>LANIE PARISH</speaker><content>That’s a good question. I can tell you this much – based on body temp and lividity our victim died between 10 and midnight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Claw marks? She was attacked by an animal?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Well, she was running from something. She’s got dirt on her feet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What animal in Central Park could maul a person to death?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>I’m not even sure that’s what happened.  These lacerations look shallow, nonlethal, but I won’t know exactly what killed her until I get her back to the morgue.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you have an ID?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>No wallet or purse, so we don’t know who she’s is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Uh –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Isn’t it obvious? Am I the only one seeing this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Red cloak, in the woods, animal attack.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>She’s Little Red Riding Hood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Great, Castle. I’ll call in an APB for the Big Bad Wolf.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Do you have a better theory?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey Ryan?  Do you think you could call dispatch, see if there are any reports of a violent animal running around the park?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>KEVIN RYAN</speaker><content>Like a wolf? A big bad one?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Really?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-22"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>That is exactly how I pictured her. It’s freaky. My older sister used to read me that story.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, when you’re done reliving your childhood memories do you also think you can canvass the area for witnesses and anyone that might know her name? And I bet you it’s not gonna be Little Red Riding Hood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-24"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>On it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> “All the better to eat you with. No sooner had the wolf said these words when he leaped up and gobbled down poor Little Red Riding Hood.” Well, the good news is the wolf can talk, so if we can find him we might be able to get a confession.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, except in the wolf doesn’t kill Little Red Riding Hood. The huntsman cuts her out of the wolf’s stomach and then she kills the wolf.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Someone’s a Brothers Grimm fan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh yeah. They didn’t sugarcoat it. They understood that fairy tales are pretty much horror stories.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Exactly. Which is why we all need them to grapple with the unknown. Which is why they tap into our primal fears, like being alone in the woods or getting eaten by monsters.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>They’re not horror stories. They’re life lessons. If you do the right thing you get to live happily ever after.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>But only in fairy tales.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Speaking of fairy tales, turns out that our victim really was Red Riding Hood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Are you drinking Castle’s Kool-Aid now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No, she was actually wearing a Red Riding Hood costume. It said so in the label.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh, okay. So then why was she wearing it in the middle of the woods at night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>On her way to grandmother’s house.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Mmm… I doubt it. Grandmother lives in Tallahassee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh great, so you got an ID?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah. Her prints popped in the DMV database. Her name is Amy Morgan. Her sister Leslie is on her way in.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>LESLIE MORGAN</speaker><content>I don’t understand. Are you saying Amy was attacked by some kind of animal?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do either of you have any idea why she was in the park?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>LESLIE</speaker><content>Amy never went there. She didn’t had time. She was too busy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Doing what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>DARREN THOMAS</speaker><content>She was an attorney for Samson Briggs in litigation. They worked her like, a hundred hours a week.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Did she have a boyfriend? Anyone she would have been with last night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>LESLIE</speaker><content>Amy’s single. She lives alone. She’s very driven.  Was. She was.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do either of you know why she would be wearing this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>DARREN</speaker><content>What is it? A cape?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s a Red Riding Hood cloak.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>DARREN</speaker><content>She was wearing that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Mmhmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>LESLIE</speaker><content>I know Amy’s closet. This was not hers. I mean, even her sweatpants were Prada.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, maybe she was going to a party. Did she mention any parties?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>LESLIE</speaker><content>I’m telling you. She would never wear a thing like this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Leslie, did your sister ever tell you about anything unusual going on at work, or in her personal life?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>LESLIE</speaker><content>I don’t know. I hadn’t heard from her all week.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And was that out of the ordinary?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>LESLIE</speaker><content>Yes. We usually talked every day and when she didn’t call I just assumed she was busy with a case or something, but …  maybe there was something else going on.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Okay, ‘bye.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey.  Thank you. So that was Ryan. He just left Animal Control and there was only 1 recent report of an animal loose in the park.  A beagle. Named Fred.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well either Fred is one vicious beagle or this mystery has just deepened.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>How does a high-powered lawyer end up dead in a Red Riding Hood costume?  Amy worked long hours under pressure, right? What if she had a secret way of letting off steam that even her sister didn’t know about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Like what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>There’s this whole … adult role playing subculture obsessed with fairy tales.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Not – not that kind of adult role play. Although, there is that one too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And you know this … how?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Did a little research.  Huh. Bo Peep.  Anyway, these people get dressed in the outfits, they play the characters, they even reenact the stories. Maybe that’s what Amy was doing when everything went horribly and tragically wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, that is a surprisingly reasonable and grounded theory.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah.  Frankly, I’m a little disappointed in myself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>We all are, bro.  So, I was going over Amy’s financials for any unusual activity. 4 days ago she took out $50,605 dollars from her savings, all in cash.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>$50,605? That’s an odd amount for a withdrawal, especially in cash.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, not only that, but the $50k? It’s not in her apartment and I can’t tie it to any recent purchases.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Contact her bank, see if they know why she made that withdrawal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content> As you wish.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ah … Lanie’s got news for us.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Oh, I’ve got news all right, but I’m not sure you’re gonna like it. I found hairs like this one in a wound on the victim’s arm.  It didn’t come from her, so I ran DNA.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Did we get a match?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>The hair isn’t human. It’s wolf hair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Ooooh!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Simmer down, Castle. I’m not done with the story.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Sorry.  What’s the rest of it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Well, from the depth and the length of the gashes it looks like the marks were made by only one claw.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>A one legged wolf?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>I don’t think it’s a wolf at all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>But the hair and the claw.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The killer wanted us to think it was a wolf to throw us off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Which would explain why there are no bite marks on the body. The gashes were inflicted by a human killer using a wolf claw.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So then what’s the real cause of death?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Well, I found two fresh needle marks, both on the victim’s back, so she didn’t put them there herself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So she was drugged?  Was there any signs of sexual assault?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>No, but tox results turned up ketamine and oxycodone. I’m thinking our guy sedated her with the ketamine then dressed her in the costume. But the dose didn’t quite knock her out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So she tried to run away from her killer -</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-18"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>And when he caught her he dosed her with oxy and it was lights out.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The drugs, the claw? This is murder, planned and premeditated. I mean, the killer staged the crime scene to evoke images of Little Red Riding Hood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, but why would he do that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, I’m less concerned about why.  What I’m wondering is who.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So the killer must have lured Amy into the park.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Which means he’s someone that she knew and trusted.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah. Like Red Riding Hood trusted her cute little Granny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah.  Ryan, what did Amy’s coworkers say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Uh, that she definitely wasn’t herself lately. Said that she’d been acting agitated since she missed a mandatory 1 o’clock staff meeting last Friday. Said it was for personal reasons.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s the same time that Amy stopped calling her sister. Ryan, can you look into her emails and phone calls? I want to know what was going on with her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yep.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yo Beckett. There’s something you need to see.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Right over there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Is that what I think it is in her hand?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Poisoned apple?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She’s Snow White.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Looks like we’ve got a fairytale killer on our hands.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yo, Beckett.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Excuse me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Her medical alert bracelet got us an ID. She’s Kristina Curtis, 25. Lives on the Upper East Side.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Does she have next of kin?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah, her husband. His name’s Noah Curtis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, I need you guys to take point on the interview. Find out what he knows about this and see if Kristina was connected to the other victim.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>You know, if our killer is dressing our victims in these costumes, I bet we can ID the manufacturer and find out where he got them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s a good idea. You run with it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ah, here it is.  “White as snow, red as blood, black as ebony.” This guy is quoting directly from Grimm’s original Snow White.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So our victims aren’t reenacting the fairy tales. The killer is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Only this woman didn’t die from the poison apple. She has the same injection marks as Amy Morgan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you have time of death?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Between 5 and 7AM this morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So he kills Red Riding Hood and 6 hours later he strikes again? That’s a pretty quick turnaround.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>It’s all the markings of a serial killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah … but technically you have to murder 3 times to be a serial killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Yeah well, let’s make sure he never gets there.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>When did you last see your wife, Mr. Curtis?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>NOAH CURTIS</speaker><content>Just before 5AM when she – she left for her jog. She – she gave me a kiss goodbye and that was the last time I saw her.  I – I – I can’t believe she’s gone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Mr. Curtis, this run she took. Who else knew she was going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>NOAH</speaker><content>Other joggers in the park, I guess. She – she went every morning, even in the snow. She – she never missed a day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>She have problems with any of the other joggers?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>NOAH</speaker><content>No. Not that she told me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Did she ever mention being followed, or watched?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>NOAH</speaker><content>You’re saying someone was stalking her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Under the circumstances this doesn’t look like a random attack. What did your wife do for a living?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>NOAH</speaker><content>She owned an art gallery on Fifth Avenue. It was family owned. She took it over from her dad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You ever seen this woman before? Or heard the name Amy Morgan?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>NOAH</speaker><content>No, I don’t think so. Why? Who is she?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>She’s another victim, Mr. Curtis. Could she be an acquaintance of Kristina’s?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>NOAH</speaker><content>I don’t recognize her. I’m sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Did you notice anything unusual about Kristina lately? Her state of mind, maybe? Or something she said or did?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>NOAH</speaker><content>There was something strange last week. We were supposed to have lunch on Friday, but she didn’t show. She called later to say she went to the art gallery for a last minute emergency.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-17"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Last Friday? Was your lunch as 1PM?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-18"><speaker>NOAH</speaker><content> Yeah. Yeah it was. W-why?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Kristina lied to her husband about why she missed their lunch. She wasn’t at the art gallery last Friday. They don’t know where she was.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, so of both our victims were unaccounted for at exactly the same time shortly before they got killed. So where did they go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>We’re still working on it. Excuse me.  Yeah, Ryan here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Maybe they knew each other.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, their families said they didn’t know each other. They had completely different careers and lived in different parts of town. It seems like their lives never really intersected.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, until they both died at the hand of the same killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So why these two women? And why fairy tales? Did the killer have some sort of random obsession or was there a deeper meaning behind all of it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, I think he’s trying to tell a story with these bodies, I just don’t know what it is yet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Maybe it’s about money. Turns out, Kristina raided her trust account. Guess how much she took out?  $50,605 dollars.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So both victims go AWOL on Friday and both pull out the exact same amount of cash? That’s not a coincidence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That is a connection. Can you get a hold of Kristina’s family? See if they know why she might have needed that money.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, I’ll retalk to the husband.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Thanks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ryan, what’d you find out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I think I might have found the pathway to our killer. Those Snow White and Red Riding Hood outfits? They were made by the same manufacturer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you know where they were sold?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-17"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I’m still waiting for a list of stores that carry the costumes, both online and brick and mortar. Should have some answers by the morning.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>This just doesn’t feel right, Marcus. Move that chair over there.  Oh Richard! Your timing is perfect. We could use your help.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Moving my furniture where I don’t want it to go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>It’s just temporary. We’re having a stage reading of my one woman show. Here, tomorrow night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ah… it’s too bad you don’t have an acting studio to do this kind of thing in. Oh wait … you do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>The little black box theater isn’t right for this, dear. It needs something much more intimate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>MARCUS</speaker><content>It’ll be very avant garde.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Exactly. Now, I think this chair should be here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Sweetie, you couldn’t have done something to discourage this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>ALEXIS CASTLE</speaker><content>I tried, Dad. But she made me stage manager. Look, it’s not as bad as you think. Just 20 or 30 people –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ah –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>And we’ll put everything back. This play means a lot to Gram. And it’s actually really good.  Now I understand things about her I never did before.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>About you, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>About me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>No, no, no… this space needs to be bigger. An actor needs space.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> ”Richard always had a dark imagination. He was destined either to become a serial killer or a mystery writer.” Mother, really?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-16"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Oh, it’s just a slight exaggeration.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And according to this, you’re responsible for launching my writing career by …  You slept with my first publisher?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-18"><speaker>MARCUS</speaker><content>Mr. Castle, I’m sure your talent would have gotten you there eventually.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>My talent did get me there. I didn’t get published because of her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-20"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Technically I slept with him after your book was out. This is just to be more salacious.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Wasn’t he practically my age?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-22"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Honey, you know I’ve always loved younger men. They have so much energy, enough to keep up with me.  Most of the time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-23"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’m going to erase that image from my mind with a bottle of scotch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-24"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Oh, darling? I invited Beckett to the reading tomorrow night, so you two might want to make a date of it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What was I supposed to do? Say no?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yes!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why are you so against your mom’s play?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Because she’s rewriting history. My history. Trust me, I lived through it. She’s making it sounds like it’s her own personal fairytale.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh, so you don’t like it when someone writes their own version of your life.  Interesting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay, are you referring to the Nikki Heat books? Because this is completely different.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>How is it different?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, for one thing –  I’m not claiming what I write is actually true.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well I don’t think she is, either. C’mon Castle. You said so yourself. Everyone needs a fairytale. What’s the harm in letting your mom have one of her own?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay, let’s – let’s change the subject to something less likely to give me an ulcer. How about that mysterious $50,605 dollars?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, um … well, we talked to pretty much everyone close to Amy and Kristina and no one seems to know why they pulled out that money.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What about where they were at 1PM on Friday?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Nothing popped on Amy’s email or phone calls. And the techs are still going through Krisitna’s computer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-14"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey guys. Think we might have caught a break. We tracked down that website that sold the costumes. They Red Riding Hood cloak and the Snow White dress worn by our victims were shipped out 8 days ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>To whom? Do you have a name?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-16"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah, Jamie Isaacson. Lives at 11th Street and 7th Avenue. And he didn’t just order 2 costumes. There was a third in the shipment as well. For Sleeping</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Sleeping Beauty? He’s gonna kill again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Not if we get to him first.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Jamie Isaacson! NYPD! Open up!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>SWAT</speaker><content>Go, go, go, go!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Room clear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>All these freaky dolls, just like I imagined this guy’s lair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Ever since Chucky I haven’t been able to look at a doll.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>SWAT</speaker><content>Detective!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>JAMIE ISAACSON</speaker><content>Did you have to knock down my door?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Ma’am, we announced ourselves.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>JAMIE</speaker><content>I was coming. I don’t move as fast as I used to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Ma’am, do you know a Jamie Isaacson?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-11"><speaker>JAMIE</speaker><content>Of course I know a Jamie Isaacson. I’m Jamie Isaacson.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You –</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>JAMIE</speaker><content>Candy?  It’s very good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> No thanks. Mrs. Isaacson, does anyone else live here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>JAMIE</speaker><content>No, dearie. Nobody else lives here. Just me and my friends.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Do you have any family that checks on you? Healthcare workers?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Other more … um… human friends?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>JAMIE</speaker><content>Well mostly it’s just us. Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Did you receive a package in the mail last week, Mrs. Isaacson?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>JAMIE</speaker><content>Oh, I receive packages all the time. Molly and Abigail are new arrivals.  Aren’t they gorgeous?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> Yes, they are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What about a delivery of fairytale costumes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-11"><speaker>JAMIE</speaker><content>Fairytale costumes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>According to our records, you ordered three from a website last week.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-13"><speaker>JAMIE</speaker><content>Well that’s just ridiculous. What would I do with fairytale costumes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-14"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> Can’t imagine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-15"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So you didn’t order any costumes from the internet?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-16"><speaker>JAMIE</speaker><content>Do I look like someone who has a habit of wasting money? I- I’m on a fixed income.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-17"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, I … happen to notice you don’t have a doorman for this building. So where are your packages left?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-18"><speaker>JAMIE</speaker><content>By the mailbox in the lobby.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-19"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Mrs. Isaacson,  did you notice any uh… unusual charges on your credit card? Anyone have access to it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-20"><speaker>JAMIE</speaker><content>Well, not unless they’re digging for gold.  Can’t be too safe these days.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-21"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So UPS confirms a package of costumes was dropped off at Mrs. Isaacson’s lobby but nobody signed for it – per buyer’s instructions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>There’s some more bad news. No security cameras inside the lobby or outside, and from what we can tell, the building’s not terribly secure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The killer probably knew that, that’s why he used it as a delivery drop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well if he knew the old lady’s credit card number, maybe he knew her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Could be. Could be he just found her credit card statements in the trash. It’s old school, but it’s effective.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You guys, for all we know he’s targeting Sleeping Beauty as we speak.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yo. I got something. The missing hour at lunchtime of Kristina’s last Friday? Tech found a map search on her tablet that day at 12:50PM. Walking directions to Glassman’s Café on the Upper West Side.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, great. You guys go to the café, see if you can figure out who she was meeting with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>On it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>In the meantime, I’m gonna get a hold of uniforms and ask them to double foot patrols in parks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Only he’s not going to strike in a park this time.  In the Grimm’s stories Red Riding and Snow White were found in the woods. But Sleeping Beauty …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Was found in her bedroom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Great, so that narrows it down to several million apartments and that is just in Manhattan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It doesn’t make sense.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What doesn’t make any sense?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>His motive. All serial killers are expressing some psychological impulse. Somewhere deep down there’s a twisted logic to their insanity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, keep going.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>In the original Grimm’s tales - Red Riding Hood, Snow White, Sleeping Beauty – they all end up near death but are saved at the last moment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>It’s like he’s trying to take away our victims happy endings.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Right. Not only that, but he could have ordered any costume. But he picked these. He took great care with the details. The wolf’s claw. The apple. He chose these characters for a reason. He chose these women for a reason. I just haven’t figured it out yet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-22"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, whatever it is, it has to be connected to the cash they withdrew.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-23"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Maybe he’s choosing women with healthy bank accounts.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Bank.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-25"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Sorry?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-26"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Kristina and Amy both withdrew the same amount of money. Maybe our Sleeping Beauty did as well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-27"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The IRS requires banks to report any transactions over $10,000, so they would have a record of it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-28"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Exactly.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>JESSE</speaker><content>Yeah, she was here. It was last Friday during the lunch rush, right after I spilled ketchup on my new jeans. They were 70% off. Amazing sale.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Was she by herself?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>JESSE</speaker><content>No, it was a party of three.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Three? Do you remember who else she was with?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>JESSE</speaker><content>Two other women.  I’ve never been questioned by cops before. Do you mind if I tweet about this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Oh, uh, yes. We do mind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>This one of the women?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>JESSE</speaker><content>Yeah. Are they criminals or something? ‘cause I was getting more of an Upper East Side vibe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No, but this third woman might be in danger so we need to identify her as soon as possible. Do you remember if she maybe paid with a credit card? Maybe you caught her name?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-10"><speaker>JESSE</speaker><content>Nope, they paid cash.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Was anyone else with them? A man?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-12"><speaker>JESSE</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Did you notice anyone watching them?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-14"><speaker>JESSE</speaker><content>Some of the other customers, but only because they were arguing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-15"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>About what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-16"><speaker>JESSE</speaker><content>I don’t know. I kind of tried to eavesdrop, but every time I went over there they gave me the death stare. Whatever they were talking about, they didn’t want me to hear.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, so the IRS search reveals 10 different cash transactions between $50 and $60 thousand dollars that day. Two belong to our Red Riding Hood and Snow White.  That leaves us 8. Five were made by males , leaving three women – Jessica Harper, Charlotte Boyd, and Dana Wilson.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, Harper and Wilson are in their 50s. They don’t fit the profile.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Which leaves us Charlotte Boyd.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Beckett.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> Hey. We were able to confirm that Kristina was here with Amy Morgan and a third woman last Friday. We think she might be our killer’s third target.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> We didn’t get an ID, but we did get a pretty good description.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Let me guess. In her 20s, brown hair, brown eyes, exotic looking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah, how’d you know?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Charlotte isn’t answering.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Her name’s Charlotte Boyd. Ryan, I’m gonna text you her address. Just meet us over there.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Beckett!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Call an ambulance. She’s still alive.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Okay, yeah. Just keep me posted on her status, thanks.  So that was the ER. Charlotte is stable, but still unconscious.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ketamine and oxycodone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah. And without treatment her heart could have stopped. Doctor says we got there just in time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Just like in the fairytale.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> So what, you’re Prince Charming now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Well, if the shoe fits …  No, I’m just glad we had a happy ending.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well it won’t be a happy ending until evil is vanquished and locked in the dungeon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>We’re closing in on him</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, but he’s still a step ahead. I’m hoping that he left some kind of evidence behind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yo. We’ve done a full sweep. No sign of the $50,605 dollars.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>A luxury condo and that much money? What does this girl do for a living?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>She worked for a real estate firm as a high end broker. If you didn’t have $10 mil to plunk down on an apartment she wasn’t your girl.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay, so we’ve got three women, all in their 20s, all successful, all have a secret meeting last Friday and then pull the exact same amount of cash out of the bank?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Maybe they were going in on something. Pooling their money.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I think we can safely rule out lotto tickets.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, there’s gotta be something that we’re missing. There’s something that links the three of them together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-17"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey guys. Look at this. I found it at the bottom of one of Charlotte’s drawers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-18"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>We got our connection.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Amy, Charlotte, and Kristina. Our three victims.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>All dressed as fairytale characters.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Dressed as the same characters that our killer dressed them as.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Check out the date.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>05/06/05. That’s seven years ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-24"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, it’s also the amount of money they withdrew.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-25"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>$50,605 bucks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-26"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah, and uh … check out the back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-27"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>“Who’s the guiltiest of them all? If you pay you’ll live to see another day.”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-28"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>They were being blackmailed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-29"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay, so something happened on that date that connects them all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-30"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Something that lead to their murders.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-31"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So who’s the guy taking the photo?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-32"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Maybe he can tell us what happened.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>CSU only found one set of prints on the photo. Charlotte’s. But they were able to determine that it was developed within the last two weeks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>How can they do that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, it’s machine processed. Like, you know, from a drugstore and there’s a control code auto printed on the back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Can we use the code to figure out where it was processed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah, already on it. Hopefully that’ll get us who ordered the prints.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>This photo was taken 7 years ago. Why is it surfacing now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yo. You’re right about the date. Something did happen 7 years ago. There’s even a police report.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I don’t suppose the report IDs our Prince Charming.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Sure does.  His name’s Owen Thomas. But he can’t be our suspect. He’s dead. He was killed 7 years ago. May 6th, 2005.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>05/06/05.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The night that the photo was taken.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>It’s also the same night that Owen attended an underground rave. Fairytale themed. He was last seen alive at 10:45.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>But … this picture was taken at 11:43.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>How did he die?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-15"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Internal bleeding complicated with high doses of ketamine and oxycodone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That explains our killer’s MO.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay, so he’s high on club drugs. But what caused the internal bleeding?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-18"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>A car. His body was found on the side of the road. The ME wrote it up as a hit and run. There were no witnesses so the trail went cold. They never solved the case.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> It’s “I Know What You Did Last Summer”. Who’s the guiltiest of them all. The killer thinks that one of these women is responsible for his death.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-20"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Maybe they are. This photo proves that they were the last ones to see him alive, yet none of them gave statements to the cops.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>But why are the murders happening now, 7 years later?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-22"><speaker>BECKTT</speaker><content>Well maybe after all these years someone found this photo. Esposito, can you look into Owen’s family and friends? Someone might be trying to get payback for his death.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-23"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You got it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Beckett.  Yeah, we’ll be right there.  Sleeping Beauty just woke up.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Charlotte? I’m Detective Beckett, this is Mr. Castle. Do you feel well enough to answer a few questions?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>CHARLOTTE</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What can you tell us about the attack?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>CHARLOTTE</speaker><content>I was at my computer, just listening to music, and the next thing you know I’m being pushed to the floor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Did you see who did it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>CHARLOTTE</speaker><content> No. They’re saying – they’re saying that I was drugged. Why would someone do this to me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Charlotte, I think you know why. All three of you received a copy of this photo.  Amy and Kristina weren’t as lucky as you. They didn’t make it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>CHARLOTTE</speaker><content>But we did what he asked. We paid him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What does he have on you? What happened to Owen that night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Charlotte?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>CHARLOTTE</speaker><content> It was just some stupid fairytale rave. Um … we were just looking to dance and have fun. And Owen had scored some Special K that hit us pretty hard, but Kristina had some of her mom’s oxy and said it would even us out. Somehow we ended up in Amy’s car. That’s where this picture was taken.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>How did Owen end up on the side of the road?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-13"><speaker>CHARLOTTE</speaker><content>He was having some seriously bad hallucinations, just screaming and grabbing at us. So we pulled the car over and we made him get out. We just figured he’d walk back to the rave. But it was all over the news the next morning, that – that there’d been a hit and run, that he’d been killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why didn’t you come forward?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-15"><speaker>CHARLOTTE</speaker><content>We were just kids then. We were scared out of our minds. Y- you have to understand, we had a lot to lose. We came from good families, we’d been accepted into college, we’d – we made a pact, we said we wouldn’t tell anyone what happened that night and that we’d never see each other again.  I’m not excusing how we handled it. We were stupid, but we didn’t do anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well someone thinks you did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What did you do with the money?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-18"><speaker>CHARLOTTE</speaker><content>The note said to put it in a dumpster at Bleecker and Thompson. We didn’t want some scandal messing up our lives, so we did it. We paid. So why did he come after us?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, so Bleecker and Thompson. There are no security cameras at the drop site and so far no witnesses.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He covered his bases.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I know. It’s really starting to piss me off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, and you get cute when you get angry.  But not when you get angry with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yo. So I took a look at Owen’s family. I think I found someone with motive. Turns out he has an older brother. And apparently they were close.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Any connection to our victims?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Oh yeah.  See for yourself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Wait, that’s Leslie’s husband Darren.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So Owen’s brother is married to our first victim’s sister?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What are the odds, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Maybe Darren somehow found out that his wife’s sister was responsible for his brother Owen’s death.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well maybe the families just knew each other socially. It doesn’t mean that Darren’s our killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-13"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>That doesn’t, but this might. CSU tracked down where the photo was processed. It’s from a roll of film and the guy who dropped it off had three copies made.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And does the guy’s description match Darren’s?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-15"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Even better. They had security cameras.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>It’s him.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>LESLIE</speaker><content>I got here as fast as I could. So, is there any news? Did you find out who did this to my sister?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Uh, first let me ask, what was Amy’s relationship with your husband’s brother? Owen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>LESLIE</speaker><content>They were high school friends. We all were. What does this have to do with Amy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>LESLIE</speaker><content>Owen died years ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You ever see this before?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>LESLIE</speaker><content>No.  That’s Amy. And that’s Owen. These two I don’t know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>It’s from the night that he was killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>LESLIE</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Your husband Darren had it printed up 2 weeks ago. Do you have any idea how he got it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-10"><speaker>LESLIE</speaker><content>Last month we were cleaning out my dad’s attic and found a camera with a roll of film inside. Darren thought it’d be fun to see what was on it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-11"><speaker>LESLIE</speaker><content>You don’t think he had anything to do with Amy.  Do you?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>DARREN</speaker><content>I don’t know what you guys are talking about. I didn’t blackmail anybody.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Right, so then you don’t recognize this photo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>DARREN</speaker><content>Absolutely not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And then, this isn’t you, is it Darren.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I can only imagine how you must have felt. After all these years realizing your own sister-in-law might be involved in your brother’s death.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We found the cash in your storage locker in Queens. $151,815 dollars.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Which by wild coincidence is exactly $50,605 dollars times 3.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-8"><speaker>DARREN</speaker><content>Owen was high. He was messed up. They knew that and what did they do? They left him there. They left him and he died like roadkill.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You could have gone to the police.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-10"><speaker>DARREN</speaker><content>Because they did such a bang up job the first time around? I just wanted them to pay something for what they did. And I was even going to use the money to set up a scholarship fund in Owen’s name.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Really? A scholarship fund? And what’s your spin on murder?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The money wasn’t enough. You wanted revenge. You wanted them to die, just like your brother, dressed in fairytale costumes, OD’ing on the same drugs he did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-13"><speaker>DARREN</speaker><content>What? No.  I don’t know who killed them, but it wasn’t me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s gonna be tough to believe, Darren. You had motive, to blamed them for Owen’s death, and you just admitted to blackmailing them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-15"><speaker>DARREN</speaker><content>I want a lawyer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Of course you do.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Darren doesn’t need a lawyer. He needs a miracle. His wife told Ryan that he wasn’t at the house when the murders were committed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So that’s it then.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, for this case. We did everything but tie a bow on it for the DA.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Right this way Ms. Morgan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>LESLIE</speaker><content>Is it true, Darren? Is it true? Look me in the eyes and tell me it’s not true!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>DARREN</speaker><content>I didn’t hurt anyone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>LESLIE</speaker><content>You blackmailed my sister! You lied to me!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>DARREN</speaker><content>No, no, no. Listen. I’m telling you the truth, okay? I didn’t kill anyone. I just wanted them to pay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>LESLIE</speaker><content>Who would do it then? You had the picture.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-10"><speaker>DARREN</speaker><content>No, no. Babe, I swear. I swear, babe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-11"><speaker>LESLIE</speaker><content>No. Get away from me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-12"><speaker>DARREN</speaker><content>Listen! Les!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-13"><speaker>LESLIE</speaker><content>Stay away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Murder does more damage to the living than to the dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah. All because of a terrible secret.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well secrets are like time bombs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Eventually they … explode.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know Castle, I’m not saying I condone what Darren did, but I do understand it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah. I understand wanting revenge. The way he went about it doesn’t add up, though.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What do you mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, blackmail is revenge from a distance. Murder is up close and personal. It doesn’t make sense he would do both.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-22"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Don’t underestimate him. I mean, the only reason that he copped to blackmail was to avoid murder charges. And like any psychopath he’s a great actor. Oh, speaking of –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-23"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Psychopaths or actors?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I was thinking about your mom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-25"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, so a little of both.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-26"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I think we can make the play.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-27"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Really?  So you want to venture into the dark scary woods?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-28"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Don’t worry Castle, I got a gun. I’ll protect you from the Big Bad Wolf.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-29"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You’d use your gun on my mother?  I’m touched.  Thank you.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ah. Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh wow, Castle. This is quite the soiree.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, it’s a family trait. We tend to go big.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Cheers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Cheers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Could you … excuse me a moment?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-9"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content> You came.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-10"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>It means so much to me, darling.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-11"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>She was worried you wouldn’t make it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Break a leg, Mother.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-13"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>We have a schedule to keep. Curtain in 2 minutes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-14"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>I can’t get this bow straight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Allow me, allow me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-16"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content> Ah… maybe I should have Alexis do it. I mean, how many bows have you tied in your lifetime?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I only tie my shoes every day, if you remember. You taught me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-18"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Ah, ah. True.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The bow. The bow was tied incorrectly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-20"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Well, I told you we should have had Alexis do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Not you bow. The other bow. The bow on her costume. We arrested the wrong man.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>CHARLOTTE</speaker><content>What? I don’t understand. So you’re saying Darren didn’t do it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, he’s guilty of blackmail, but that’s as far as it goes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>CHARLOTTE</speaker><content>So what if the killer’s still out there. What if he comes after me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He won’t. We have officers outside 24/7. We’ll find him, Charlotte. We just um… we need a bit of your help.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>CHARLOTTE</speaker><content>Of course. Whatever I can do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, we think that the key to finding the real killer is through understanding exactly what happened the night of Owen’s death. Can you answer a few questions?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>CHARLOTTE</speaker><content>Yeah, I mean, I guess so, though I’m pretty sure I told you everything I know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well last time we spoke, you said that everyone was in Amy’s car?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-9"><speaker>CHARLOTTE</speaker><content>Right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And who was driving?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-11"><speaker>CHARLOTTE</speaker><content>She was. Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, we did a little bit of checking. The day after Owen died Amy brought her car to a body shop. She had a broken grill and a dented bumper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Any idea how she got those dents?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Charlotte, what really happened that night? Did Owen try to get back into the car? Maybe Amy panicked? Accidentally hitting him as she drove away?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Charlotte.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-16"><speaker>CHARLOTTE</speaker><content>I begged Amy to go back. Kristina and I both did, we begged her, but she just kept driving. She didn’t mean to hurt him. It was just an accident.  That’s the truth. That’s what really happened.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Is it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Take a look at how the bows are tied on the victim’s costumes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-19"><speaker>CHARLOTTE</speaker><content>What about them?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well the killer tied these bows after the victims were drugged. See how they look? How the loops are pleasingly horizontal?  Now, look at the bow on your Sleeping Beauty outfit. See how the loops are vertical? That’s a little weird. I mean, if the killer tied all three bows, why would yours be different?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>It’s because you tied all three bows. This one is different because you tied it on yourself, behind your back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-22"><speaker>CHARLOTTE</speaker><content>No. I was attacked. I’m a victim.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-23"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yet your doctor said you received half the dose of oxy that the other girls got. A nonlethal dose.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>How soon after we pulled up outside of your building did you give yourself that shot?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-25"><speaker>CHARLOTTE</speaker><content>This is crazy. Why would I fake an attack on myself?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-26"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So no one would suspect you of silencing the only two witnesses to your crime.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-27"><speaker>CHARLOTTE</speaker><content>What are you talking about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-28"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>At the time, Kristina and Amy were willing to bury your secret, but then this photo showed up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-29"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I mean, how long could you expect them to keep the secret? Especially since you were at fault.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-30"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>All you could think about was the scandal. Jail. How it would ruin your life. All because Kristina and Amy knew the truth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-31"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Charlotte, you were behind the wheel in Amy’s car. It was you that hit and killed Owen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-32"><speaker>CHARLOTTE</speaker><content>No, Amy was driving. I told you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-33"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Then why did you pay for the car repairs?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-34"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We have the receipt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-35"><speaker>CHARLOTTE</speaker><content> You don’t know what happened that night. You can’t prove that I hit Owen and you can’t prove that I killed Amy or Kristina.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-36"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yes I can. Your firm handled the reverse mortgage of an old woman named Jamie Isaacson. She paid closing costs with her credit card. That’s the same credit card that you used to pay for all three costumes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-37"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Charlotte Boyd, you are under arrest for the murders of Amy Morgan, Kristina Curtis, and the wrongful death of Owen Thomas.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-38"><speaker>CHARLOTTE</speaker><content>The bows? Seriously?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>She’s actually the perfect fairytale villain. Like the Big Bad Wolf she disguised herself as innocent, but like Snow White’s Evil Stepmother she was willing to do anything, even kill, to protect her image.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>After all these years maybe Owen’s family can have some closure about his death.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, but at what cost? Two women are dead, Darren’s still being charged with blackmail, and I’m sure his marriage is over.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And that’s why we need fairytales in the face of too much reality to remind us that happy endings are still possible.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Ah … see you in the morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Later. Speaking of fairy tales, my mother is ready to give her encore performance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Time to go back into the woods?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Still got your gun?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>It was the opportunity of a lifetime. The chance to originate the Wicked Witch on Broadway. But it would mean being away from home 6 nights a week, 2 matinees … huh. What was I to do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Realize that none of it ever happened.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Francis Bacon once wrote, “He who hath children hath given hostages to fortune.” Well, if I was a hostage, then my son Richard was my captor, my enslaver.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hey, I’m right here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>I turned down the role. Turned my back on fortune. And it was the best career move I ever made, for an even greater role came my way. A part, perhaps the greatest role that I have ever played.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-6"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>That of mother.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s sweet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You’re right, that is sweet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-9"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Shhh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-11"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Now, if Richard had only been able to embrace the role of son with the same level of commitment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And into the woods we go.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>