<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>


<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>NURSE ONE</speaker><content>God, her face.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>NURSE TWO</speaker><content>What happened to her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>NURSE ONE</speaker><content>I’ve got a pulse. She’s still alive. Get a gurney.  Now!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>RICHARD CASTLE</speaker><content>Where’d it go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>MARTHA RODGERS</speaker><content>Where’d what go, darling?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>My leftovers from Le Cirque. They were right here where this hole in the fridge is. I was going to use that Chateaubriand for my morning scramble.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Well, I certainly didn’t eat them. I wouldn’t look this good if I was pigging out on leftovers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yes well, this isn’t the first time this has happened. Food has been going missing for the past month. It’s not just leftovers, either. It was the peanut butter, uh … artichokes, a whole quart of Mulligatawny soup, gone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Well, maybe you’ve been sleep eating … again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Again? I’ve never sleep ated - sleep ate - eaten.  Have I?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>ALEXIS CASTLE</speaker><content>Hey, I’m off to class.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hey. How did you like that Chateaubriand? Wasn’t that a wonderful white wine reduction?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>What Chateaubriand?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>All right. It’s the housekeeper. I knew it. She has been putting on weight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Sorry, darling. She hasn’t been here for three days.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Maybe there are tiny borrowers living under the floorboards who come out at night to steal your food.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Not realistic. They’re too small to get the fridge door open.  No, but something is going on here. And I’m going to find out what.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>KATE BECKETT</speaker><content>So some food disappeared, Castle. What’s the big deal?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It wasn’t you, was it? I know you hate to go grocery shopping.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Seriously, Castle? I haven’t been to your place since Tuesday.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ugh. Right. Maybe my apartment’s being invaded by some kind of super rat. Whatever’s going on, I’ve taken bold steps to ensure it never happens again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>JAVIER ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yo. These two nurses saw some guy do a dump and drive around 4AM. The trauma unit tried to save our vic but she didn’t make it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>If he’s our killer, why take her to the ER?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Maybe he had a guilty conscience. Did the nurses get a good look at the driver?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No, but they did see his car. It was a blue sedan. Hospital security’s trying to get me footage to get the license plate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay. Set up a canvass around the hospital. We need to find someone that got a good look at the driver. And where’s our vic?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Her body’s still in the trauma bay. Word is she was pretty messed up.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>SIDNEY PERLMUTTER</speaker><content>Let me caution you. This is not for the faint of heart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>For once I agree with you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> What did this to her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>PERLMUTTER</speaker><content>Could be anything from a crowbar to a box cutter. But they look like claw marks. I just can’t tell what kind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>If it was an animal wouldn’t there be bite marks?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>PERLMUTTER</speaker><content>I might not find them until I do a complete exam to determine the cause of death.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Given that we don’t have a crime scene, is there any indication of where she was attacked?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>PERLMUTTER</speaker><content>No, but I can tell you one thing. Based on the inflammation, I’d say the victim sustained her injuries 5 to 6 hours before she died.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>While we figure out who she is we’ll find out how she wound up this way.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>KEVIN RYAN</speaker><content>Name is Anne Cardinal, 27 years old. She was Native American, she grew up on the Onondaga reservation in central New York.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Any next of kin?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>No, she had no siblings and both her parents are gone. She lived in off campus housing at Hudson University where she was working towards a Ph.D in evolutionary biology.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>All right, send CSU to her apartment. Talk to friends and neighbors to see if they know of anyone in her life who drove a blue sedan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And who wanted to mangle her face.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I may have an explanation for those facial wounds. Turns out our victim worked at a retirement home called Haven House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Vicious blood thirsty old folks? Is that your theory?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>This home is not for people, Castle. It’s a primate sanctuary. Mostly for apes and chimpanzees and monkeys who have retired from the movie business.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I always wanted a pet monkey when I was a kid. Big Curious George fan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, wait ‘til George grows up. An adult chimpanzee can reach 200 pounds, tear off a man’s face, hands, and naughty bits.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>All right, we’re going to go to the primate sanctuary. If Anne was attacked there, maybe someone dumped her body to cover it up. And call me if you get anything on that sedan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>George would never do that!</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>PAUL DEVLIN</speaker><content>This is a terrible loss. Anne was a brilliant student and a lovely person.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Given her wounds, I need to ask. How much interaction did Anne have with the primates here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>PAUL</speaker><content>Well, very little in terms of direct contact. But we have very strict training guidelines for all of our employees.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Still, I’ll need the crime scene unit to do a thorough investigation of this investigation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>PAUL</speaker><content>Of course. Anything I can do to help.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>PAUL</speaker><content>I can’t imagine she was harmed by any of our animals. They’ve never shown any aggressive behavior toward her or anyone else.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Now, Dr. Devlin, how well did you know Anne Cardinal?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>PAUL</speaker><content>I was her faculty advisor at Hudson University. And when I found out she was taking time off a couple of months ago, I offered her a job here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And what sort of work did she do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>PAUL</speaker><content>Well, I have a grant to study the social behavior of primates, and I hire Hudson students like her and Franco here to help manage the animals’ care.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And none of them have homicidal impulses? Not even Moonshine here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>PAUL</speaker><content> Especially not Moonshine. He’s been around people his whole life. And he’s very social.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And when was the last time either of you saw Anne?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>FRANCO</speaker><content>We were together yesterday. She seemed totally fine. She did leave early. That wasn’t like her. Said she had something important to do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Did she say what it was?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>PAUL</speaker><content>It might have something to do with that argument she had.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What argument?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-18"><speaker>PAUL</speaker><content>I saw her in the parking garage around lunchtime talking to a man. I’d never seen him before, but he seemed very angry with her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you think you could describe him to a sketch artist?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-20"><speaker>PAUL</speaker><content>Yeah, I most definitely could.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, I know who the killer is. Did you see how that gorilla looked at me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, I think it was lust, actually, Castle. You are ruggedly handsome.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Blood lust, maybe. Don’t let Moonshine fool you. I’m betting he and his fellow  retirees are actually super intelligent apes plotting to take over New York City. They’re going to round up all the people, put us in a sanctuary.  Most likely Anne got on to them –  – they took her out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Now if this monkey cabal really wanted to get Anne out of the picture, why did they drop her off at the hospital?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, obviously they were conflicted. It’s a complicated relationship between man and primate.  Didn’t you see Rise of the Planet of the Apes? Cautionary tale.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Sorry to burst your bubble, Castle, but CSU hasn’t found a crime scene at Haven House. Anne wasn’t attacked there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well then, where was the attack? And by what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hey. So uh, a witness saw a blue sedan take out a side mirror about a block away from our hospital, and they got a plate. The owner of the car was Eddie Maslon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>How is he connected to Anne?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I’m not really sure, but Eddie knows how to put the hurt on people. He just did eight years in Sing Sing for murder two. And he had a way to mess up Anne’s face. City records show he had a pit bull named Badass.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>A convicted killer with an attack dog? All right. Pick him up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Right on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Damnit. I really liked Moonshine for this.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>EDDIE MASLON</speaker><content>I’ve never seen her before.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You dumped her outside of the ER last night, except she looked more like this.  Your dog do that to her?  Eddie, you’ve been out of prison for three months. You better start talking unless you want to go back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>EDDIE</speaker><content>Okay, look. I didn’t touch her. And neither did Badass. Whatever did that to her, that wasn’t no dog.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Then how’d she end up in your car?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>EDDIE</speaker><content>I was leaving a bar last night and I happened to make a wrong turn down an alleyway. And I saw her lying there. She was all messed up. I couldn’t just leave her there to die.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh, so you’re a good Samaritan now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>EDDIE</speaker><content>If I wanted to kill her then why would I bring her to a hospital?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>If you wanted to save her why would you ditch her outside of one?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>EDDIE</speaker><content>Because with my record I knew I’d get blamed, which is exactly what’s happening now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>EDDIE</speaker><content>No good deed, huh?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, fine. Then why don’t you tell me where you supposedly found her?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, that’s blood. Maybe Eddie was telling the truth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Beckett? You need to see this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What the - ?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Footprints. Giant footprints made by some kind of beast.  Those vicious claw marks? Savage wounds. Her blood. These footprints.  It all adds up to one thing. She was killed by Bigfoot.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Seriously, Beckett? Do you have any idea what this means? We are about to be the first people in the nation - no, the world – to solve a Bigfoot murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Very funny, Castle. But there is no such thing as Bigfoot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Tell that to the people who’ve been sighting him for 400 years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>PERLMUTTER</speaker><content>So I typed the blood. It’s a match to our victim.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Never mind the blood. What is your opinion on these?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>PERLMUTTER</speaker><content>Professionally I can’t speculate what those are, Mr. Castle, but personally I can say that anyone who believes in Bigfoot is an ass.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, that is a common assertion amongst the uninformed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, buddy. Let’s say there is a Bigfoot. How does a giant hairy ape man get around the city unseen?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Easy. Follow the big, fat footprints.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Subway access tunnel. Since Hurricane Sandy a lot of those are still closed, so Bigfoot’s been using them to get around.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, that’s ridiculous.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>How can you say – look at these footprints.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>These are the footprints I’m interested in. They’re near where the body was. CSU said that they were made within the last 24 hours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Could be Eddie Maslon’s.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>A size 13? The guy’s too short to have feet this big. No, these boot prints are our best lead. These prints. Not the tracks from the giant clown feet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yes, let’s go to a crime scene and ignore the evidence.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You’re saying someone framed Bigfoot?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Al I’m saying, Castle, is that someone, a human being, left the Bigfoot prints in that alleyway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, and staged the crime scene to make it look as though Bigfoot was the killer. Why go through the trouble of blaming Bigfoot, a creature select few of us even believe exists, never mind could be a murder suspect.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Speaking of suspects, Anne’s boss came through with a sketch of the guy she argued with the day she died.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Take a look, Castle. A person of interest. Emphasis on the word ‘person’.  Talk to Anne’s friends and family and see if anyone recognizes him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Um, I wouldn’t rule out Bigfoot just yet. Turns out there have been dozens of reported Bigfoot sightings in the city in the past couple months.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Is that right? Why, Detective Ryan, tell us about this new and extraordinary development.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Like this woman in Brooklyn. She says that Bigfoot tried to break into her apartment – on the second floor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Gentlemen! I hate to rain on your parade –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Do you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No. But here’s the reason that Bigfoot reports have spiked.  Two months ago a TV show, Mission: Monster, put out a million dollar reward for the capture and/or proof that Bigfoot exists.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> See, Castle? All of this evidence that you claim proves Bigfoot’s existence is actually people angling for money.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So you’re saying it’s just a coincidence that Anne was working with primates and was mysteriously killed where Bigfoot prints were found?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, not a coincidence. Just a hoax.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>If it’s such a hoax then tell me why I found this.  I dug through her phone records. Turns out, the last phone call she ever made was to Darrell Meeks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The Darrell Meeks?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-17"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Just a world-reknowned cryptozoologist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s a scientist who searches for as yet undiscovered creatures.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Such as unicorns and centaurs?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-20"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Banshees and leprechauns?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-21"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Doctor Meeks happens to be the foremost authority on Bigfoot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And lo and behold, she called him on the very day that she died. Still think Bigfoot has nothing to do with this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Perlmutter’s got something for us.  Why don’t you guys head over there? Castle and I’ll talk to the world’s foremost authority on Bigfoot.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>PERLMUTTER</speaker><content>Oh. The B team.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Talk about the B team.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>PERLMUTTER</speaker><content>I’d hoped to see Castle’s look of dismay when I told him cause of death was nothing more exotic than blunt force trauma to the cranium.  It seems she was clobbered over the head with a club or a pipe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You could have said so over the phone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>PERLMUTTER</speaker><content>Ah, but I also made two highly intriguing discoveries.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>About the wounds on her face?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>PERLMUTTER</speaker><content>Well… their cause is still undetermined. But a far greater interest is that –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Because they could be claw marks.  Bigfoot has claws.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So does Wolverine. Is he real?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>PERLMUTTER</speaker><content>Are you done?  I found this glass embedded in her head wound. It has an anti-reflective coating, like on prescription glasses.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>But she didn’t wear glasses. So where did it come from?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>PERLMUTTER</speaker><content>All I can tell you is that it was practically hammered into her skull by whatever hit her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>We’ll send it in for analysis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-16"><speaker>PERLMUTTER</speaker><content>Yeah well, you should take this while you’re at it.  I found that in her stomach.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-17"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>A pendant? In her stomach?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-18"><speaker>PERLMUTTER</speaker><content>It appears she swallowed it 5 to 6 hours before she died.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-19"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>The same time she was attacked.  Why would she swallow it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-20"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Maybe she knew she was going to die. She was trying to send a message.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-21"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Or she was trying to keep this pendant from her killer.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Did you take this photo?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>DARRELL MEEKS</speaker><content>Yes, it’s an expedition I led in western Canada. It’s the closest I’ve ever gotten to him in 23 years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Dr. Meeks, you were the last person that Anne spoke with just before she died. Why did she call you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>DARRELL</speaker><content>Yes, I – I think she called me to ask if I thought if Bigfoot would venture into an urban area.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And what did you tell her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>DARRELL</speaker><content>Well, given development and urban encroachment on wilderness, sooner or later it was inevitable. And I suspect that she had evidence of the presence of Bigfoot here in the city.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I don’t understand why she would talk to you about something like that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>DARRELL</speaker><content>Well, Anne was studying evolutionary biology. She was an honors student at the university. But she was actually a hugely respected Bigfoot expert.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>DARRELL</speaker><content>She even gave me that extremely rare Yeti finger.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Are you saying Anne was a Bigfoot hunter?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>DARRELL</speaker><content>No, no, no.  No, not a hunter, no. Uh, Anne was Native American. And uh, in her tribe’s culture a Bigfoot was considered benevolent or a protector. When she was a child she actually saw a Bigfoot and so after that after that she devoted her life to their study.  Excuse me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So are Bigfoots – uh, Bigfeet – uh, violent or aggressive?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-13"><speaker>DARRELL</speaker><content>Well, they certainly can be. What were the nature of her injuries?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Uh –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-15"><speaker>DARRELL</speaker><content>Well, I mean, was she attacked by a Bigfoot?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Not a chance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-18"><speaker>DARRELL</speaker><content>Well, in the name of science, would you allow me to examine where she died?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No. Now, as far as you’re aware, did she have issues with anyone? Other than Bigfoot?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-20"><speaker>DARRELL</speaker><content>Uh, well, she was under a very high level of scrutiny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Scrutiny from whom?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-22"><speaker>GARLAND MEEKS</speaker><content>Oh, some TV show offered a million dollar reward, which unleashed a tide of idiots all searching for Bigfoot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-23"><speaker>DARRELL</speaker><content>Yes, and this is my wife Garland. Uh, she’s the skeptical one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-24"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Trust me, I feel your pain.  Pleasure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-25"><speaker>DARRELL</speaker><content>On the case, I think when people found out Anne’s area of expertise, they wanted to follow her to see if she would actually take them to a real Bigfoot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-26"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know, the day that she died Anne was seen arguing with this man.  Do you recognize him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-27"><speaker>GARLAND</speaker><content>Oh, yes. All too well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-28"><speaker>DARRELL</speaker><content>This man is the Bigfoot community’s worst enemy.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>His name is Chase Diggins and he’s an Australian adventurer and big game hunter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Kind of Crocodile Dundee meets Indiana Jones meets Ted Nugent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Now according to the Meeks, he’s violent and highly unstable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What’s more is that this guy is hell bent on bagging a Bigfoot. I found him on Youtube bragging about how he was going to mount one on his wall.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do we have anything other than speculation on a mythical ape man that will connect him to the murder?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>We have this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Diggins has a prosthetic hook for a hand?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Says he lost it in a Bigfoot attack and he almost –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>However it happened -  - that hook could have been what did a number on Anne’s face.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Where’s Chase Diggins now?</content></utterance>
</scene>


<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>This guy is an international adventurer. What the hell is he doing renting an industrial craphole like this? Why not a hotel?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>The guy hunts Bigfoot. I don’t think that rational behavior is something he’s familiar with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Whoa. Did you hear that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Dude, there’s something down there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Chase Diggins! NYPD! If you’re down here you better identify yourself right now!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Dude, I’ve got a bad feeling about this thing, man. I – I don’t think that we should –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>CHASE DIGGINS</speaker><content>You gents looking for me?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Bloody shame about Anne. She was one hell of a tracker. Actually, the only reason I cane to the city. Word was, she knew the whereabouts of an actual ‘squatch and I figured she might lead me to him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You came to New York to hunt Bigfoot?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>You see this, Detective? Nepal, 2008. Rocky crags for the Himalayas. ‘squatch came out of nowhere and ripped my arm clean off. So I will hunt down every last one of those bastards until I have my payback.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What did it look like?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>500 pounds of fur and death, mate. Eyes like a rabid dog, but smart. Anyway, they say that she found one. Everyone knew it, but Anne wasn’t talking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Is that why you went to see her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Who told you that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Witnesses saw you and Anne arguing outside of her work yesterday.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Merely a polite conversation between colleagues.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Really? ‘cause later that night she turned up dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-11"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content> You’re squatting in the wrong bush, Detective. I was at a target range last night with my mates. Keeping my aim sharp. You can check it out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s funny, ‘cause we found a bootprint in an alleyway near Anne’s blood with the same tread as the boots you’re wearing now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-13"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>All right, look. I was in that alley. But not last night. It was the night before.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What were you doing there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-15"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Well, I figured she was tracking the beast, so I tracked her. I followed her to the alley and that’s when I caught the wily b*tch in the act.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The act of what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-17"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Stamping fake ‘squatch prints in the ground is what. Using molds of giant feet. She was faking the damn evidence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh – whoa – hang on. Anne was a respected researcher. Why would she fake evidence of Bigfoot?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-19"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Because I reckon she found the real thing. She was trying to throw the rest of us off the scent, but I was on to her so I confronted her at work. Offered her anything she wanted, but she told me to bugger off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know what I think? You faked that site because somewhere in your twisted mind it makes sense that the expert on Bigfoot would be killed by one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-21"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>I knew it. She found him. Little b*itch found my Bigfoot.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Look, he’s either crazy or he’s lying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I’d go with crazy, because it looks like he’s telling the truth. Tests on his prosthetic hook show no trace of Anne’s DNA. And his alibi checks out, so it’s not him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, it looks like we’re back to this guy as our number one suspect.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, could you please take that down?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You got it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>The lab also was able to identify the glass shards we found in our victim’s head wound. It’s from a camera lens.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>There was no camera at the crime scene.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Maybe our killer took it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Which would explain why there’re so few photos of Bigfoot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I meant our human killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Let’s recanvass near that alleyway. See if we can find that camera.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-13"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey, so I looked into that pendant Anne swallowed and I found something strange.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-15"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I talked to her friends and neighbors. The pendant wasn’t Anne’s. It belonged to Justine Bolton, Anne’s roommate at Hudson University last year.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Does the roommate have any idea what Anne was doing with it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-17"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Ah … I’d love to ask her. There’s only one problem. Justine was murdered a year ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And a year later her pendant is found in her murdered friend’s stomach?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That can’t be a coincidence . What do we know about Justine’s murder?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-20"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I ordered up her case files. They should be here by morning.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Look, Castle, I don’t care how much research you do, you’re not going to convince me that there’s a Bigfoot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I just follow the evidence and the insanely large footprints.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Is there anything that you don’t believe in?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Sure there is. There’s … um …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay, well, what about you? If not Bigfoot or zombies or ghosts, what do you believe in?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I just – I believe in the everyday magic of life. I mean, things that I can see and touch, like um … the green shoots that pop through the snow in February or the Flatiron building or the way that I feel when I hear Coltrane. It’s –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No, I can appreciate the everyday, but why not live in the possible? The world just doesn’t have as many mysteries anymore. There’s no new continents to explore. There’s no more deepest, darkest Africa. Everything’s all mapped out by satellites and sonar, yet still people reach for the unknown. It’s what makes us grow. Coltrane wouldn’t have had that saxophone if Antoine Sax hadn’t imagined it. Isn’t that what separates us from uh, say, Moonshine?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well you know, there is one –  – inexplicable, mysterious phenomenon that I do believe in still.  Us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What was that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Something set off my trap!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You set a trap?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I got you now, you super rat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No one steals from me!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Alexis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What are you doing here?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, she’s still not taking my calls.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, can you blame her, Castle? You practically turned her into a Smurf.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Na’vi would be a more contemporary reference. No, the point is, she lied to me. She looked me right in the eye and she blamed the Borrowers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I’m sure she had a good reason.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>For what? Not having food? I mean, I give her a sizable allowance and if that’s not enough, she can always ask for more.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Like I said, Castle. There are plenty of mysteries in the everyday.  Hey, Ryan? Has Justine Bolton’s murder file come in yet?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Ah, she was attacked in the apartment that she shared with Anne Cardinal. The way she was choked and bruised looked like it was a crime of passion.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Did they have a suspect?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Unfortunately he fled. And he hasn’t been seen since the murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Any chance he had long shaggy hair and he was 8 feet tall?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Uh, no. Sorry, Castle. It was Justine’s boyfriend, Kurt Wilson.  He was the one that supposedly found the body. He was a football player with a history of assaults on and off the field. It looked like Justine was trying to get away from him. One the day that she was murdered she contacted the dean and told him that she was dropping out of school even though she was top of her class. By the time the cops realized that all roads led to Kurt Wilson, he disappeared.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>How does Anne figure into this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-13"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, as her roommate it looks like Anne took Justine’s death pretty hard. When I spoke to the lead detective he told me she came to him a few months back and asked to Justine’s case file. He refused since it’s a pending murder case, but still it means –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Anne was looking into Justine’s murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And a few months ago, that’s when Anne took time off school.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So then maybe Anne wasn’t tracking down Bigfoot. She was looking for Kurt Wilson.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-17"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Maybe she found him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-18"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yo. Canvass didn’t turn up Anne’s camera, but the lab came back with a serial number on that lens. Now it was made for a specific model – a wifi enabled camcorder that’s designed to sync up to a cloud account. I checked; Anne has a cloud account.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Can we access it?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>ANNE</speaker><content>Testing … one, two, three.  Okay, good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Look at the time stamp.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>12:20AM. The night she died.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, but she’s not in an alley. Where the hell is she?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>ANNE</speaker><content>He’s after me! He’s after me!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So the attack took place in the woods, not that alley. But what we need to find out is where these woods are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Tech is trying to get the geodata off that footage to see if we can pinpoint the exact coordinates.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>If she was attacked in the woods somewhere why move her to an alley?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Because the killer was trying to throw us off his trail. If Anne was looking for Kurt Wilson then the last thing he would want to do is leave her body near the same spot where he was hiding out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Unless she as looking for someone else in those woods.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Something with fur?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What do we really see of our killer in this video? He’s dark, looming, powerful. Holding a primitive weapon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, that is a person.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>All I see is the silhouette of a hulking humanoid form. Of Darrell Meeks and that one-armed Ozzie were right and Anne did know where Bigfoot was, well that could be him on that video.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Then what, Bigfoot carried her body into the city on foot from wherever these woods are and left her in that alleyway?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well you said yourself, Kurt Wilson wouldn’t want to leave Anne’s body where he’d been hiding out. Why would Bigfoot?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay. Why don’t you circulate Kurt’s photo to Anne’s family and friends and see if anyone has seen him around. Castle and I will talk to tech to see if we can figure out where these woods are.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>FRANCO</speaker><content>I don’t know. Maybe. If you rough him up a little he could be that homeless guy I saw hanging out in the parking garage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>When was that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>FRANCO</speaker><content>Last week sometime.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>What was he doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>FRANCO</speaker><content>Nothing, man. He just looked like he was waiting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> Well, we’re going to need security cam footage of the garage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>FRANCO</speaker><content>It’s run by a separate company. I’ll get you their number.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>If Wilson knew that Anne was after him he might have been following her. Preparing to kill her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I’ll set up a canvass and pull traffic cam footage from that area. Maybe we can get a hit on where he went after he left that garage.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>ANNE</speaker><content>Testing … one, two, three.  Okay, good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>TECH</speaker><content>The camera started syncing to her account right when she started filming. We couldn’t pull any geodata, but the sync was routed through her cell phone. It pinged off this cell tower here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Are they any woods near that tower?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>TECH</speaker><content>Yes, in a 10,000 acre nature preserve called Branch Cross.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s a perfect hangout for Bigfoot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Or a fugitive.  Now is there any way to narrow down where she was when this was being filmed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>TECH</speaker><content>Not as much as I’d like, but I checked with the forest service. The species of tree in the video grow mostly in this 6 square mile are.  Also between the moon’s position in the sky and the orientation of the shadows I can tell you that she was moving in a south easterly direction.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Wow. She’s good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Uh… could you turn up the volume on the video?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you guys hear that in the background?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-11"><speaker>ANNE</speaker><content>He’s after me. Oh God.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you think you could isolate that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That sounds like water. Are there any streams or rivers nearby?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-14"><speaker>TECH</speaker><content>Right there. She must have been near that creek, which gets us down to a 2 square mile area.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, the good news is we have our crime scene. The bad news is it’s in 2 square miles of remote wilderness with no access by road.  You up for a hike?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh I’m well equipped for a hike.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Knocking on wood and vocalizing. It’s how Bigfoot communicates over long distances and how the real Bigfoot hunters lure him out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah well, the real police don’t do it so our human fugitive won’t know that we’re coming.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, trust me. Kurt Wilson has been hiding out here for a year. We are not gonna find him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, we’re close. GPS is showing that this is the general area of the attack. We just need to find some landmarks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>It happened by this downed tree, so all we’ve gotta do is find the tree and we’ve found our crime scene.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle! Castle, please. No more Wookie calls.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s not Wookie. I’m not doing Wookie. I can’t do Wookie. Alexis does a really cute Wookie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, whatever you’re doing could you stop?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Are you scared it might work?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, I’m scared that I might murder you and then I’ll have two crime scenes on my hands.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You know, a lot of highly respected individuals believe in Bigfoot. Teddy Roosevelt wrote about him in his journals. Jane Goodall has gone on record saying that she’s open to the possibility.  And right now, as we speak, professors at Oxford are studying Bigfoot DNA samples. No, it is possible. You just have to be open to it.  Because at any moment life can surprise you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ugh, that is not good for my knee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Yeah.  Where are we?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s some kind of trap.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Which we’ve got to get out of. Castle, do you have anything in your vest that can help us?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh yeah, heck, I’ve got a guppie multitool, I’ve got a solar powered hand fan, got camo glasses, built in compass, snake bite kit –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So nothing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well not nothing. I can build a fire.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>All right, Castle. I can pull myself out if you can boost me up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well then how am I going to get out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I have a rope in the car. I was going to hike back and get it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You’re going to leave me here alone?  ‘kay, whoa, just hold on a second. Let’s just back up and think about this. What is</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Something Castle? You think that Bigfoot came out here with a shovel?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No, you’re probably right. I don’t think Bigfoot built this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, some hunters or poachers probably dug it up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hunting what? Look at the size of this thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Maybe our fugitive built it in case anyone came out here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I was more comfortable with the idea of Bigfoot building it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>C’mon, Castle. Why don’t you pop a squat? We’ll pull a cheerleader move.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Will you be wearing a short skirt for this? That’s the rule.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You know, this pit is kind of crudely built. Some primates have been known to – make – they have been known to use tools to trap prey –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Could you stand still? Holy –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Now!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-25"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, I’m just saying I don’t want to end up as Bigfoot dinner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-26"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know, Castle. There is a bit of poetic justice in this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-27"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Poetic justice how?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-28"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, I mean, think about it. You set a trap for Alexis and now someone – or something – has set one for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-29"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Promise me you’ll come back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-30"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>In case I don’t make it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-31"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh … that’s cute. But seriously, hurry back!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-32"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>‘kay?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What’s that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Nothing. What do you got?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Grab your coat. We got a hit on that photo of Kurt Wilson. One of Anne’s neighbors just saw him go into her apartment.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey, Wilson. NYPD.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Woohoohoo. Not much of a running back there, Wilson. But then, you’re out of training.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>All right. Let’s go.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>We got him. And he’s not talking. What do you want us to do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, check his clothes for Anne’s blood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>How’re you guys doing on the crime scene?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Uh … we ran into a little snag. But when we find it hopefully we find evidence that leads us straight to Kurt Wilson and we won’t need him to talk.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ah, spork. They all laughed at you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Stupid –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Beckett? Thank God you are back. What took you so long?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ha ha ha ha ha. Okay, get me out of here now.  Beckett? Ka –</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Help!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Help!  Help.  Please … don’t eat me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Police! Turn around!  Put your hands up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Beckett, what are you doing? Are you crazy? He can’t understand you!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Now!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Whoa! Shoot it! Shoot it! What are you waiting for?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Whoa, whoa, whoa. It’s talking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-8"><speaker>DARRELL</speaker><content>Don’t shoot! Don’t shoot! Don’t shoot! Please don’t shoot!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Don’t shoot him.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well this is a huge disappointment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>DARRELL</speaker><content>No, this is a big misunderstanding!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Is it? Because those claws could have easily caused Anne’s injuries.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>DARRELL</speaker><content>What? I would never hurt Anne.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you expect us to believe that with you dressed up in this … getup … right in the same area she was attacked?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>DARRELL</speaker><content>Wait, she was attacked here? I – I – I thought she was attacked in the city.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-8"><speaker>DARRELL</speaker><content>O – o – okay, okay.  This looks bad. Let – let me just try and explain, okay? I knew that Anne was coming out here on her own and – and I – I admit that I followed her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-10"><speaker>DARRELL</speaker><content>Because I think she found Bigfoot!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Or maybe she just found an idiot dressed up as Bigfoot then killed her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-12"><speaker>DARRELL</speaker><content>No! I didn’t hurt Anne!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh, okay. So you just stalked her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-14"><speaker>DARRELL</speaker><content>Look, I just – I just wanted – just this once – to lay eyes on this elusive beast. And – and that’s why I – I built this man trap and – and I’m in this suit, drenched in deer musk –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Is that what that is? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-16"><speaker>DARRELL</speaker><content>Yeah, it’s an attractant. It lures them out. And it’s working, too! I mean, about an hour ago I – I heard vocalizations and knocking on wood. And those are – are classic Bigfoot mating calls.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-17"><speaker>DARRELL</speaker><content>And I found some half-eaten food and some scat. And not to mention a tool that Bigfoot used to club his prey. And there was blood on it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Wait a minute. You saw a bloody club?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-19"><speaker>DARRELL</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Show us where you found it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you recognize this? That’s Anne Cardinal’s blood. We’re checking your clothes for it, too, along with the dirt that is going to place you in the woods.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>KURT WILSON</speaker><content>You’re just like those other cops. You’d rather make your case than see the truth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Then what is the truth, Kurt?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-4"><speaker>KURT</speaker><content>I was living out in those woods. But Anne wasn’t trying to hunt me down. She came out there to help me, to bring me food and supplies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why would Anne help the man that murdered her roommate?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-6"><speaker>KURT</speaker><content>A few months ago I came out of hiding to find Anne. I told her that I was innocent, that I didn’t kill Justine, and I begged her to look into the case. And she agreed to because she believed me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah well, I’m a little more skeptical.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I can vouch for that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You have a history of violence, Kurt. And it’s pretty clear that Justine dropped out and tried to break up with you so you killed her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-10"><speaker>KURT</speaker><content>Justine did not drop out to get away from me. She and I were in love. When she told me she was quitting Hudson, I decided to go, too. The two of use were planning on transferring to another school. We had even toured the campus at SUNY Binghamton the week before. And I’m sure they have a record of that somewhere.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>If you weren’t the reason why Justine left Hudson, then what was?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-12"><speaker>KURT</speaker><content>She never told me. She just said that things weren’t working out. And I’ve spent a lot of time thinking about that. And the only thing that makes sense is if there was someone there that she was afraid of.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Like who?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-14"><speaker>KURT</speaker><content>A classmate. A professor. I don’t know. But I think Anne found out. Last week when I came to see her at her work she said she was close to having answers. And the next thing I know, she’s dead. So I figure whoever did it killed Justine, too. And that’s why – why I broke into her apartment. I was looking for … I don’t know. Clues, answers … anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The person that you think killed Anne and Justine, do you have any idea who it is?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-16"><speaker>KURT</speaker><content>It had to be someone that could talk Justine into opening her door. You know, someone that she knew. That’s the only reason they would steal her necklace. It wasn’t worth anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You wouldn’t be referring to a lapis pendant, would you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-18"><speaker>KURT</speaker><content>Justine never took it off. When I found her, that pendant was gone. Whoever killed her took it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Kurt, is this Justine’s pendant?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s why Anne had it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The pendant is proof. She found the real killer. It has to be someone she spent time with recently. Someone she got close to.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Professor Devlin?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>PAUL DEVLIN</speaker><content>Can I help you with something, Detective?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>As a matter of fact, you can. What can you tell us about Justine Bolton?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-4"><speaker>PAUL</speaker><content>She was a student at Hudson who died rather tragically.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well you knew her as more than that.  She took your introduction to anthropology class her freshman year.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-6"><speaker>PAUL</speaker><content>Yes she did. Which made her loss a personal one. But I fail to see what that –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Were you aware that after she took that course she told her counselor that she was afraid because of someone on campus. She never said who. But someone was obsessed with her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-8"><speaker>PAUL</speaker><content>Well no doubt she was talking about her boyfriend. The young man who killed her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ah, but she took the meeting with her counselor before she met her boyfriend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>But she had met you. You’ve had an odd career, Professor.  You taught at four schools in six years so I made a few inqueries and there were intimations of stalking, sexual harassment, and even worse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-11"><speaker>PAUL</speaker><content>All of which were false! And let me point out, no action was ever taken against me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Justine had scheduled a meeting with the dean on the day that she was killed to explain why she was leaving.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You couldn’t let her take that meeting. If she did your dirty history would be exposed. You’d be finished. So you killed her. And being the predator that you are, you took a souvenir. Her pendant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>With all the suspicion on Kurt Wilson no one was looking at you. Until Anne came along.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-15"><speaker>PAUL</speaker><content>I don’t know what you’re talking about.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Anne found that pendant. She knew it was you. And when she went into the woods, you followed her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-17"><speaker>PAUL</speaker><content>What woods? I wasn’t in any woods.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We checked your phone records. Your cell pinged the same tower as Anne’s did around the time that she was attacked. That places you at the crime scene. We also found a club with Anne’s blood on it and someone else’s DNA. And based on the look you’re giving me right now, I’m pretty damn sure it’s yours.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="34"><utterance uid="34-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So Castle, are you disappointed that there’s no Bigfoot after all?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well I’m not so sure there isn’t. I’m thinking maybe he’s out there somewhere. And if he is, I’m hoping to see him one day. Preferably from a safe distance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-3"><speaker>KURT</speaker><content>Thank you. For finishing what Anne started. Because of you guys, Justine’s killer will pay for what he did to her and I’m a free man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So what’s next for you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-5"><speaker>KURT</speaker><content>I’m going to continue Anne’s work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You’re going to research Bigfoot? Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-7"><speaker>KURT</speaker><content> Well when she suggested I hide out in those woods she said I’d have company out there.  She was right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Did you hear that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mmhmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I gotta go get my outfit.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="35"><utterance uid="35-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ooh. Hey. You um, you still got a little – on your  –  I’m – I’m so sorry about that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-2"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Do you know how humiliating that was?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I swear, I had no idea it was you. But Alexis, why were you stealing food?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-4"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Because I ran out of money.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>How could you have possibly spent all your money? Unless … wait, no …are you … are you in some kind of trouble?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-6"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>I didn’t spend it. I gave it away. Invested it, really.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Invested in what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-8"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>My friend Jonah at school has a crowdfunding campaign to plant bamboo forests on the roofs of skyscrapers to help clean the air.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, why didn’t you just come to me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-10"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Because I didn’t want the speach.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I don’t – what speech?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-12"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>That people like us need to be careful with the kind of money we have. People might try to take advantage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, that speech. Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-14"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Dad, you believe in all these unbelievable things, like Bigfoot.  And I don’t judge. But I believe in people, in that that can accomplish. I believe in Jonah and his vision and I wanted to support him. I think he could make a real difference in the world. And okay, maybe it was stupid to give him all of my allowance, but I’m not the first person to do something stupid for something they believe in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No. No, you’re not. Matter of fact, it’s a bit of a family trait.  But … you do owe me a Chateaubriand, so let’s go to Le Cirque.  And then call this Jonah guy. Have him meet us. I’d like to hear about how he’s going to change the world.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-16"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content> Really?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I believe in people, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-18"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>And Borrowers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And Bigfoot.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>