<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>REPORTER</speaker><content>Regina, your new album Fatal Impact drops next week. What can you tell us about it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>REGINA CANE</speaker><content>It’s about love, heartbreak, and revenge. It’s my best album yet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>REPORTER</speaker><content>Oh my God, it’s Josie Lang!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>REGINA</speaker><content>What the hell is Josie Lang doing at my release party?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>PUBLICIST</speaker><content>Her album’s out next week, too. Having both of you here gets us more press.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>REGINA</speaker><content>More press for who? Me or her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>JOSIE</speaker><content>Regina! Thank you for the invite. You know, you’re the reason I’m a pop star. I’ve been a fan ever since I was in grade school.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>KATE BECKETT</speaker><content>That is ridiculous. I do not lose a turn.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>RICHARD CASTLE</speaker><content>Are you kidding? No, that’s the rules. You absolutely lose your turn. Ask him. Esposito!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>JAVIER ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Ask me what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>In a relationship, if you choose a movie and you choose very, very poorly, do you lose your turn?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>How poorly?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Valentine’s Day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You should lose two turns.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, I’m just saying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Those are the rules.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Those are the rules.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s ridiculous.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So, the body was found in this dumpster over here by a homeless dude that was looking for cans. It was wrapped up in this tarp.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Cause?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>LANIE PARISH</speaker><content>GSWs. Near as I can tell, she was shot at close range. Minimal blood seepage and lack of spatter in the area suggest she was killed elsewhere then dumped here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So someone was hoping she’d catch a ride with the morning haul. Disappear into some landfill.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Any idea who she is?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>KEVIN RYAN</speaker><content>Well, according to her ID her name is Holly Rhodes. But her business card has her listed as DJ Beat. Called the number and her booking agent said she was DJ’ing an album launch party in SoHo last night for pop star Regina Cane.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What? Oh, dude … you remember that music video where she was dressed up as a sexy little Girl Scout? I don’t care what those cookies cost, I would sell my left –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Anyway, she was booked at the party until 1AM.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>1AM?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah, why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>I’m placing the time of death between 11 and midnight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So whatever happened, happened at that party.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>This ink looks fresh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>It’s an unlisted number. I got a call in to the phone company.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>All right, you guys set up a canvass for anyone who saw the body dump. Castle and I’ll head down to SoHo, see what happened last night.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh-kay. Good morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Killer party.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, it looks like Regina went all out to promote her new album.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I remember when Alexis used to play her big hit "Call Me Crazy" over and over again. Drove me crazy. Of course, it was no Valentine’s Day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Excuse me, NYPD. Where’s the host?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Forget the host, where’s your pants?  Am I right?  No, I’ve been there. Check by the pool.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>REGINA KING</speaker><content>Wait, you’re NY what now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>PD. As in … a detective. We’re here about Holly Rhodes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>REGINA</speaker><content> Who’s Holly Rhodes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>DJ Beat? She was your DJ for your party.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>REGINA</speaker><content>Oh. That skank. That b*itch almost ruined my entire party. When I left to get ready for my performance she was supposed to stay and get the crowd pumped. Instead, the music stopped and she was gone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>REGINA</speaker><content>She didn’t even come back to get her equipment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So you’re saying that she left early?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>REGINA</speaker><content>Yeah. Around 11 after jacking in a playlist. I didn’t pay for a playlist. If you see her, tell her I want my money back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That might be a little tough, seeing as she’s dead. She was killed just after leaving your party.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>REGINA</speaker><content>Great. Now I feel bad for complaining.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Did you notice any unusual behavior? Was she having problems with any of your other guests?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>REGINA</speaker><content>No. But then again, I was busy making my rounds.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Right. Well, I’ll need a guest list along with the names of everyone that was working … last … night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>REGINA</speaker><content>No problem. I’ll have my publicist send it right over.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>So I spoke with several of the other party guests and they confirm Regina’s story. Apparently Holly just suddenly left.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>In the middle of her set? Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, we answer that, we’ll find out why she was killed. Anyone see where she went?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>No, and there’s no security cameras. I’m seeing if I can pull tape from the businesses across the street.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Did you get ahold of next of kin?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>No, she doesn’t have any.  Holly was an only child. Bounced around foster care until she was 18.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That can’t have been an easy childhood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Probably why her hobbies as a teenager include burglary and shoplifting. Then she graduated to grand-theft.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Anything more recent?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Not in the last 7 years. She must have cleaned up her act when she got serious about being a DJ. Oh, and get this. The uniforms canvassing Holly’s apartment building found a neighbor who saw a man pounding on Holly’s door a few days ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What was it about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Neighbor said he screamed ‘you won’t get away with this’. Either Holly wasn’t home or she wouldn’t answer the door and eventually the guy took off. Neighbor’s with a sketch artist as we speak.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yo. I got a hit on that phone number written on Holly’s hand. It belongs to a Tyrese Wilton. Apparently he’s some big time record producer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> He’s on the guest list. He was at the party.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You guys see what he knows. Castle, Lanie knows where our victim was killed.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>I noticed it when I was cutting her out of her clothes. Stains on her outfit. The lab identified it as peanut oil with high concentrations of MSG.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Meaning … what? She was eating Chinese food and spilled some on herself?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Except  I checked the contents of her stomach. No Chinese. And they weren’t serving any at the party, either. So I checked with CSU. They said there was no trace of it in the dumpster, but it’s all over the tarp, meaning …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She may have been killed at or near a Chinese restaurant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Narrowing it down to every single block in Manhattan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Uh … what about the gun?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>The slug is from a .380 but there were no ballistic hits in the system. Oh, and when CSU processed the tarp and the clothes they also found these.  Synthetic fibers. They didn’t come from the dumpster either, but the lab is still running tests. I’ll keep you posted.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>If Tyrese is such big time, why is the entrance to his studio in an alley?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Because. Celebrities don’t want paparazzi taking their picture all the time.  Yo. Did you just do the hair thing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>What hair thing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Every time you’re about to meet a celebrity or a pretty girl you run your hand through your hair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> TMZ said that Tyrese was at that party with Josie Lang. He’s producing her new album.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah well, she’s no Regina.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I understand the image of her as a girl scout is seared into your memory, but Josie is a real vocalist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Whose fan base consists of 12 year old girls … and you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>TYRESE WILTON</speaker><content>Stand by.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>JOSIE LANG</speaker><content>Hey Ty, you want me to take that from the second bar?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>TYRESE</speaker><content>Sorry Jo, we’ve got to take 15.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey, since Josie was at the party I should probably take her statement, right? You got this, right bro? Thanks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>TYRESE</speaker><content>Sorry, this is such a crazy thing. I can’t believe she’s dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>How well did you know Holly, Tyrese?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>TYRESE</speaker><content>I met her for the first time at the party. I was there with Josie because we had been working on her album and I used to produce Regina back in the day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Can you tell me why we found your phone number written on the victim’s hand?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>TYRESE</speaker><content>What, that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Mmhmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>TYRESE</speaker><content>I gave her my digits so we could set up a meeting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>About what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>TYRESE</speaker><content>If there’s one thing I’m good at, it’s spotting talent. Her mashups and beat match were better than most of the guys droppin’ albums today. I was blown away. I told her I wanted to take her to the next level.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So how did she react to that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>TYRESE</speaker><content>She was thrilled. Said a break like this is what she’d been working for. She was supposed to call me today.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You have any idea why she rushed out of that party early?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>TYRESE</speaker><content>No. Could’ve had something to do with that fight, though.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What fight?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-19"><speaker>TYRESE</speaker><content>You heard of MC Thug?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-20"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>MC Thug? Yeah, the rapper. He’s been shot, like, 7 times, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-21"><speaker>TYRESE</speaker><content>That’s the one. Now on Holly’s first break, he walked up to her booth, starts talking to her real low and angry. I could see she was getting upset, trying to push him away. But he grabbed her wrist and said ‘next time, it’s gonna end different’. Then he saw me coming and bounced. I was going to talk to her about it, but you know, I got caught up with some folks.  Next thing I knew, she was gone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-22"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>This MC Thug. You see him at the party anymore after Holly left?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-23"><speaker>TYRESE</speaker><content>No. In fact, I didn’t see him the rest of the night.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>So if you could just make it out to Jenny and Kev.  It’s short for Kevin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hey. Fanboy. Let’s go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Thank you, so much. She’s going to die when she sees this. Thank you! Nice to meet you!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>MC Thug.  AKA Darius Carson. His rap sheet includes assault with a deadly weapon and attempted murder. And that was just at this year’s hip hop music awards.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>How did Holly wind up in the sights of a guy like that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, whatever was going on between them started way before that party. The guy that was pounding on Holly’s door, threatening her? The sketch came in from the neighbor. Look familiar?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Darius Carson.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>DARIUS CARSON</speaker><content>No one calls me Darius unless you my momma. And by the looks of that body, you ain’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah well, I’m sure your momma’s so proud.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>CARSON</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So, Darius. According to Regina Cane’s party planner you weren’t on the original guest list until you made a last minute phone call to get in the party.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>CARSON</speaker><content>I’m a fan of her music. That a crime?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No, but murder is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>CARSON</speaker><content>I know you ain’t a cop with that fancy shirt and poufy hair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He might not be, but I am. Are you sure you went to the party to see Regina?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>CARSON</speaker><content>Yeah, I’m real sure. Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We know you visited DJ Beat’s apartment before the party. We know that you fought with her that night, and then she turned up dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>CARSON</speaker><content>I had nothing to do with that mess.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, but you had something to do with her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>CARSON</speaker><content>Damn straight. I wanted my girl’s bracelet back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Who had your girl’s bracelet?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-16"><speaker>CARSON</speaker><content>I threw a party at my crib last week. I hired DJ Beat to spin. The next day, my girl Dakota realized her diamond bracelet is missing. Now that b*itch and the little b*itch of an assistant are the only ones there that I couldn’t vouch for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The b*tch had an assistant b*tch?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-18"><speaker>CARSON</speaker><content>Yeah, the little punk that works for her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So you tracked her down to the party and when she ran you followed her and you killed her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-20"><speaker>CARSON</speaker><content>No, I told her she had a day to cough it up. Or else.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Or else what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-22"><speaker>CARSON</speaker><content> Or else is usually enough.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Where were you between 11 and midnight?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-24"><speaker>CARSON</speaker><content>Upstairs.  With my girl.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-25"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Dakota.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-26"><speaker>CARSON</speaker><content>Different girl. Kaya.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-27"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>All right, I’m going to have to hold you while we look in to that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-28"><speaker>CARSON</speaker><content>Good. That helps my street cred. You guys are going to do a mug shot, right? ‘cause I brought my lighting guy with me.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Thanks.  Hey guys. So Kaya confirms she was “hanging out” with MC Thug in one of the bedrooms ‘til 12:30.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>And he did file a police report about the missing bracelet, so I requested a list of all the parties that Holly worked in the past year. Of the more than 50 events, turns out that thefts were reported in 7 of them. The MO was the same every time. Mostly high-end jewelry. In total, almost half a million bucks.  All from parties at upscale residences. And I also confirmed with Holly’s booking agent that she always worked with an assistant. Paul Travers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mmkay, so the of them were a crew using her DJ skills to access high-end homes and then cleaning them out along the way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>She does have a history of theft, so maybe she went back to her old ways.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>But if the assistant were at the party with her, where is he and why hasn’t he come forward?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>There’s only one reason. He was involved.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>PAUL TRAVERS</speaker><content>Involved in what? My friend is dead and now you’re saying, what, that we were like Bonnie and Clyde?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Paul, thefts were reported at seven of the parties that you both worked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>PAUL</speaker><content>Oh, and because of her history it’s gotta be her? Music saved her. She was done with that life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And what about you? According to Holly’s agency, you were responsible for setting up and breaking down the equipment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>PAUL</speaker><content> So?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So you never broke it down last night. You left the party and never came back, same as Holly, only you’re still alive and she’s dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>PAUL</speaker><content>Last night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mmhmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>PAUL</speaker><content>I wasn’t even there last night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Paul, don’t lie. She’s got you listed on her invoice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-11"><speaker>PAUL</speaker><content>Yeah, I – I know. A few times this past year she’d call me up last minute to say she was using another guy. It was like her cousin or something and he needed the work. I know she felt back about it because she still offered to pay me anyway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-12"><speaker>PAUL</speaker><content>I was at a birthday dinner yesterday night. I have witnesses.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Which of these parties did the other guy work?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-14"><speaker>PAUL</speaker><content>This one, this one, here -  – this one, this one, this one, and … that one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The same ones that reported robberies.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>So far only one witness, a caterer, remembers seeing a guy setting up Holly’s equipment last night. And she only saw him from behind and he was wearing a hoodie, so we reached out to other party guests, see if we can get a better description.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So was anything stolen from the party last night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>No. We asked everyone and so far no one’s reported anything missing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yo. So unis searched Holly’s apartment again. There’s no sign of the stolen goods. And there’s no influx of cash into her account, so if she was making money off this thing, there’s no evidence of it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What if this mystery assistant is the one behind it all? I mean, think about it. He forces Holly to get him into these parties. While she’s busy spinning, he’s free to walk around these fancy apartments. And since he’s hired help, nobody pays him extra attention. It’s candy from a baby.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>But when MC Thug confronted Holly, she got scared. So she threatened to blow the whistle on the assistant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, that would certainly give him motive for murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>But with Paul’s name on the invoice, there’s no record of him. How’re are we going to find him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He helped set up that equipment last night, right? His fingerprints would be on it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Get CSU on it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ooh, grunt work. I’ll come back later.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So long as you leave the coffee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What did you find?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Holly’s phone records. She received calls from a payphone in Washington Heights the same days she was booked for the parties where the thefts happened.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, maybe it’s her mystery assistant calling for details.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Holly grew up in the Heights so it might be someone from the old neighborhood, but it doesn’t bring us any closer to finding him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Doesn’t need to.  CSU matched a print on that equipment to one Joey Malone, street name Monster. He’s got a list of priors a mile long. Unis took him down in Washington Heights. He’s in the box. Go take a look.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Monster. Now that sounds like the kind of ganged up thug that would shoot you dead and leave you in a dumpster someplace. Probably half man, half mountain, full of prison tats. Or is he quietly dangerous? Like Javier Bardem in any movie where he’s got weird hair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Just … take a look for yourself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Behold. Monster.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>More like Cookie Monster.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So what do we know about this kid?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, he’s not related to Holly, for one. His father died of a drug overdose when he was seven. His mom committed suicide a couple of years ago. His uncle, Martin Decker, is the one who took over guardianship.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Where’s his uncle now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>He’s not at home. I notified social services thinking they might know how to reach him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You said he had priors?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, he was busted for breaking and entering, burglary, resisting arrest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Now he’s moved up to the big leagues.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So, uh, what’s the plan here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I’m gonna go in alone, so he doesn’t feel outnumbered. See what he’s made of.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He’s 14. It’s hard to believe he’s capable of something like this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Not in his world it isn’t.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hi Joey, I’m Detective Kate Beckett.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>JOEY MALONE</speaker><content>A major hottie is what you are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Okay, now that we got that cleared up, I need to ask you a few questions .</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>You need permission from my guardian. The last time I checked, I’m a minor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, we’re making our best effort to get ahold of your uncle. In the meantime, NYPD policy allows me to talk to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>So talk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We’re looking into the murder of Holly Rhodes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content> Heard about that. Real sad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I understand that two nights ago you worked for her. Did you see her having problems with anyone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you know why she left the party early?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-12"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Nope.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you know where she went?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-14"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>No clue.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, let me ask you this. Why do you think Holly hired a 14 year old kid with a record to be her tech assistant?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-16"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>‘cause I’m the best.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The best at what? Stealing?  Every time you’ve worked for Holly, high-end jewelry has gone missing. Every single time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-18"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>I don’t know nothing about that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Did Holly know about the stealing or did she find out that night? Is that why you killed her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-20"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>What – what, kill her? No. No. I didn’t do that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We have witnesses that saw you leave the party right after she did and you never came back for the equipment. So where were you between 11 and midnight?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-22"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>I was at – I was at TV King.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You left the party and equipment to go to TV King in the middle of the night? You’re going to have to do better than that, Joey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-24"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content> You may be allowed to talk to me, but I don’t have to talk back.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Robbery and murder? Maybe Monster wasn’t such a bad nickname after all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know what? I’m not so sure about that. He expected the conversation about the stealing, but when I accused him of murdering Holly that threw him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>And I think I know why. Joey’s alibi checks out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Seriously? He was at TV King?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>The assistant manager sometimes lets him play video games up on the big screen. And that’s where Joey was during Holly’s time of death.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well then, if he didn’t kill Holly then who did?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>The brains behind this operation, that’s who. A kid like Joey goes from smash and grab to stealing a half a mil in jewelry? I don’t think so. Someone put him up to this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>No, it makes sense. Some savvy criminals use minors to do their dirty work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Of course. A Fagin to Joey’s Oliver Twist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>And if Holly’s involved, that makes her the Artful Dodger. Or the Artful DJ.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ooh, nicely played.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And that would explain why we never found the stolen loot in Holly or Joey’s apartments. Fagin has it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-13"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>That gives him motive to get rid of Holly if she ever gave him any trouble.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, if we’re right, Joey knows who our killer is.  I get this kid. Let me get a crack at him.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Hey, where’s the super hot detective?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Oh, you’re lookin’ at him.  Don’t laugh. I was featured in the NYPD calendar.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Bet that was a big seller.  So uh, you must be the good cop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, I don’t know about that. But I could be your ticket out of this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Yeah? How’s that work?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>We know you didn’t kill Holly. All you did was lift a bunch of jewelry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Man, I didn’t –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Just save it. We don’t care about the jewelry. We can take those charges off the table. All we want is the guy who put you up to it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content> I don’t even know who you’re talking about.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Joey, c’mon. I just gave you the winning lottery ticket. Now the right move here is to cash that in, not tear it up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>I bet this is the part where you tell me I don’t know the seriousness of my situation. How unless I tell you everything that I know you can’t help me. And then you’ll lean in close like you care about me, like you’re my friend. And you’ll make promises you’ll never keep.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I keep all my promises, bro.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-13"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>That’s what everybody says.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>This is a limited time offer, Joey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-15"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content> Not interested.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-16"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Okay.  I want you to take a look at this. This is how Holly ended up. Shot. Tossed in the garbage. Do you think she deserved that? Hum?  Oh, what? No smartass comeback now? You work with this woman. You knew her. The same guy that has you stealing jewelry did this to Holly. He uses kids like you. And then he just gets to walk away while you have to sit in here and answer all my questions. You know what you are to him right now? You’re a loose end.  So take a hard look. Because this is your future. This is you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-17"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>You’re wrong. He won’t hurt me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-18"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>He won’t. Not once we stop him. All I need is his name, Joey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-19"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>I still don’t know who you’re talking about.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, we think that the thefts were someone else’s idea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Do you know of anyone in his life that might have drawn him into this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What about his uncle? Where is he now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Guy sounds like a real prize.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We were hoping not it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Whoa, whoa, whoa. He’s not safe out there in the world right now. The guy that we’re after killed a woman. He could do the same thing to Joey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I - I can’t just throw him in juvie. I’m trying to gain his trust here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ms. Cooper, this boy is the key to us solving a murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What if I take him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>That way he’s not locked up and I can keep him safe.  And I can continue to work on him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What about that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>That’s cool. I got this. The kid doesn’t have a father. He probably just needs someone to connect with.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>I’d rather have a pajama party with the lady cop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah well, it looks like I drew the short straw. Literally.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Man, no wonder you’re single! No woman would spend time here unless it was against her will.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah? What about you, Martha Stewart? What’s you place supposed to be? Shabby chic? Emphasis on shabby?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>It’s a dive. But it’s not my fault. My uncle would rather blow all of his money at the tables.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Must be why he’s too busy to call us back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Don’t wait by the phone. He only cares about claiming me as a dependent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>My parents split up when I was 5.  Man, get your feet off my table.  Dad moved to Florida with his new wife. Most I ever got after that was a phone call and a post card.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Post card?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content> Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>How old are you, anyway?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Ancient. But I’m young enough to remember what it was like.  Must miss your folks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-13"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>After my dad died, my mom kept going. You know, she tried to pretend that we were still a normal family. She did her best to take care of me until … she couldn’t do it anymore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Now you take care of yourself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-15"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Yeah.  Look, man. I know you didn’t have to do this. Take me in, I mean. So uh, thanks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-16"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Im’ma go grab you a blanket. Pillow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-17"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Hey, at least you didn’t skimp out on the audio visual budget.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-18"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You know that’s right. Oh, and I’ve got Assassin’s Creed 3. So go ahead and knock yourself out. Oh, and uh … put it on dual player mode so I can come back and school you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-19"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>$20 bucks says you won’t make it past level 1.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-20"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content> You’re crazy.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Sit down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Okay. Care to explain?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What? The handcuffs?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>No, no. The stylish shoes that you’re wearing. Yes, the handcuffs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, junior here tried to pull a Houdini on me last night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Who the hell is Houdini?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content> Shut up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Out the window?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Down the fire escape?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah. And then on to a moving garbage truck. Then on a skateboard for five blocks that took him all the way to the L-train.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> How’d you keep up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-13"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>He didn’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Shut up. What the –  Give me that.  Commandeered this dude’s bicycle. Then he lost me in the subway.  But then I caught him. At the next stop. Kid’s wily. But I’m wilier.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-15"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Wow. Just like The French Connection. In the meantime, CSU was able to ID those fibers found on the tarp that holly’s body was wrapped in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-16"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Where’re they from?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-17"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Germany. Based on the chemical composition and color, they’re fibers from carpeting used by a high-end European car manufacturer to line their vehicle’s trunks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-18"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Mmm. Now we know how Holly’s body ended up at the construction site.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-19"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>CSU narrowed it down to a model 2010 to 2012 X-5. I’ll canvass around the construction site, see if anyone saw a car like that hanging around the dumpster.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So we pulled Joey’s juvie files from the central clerk’s office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Theory being, whoever he’s involved with might be in there somewhere. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-22"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Unless he gave you a name.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-23"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Uh … no. Not exactly.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Look, we find out who Joey got mixed up with, we find our killer. There’s gotta be something in these files that points to him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Looks like he got his first taste with a B and E when he was 11 years old.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He graduated to burglary when he was 12 when he broke into a mom and pop corner store along with an unidentified adult male.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Maybe he’s the one we’re looking for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No, we’re not looking for someone he was busted with. This guy’s smart enough to stay above it all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Check this out. Two months ago someone named Shane Winters bailed him out after he was picked up on a shoplifting charge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Shane Winters? I remember that name.  When Holly Rhodes, our victim was 17, she was busted on a grand theft charge and check out who posted bail.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Shane Winters.  That’s our guy.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Shane Winters.  Trafficking, grand theft, assault with a deadly weapon, extortion. This dude’s dabbled in everything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So when Holly was a troubled teen she must have worked with Shane just like Joey is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>But then she cleaned herself up, got out of the life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>When he figured out what kind of access she had at the parties, he pulled her back in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, that explains why Holly had to hire Joey as an assistant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Just ran Shane Winters. Guess was he drives. 2010 X-5.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>That would have the carpet fibers we found on the tarp.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, and a roomy trunk for all your body moving needs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We gotta bring him in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>We tried to. Unis busted in on his last known address. He’s not there.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>So what are you? Officer Babysitter?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>You get paid extra for doing that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Where’s Shane Winters?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Where’s my soda?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>LT.  You figure you’re special to him, don’t you? Well, you’re not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Man, you don’t get it. I’m not giving him up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You know how much time keeping your mouth shut will buy you with Shane? Huh? As long as it takes him to pull his gun and shoot you with it. And then he’s just going to move on to the next lost kid. Don’t let it end that way, Joey. Just tell me where I can find him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>I’m not a rat.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Any luck?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Eh, I just want to wring this little bastard’s neck right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I call that a no.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So we’ve got a BOLO out on Shane and his car.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Freakin’ kids, man.  I don’t know how you do it, bro.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ooh. No, no. I lucked out with Alexis. At a certain point you realize you’re just dealing with someone who hasn’t been around as long as we have. They have to find their way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>The problem is, he’s already found his way. He just doesn’t see where it’s going to put him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey. No luck on the BOLO, but I talked to Garcia in robbery. We got a tip on Shane’s location. Wanna roll?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You know what? Let me get this one.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>BARTENDER</speaker><content>Hey sugar. What’s your poison?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>BARTENDER</speaker><content>Hello? What’re you drinking?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>BODYGUARD</speaker><content>Mr. Winters is not taking any meetings today.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Can I just get a bag of ice, please?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>BARTENDER</speaker><content>What the hell do you want with a bag of ice?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>It’s for him.  Excuse me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>SHANE WINTERS</speaker><content>You must be Detective Esposito. Joey told me you two had been hanging out. Said sooner or later you’d find your way down here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So he warned you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-9"><speaker>WINTERS</speaker><content>No, he’s a good kid. Dependable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Put ‘em on.  Or better yet, resist arrest. Please.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-11"><speaker>WINTERS</speaker><content> Some other time maybe.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Do you know a woman named Holly Rhodes, Shane?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>WINTERS</speaker><content>Name sounds familiar.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, it should. You ran with her back in the day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>WINTERS</speaker><content>Oh, she ran. But not with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Why did you bail her out when she was a teenager?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>WINTERS</speaker><content>Oh, I got a soft spot for kids, man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah, yeah. You’re just like a regular Mr. Rogers.  When was the last time you saw her, Shane?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-8"><speaker>WINTERS</speaker><content>Ah … last time I saw Holly.  Don’t recall.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, let me help you out with that. It’s three nights ago. When you killed her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-10"><speaker>WINTERS</speaker><content> You’re wrong about that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Mmm, I don’t think so. See, when this whole DJ’ing gig of Holly’s took off, wealthy clients, penthouses, you saw a golden, diamond encrusted opportunity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And that’s when you pressured Holly into bringing in Joey Malone as an assistant. He’d go into these fancy parties and he’d walk right out the front door with half a million in high-end jewelry. And your hands would stay clean.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-13"><speaker>WINTERS</speaker><content>You are right about that part, at least.  My hands are clean.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>But then something went wrong at the last party.  I mean, maybe Holly pushed back. Or maybe she wanted you out of her life once and for all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-15"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>But she knew too much, so she had to go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-16"><speaker>WINTERS</speaker><content>Look, all I hear you guys saying is a whole lotta stuff that you can’t prove.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-17"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, we can prove that her body was in your trunk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-18"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Fibers that stuck to the tarp that Holly was wrapped in match your X-5.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-19"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>We’re impounding it right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-20"><speaker>WINTERS</speaker><content>Well then, I guess you guys didn’t hear about it. About the little problem I had with my vehicle this morning. You see, I got a little careless. I was uh, lighting a cigarette and the next thing I know the whole car catches on fire. Inside, outside, the carpet. Whole thing burned to a crisp. I hate to tell you, but there’s probably not a fiber left to match.  Crazy how things happen sometimes, huh? So again, whole lotta noise that you can’t prove. That being said, I’d like my lawyer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-21"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content> I need a minute alone.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You tipped off Shane.  After you bolted last night. You called him. Warned him that he was a suspect. Which gave him a change to torch his car. Cover up his role in Holly’s death. Congratulations, Joey. You helped him get away with murder.  Now I’d beat your skinny little ass for being stupid if it’d change anything. But it won’t because, well, you’re so loyal. Now, let’s see how Shane returns the favor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>WINTERS</speaker><content>I can see that you’re a little slow, but I just said I want my lawyer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>This is about the thefts. Somebody’s going to go down for them, and we know it’s going to be Joey Malone. The DA wants to try him as an adult. That means hard time. All you gotta do is man up. Man up about the thefts. Then maybe I can talk to the DA, get Joey a deal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>WINTERS</speaker><content>Look, man. The kid did the crime, he’s gotta do the time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Have you seen enough? You still want to protect him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-6"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Look, it was like you said. I go in with Holly, lift pricey jewelry. The more the better. But this time it was different.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-8"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Shane told me that my mark was this music producer. Tyrese –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Tyrese Wilton.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-10"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Yeah, yeah. It was weird. I was supposed to boost his cell phone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content> Why his cell phone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-12"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>I don’t know. But I took it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah? And then what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-14"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Somehow Holly found out. And she flipped. She got in my face and told me to give the phone back. And I got scared because I knew she carried heat, but I had already handed the phone off to Shane. So I – I got out of there and … that was the last time I saw her. I didn’t know she would end up dead. I didn’t know Shane would kill her.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So no doubt a guy like Shane would kill her, but it’s starting to look like he didn’t. He’s got an alibi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I don’t believe it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Affidavits from six bar patrons all stating that Shane was there between 11 and midnight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, he practically runs the place, so the patrons will say what he tells them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So CSU just confirmed that his car was too burned for them to match the fibers or pull forensics, so we can’t even prove that he transported the vic’s body.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>We also can’t tie the murder weapon to him, either. According to her assistant Paul, Holly used to carry around a .380 pistol for protection. She might have been killed with her own gun.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Here’s something that doesn’t add up. Tyrese Wilton’s phone. Why would Shane tell Joey to steal a phone worth a couple hundred bucks? Especially when there had to be so much bling at that party.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Dude, nobody says bling anymore. Try shine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Here’s something else that doesn’t add up. All the guests were contacted and asked if they were missing any personal items. They all said no. So –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why didn’t Tyrese Wilton mention that his phone was gone?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yo. Check this out. It’s Yang Dynasty.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>That could explain the peanut oil on Holly’s clothes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>There’s blood spatter on the wall.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Looks like we found our crime scene.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yep. And it’s right at Tyrese’s doorstep.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>TYRESE</speaker><content>Are you saying that Holly was killed right outside my studio?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>That’s right. So why don’t you tell us what she was doing here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>TYRESE</speaker><content>How the hell should I know?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hum. Then maybe you can tell us what you were doing between 11 and midnight the night of the party.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-5"><speaker>TYRESE</speaker><content>I was at the party. I stayed there until just after 1. You can check.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You were also asked if any of your stuff went missing the night of the party. You didn’t mention your phone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-7"><speaker>TYRESE</speaker><content>Because my phone wasn’t missing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You don’t have to lie to me, Tyrese. I talked to the kid who stole it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-9"><speaker>TYRESE</speaker><content>I mean, it was missing for an hour or two, but then it turned up.  See? I found it in the bathroom at the end of the night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>If Joey stole the phone how did it end up back at the party?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Whoever brought that back didn’t want it missed. Based on Shane’s MO, he was after something valuable, something he could sell. Yo Tyrese, what’s on that phone? Financial info, pictures, valuable data?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-12"><speaker>TYRESE</speaker><content> Only one thing that really matters. I use this phone as an e-key.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>An e-key?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-14"><speaker>TYRESE</speaker><content>An electronic key. It opens up this studio.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-15"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, did Holly know that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-16"><speaker>TYRESE</speaker><content>Yeah, I mentioned it to her when I discovered it was gone. I went to text her my number, but I had to write it on her hand instead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-17"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>That’s why Holly was here. She realized that Shane stole the phone because he was going to rip the studio off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-18"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>She couldn’t let that happen, not with Tyrese here about to give her her big break.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-19"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Right, so she races over here to confront Shane to stop him before he ripped you off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-20"><speaker>TYRESE</speaker><content>Looks like she did, because nothing’s missing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-21"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You sure?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-22"><speaker>TYRESE</speaker><content>Positive. I’ve got over two mil in equipment here and nothing –  Oh, God.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-23"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-24"><speaker>TYRESE</speaker><content>The recordings. If someone got their hands on an unreleased album …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-25"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>It’d be worth a fortune.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-26"><speaker>TYRESE</speaker><content>Not to mention tanking our record sales if it leaked online.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-27"><speaker>TYRESE</speaker><content>Oh no. Josie Lang’s album was accessed at 11:45 the night of the party. Someone downloaded the masters.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-28"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Shane.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-29"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="34"><utterance uid="34-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Look, I’m telling you. Shane’s alibi is rock solid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>How is that even possible?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We interviewed everyone in the bar. We even talked to the cabbies outside. And everyone said that he left around midnight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Why would he torch his car if he didn’t dump her body?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He might have dumped her body, but our timeline says that he did not kill her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Wait a minute. We gotta be missing something here. So let’s just go over it again. We know that Joey handed Shane that phone around 11. And we know that Josie’s album was downloaded at 11:45. Holly was murdered sometime between 11 and midnight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Wait a minute. The key to this whole thing is that phone. We’re assuming that Shane was the one that used it to break into the studio.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Because he’s the one that Joey gave the phone to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Right. But witnesses place him at the bar at 11:30 to midnight. The album was downloaded at the studio at 11:45. It had to be someone else.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Like who?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> We’ll, it’d have to be someone from the party.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So then whoever broke into the studio must have returned the phone to the party so that Tyrese wouldn’t realize that it was even taken.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>All we have to do is figure out which one of the guests had something to gain from stealing Josie’s album.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="35"><utterance uid="35-1"><speaker>DANCE INSTRUCTOR</speaker><content>Five, sex, seven, eight. Rock one, two, three, four. Step. Nice. Good. Point again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-2"><speaker>REGINA</speaker><content>Hi. Did you guys not get the guest list that we sent over?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah.  We – we did. We just need to ask you a few questions about your schedule the night of the party.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-4"><speaker>REGINA</speaker><content>Yeah, sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So according to your party planner you excused yourself at 11 to do a costume change for a performance of a track from your new album, is that correct?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-6"><speaker>REGINA</speaker><content>That sounds about right. But I just go where they tell me to. You know how it is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Only your planner told us that you insisted on having a full hour.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-8"><speaker>REGINA</speaker><content>Have you ever tried changing into skin-tight leather pants? It’s time consuming.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-9"><speaker>REGINA</speaker><content>Why? What’s the point?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, that hour gave you enough time to get to Tyrese Wilton’s studio, download Josie’s new album, and get back to the party to perform your song.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-11"><speaker>REGINA</speaker><content>Are you insane? Why would I do anything like that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Because your album sales have been sagging for years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>If your album didn’t perform, your record label was going to drop you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-14"><speaker>REGINA</speaker><content>I’ve been with Harmony 360 for ten years. They love me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>It’s no secret that Josie Lang’s eclipsed you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-16"><speaker>REGINA</speaker><content>Oh please. She’s been around for 2 seconds. Give it a year. You won’t even remember her name.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It doesn’t matter. Both your albums come out next week and she’s going to crush you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Unless someone mysteriously leaks Josie’s new album online.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Your plan was simple. Hire Shane to steal the phone, that way you can get into the studio.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The one thing that you didn’t plan on was Holly. She showed up and caught you just as you were leaving the studio.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And you couldn’t risk her exposing you. You fought, she pulled out her gun to protect herself, but you managed to use it on her instead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-22"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So you called Shane and you got him to get rid of the body.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-23"><speaker>REGINA</speaker><content>Are you kidding me? That’s all speculation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The one thing that’s not speculation is that you hired DJ Beat.  How did you find out about her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-25"><speaker>REGINA</speaker><content>Word of mouth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-26"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>More like your bodyguard grew up with Shane Winters. Shane had you hired DJ Beat so that Joey could get in and steal that phone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-27"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You know what else isn’t speculation? The warrant she served on your ISP.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-28"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That warrant revealed the email account that you created to communicate with the hacker that was going to leak Josie’s album online. Is that enough fact for you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-29"><speaker>REGINA</speaker><content> My record sales may be down, but I can still afford a damn good lawyer.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="36"><utterance uid="36-1"><speaker>WINTERS</speaker><content> You keep showing up here like this, the boys are going to think you’re sweet on me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content> Not anymore they won’t. Huh. You are walking on grand larceny and accessory after the fact. Wow. Now, that kind of luck does not last long.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-3"><speaker>WINTERS</speaker><content>Well, I guess I’ve gotta go play the Powerball then tonight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>This is my gun.  And this one will be yours. You ever go near Joey, or any other kid, ever again, the story’s going to go like this. You pulled that piece on me.  And I had to defend myself. So I killed you. You understand me?  Or should we play out that story right here, right now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-5"><speaker>WINTERS</speaker><content>Um … I hear you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Good.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="37"><utterance uid="37-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yo. Reach back there and grab that file.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-2"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>What am I? Your secretary?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Just grab the file.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-4"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Haven’t I done enough to solve this case for you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Read it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-6"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Juvenile record for Javier … Esposito.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yep. The good old days.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-8"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>So assault, resisting arrest, unlawful possession –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content> Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-10"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>You were a mess.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah. But it’s all I knew. My dad was gone, my mom was working two jobs. In my neighborhood, you had to do what you had to do to survive. Not everybody made it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-12"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Is this where you tell me to man up and get my act together like you did?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No. It doesn’t work like that. You need help. For me it was one of my teachers. Saw a future in me that I didn’t even see in myself. But it was up to me to make a choice. To pick which road to go down. I talked to your school counselor –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-14"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-15"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>She’s going to call me if you keep ditching.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-16"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>C’mon, man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-17"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And I’m going to call you once a week. Check in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-18"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>All right. I’ll go. If you agree to get new furniture.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-19"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>You can’t get laid on the regular with that junk you have. I’m just looking out for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-20"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Here. If you need anything, day or night, call me at that number.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-21"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Okay.  You’re all right. For a cop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-22"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I know. Now get out of my car.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>