<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>



<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>RICHARD CASTLE</speaker><content>You’re cooking. This must be a dream. Or perhaps a nightmare.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>MARTHA RODGERS</speaker><content>I choose to take the higher ground and ignore that.  Breakfast is served.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>These are my patented, special pancakes that I make for Alexis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Well, not so special. I learned how to prepare it for her this past year.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ah. The student becomes –  – the failed student. The dropout. You fed her this?  Mother, you are forever forbidden from practicing the art of pancake dough.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content> Where did I go wrong?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Where do I begin? Alexis isn’t even here. Why are you making these?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You miss her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Oh.  Well, don’t you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yes, of course I do. But Columbia is just a cab ride away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Well, she was the center of our lives for so long and now she is just …  … gone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Right now is just Alexis’ time to make her own way in the world. But she’ll be back.  Like Simba in The Lion King. It’s the circle of life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Oh darling.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>KATE BECKETT</speaker><content>You seem to have adopted a real Zen-like attitude about this, Castle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, I realized I’ve been a little overprotective of Alexis at times.  Okay, constantly. But since she’s left for Columbia I‘ve learned to let go. You know, stop checking her video blog. I don’t ask to meet her boyfriend anymore. I’ve come to realize that like a bird, Alexis needed to leave the nest. So I let her fly. Turned around and strode away. That’s acceptance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Wait, wouldn’t acceptance be letting her go, seeing where she flies, and then being okay with it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, but I wouldn’t be okay with that. I don’t want to see where she goes. What other birds of prey are out there, or what other nests, or –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So is that acceptance or denial?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, it was acceptance ‘til you started applying your fiendish logic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>LANIE PARISH</speaker><content>How about you guys apply some fiendish logic to this. Meet Hasim Farouk, man versus van. At 1AM last night he was killed instantly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>JAVIER ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Knocked right out of his shoes at the point of impact.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So hit and run?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, that’s just the tip of the iceberg. A witness, homeless guy, said that the victim emptied his gun at the van and just stood in the middle of the street, shooting right until it hit him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Why would he do that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I don’t know, but he definitely knew his way around guns.  Jan!  This is a Sig P 220 S with a weight compensator, target sights, and custom molded grip to his hand. This was a serious shooter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What else do we know about him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>KEVIN RYAN</speaker><content>Well, Hasim Farouk is a Saudi national living here as a student.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Majoring in what? Urban warfare?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Uh, undeclared, actually. Up at Columbia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So what was he doing in lower Manhattan?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>More importantly, what is Columbia doing admitting gun toting lunatics and are there any more of them?  For the record, I’m not calling to check on Alexis. I’m just checking my email.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Acceptance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Have tech search traffic cam footage of that van and let’s look into Hasim Farouk’s life. See if he had any enemies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Looks like he had at least one. Assault charges were filed against him two days ago by one -  - Bram Stoker.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Bram Stoker, author of Dracula, died in 1912?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-23"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Uh, if it’s him I’d say he’s immortal.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Excuse me, Bram Stoker?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>BRAM STOKER</speaker><content>Yeah?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Detective Kate Beckett, NYPD.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And might I say how youthful you look.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>BRAM</speaker><content> Witty. I’ve never heard that one before.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’ve never heard of anyone named Stoker before, except Bram Stoker.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>BRAM</speaker><content>Apparently he’s a distant relative and both my parents are English scholars. They thought it’d be cute. It wasn’t.  So, what is this about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The late Hasim Farouk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>BRAM</speaker><content>The late?  He’s dead?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yes, he was murdered the day after you filed an assault charge against him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>BRAM</speaker><content> I certainly did not kill him. I filed those charges to protect myself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>From what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>BRAM</speaker><content>Hasim was a student of mine. I’m a TA for a seminar on Joyce.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What was the problem with the two of you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>BRAM</speaker><content>I didn’t think that there was one, and then three days ago he confronts me after class. Starts accusing me of being … overly familiar with some female students. Said if I didn’t stop he’d kill me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>For harassing those women?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>BRAM</speaker><content>No, I was not harassing them. I – I might flirt with students on occasion, but believe me, it was never unwelcome. Ladies are kind of digging on vampires right now and my name is Bram Stoker. For once in my life it’s working for me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Maybe Hasim was jealous. Were any of those students his girlfriend?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>BRAM</speaker><content>Uh, no. I don’t think he had a girlfriend. Or friends at all, for that matter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>‘kay, well I’m going to need a list of all the girls that you flirted with.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Look at this building. Hasim was living large for a college student.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, add that to the list of things about this dude that don’t add up. His records say he started as a freshman at 24. Now who does that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Late bloomer?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Or a sleeper cell terrorist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Think about it. Saudi national? He shot up a van with a customized Sig? I’m just saying, could be a terrorist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Whoa.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Whoa! Look at all this gear. This guy practically has his own dojo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Huh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Uh, yeah. And if his black belt skills didn’t get it done he always had this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Wow. That’s not all he’s got.  Look. Surveillance gear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Ooh. State of the art. Light years ahead of anything the department has.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah.  Who the hell is this guy?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Look, the guns could have fit with terrorism, but the wiretapping equipment?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Maybe he’s a spy. He’s got military training. Says here he was a commando in the Saudi special forces.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>But then there’s this.  $25 grand wired to him every month from a Swiss bank account. Whatever he was doing he was well funded.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What did his fellow students have to say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, I talked to most of the girls on Bram Stoker’s list and none of them noticed Hasim in class or even knew who he was. It’s like the guy was invisible.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He was hiding in plain sight. Foreign agent in deep cover on some kind of special reconnaissance mission.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So then why would he shoot up a van?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Maybe Jack Bauer was driving.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yo, Ryan’s hunting through traffic cam footage looking for that van. In the meantime, things with Hasim keep getting weirder. Tech went over that surveillance gear. It looks like he was using it to monitor an active bug installed in some apartment about a half a mile from his place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Whose apartment was it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>According to the lease, it belonged to this chick.  Sara El-Masri. I called and left a message on her cell phone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Wait a minute, Sara El-Masri was one of the students in the Joyce class. She was one of the girls on Bram Stoker’s flirt list.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What did she say about Hasim?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I couldn’t reach her. I just left a message.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey guys?  I got something here you need to see.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Unfortunately there were no traffic or security cams near the crime scene, but we did find this footage shot down the street from where Hasim was hit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>That’s definitely the van that took him out. Front end’s all crunched up. You can see the bullet holes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah, but watch this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Wait – go back to where she ran out.  Zoom in on her face.  That’s Sara El-Masri. She was abducted.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And Hasim died trying to stop it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Whoever this is, he abducted a girl and he killed our victim. So what do we know about him from the video?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well he’s a male, late 30s, no distinguishing scars or tattoos. But we sent the footage over to the FBI, see if they can run it through their facial recognition software.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Are they updated on the abduction?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yes. And they’re sending over an agent to liaise. Meanwhile, we’re checking other traffic cams. See if we can track where that van went after Sara tried to escape.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hasim was surveilling her apartment and he was nearby when she was kidnapped, but why? What was their relationship?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, Sara’s roommate’s coming in. Maybe she has an answer. There were no phone calls between them. It’s looking like more like he was stalking her. Not only did he wiretap her place, he was also taking two classes that she was in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Maybe he’s like The Conversation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I’m sorry, I don’t –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Francis Ford Coppola.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Gene Hackman. Very underrated.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Thank you. Um, in it a surveillance expert overhears a plot against the woman he’s bugging. Maybe Hasim got wind of the kidnapping, tried to thwart it, and paid with his life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ah, that still doesn’t explain the guns in his apartment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>True. Gene Hackman did not possess an arsenal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>So it could be that Hasim was in on the kidnapping. And it went sideways.  Or he got cold feet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>All right, dig into his emails and phone records. Let’s see who he was in touch with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>On it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So, here’s what I’ve dug up on Sara El-Masri. She’s a sophomore majoring in marine biology. She was born in Cairo to an über-wealthy Egyptian family.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So this could have been a kidnapping for ransom. Where are her parents?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>The El-Masris have a place at the Dakota. They’re on their way in now.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And we’re doing everything that we can to make that happen, Mr. El-Masri. Along with the FBI.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, so far we know that at least two people were involved. The driver and this man.  Does he look familiar to you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>ANWAR</speaker><content>No, not to me. Lina?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>LINA</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>ANWAR</speaker><content>I will pay them. I will pay whatever they ask.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>LINA</speaker><content>What if that isn’t what they want? You’ve made enemies, Anwar.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>ANWAR</speaker><content>In Egypt. Not here. This is about money. It is always about money.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s also about this man.  Hasim Farouk. Have you ever seen him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>ANWAR</speaker><content>Yes, I tried to reach Hasim when I learned of this. Perhaps he can help us. If he –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Wait, you know him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>ANWAR</speaker><content>Sara would not accept a bodyguard, so I hired Hasim to watch over her discreetly. Where is he?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He died trying to protect her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Now, you hired him to guard Sara. Was she receiving threats?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>ANWAR</speaker><content>No. But a man in my position …  I – I begged Sara to be careful. But she said, “Papa, you worry too much”. She thinks like an American. Trusts like an American.  I will pay anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>ANWAR</speaker><content>She’s my only child. Please.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Would you excuse us for a second?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>CAPTAIN VICTORIA GATES</speaker><content>Detective Beckett, Mr. Castle. This is Agent Harris. He’ll be running point on the kidnapping.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>FBI AGENT HARRIS</speaker><content>Good to meet you. Detective Ryan brought me up to speed on things. How are the El-Masris?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Scared. Devastated.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>HARRIS</speaker><content>Okay, that’s good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It is?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>HARRIS</speaker><content>It beats angry or defensive. They want to be helpful and honest, which is important. Because at the end of the day it’s the accuracy of our information that can determine if this ends well or badly. I’ll keep you in the loop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We’ll do the same.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So I’ve got Ryan and Esposito looking into Sara’s movements from last night. I figure if we can find out what she was doing in lower Manhattan that could lead us to whoever killed Hasim.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Are you okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, yeah. I just – can’t imagine what they’re going through right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you think this is really about money?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Did a web search on El-Masri. He’s worth over $300 million.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, but still. Who hires an ex-commando to babysit their daughter?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’ve considered it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> And I don’t doubt that. But did you see how he shut her down when she brought up enemies?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He just doesn’t want to believe the worst. And frankly, I can’t blame him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey. So I just interviewed Sara’s roommate, Amber. She wasn’t any help with Hasim or the kidnapping. But she did say that Sara went out last night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Where did she go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>All she could remember was that it was some kind of science thing.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Okay, I found three science related events in lower Manhattan from last night.  First, a sci-fi movie marathon in an art house theater 8 blocks from where Hasim got clocked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Though by definition, science fiction is not science.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content> It has the word in it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s – that’s an excellent point.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What are the other two?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Uh, a stargazing tour led by an actual astronomer and a speech from a scientist names Hayden Posner.  Uh, in the ballroom of the Beaumont Hotel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Dr. Posner. He’s an expert on climate change. Alexis bought me his book … which I still haven’t read.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And the Beaumont Hotel would explain why Sara was in lower Manhattan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And she’s a marine biology major, which means she would be interested in climate change.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Let’s go.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>MANAGER</speaker><content>Yes, I remember her. Very lovely young woman. Sara El-Masri, yes, she definitely attended. I checked her in myself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Did you notice anything unusual about her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>MANAGER</speaker><content>No. After Dr. Posner’s presentation she stayed for the Q and A, which went rather late, and then she left.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Any idea where she went?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>MANAGER</speaker><content>All I know is that she exited the ballroom. I stayed on to set up for a wedding reception.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Did she speak with anyone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>MANAGER</speaker><content>Just the person she was with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Who was that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>MANAGER</speaker><content>A young woman. They sat together. They seemed to be friends but I couldn’t tell you her name.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you think you could describe this woman?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>MANAGER</speaker><content>Red hair, pale skin. Also very lovely.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Can I – see that for a moment?  It’s Alexis. She’s on the list. She was here last night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, maybe she knows her, or maybe they met at the event.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>At the very least I’m sure she can help us out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s her ringtone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What’s that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-17"><speaker>MANAGER</speaker><content>Our lost and found. In fact, a guest turned in a phone last night. They found it in the street out front.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>They took Alexis, too.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>HARRIS</speaker><content>Mr. Castle, we will do everything in our power to get your daughter back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I don’t want to be handled. Just let me know where things stand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>HARRIS</speaker><content>Let’s start with the facts as we now understand them. You daughter attended last night’s event with Sara El-Masri. Apparently they met in an environmental science class and became friends. GPS on her phone shows that it was left outside the hotel shortly after the event ended. That, plus the fact that no one has seen or heard from her in the 16 hours since, leads us to conclude that she too was forced into the van.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Now why would they take Alexis if Sara was the target?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>HARRIS</speaker><content>She was probably with Sara at the time. She was a witness. It would have been easier to take her than  – not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So you’re saying she was just in the wrong place at the wrong time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>HARRIS</speaker><content>It appears that way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you have any suspects?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>HARRIS</speaker><content>We have a name.  Facial recognition gave us an ID on the man in the video. Roger Henson. We know him mainly as a mid-level narcotics smuggler.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> If we know he’s out there we can get him. We can initiate a manhunt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>HARRIS</speaker><content>We’re already searching for Henson. Along with all his known associates. But he is a career felon. Finding him won’t be easy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What’s a drug smuggler doing involved in a kidnapping?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-13"><speaker>HARRIS</speaker><content>We’re not sure. But Roger Henson is not a shot caller. He’s a middle man, a hired gun. He may have been hired to abduct the girls.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What happens now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-15"><speaker>HARRIS</speaker><content>We press ahead on multiple fronts. We focus on Henson. Locating him could crack the case. We’re also creating contingency plans for when and if the kidnappers make contact.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>If?  What do you mean, if?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We know that the El-Masris are wealthy and you told us Sara was the target.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-18"><speaker>HARRIS</speaker><content> Mr. El-Masri admitted he had close ties to the previous regime in Egypt. As a result, he made some very powerful enemies. It’s possible his daughter’s abduction was motivated by revenge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay, where does that leave my daughter? I mean, if – if she wasn’t the one they were after then she’s just in the way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-20"><speaker>HARRIS</speaker><content>Mr. Castle, you need to stay positive. Whatever their motives, the kidnappers will realize she has value.  Now what we need to do next is go to your home and set up a trap and trace on your phone line so we’re ready for their call.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-21"><speaker>HARRIS</speaker><content>I’ll wait for you outside.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Gates will see.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I don’t care.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-24"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I can’t believe this is happening.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-25"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We’re gonna find her, Castle. We will.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>You do whatever you need to do to get him back his little girl. Anything you need, Detective.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Thank you, sir.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>How’s he doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>It’s Alexis. He’s gotta be wrecked. Hell, I’m wrecked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah well, we’ve gotta put all of that aside and help him find her. Where are we on the van?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>We’ve been working the traffic cam footage and we’ve made some headway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>After the van left lower Manhattan we picked it up on East River Drive heading toward the Queens-Midtown Tunnel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We gotta figure out where that van went. Let’s bring in some more bodies to review the footage. We find the van, we find Alexis.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Let us know if you need anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>FBI TECH GUY</speaker><content>Certainly, sir.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, Mother. I’m sorry. I am so sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Richard. This is not your fault.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I don’t know. Maybe if I’d just –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>No ifs. Do not torture yourself with ifs. The only people to blame for this are the ones that took her. Alexis is her father’s daughter. She is strong and she is smart and she is going to get through this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Yeah, I know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>No, no, no. I’m not just saying this. She’s going to be all right. I feel it in my heart and my heart is never wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What about your first marriage?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-10"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Well …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And your second?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-12"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Okay, fine. Fine. Occasionally my heart is wrong, but it is not in this case.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I just keep wondering, how did the kidnappers know Sara was going to be at the Beaumont Hotel?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-14"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>You have Kate Beckett and the FBI tracking Alexis down. Just let them do their job. And they need for you to be here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Okay.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What do you got?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>The van exited the Queens-to-Midtown tunnel to Greenpoint. Took Greenpoint Ave to McGuinness. They went west on Huron.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Then where did the van go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, we’re not sure. But this area right here?  It’s pretty much boxed in by Greenpoint Ave, McGuinness, and Franklin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>We checked the video feeds from those streets. The van went in but never came out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>The girls have to be somewhere in there.  Along with Henson.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, so how big is our search zone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Twenty square blocks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay. Coordinate with Feds and Queens PD. We need to do a street by street search for that van. Plain clothes and unmarked cars only.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>So, I’m sitting by the fountain on the south quad this morning, sipping my macchiato, trying to study for a chem quiz and I had this – I guess it was another freshman moment. I’m sure eventually I’ll become jaded and cynical, but not today. Today I look around and I see beautiful buildings. I see students that are just like me and nothing like me. And I feel … overwhelmed. With all the possibilities, with how lucky I am to be a part of this, and how there’s nowhere on Earth I’d rather be right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Now, stand by for a geek alert. My friend Sara and I got tickets to go see Dr. Posner speaks at the Beaumont tonight.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>And for those of you that don’t know, Dr. Posner is one of the foremost thinkers on climate change a personal hero of mine, and …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Do you see? Are you watching?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, if the kidnappers knew that Alexis and Sara were friends –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>They did know. They had to know. They tracked Sara to the hotel from this video. Alexis posted it yesterday afternoon at 2:36. The kidnappers must have access to her website.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, I’m contacting tech right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Have them trace every IP address that accessed that site after 2:36PM.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Which might take time, depending on –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What if she doesn’t have time?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, listen to me –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Don’t.  Don’t promise me you’ll find her unless you can do it. Because …  … I would never forgive you.  Any more than I’d ever forgive myself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Beckett?  We got something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What’s that? Beckett? What’s going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Castle, I gotta go. I’ll call you as soon as I find something, okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Beckett, wait –</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay, thanks. Yeah, I will.  That was LT from the precinct. He said all he knows is that they found the van parked since last night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Well, Beckett will call you as soon as she has some news.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The van’s in Greenpoint. She would have gotten there over an hour ago. The only reason she wouldn’t have called –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Stop it, Richard! We – we don’t know that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Oh darling, go to Greenpoint. Go, go. I can handle things here.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle. What are you doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The precinct told me you found the van. Why the hell wouldn’t you call me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Because we don’t know what this is yet. Castle, please. You don’t need to see this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What’s in the van?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, just please –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What’s in the van?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh – oh God.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Lanie, whose blood is that? Did someone die in there?  Lanie, did she die in there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, we don’t know, okay?  Lanie just got here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>What is Alexis’ blood type?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>A+.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-13"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Okay, just give me a minute.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>C’mon. Let’s … go over here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Is it a match?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-16"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>It’s B-. It’s not from your baby.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>God, thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-18"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>I’m right there with you honey. I got to go let Agent Harris know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So she’s safe, she’s here somewhere, right? She’s gotta be around her somewhere.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She was. Castle, there was a blood trail that led from the van and it stopped. We think that the kidnappers changed cars.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Whose van is it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-22"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>It was stolen a week ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-23"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Any fingerprints?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>CSU’s looking. We’ve got uniforms canvassing the area. Castle, listen. If there is a lead, we are going to find it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-25"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Beckett.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-26"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> I’ll be right back. Okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-27"><speaker>LINA</speaker><content>The blood. It’s not from Sara.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-28"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Not Alexis either.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-29"><speaker>ANWAR</speaker><content>Then there’s hope.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-30"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-31"><speaker>ANWAR</speaker><content>I – I regret that your daughter was dragged into this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-32"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What is it exactly they’ve been drawn into?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-33"><speaker>ANWAR</speaker><content>I wish I knew.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Sara?  Sara? Sara, are you okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>I don’t know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>SARA</speaker><content>Wait. The speech. The hotel. We left the hotel and then that guy … he forced us into a van and then …  … oh, it’s all a bit of a blur.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>I think we were drugged.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>SARA</speaker><content>We still have our clothes on. That’s a good sign.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>SARA</speaker><content>This is all my fault. My parents warned me about this since they first sent me to boarding school. They even made me sit through a lecture on kidnapping from the head of corporate security.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Wait, why would someone kidnap you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>SARA</speaker><content>My father’s crazy rich. But the good news is that he’ll pay the ransom. I mean, that’s what this must be, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>And my dad will find us. He works with the police. I’m sure he’s looking for us right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-11"><speaker>SARA</speaker><content>So they’ll get us out of here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-12"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Wonder what’s in there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-13"><speaker>SARA</speaker><content>Okay, this is creepy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-14"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Clothes? Towels? At least this means they want us alive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-15"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>See? They’re taking care of us.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That was Agent Harris. A witness saw a black Yukon leaving Greenpoint just after the van arrived. Kidnappers must have switched over to the Yukon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>They’ve got a 24 hour head start. They could be anywhere by now. Where’s CSU on the blood?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, spatter analysis shows that it came from the driver. He was shot by Hasim.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He would have left prints in the van. He must be in the system.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, CSU only found Roger Henson’s prints. There’s no other matches.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>We must have a lead here somewhere.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Maybe we do. CSU inspected the van. Found that a bunch of performance tweaks were done to it. Octane booster in the tank, catalytic converter was bypassed, the ECU was rechipped to boot up the horsepower.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Somebody upgraded it to a getaway car.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Not just somebody. A real pro. Probably our driver.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, look for a man whose MO is to steal getaway cars and retune them. Someone with B- blood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Right.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>That security guy. You said he talked to you about kidnapping. What kind of stuff did he say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>SARA</speaker><content>What if no one’s looking for us? What if they don’t even realize that we’re gone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Sara, let’s focus on the questions that we can answer. Build on what we know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>SARA</speaker><content>We don’t know anything! That’s the problem. We don’t know who took us, or for how long we’ll be here, or even where we are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Okay, well, let’s figure that out. Let’s figure out where we are. Um …  … hear that? There’s space under the floor. So we’re not in a basement.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>SARA</speaker><content>And this is a much older building.  Based on how worn the floor is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>And there’s the sound.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>SARA</speaker><content>What sound?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Exactly. No car honks, no traffic noise. Either this room is seriously soundproof or we’re not in New York.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Looks like your hunch paid off. Douglas Stevens. He did a nickel as a getaway driver for a bank robbery and guess who did time with him. None other than Roger Henson.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do the prison records show his blood type?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>B-.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, I’m going to put out an APB and alert all hospitals. With the amount of blood that he lost he’s going to need medical treatment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>He might not need a hospital. Douglas Stevens has a sister who’s a nurse. Guess who called in sick today?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>NYPD! Open up!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We’re here for your brother.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah well, we’re not going to take your word for it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Actually ma’am, we can. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>NYPD! Don’t move! Douglas Stevens, you are under arrest.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The girls that you took. Where are they?  Where’s your partner Roger Henson?  Who put the two of you up to this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>DOUGLAS STEVENS</speaker><content>I got nothing to say.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well then, you’re going to go down for all of it. You were driving the van. That’s murder, two counts of kidnapping. Do you know how many years you’re going to be in jail for? It’s in the triple digits. Tell us where the girls are. That’s your only hope.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>STEVENS</speaker><content>Let me know when my ambulance gets here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’d like a minute with him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>STEVENS</speaker><content>I just said I don’t want to talk. So you can’t question me. I have rights. I’m not going to say anything without a lawyer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’m not a cop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>STEVENS</speaker><content>Then who are you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You remember the girl with the red hair?  I’m her father.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Please know, I will do whatever it takes to get her back. Those police outside are my friends. My daughter’s friends, too. So it’s just you and me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-11"><speaker>STEVENS</speaker><content>If you touch me I’ll press charges.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I don’t care. Where are they?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-13"><speaker>STEVENS</speaker><content>I’m just a driver. I – I don’t know anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>We know Henson ditched the van for the black Yukon. So where did he go? Where did he take the girls?  I won’t ask you again. Where did he take the girls?</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>The address Stevens gave you is to a farm off Route 301. That’s 60 miles north from here. Agent Harris and a tactical team are heading to the location.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Already?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>They should be arriving at the farm any moment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And what will they do then?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Whatever is necessary to recover Alexis and her friend.  But I’ll let you know the moment I have any news.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you want a coffee?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No. No, thanks. My adrenaline will suffice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Did you find out who owns the farm?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Nobody. The property’s been tied up in foreclosure since 2009. It’s been sitting empty. It’s isolated.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Look, the FBI knows what they’re doing. They’re trained in hostage rescue. Alexis is in the best possible hands.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I’m tied into state police dispatch.  Feds are on the scene now.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>HARRIS</speaker><content>That’s our SUV.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Okay, sooner or later someone will show up to bring us more food and we need to be prepared. So what did that security guy tell you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>SARA</speaker><content>Avoid eye contact with the captors so they don’t perceive you to be a witness.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Good. What else?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>SARA</speaker><content>Be vulnerable. Try to let the captors see you as human. Someone they can relate to. Try to build up trust, build a relationship.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>How are we supposed to build a relationship without eye contact?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>SARA</speaker><content>That’s a good question.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The minute she knows, you’ll know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> I just wish that minute was now. It’s all happening too fast and too slow at the same time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Tell me what happened with Douglas Stevens.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I appealed to his humanity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I didn’t think you had that side to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, when it comes to the people I love, I do.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>CAPTOR</speaker><content>Put the food tray under the door.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>My name’s Alexis. This is Sara. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>CAPTOR</speaker><content>Put the food tray under the door.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>It’s kind of cold in here. Is there any way we could get some more blankets?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>What just happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-3"><speaker>SARA</speaker><content>The man on the radio? He was speaking Arabic. He said, “Return to your post. We have visitors.”</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>HARRIS</speaker><content>Go! Go, go, go, go!</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="34"><utterance uid="34-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You know, I still remember … when Alexis was born they handed me this tiny person, all bundled up. She just … stared up at me. And when I looked down at her, this feeling hit me. Like I’d been struck by lightning. It was love. That instant, inexplicable love you can only feel for your child.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>In that moment I knew. I knew my life had changed forever.  And now it’s about to change again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-3"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Gates.  Okay.  The farmhouse was empty.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-4"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Alexis and Sara aren’t there.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="35"><utterance uid="35-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Are you sure she’s not in the cellar or some hidden room somewhere?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-2"><speaker>HARRIS</speaker><content>We searched top to bottom. They’re gone. We did find these.  Either of them belong to Alexis?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, that one there. That’s … that’s hers. What does it mean that her coat’s here and she’s not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-4"><speaker>HARRIS</speaker><content>This must have been a way station until they moved the girls someplace else.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>They’ve been one step ahead of us this whole time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-6"><speaker>HARRIS</speaker><content>These people that we’re dealing with are sophisticated. There are webcams outside. Our approach was streamed to an anonymous IP address. That same IP accessed your daughter’s website.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And you can’t trace it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-8"><speaker>HARRIS</speaker><content>It was routed across four continents. We’re not optimistic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What about Roger Henson?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-10"><speaker>HARRIS</speaker><content>He was shot to death after being tortured at length by someone who knew what they were doing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>His fingernails were pulled off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I don’t understand. Henson was working for the kidnappers. Why would they torture him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-13"><speaker>HARRIS</speaker><content>I don’t know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well then, what do you think? What is your best guess as to what this means for Alexis? For the girls?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-15"><speaker>HARRIS</speaker><content>It means getting them back may be a little more complicated.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="36"><utterance uid="36-1"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Were you crying in there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-2"><speaker>SARA</speaker><content> I thought the running water would cover it up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-3"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>We’ll be all right, Sara.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-4"><speaker>SARA</speaker><content>I thought this was all about the money. But these people speak Arabic.  My father is a hated man back in Egypt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-5"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>We need to get out of here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-6"><speaker>SARA</speaker><content>The only way out is through that door and it’s locked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-7"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Hey, are those … bobby pins?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="37"><utterance uid="37-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>There are hopeful signs here, Castle.  They’ve gone out of their way not to harm the girls. They want them alive. That’ll give us time to track down whoever is behind this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>How?  Our main suspect is dead. The only thing Stevens knew is where the farmhouse is, and … we have no idea who we’re looking for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The FBI is searching the farm for evidence. They’re canvassing the area for witnesses that might have seen whoever was on the property.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>All of which is just another way of saying that we’re back to square one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Won’t be the first time.  We’re gonna solve this, Castle. We will find a way. We’ve done it before with less to go on. You know who told me that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> I did.  In a fit of irrational optimism.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, go see your mom. Go home, get some rest. Come back in the morning. No one is giving up here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I can’t. I’m –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Here’s a decaf. It’s for the road.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="38"><utterance uid="38-1"><speaker>SARA</speaker><content>It’s been hours now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-2"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>My dad taught me how to do this when he was researching for one of his books. He actually bought a door for us to practice on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-3"><speaker>SARA</speaker><content>This was recently?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-4"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content> I was 10.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-5"><speaker>SARA</speaker><content>Oh God.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-6"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>I can do this. One bobby pin is the torsion wrench, the other is the lock pick. You just have to be careful not to apply too much pressure –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-7"><speaker>SARA</speaker><content>Did you just break the hairpin? Because that’s the last one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-8"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>No. I got it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-9"><speaker>SARA</speaker><content>Oh my God!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-10"><speaker>SARA</speaker><content>What’s out there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-11"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>A hallway. Like in an office building. I don’t see anyone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-12"><speaker>SARA</speaker><content>What if they catch us? Then what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-13"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>They want us alive. Just remember that. Here’s the plan. We head down the hall. There has to be a way out. If it looks like there’s two ways we split up and double our chances that one of us makes it out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-14"><speaker>SARA</speaker><content>I think I’m going to throw up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-15"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>You’re not going to throw up. You’re going to get out of here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-16"><speaker>SARA</speaker><content>Okay.  Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-17"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content> C’mon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-18"><speaker>SARA</speaker><content> No, no.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-19"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content> We talked about this! Go!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="39"><utterance uid="39-1"><speaker>FBI TECH GUY</speaker><content>Were you expecting someone to Skype you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Alexis!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-4"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Daddy? Oh my God!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-5"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>I tried to call 911 but it wouldn’t go through.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Baby, are you okay? Where are you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-7"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>I don’t know.  The phone’s about to die. Um … I – we’re - we’re in some building. We were locked in a room but we got out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Where? What building? What’s out – what’s outside the window?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-9"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Nothing, nothing – I can’t see outside – the windows are covered up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-10"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content> They’re coming.  They’re coming. They found out we’re gone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Baby, get out of there. Get out of there now. Go!  Go!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="40"><utterance uid="40-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Can you tell where the call’s coming from?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-2"><speaker>FBI TECH GUY</speaker><content>Tracking now.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="41"><utterance uid="41-1"><speaker>FBI TECH GUY</speaker><content>This can’t be right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Why? What is it?</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="42"><utterance uid="42-1"><speaker>FBI TECH GUY</speaker><content>This says that the call originated from a cell tower in … Paris, France.</content></utterance>
</scene>


<scene id="43"><utterance uid="43-1"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Help!</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>