<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>


<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>MICHELLE</speaker><content>What are you –</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>RICHARD CASTLE</speaker><content>Your throat feel any better?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>ALEXIS CASTLE</speaker><content> Why’d I have to get mono?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, it’s called the kissing disease for a reason. I assume you and Max were – I’m going to stop right there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content> I think that’s best.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Make you some tea.  Sorry about this. I know this isn’t what you expected when you asked to stay here while your place is being fumigated. Alexis was supposed to be going to Paris with her mother.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>KATE BECKETT</speaker><content>It’s fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay, well –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>MARTHA RODGERS</speaker><content>I’ll get it!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>- if you wanted to stay in a hotel I would completely understand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No. No, I’m not going to leave you just because your daughter’s sick.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Richard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I am going to make this up to you in so many ways.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Richard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Your ex-wife is here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Meredith?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Mom?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>Hello Kitten.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Uh, wha- what are you doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>Alexis, oh, my poor baby.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Aren’t you supposed to be in Paris?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-22"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>Not without my daughter. And since you can’t go to Par-ee, I’m bringing Par-ee to you. French pastries and Funny Face. We can enjoy them as I nurse you back to health.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-23"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Meredith, how – why – why so much luggage?  Oh.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I cannot believe that you are actually letting your ex-wife stay with you. With us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What was I supposed to do, stick her in a hotel?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yes.  Look, I get her taking care of Alexis. But staying at your place?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay, wait. Hang on. I turned to you, I said “is it all right with you?” and then you said yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What am I supposed to say? Everyone is looking at me. I’m not meant to be the bad guy in this case. You are. Besides, I gave you the look.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What look?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The look look. My look.  Please don’t tell me after four years you don’t know the look.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> You’ve gotta understand –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know what? I’m not talking about this right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Good morning, Lanie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>LANIE PARISH</speaker><content>Not from the way you sound. What’s wrong?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Men are clueless.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Men? Or just Castle?  Well, no matter how miserable your day is, it’s not as miserable as Michelle Twohey’s. She took an icepick to the side of the neck.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Michelle Twohey, the divorce lawyer for the rich and famous? Isn’t she the one who only represented women?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And strikes fear into the heart of many a soon-to-be ex-husband.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>There’s something else. When I got here she had a piece of paper clutched in her hand with a name and an address. Ryan!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>KEVIN RYAN</speaker><content>Name on the paper is R. Garrison. It’s a Scarsdale address.  And it’s not in our victim’s contact numbers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>JAVIER ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yo. This night clerk around the corner saw a man fleeing the scene at 11:45OM. Suspect ducked into that subway entrance over there. We’re pulling video from the security cameras and the clerk’s going to sit with a sketch artist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What about the victim’s family?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-20"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Not anyone local. Her office gave me the boyfriend’s number. A guy named Corey Francis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay. You guys see how R. Garrison figures into this. Castle and I’ll take the boyfriend.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So Corey, how long had you and Michelle been dating?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>COREY FRANCIS</speaker><content> Less than a month. When we met, we just – it was like magic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>When was the last time you spoke with her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>COREY</speaker><content>Over the weekend. She was in the middle of a divorce case.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’m sure in her line of work she made a lot of enemies. Was there anyone in particular giving her trouble?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>COREY</speaker><content>I don’t know. Her cases involved big money, big egos. But she was just doing her job. She didn’t deserve this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We had a witness that saw somebody running away from the crime scene.  Do you recognize this man?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>COREY</speaker><content> No, he doesn’t look familiar.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We found a Scarsdale address on her. Does the name R. Garrison sound familiar?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>COREY</speaker><content>No. I never heard her mention it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Man. Look at this place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Eh, it’s all right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Are you kidding me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>It has always been a dream of mine to come home to a house like this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Screw the house. It’s always been a dream of mine to come home to a woman like that.  Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Right. Until, of course, things got serious, which is when you’d dump her and start looking for your next dream woman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>NYPD ma’am. I’m Detective Ryan, this is Detective Esposito –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content> Just – call me Javier.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Is there an R. Garrison here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>JANE GARRISON</speaker><content>Yes, that’s my husband Rob.  C’mon in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> Hear that? Husband.  And suspect.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hmm.  Yeah.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>ROB GARRISON</speaker><content>No, we’ve actually never met.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Do you have any idea why she’d have your name and address on her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>ROB</speaker><content>Well I gave it to her last night when I spoke to her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>ROB</speaker><content>I’m a forensic accountant. It’s mostly bankruptcies, but I do a lot of consulting for divorce attorneys. So Miss Twohey called me up, out of the blue, and wanted to meet and go over some financial issues.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Whose financial issues? Her own?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>ROB</speaker><content>She didn’t say. But I recognized her name and I knew her reputation, so I assumed it was about one of her clients.  It was an odd conversation, though.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Odd? How do you mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>ROB</speaker><content>Well, she insisted on meeting today. So whatever the issues were, Miss Twohey was a bit frantic about getting them resolved quickly.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Look, if that meeting was about a client then we’ve gotta figure out which one so head down to her office and see what cases she was working on. And you know what? Since Michelle only represented women see if any of the men she went up against threatened her.  Yeah, men are known to do stupid things when it comes to their ex-wives.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hey. I’ll get that for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s okay, I got it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So, just to let you know, I’m real sorry about that whole Meredith thing. But I am going to take care of it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Beckett.  Yeah okay.  Lanie’s got something for us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You go deal with that. I’m going to go deal with – the other thing.  Take care of it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>No, you gotta take care of it. This is Meredith we’re talking about. The deep fried twinkie that Castle has ex sex with whenever she rolls back into town.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Lanie! Look, I trust him. He’s not going to have sex with her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Fine. Let’s say it isn’t about sex. It’s about boundaries. Meredith is marking her territory. You can’t just let her waltz in and out whenever she pleases.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He’s in a catch-22. Alexis is sick –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Doesn’t matter. This is a war, girl. And guess who’s losing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> I don’t know. Maybe you’re right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Maybe I’m right? Of course I’m right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Lanie, I didn’t come down here to talk about this. You said you had something case related.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Yes. Are you ready for some good news now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That would be nice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>I processed the victim’s clothing and found trace amounts of someone else’s blood on her jacket button.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Which means that our killer could have gotten cut during the attack.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>I’m running DNA now. I’ll call you when I got something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Mmhmm.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>So, each one of Michelle’s employees at her law firm alibied out. But they all said she was acting odd during the past few weeks. They assumed it had to do with a case.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Which case?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Pick one.  Introducing the wealthy men of Manhattan. Michelle represented all their wives in ongoing divorces and some of these angry husbands had threatened her. The only problem is, none of them matched our sketch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Maybe that’s because one of them hired our mystery men to kill Michelle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>But we won’t know which one until we find this guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And I just did. On the subway security video I saw our suspect swipe his MTA card.  He used a credit card to buy it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Herman Poquille. A few B and E’s, aggravated assault, oh, and several attempted murders.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Congratulations. You finally succeeded.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Only thing is, we can’t figure out why you’d want to kill Miss Twohey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Purse wasn’t stolen, car wasn’t jacked. So why’d you kill her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>HERMAN POQUILLE</speaker><content>I didn’t kill her. It’s not what you think.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>C’mon, Herman. You can talk to us. Someone hired you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>POQUILLE</speaker><content>Yeah. She did. Like I said, it’s not what you think. I used to work for Michelle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> Doing what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>POQUILLE</speaker><content>Photographer. Shots of husbands cheating on their wives. Stuff like that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>That still doesn’t explain what you were doing at the crime scene.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>POQUILLE</speaker><content>Look. I botched an assignment a while ago and Michelle fired me. Then all of a sudden she’s calling me, asking me for my help on some big job.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What big job?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>POQUILLE</speaker><content>She didn’t say. She said she was heading home and would wait for me near the subway. By the time I got there she was dead. I didn’t want to get mixed up in the murder, so I ran.  You don’t believe me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Uh uh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>POQUILLE</speaker><content>Check the texts on my phone. It’s all there.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>So I went through Herman’s phone and he wasn’t lying. Michelle wanted to hire him to take photos and she seemed pretty desperate. Herman didn’t want to take the job and he kept texting her no, but she seemed to finally win him over with this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>MICHELLE</speaker><content>Okay, Herman. My texts aren’t changing your mind, so maybe this will. Look at me. I’m pleading. I have a huge problem and I need you and that camera of yours for one last job. Please. A life hangs in the balance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>A life hangs in the balance? What the hell does she need a photo of?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>Hi there. Did you catch the killer already?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Uh, no. Not yet. How’s Alexis?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>Sleeping. But I’m going to wake her with some soup. Want some?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, um … no thanks.  Listen, Meredith, about you staying here –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>Thanks again, Richard. I can’t tell you how much this means to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah. It’s just, Beckett and I –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>Are wonderful. It’s so refreshing to see how secure you two are in your relationship. You know, most women would take issue with an ex-wife staying with her boyfriend. But not Kate Beckett. She gets it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, Kate gets it.  Um, here’s the thing, Meredith. I –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>I know. And … it isn’t easy for me to admit. I haven’t been the best of mothers. I missed so much of our daughter’s life. The fact that you’re letting me be here now, for Alexis during her time of need, Richard, I’ll never ever forget this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Neither will Beckett.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well what?  Oh, that. Still working on that. What about – any progress on finding Michelle Twohey’s killer?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No. Not yet. We’re still checking on the ex-husband’s alibis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey guys? Uh … I think we might have our theory backwards. What if it wasn’t an angry ex-husband that killed Miss Twohey? What if it was an angry ex-wife?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh, wow. Troublesome ex-wife? Imagine that?  So you think one of her clients killed her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Uh, well, Lanie got a hit on the blood on Michelle’s jacket. It belongs to a Samantha Voss. She’s in the system due to a DUI in Los Angeles.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Did she have a grievance with Michelle?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Oh, I’d say so. The morning of Michelle’s murder, a judge came down with a ruling on Samantha’s contentious divorce case. She lost big.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>How big is big?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Uh, Upper East Side apartment big. Cars and boats big. Half of her multi-million net worth big.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s big.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Especially when Samantha went off on a courtroom tirade accusing Michelle of screwing up her case.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>SAMANTHA PETERMAN</speaker><content>Of course my blood was on her. Michelle completely mishandled my divorce. I was furious. Our spat became physical and I cut my hand on one of her metal jacket buttons. But I didn’t kill her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mrs. Voss –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>SAMANTHA</speaker><content>Mrs. Voss is dead. I’m back to Ms. Peterman now, thank you.  Oh, no, no, no, no. Don’t pack the china. That stays with my ex now.  The jackhole.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ms. Peterman, where were you last night between 10 and 1?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>SAMANTHA</speaker><content>I was at a charity auction, which I chair, until 2AM.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>SAMANTHA</speaker><content>There are over a hundred donors that can vouch for that. Check into it if you’d like.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well you may not have killed Michelle but you certainly murdered that original Zarziny. She stabs the box with the box cutter and CASTLE grimaces.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>SAMANTHA</speaker><content>I don’t have to kill to get revenge when there are so many other ways to get back at my ex.  Shame. That</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ms. Peterman, if you could just refrain from destroying anything else you actually might be of some help. Now, did Michelle say or do anything out of the ordinary.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>SAMANTHA</speaker><content>Mmm, now let me tell you, something was sure as hell wrong in that woman’s life. Because for the for the past month she was just distracted. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Distracted by what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-12"><speaker>SAMANTHA</speaker><content>She got lost in the details of my case that had absolutely no bearing on securing a better settlement.  And don’t even get me started on her personal problems.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What do you mean her personal problems?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-14"><speaker>SAMANTHA</speaker><content>Detective, I was her client, not her BFF. I don’t know. Although I can tell you, yesterday she came to court late.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-15"><speaker>SAMANTHA</speaker><content>And she was  crying.  Oh!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Did she tell you why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-17"><speaker>SAMANTHA</speaker><content>Yes. She said she was having messy personal issues.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-18"><speaker>WALTER VOSS</speaker><content>What did you do to my Zarziny?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-19"><speaker>SAMANTHA</speaker><content>Oh joy, my ex is home. Walter, Walter, Walter. Come in, we have company. Say hello.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-20"><speaker>WALTER</speaker><content>You b*itch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-21"><speaker>SAMANTHA</speaker><content>No dear. The b*itch is the skank you paid to have sex with you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-22"><speaker>SAMANTHA</speaker><content>Walter, no. No, Walter. No!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Next person to break anything goes to jail.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>WALTER</speaker><content>This is all your fault.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>SAMANTHA</speaker><content>And it was so worth it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Wow. Hell hath no fury.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Did it ever get that bad with either of your exes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No. No, both my divorces were amicable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, a little too amicable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So something was going on with Michelle Twohey. On the morning of her death, she arrived to court late and she had been crying. So where was she coming from?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well according to her financials, she paid for breakfast at a café right before court. So maybe someone there will let us know what was so upsetting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Bro. What was that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What was what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Your girlfriend just uttered a sarcastic remark about your ex-wife and all you’re going to say “what was what”?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, that was nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Spit it out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-14"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Tell us!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Uh, okay, as you know Beckett is staying at the loft while her place is getting fumigated. Alexis is home sick as well, and then Meredith showed up and she said she wanted to stay in the loft –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-16"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And you said no.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-17"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Tell me you said no.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-18"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Wow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-19"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Really?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-20"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Really? Letting an ex stay with you when you’re with someone else. That’s like throwing gasoline on fireworks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>C’mon, guys. It’s not that bad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-22"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Castle. You are on the edge of a very, very steep cliff, my friend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-23"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>If you don’t do something about it quick … </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So the café owner remembers Michelle having an argument with a tall, good looking man, mid 30s, light brown hair, and blue eyes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-25"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Her boyfriend Corey Francis? I thought he hadn’t seen Michelle since the weekend. Now why would he lie?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-26"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Looks like he’s hiding something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-27"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Let’s bring him down here and find out what.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yes, and if you could have some strawberries and champagne sent up there waiting … perfect. Cedric, I owe you. Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Michelle fights with her boyfriends, sets up a meeting with an accountant, and then she hires a photographer. What the hell was she in to?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I don’t know. But why don’t we discuss it tonight in our oversized Jacuzzi at the Four Seasons where I just booked us the Ambassador Suite.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why would you do that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Because your place is still being fumigated and my loft is still overrun with redheads. So I thought, why not just go an enjoy ourselves?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You guys? Where’s Corey Francis?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, we got a problem. He’s disappeared.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>His cell has been disconnected, his address is bogus, and so is his name.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The guy that our victim was dating doesn’t exist?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And what’s worse, we have no way of finding him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No, wait. Um … he was wearing a ring. Class ring. College ring. New York something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Uh yeah. It was uh … red, with a cathedral imprinted on it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-13"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Uh … University of New York.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>It might be part of his cover identity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>University of New York? C’mon. If you were going to pick a cover identity wouldn’t you pick a better school than U…  … University of New York?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know we can ID him using the yearbooks. He’s in his mid-30s? So why don’t we grab everything from the University library from ’96 and on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-17"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> Ah well, that’s upstate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-18"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>We’ll have it for you in the morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-19"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-22"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No on the Four Seasons. If anyone should be sent to a hotel, it’s Meredith.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-23"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I tried. It just – it means so much to her to be there for Alexis and … it just seemed heartless to kick her out and send her to a hotel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Really Castle? Because you just tried sending me to one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-25"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No! But that was because –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-26"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>But nothing. Button up, Kitten. We’re going home.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>Oh, that smells delicious. Can I have a cup?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I – was just making that for Castle, but  yeah, here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So how’s Alexis?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>She’s asleep. She’s always asleep. I love her, but with mono she’s a bit of a bore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>So. You and Rick?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yes. Me and … Rick, so …  You know, you might wanna put some pants on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>Why? It’s not like I’m going anywhere.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh. Hey, you too.  What’s going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-10"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>Nothing. Just making coffee.  Here, this is for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, thank you.  Mmm… what is in this? Did you add – nutmeg.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-12"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>Nutmeg.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Nutmeg?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-14"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>Whenever Rick pulled all-nighters I’d sprinkle nutmeg in his coffee.  Gave it an extra kick. You want to try?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Uh, no. Thanks. I think I’ve had enough kick for one morning.  I will be at work.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Hey. Listen, um … that whole coffee thing, Meredith didn’t mean anything by that. She’s just trying to be thoughtful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> I’m sure she was.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So you’re not mad?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>About what? About how comfortable your ex-wife is in your home and with your family? How she seems to know things about you that I don’t know? Why would I be upset?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Okay, see, this is why I wanted to stay at the Four Seasons. So you wouldn’t have to deal with this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, I shouldn’t have to deal with this because you should have said no.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yes, but I didn’t. And now I can’t. I know. I’ll – I’ll send Alexis and Meredith to the Four Seasons. I’ll just hire a concierge doctor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, Castle. I am a big girl, okay? I can be in the same place as your ex-wife.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So you’ll stay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah. Sure. I’ll just be subjected to her parading around half naked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Okay. I can’t win, can I?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh, right. Because this is all about you now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well you made it – I –  Okay, you know what? You’re right. You are absolutely right. All we have to do is get through the next few days with my crazy ex-wife. What do you say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Noah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, not no. Noah. Kesswood. Corey Francis is really –</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Noah Kesswood. Former officer in the army’s military intelligence core.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Former military intelligence?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Noah uses a fake identity, starts dating Michelle and then he disappears just after she’s killed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s the Bachelor meets Homeland.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Whatever he was up to the only trace of him I could find is a loan out corporation registered in his name. There’s been a lot of recent activity. Several large wire transfers were made from a local law firm, Benedict, Cole, and Shuester.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Those payments started around the time Noah started dating Michelle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Think someone was paying Noah to spy on her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well Michelle’s cases has outcomes in the millions. Maybe an opposing lawyer was angling for an advantage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>If Michelle found out she was being spied on, then that lawyer would face an ethics violation and disbarment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It might have made it desperate enough to pay Noah to kill Michelle to make the problem go away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>It is possible. But the best way to find out is to track down the lawyer that authorized those payments.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>HOTDOG VENDOR</speaker><content>Here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Mr. Schuester! Your office said we’d find you down here. I’m Detective Esposito, this is my partner Detective Ryan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>SAMUEL SCHUESTER</speaker><content>I’m guessing you’re not here for the hotdogs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>We’d like you to come answer some questions about Noah Kesswood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>SCHUESTER</speaker><content>I’m sure you know I’m a criminal attorney who’s very aware of his rights. I’m not going anywhere.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Ah. Then we can talk here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>SCHUESTER</speaker><content>You want to discuss the virtues of processed meat in tube form, fine. Otherwise you’re wasting your time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>How about we discuss the wire transfers you made to Noah Kesswood, a suspect in the murder of Michelle Twohey?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>SCHUESTER</speaker><content>Save your foie gras, your roast duck, your coq au vin, for me fine dining is a New York hotdog.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Mr. Schuester, we know the last transfer was for ten grand, sent the morning Michelle was murdered.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Sounds like your law firm paid Noah to kill a fellow attorney.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-12"><speaker>SCHUESTER</speaker><content>That’s ridiculous.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-13"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Maybe, but when we connect the dots you think the media will see it that way?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-14"><speaker>SCHUESTER</speaker><content>Okay, here’s what’s going to happen, Detectives. You’re going to find out I was instructed by a client to pay Noah Kesswood for his service. You’re going to ask what that service was. I’m going to say “I don’t know”, then you’re going to puff up and demand the name of my client, to which I’ll reply, that’s privileged information, kindly go screw yourselves. Have a hotdog, boys, they’re delicious.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Mr. Schuester may have attorney client privilege, but who he represents is a matter of public record. So, I look back into his law firm’s cases for the last five years. Turns out Schuester represented Billy Piper. You guys remember the story, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah. It was all over the news for months. Famous pro golfer, getting a divorce, takes a boating trip to the Caribbean to work on his marriage –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Only his wife never makes it back to shore. Billy claimed that the two of them were drinking and his wife accidently fell off of the boat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Everyone assumed it was murder but the Feds never had enough to indict him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Indeed. So, what does any of this have to do with our victim?  Three years ago Michelle had a client who disappeared from her boat. That client was Leann Piper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Billy Piper’s wife?  That can’t be a coincidence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I don’t think it was. In fact, I found a file on Michelle’s computer that showed she’d been looking into Leann Piper’s murder for the past month.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Wait a minute. What if she figured out how Billy killed his wife?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>You mean, by finding actual evidence?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Right. Then the only way Billy could stop that proof from coming out –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>- was to have Michelle killed.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>BILLY PIPER</speaker><content>It’s my pride and joy. Won it in Augusta in ’02.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You eagled for the win.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>BILLY</speaker><content>That’s right. Can I get either of you two a drink?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>This isn’t a social visit, Mr. Piper. We’re here to talk to you about Michelle Twohey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>BILLY</speaker><content>Michelle Who-ey? Sorry, it doesn’t sound familiar.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>It’s odd that you don’t remember your late wife’s divorce lawyer. Did you know that she turned up dead? The reason I’m asking is because she visited you about a month ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>BILLY</speaker><content>Hmmm… don’t recall any visits.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You sure about that? It was right after that visit you hired Noah Kesswood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>BILLY</speaker><content>Who’s Noah Kesswood?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The man that you paid to spy on her. And then she winds up dead. That’s awfully suspicious, don’t you think?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>BILLY</speaker><content>You people. Somebody dies, question Billy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well can you blame us? Especially after what happened with your wife?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-13"><speaker>BILLY</speaker><content>Okay. Let’s talk about what happened with my wife. Leann files for divorce and I fight her on it because where I’m from marriage is sacred. So Leann and I decide to go for a boat ride, like the old days. But instead of recapturing our magic Leann got drunk and fell into the ocean. So why am I the bad guy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh, so you’re the victim here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-15"><speaker>BILLY</speaker><content>You bet your ass I am. I lost my endorsements and my status. My own family wants nothing to do with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Interesting. In the list of things you lost you didn’t include your wife.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-17"><speaker>BILLY</speaker><content>Well. She never was my favorite trophy.  Now why don’t the two of you get the hell out of my home?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well Billy did it. Killed his wife to keep his money, then had Michelle murdered when she found evidence of it. Only how do we prove it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, all roads lead to Noah. So if we can catch him we can get him to turn on Billy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Perfect. Only we don’t have any way of finding him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Actually, we do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Turns out the garage in Billy’s building has an automated valet system. The manager was able to pull up the records of when Noah parked there and we got his license number.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>The car belongs to a fleet of vehicles that’s registered to a pharmaceutical company.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Was Noah an employee there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>No, he has no affiliation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>All right. You guys keep digging. There’s gotta be a connection somewhere.  Hello? Yeah, Meredith. Yeah, Castle’s right here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I’m sorry, what? You want to talk to me?  Uh, yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No.  Okay.  Fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> What did she want?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She asked me to dinner tonight.  Just the two of us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>To – dinner. And you said yes? How could you say yes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Same way you did when she asked to stay with you.  Besides Castle, if I said no that would have made me look insecure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Is this as bad as it seems?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-17"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No. It’s much worse. Much, much worse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No. Okay, hang on. It’s – take a step back from this, let’s just think about it.  Just dinner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-19"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Just dinner between your ex-wife and your new girlfriend. That’s deadly. Castle. You have two worlds</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-20"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Two.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-21"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Now they’re both coming together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-22"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Uh oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-23"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>What happens when worlds collide?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-24"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Boom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-25"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay, guys. You are taking this a little too far.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-26"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Castle!  Meredith knows things about you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-27"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-28"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-29"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>So. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-30"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So is there anything Meredith knows that you don’t want Beckett to know?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-31"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Boom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-32"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Two worlds colliding.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hey.  Have I told you how lovely your penmanship is? The font is just so friendly. I just look forward to seeing it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, what is it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> I just want to make sure you want to go to dinner with Meredith. Remember, she’s a little crazy and of course, dramatic.  Ugh. Miserable combination.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> What are you so worried about? I mean, it’s just two people who you’ve been intimate with coming together, comparing notes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Comparing notes.  What notes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Seriously, though. What notes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey Espo, what do you got on Noah?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I just got off the phone with the vice president from that pharmaceutical company.  Guess where he went to college?  University of New York.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Sorry about that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Not only was he giving Noah access to the company car, but he’s also been letting him stay with him for the past month.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay. Pick him up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content> Boom.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>There he is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hey, Noah Kesswood. NYPD. Come here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>That hurt as much as it looked?  Good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And now you’re under arrest.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Look at him. Nothing like the devastated boyfriend that I met yesterday.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Noah. You’re good, man. But not that good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, let’s not waste any time. We know that Billy hired you to spy on Michelle to see if she had any proof that he killed his wife.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And when you discovered she did, on Billy’s orders you put an icepick through her neck.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>NOAH KESSWOOD</speaker><content>I didn’t kill Michelle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I don’t believe you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>NOAH</speaker><content>You don’t have to. See when Michelle was being shish kebob’ed I was all the way up at the University of New York watching my alma mater play West Virginia.  We won, by the way. Go Broncos.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>If you didn’t kill her then why’d you work so hard to disappear?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>NOAH</speaker><content>Detective, what do you say you buy me a soda, hum?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Excuse me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-11"><speaker>NOAH</speaker><content>Not you.  You.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>NOAH</speaker><content>All right, look. I deal in intelligence. Not murder. Never murder. You want the truth? Okay, here it is, free of charge. Billy Piper’s absolutely paranoid. So when Michelle came around asking questions about that night on the boat he went into full on panic mode. Figured she probably had a vendetta against him. Wanted him in jail for murdering her client. Reality is, he was probably right. She said she was close. Very close to finding out what happened on that boat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Are we talking actual evidence?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>NOAH</speaker><content> Maybe. She was gathering the final puzzle pieces at the New York office of the DEA.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The Drug Enforcement Agency? Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>NOAH</speaker><content>You’d have to ask them, Detective.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, well, I’m still gonna have to hold you, you know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>NOAH</speaker><content>For up to 24 hours. And then you’ll never see me again.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>All right, thanks Bill. Well, Noah’s alibi is solid. He’s definitely not the killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>But do we believe his story about the DEA? I mean, what does any of this have to do with drugs?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, there’s only one way to find out. Ryan, see if you can uncover was Michelle was doing at the DEA.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> I’ll try, but it’s late. Probably won’t hear anything until the morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, I guess we should call it a night. Okay, Castle. See you later.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Later? We can go back to my place together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Um, I have a dinner date with your ex-wife, remember?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah. I remember. I was just hoping you’d forget.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, don’t wait up.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Oh darling, please. Just relax.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I can’t relax, Mother. My worlds are colliding, okay? My – I can’t relax.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Well, have a glass of wine. Works for me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Bet they’re out there right now, telling secrets about me. Boom What do I do?  Should I call them? I should call them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>No. No. No. What you shouldn’t have done was let Meredith stay here in the first place. This isn’t a flop house, darling. You’ve gotta stop letting freeloaders just live here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Please tell me you see the irony.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh, Meredith. Castle did that? I can’t believe that you married … him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What can’t you believe? What – no. What? No. C’mon, Beckett. There’s two sides to that story that – what did you – what story – what did you tell her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-9"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>The truth, Richard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, you’re not the man that I thought I knew.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’m the man that you thought you knew. I’m the man you know. I thought you – I’m that – you think – I know you. I’m him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>This is so not cool.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh, you’re right. He does lean to the left.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-14"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>Told you. Only when he’s stressed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I never even noticed that before.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What – what leans?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Thank you, Meredith. That was so fun.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-18"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>Thanks for coming.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You have a great night. Night Martha.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-20"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content> Night, darling.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay, what did she say about me?  Ugh, c’mon. I get it. I get it. I mishandled this whole thing. But believe me, I am sorry. Please? Tell me what Meredith said. Is it anything I need to be worried about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know what, Castle? As much fun as it would be to continue torturing you, I actually like you a little bit more now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mmhmm, yeah. Meredith is a fun, dynamic, and hard to say no to woman.  But, as long as we’re together, she never stays here again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> That goes without saying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Let it go to voicemail.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh, it’s the precinct.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Beckett.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey, I just got off with the DEA. You need to get down here right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, okay. We’ll be right there.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Michelle was very interested in the DEA’s Caribbean drug interdiction efforts, which involve the tracking of planes and boats using satellite photos. She obtained this three year old satellite photo from the night of Leann Piper’s murder. Take a look.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>There’s two boats.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah. Less than 50 feet apart. And they identified that one as Billy Piper’s.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s how he got away with it. That’s why Leann was never found. Billy was afraid her body would wash up so he enlisted an accomplice to take the remains and dump them where nobody would ever look.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>If Michelle got on to this, that accomplice might be the person who murdered her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, but how did she know to look for another boat?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>It was recently listed as an asset in one of her divorce cases. And guys, you’re never going to guess who the accomplice is.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hello, Walter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>WALTER</speaker><content>Can I help you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, we’re here to see a man about a boat.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>WALTER</speaker><content>Why would I kill my ex-wife’s divorce lawyer? She did a terrible job, and because of that I won.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you want to know why you won? Because Michelle was spending all of her time sifting through your financials from three years ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>She became very interested in how your family and Billy Piper’s family were all members of the same yacht club.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-4"><speaker>WALTER</speaker><content>So?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>You and Billy Piper were friends.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-6"><speaker>WALTER</speaker><content>Again, I respond, so?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So Michelle found proof that you refueled your boat near the waters where Billy’s wife was killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>She tracked your boat using satellite photos.  This is Billy Piper’s boat, where his wife was last seen. And who is this over here? Oh, it’s yours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The DEA identified it as your boat. You were Billy’s accomplice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>The two of you had a pretty good plan. Except that there was one thing that you couldn’t foresee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That your wife would hire Michelle to represent her in your divorce.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Michelle was probably looking for proof of an affair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Except she found something much worse. That little boat trip you took to the Caribbean? As she looked closer to who you were with and why you were there, she discovered the truth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-14"><speaker>WALTER</speaker><content>I want to talk to my lawyer.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="34"><utterance uid="34-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Without a confession our case is purely speculative.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>We could dig into Walter’s life. Maybe find some proof?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And some motive too, if we’re lucky.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay, so it’s not just me. Walter has no real motive, does he?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No. I mean, why would Walter help Billy kill his wife? Yeah, sure, they’re friends, but what was in it for Walter?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s not like they agreed to kill each other’s wives like Strangers on a Train. Though what we saw of Walter’s relationship, I’m sure he thought about it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hey guys. I found something in Walter’s phone records and I’m not quite sure what to make of it.  On the morning of Michelle’s murder Walter made a 20 minute phone call to the Garrison residence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Garrison? The accountant that Michelle was so desperate to meet? Why would Walter call him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Who’s this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>The woman of my dreams. She’s married to that accountant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Guys, look at Billy’s dead wife.  And now look at the accountant’s wife. Different hair, different nose, different chin, but –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>They’re the same woman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s why they never found a body. Because Billy’s dead wife Leann … is alive.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="35"><utterance uid="35-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Again, thank you, Mrs. Garrison, for coming down here at such a late hour.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-2"><speaker>JANE GARRISON</speaker><content>Didn’t my husband answer all the other detective’s questions?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, he did. But there was just one that only you can answer.  Who’s this woman?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Here. Let me get that for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-5"><speaker>JANE</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-7"><speaker>JANE</speaker><content>Sorry, I don’t recognize her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You sure about that? ‘cause, you know, you can change your name, you can change your looks. But there is one thing that you cannot change.  Your fingerprints. We know who you are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hello Leann. Welcome back from the dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-10"><speaker>JANE</speaker><content> I think you must have the wrong person.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You can drop the charade, Leann. We spoke with your current husband. He said you drove into the city the night Michelle was killed. And he also identified the murder weapon as a mahogany handled icepick missing from your kitchen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You know, it’s funny. For a minute there we thought Walter was helping Billy. But actually, he was helping you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The only thing that we couldn’t figure out was why? Why did you go through all of this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-14"><speaker>JANE</speaker><content>Because everybody loved Billy. You try being married to him. He was a hero in public and a monster at home. When I finally got the courage to divorce him do you know how the media portrayed me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>As another gold digging trophy wife looking for her half.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-16"><speaker>JANE</speaker><content>He destroyed my reputation. He was going to destroy me. The only way that I could get my life back was to die.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And you needed help.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-18"><speaker>JANE</speaker><content>And Walter needed the money. At least he did at the time. So we devised a plan. I convinced Billy to take the trip. And then when the scotch put him to sleep –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You escaped onto Walter’s boat, turning your husband into a wife killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-20"><speaker>JANE</speaker><content>It’s what he deserved. And I got to start over. I was supposed to leave the country, but I met Rob and I fell for him. We were so happy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Until Michelle put the pieces together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-22"><speaker>JANE</speaker><content>She said she couldn’t live with the injustice. I mean, can you believe that? From a lawyer? She sided with Billy. I mean, she knew what he was like. She knew what he did to me. Why couldn’t she just leave it alone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Stand up.  Let’s go. C’mon. Stand up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Turn around, hands behind your back.  Leann Piper, you are under arrest for the murder of Michelle Twohey.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="36"><utterance uid="36-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I mean, I know your apartment is habitable again. I just – do you have to leave?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you want me here because you actually want me here or do you need protection from the redheads?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> A little of both.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, I’ll tell you what. If it gets to be too much, you can come and stay at my place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-6"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>Are you sure it’s okay that I’m going to Par-ee without you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-7"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Just because I’m sick, you shouldn’t miss it. I want you to go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-8"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>We all do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What’s going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-10"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>I just feel so guilty that Mom is missing her vacation because I’m sick, so I told her to enjoy Paris for the both of us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Are you sure, Alexis? I mean, your mother –  – should … enjoy her vacation. Have a safe trip, Meredith.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-12"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>Mmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-13"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Je t'aime maman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-14"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>Moi aussi, je t'aime.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-15"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Adios, dear. Have fun.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-16"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>Martha. Well, this has been … oh shoot. I left my purse upstairs. Be a dear –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’ll grab it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-18"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>Detective Beckett, it was a real pleasure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yes, it really was. You know, Meredith, it’s so funny, when you first came and insisted on staying here I was afraid that you might have had a secret agenda.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-20"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content> Actually, I did.  When Alexis told me about you two and how this one was serious, I knew I had to check it out for myself. And I’m so glad I did. You two are great together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Thank you.  Can I ask you a question? Why didn’t it work out? Between you and Rick?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-22"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I’m sorry, is that too personal?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-23"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>Oh no, no, no. It’s fine. You know, being married to Richard was great. Full of romance and excitement. Like a deliciously sweet soufflé. And then one day I realized he knew everything about me. My deepest secrets, my worse pain. Enough to fill a million novels. But I didn’t know enough about him to even write a pamphlet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I don’t understand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-25"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>For instance, whenever I asked him how he felt about never knowing his father, he would smirk. You know the way he smirks. And then he would throw out a quip and change the subject. Our marriage went one way. It wasn’t enough for me. I mean, soufflé’s are wonderful. But sooner or later, they always fall.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-26"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>Oh, but that was a long, long time ago. What, 15 years in fact. He’s a totally different man now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-27"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yes. Of course. I was just curious.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-28"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay, here we go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-29"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>Oh, you are the best, Rick.  Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-30"><speaker>MEREDITH</speaker><content>Oh, I hope we see each other again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-31"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Me too. Have a wonderful trip.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-32"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>‘Bye.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-33"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>How about I make you a little breakfast before you leave?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-34"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’m going to whip you up a smore’lette. It sounds better than it tastes, but that’s – it’s – you’ll love it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-35"><speaker>THE END</speaker><content>CASTLE</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>