<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>


<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>RICHARD CASTLE</speaker><content>This is straight out of a slasher flick. We usually find murder victims at the end of hallways like these. I cannot believe Alexis lives here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>MARTHA RODGERS</speaker><content>Richard, Alexis and Pi have invited us for dinner. This is a big step for them. So let us not be judgmental.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Besides, remember the hovel you lived in in college?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The difference is I wasn’t shacking up with Pi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Well, it’s nice that you’re keeping an open mind, dear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>ALEXIS CASTLE</speaker><content>Hi! You’re here! Come in! I’m so excited for you to see our place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Oh … my. Your first place. Oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>PI</speaker><content>Hey, Mr. C!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>PI</speaker><content>Welcome. And prepare yourself for some savory and sustainable dining.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, let me guess. There will be fruit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>PI</speaker><content>I’ll make a fruitarian out of you yet, Mr. C.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Ah, here is a … um … little housewarming present. And it needs sunlight and there’s a little giftcard as well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Thank you, Gram.  Well, what do you think?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Oh, I think it’s adorable. I love what the two of you have done with this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>PI</speaker><content>Yeah, we’ve had lots of fun fixing it up. We were eating on a blanket on the floor and then we found this old door and set it up as a table.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>And I found the chairs next to a restaurant dumpster.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Oh!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Dumpster chairs. That’s …  … great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-20"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Well there’s nothing like la vie boheme to get the blood flowing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-21"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content> Be nice.  A futon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You know, if you guys want something real to sit on I have an old couch in storage. I could just …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-23"><speaker>PI</speaker><content>Um … I don’t know, Mr. C.  What color is it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-24"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Free.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-25"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Dad, we’re fine. We have everything we need.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-26"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>So Pi, Alexis tells me that you have a new job.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-27"><speaker>PI</speaker><content>I do indeed. I’m tracking bee populations in the city for an NGO.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-28"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Ah ha.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-29"><speaker>PI</speaker><content>It’s a lot like the job I did in Costa Rica. We’re assessing the colony’s strength and numbers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-30"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So you’re … counting bees?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-31"><speaker>PI</speaker><content>Well, there’s a lot more to it than that, Mr. C, but yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-32"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And that’s a real job?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-33"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content> Yes, it’s a real job. Bees are vital to the food supply. It’s important work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-34"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, so long as it puts fruit on the table.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-35"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Well, speaking of the table, I am famished. Shall we dine?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-36"><speaker>PI</speaker><content>Yes, let’s do that.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Needless to say, dinner was a disaster. But the real disaster is that Alexis has moved in with this guy. He’s just so wrong for her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>KATE BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah well, she’ll figure it out. At least she’s not living in squalor. That’s good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No, it’s not good. I was hoping for squalor. I was counting on squalor. Because Alexis cannot last in squalor. I was just hoping this whole thing would blow over. She would see Pi for the ambition free hippie that he is. And now he’s morphed into some … new age crusader? It’s a though he’s turned being a charming man-child into a career.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Now that doesn’t sound familiar, does it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What I need is a good murder so I can stop obsessing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>KEVIN RYAN</speaker><content>Well, we’ve got one for you, Castle. Victim is Susannah Richland, 28. Business card says she’s an accountant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>How does an accountant end up like this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>LANIE PARISH</speaker><content>Freaky, huh?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Look at those marks on her hands.  They look like stigmata.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah. Like she’s posed in a suggested crucifixion.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Except the cause of death is probably that stab wound to the throat from a double edged blade, like a dagger.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>A dagger. Maybe this is some kind of ritualistic sacrifice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Or maybe the killer wanted to make it look like it was.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Note the lack of blood. I’d say that she was moved here but killed somewhere else.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Might I suggest a sacrificial altar?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, you may not.  Do we have a time of death?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>I’m thinking ten to midnight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>All right, uh … I’ll start a canvass, start gathering security video. See if I can find someone that witnessed the body drop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, and get ahold of the FBI. See if they have any other murders with the same MO.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah, okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>JAVIER ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hey. Just got off the phone with Susannah’s boss. He knows of nothing in her life that would explain this. But he did say that she’d been acting odd lately and that she’d asked for a week off to handle a personal matter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>But he didn’t know what it was?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-23"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No. Neither did any of her coworkers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>All right, contact her family and friends. Let’s see if they knew. Castle and I are going to go to her apartment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-25"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>All right.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Did you know of any personal matters she might have been dealing with?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>LANDLADY</speaker><content>No, but something was up. Last week she started keeping odd hours. Staying out late. It wasn’t like her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Did she have visitors? Any men in her life?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>LANDLADY</speaker><content>Not that I ever saw.  Be sure to lock up when you’re done.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Thanks.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>An apparently ordinary accountant brutally slain and ritually posed. All while tending to a personal matter shrouded in secrecy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>It’s not shrouded in secrecy. We just don’t know what it is yet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, my version has more dramatic flair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>She’s got a lot of books here on medieval history. Maybe her dark secret has something to do with the dark ages. That could explain the way we found her body.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, you might be on to something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Look at this. Religious icons and pagan symbols.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>This fascination of hers is recent. All these books were checked out of the library three days ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, so what does that have to do with our murder?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Maybe I know the answer.  The pentagram, the all seeing eye? Both of those are power objects in dark magic. All these elements – earth, air, fire, water, ether – all medieval symbols that are sometimes associated with satanic practices. Susannah was into the occult.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>HENRY COLLINS</speaker><content>The occult? I know my cousin. No way was she mixed up with that kind of thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, we found these symbols at her place, Mr. Collins. Along with some books on medieval history. Any idea why they’d be there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>HENRY</speaker><content>No. I mean, she was a history buff, but more American history, not that kind of thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Did she have any … uh … enemies in her life, Mr. Collins? Any relationship issues?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>HENRY</speaker><content> Not that I know of. I just – I don’t understand who would do this to her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>When was the last time you saw her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>HENRY</speaker><content>Maybe three weeks ago? I was her only family, so we’d get together for dinner every few months. But it’s strange. She, um … she actually called me last night. Out of the blue.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And what did she say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>HENRY</speaker><content>That she had something that she wanted to talk to me about.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What was that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>HENRY</speaker><content>I didn’t even get a chance to ask. She got interrupted or something, said she’d call me right back. But she never did. And now I know why.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So the FBI doesn’t have any murders in the database that match this MO.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Which leaves us with my theory. Our victim was dabbling with black magic and she conjured up a demon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Or maybe she ran afoul of some obscure religious sect and they sacrificed her to their pagan deity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Making stuff up, just like you do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, because that’s my job. It’s your job to follow the evidence. You’re messing with the natural order of things.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey guys? There’s something you need to see.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>So our canvass couldn’t come up with anyone that witnessed the body dump. But Susannah had a Metro card in her pocket. So I had MTA run its history. Her card was swiped yesterday on an M3 bus. She got on at 8:45 near her apartment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Where was she going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Bus cam has her exiting at West 168th Street, Washington Heights.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s about a half mile from where her body was found.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What was she doing way up there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I don’t know. But I checked traffic cam footage in a 10 block radius and I found Susannah crossing Saint Nicholas at West 173rd Street. And it looks like she had company.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>A monk?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> Check out the timestamp. 10:05. Right in our time of death window.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>A posed body, mysterious medieval symbols, and now a murderous monk.  It’s a real life Da Vinci Code.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do we have any idea who this guy is?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’ll tell you who he is. He’s part of a brotherhood of assassins, chosen to guard an ancient secret.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Stalking a woman obsessed with medieval symbols? This is what the evidence suggests.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Can we get a closer look at his face?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>No, he never turns his head.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Wait, zoom in on his scalp.  There. Do you see that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ritual markings. Left by some unholy initiation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>They’re more like surgical scars.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I’ll see if I can look into a medical procedure that can cause those. Might help us ID him.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’m telling you, our monk, our victim, and these symbols are all connected. I’m betting Susannah Richland decoded these symbols and uncovered some dark, long-held secret - and paid for it with her life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Look, Castle, I agree that her recent interest in all things medieval might be relevant, but it doesn’t mean that she was killed in some baroque plot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Ah, I wouldn’t be too sure about that. Castle might be right about this Da Vinci Code thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>- don’t ruin it. According to Susannah’s phone records, she made a call to a Professor Jason Byford at Hudson University the day before she died. And get this, he’s an expert in ancient languages and symbology.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Just like Tom Hanks in the movie. It’s not a baroque plot. It’s a best-seller plot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, at the very least he should be able to tell us what Susannah was up to. Castle and I’ll go talk to him. In the meantime, I need you to go to the morgue. Lanie says she has something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>‘kay.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>So I was finally able to identify the murder weapon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I thought you said it was a dagger.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>I know what I said, but based on the curvature of the wound and the injuries to the neck, our victim was stabbed with a sword.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>A sword?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Yes, a double-edged saber like this, with a hilt that left a crenellated bruising pattern on her neck.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Very old school.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>I took a closer look at her hand injuries and I found something. There was ink residue in this wound on her palm. I was able to draw it up from the lower dermis. It looks like she drew this symbol on her hand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>All right. I’ve gotta get this to Beckett.  Head back to the precinct.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>PROFESSOR JASON BYFORD</speaker><content>Yes, I met with Susannah.  People often call with research questions, so I try to be helpful. She wanted to know what these symbols meant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What did you tell her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>BYFORD</speaker><content>I said that it all depends. Some of these have existed for thousands of years. They signify different things to different cultures.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Are any of them tied to anything dangerous like cults?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>BYFORD</speaker><content>Oh, a few, yes. But mostly these are associated with the Freemasons, which is why you see so many on buildings and icons in the US.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>A lot of our founding fathers were Freemasons.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Yes, I saw National Treasure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>BYFORD</speaker><content>As did I, sadly. Some odious factual errors. Though it is true that during the American Revolution, symbols like these were used as markers for war secrets and buried treasure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh …  … treasure?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>BYFORD</speaker><content>Like the British gold left behind when they lost the war, or the missing half-dimes, the first coins minted by the US Treasury.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Professor, did Susannah ask you about this symbol?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>BYFORD</speaker><content>Uh … I don’t believe so. Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She was killed last night, and we believe all these symbols are relevant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>BYFORD</speaker><content>Killed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What is it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-16"><speaker>BYFORD</speaker><content>Um … there’s something you need to see.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>BYFORD</speaker><content>She had this letter with her. She wanted to know if it was connected to the symbols. Now, I’d never seen anything quite like it so I uh … well, I snuck a picture of it while she wasn’t looking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> “I, Theodore Rose, of New York City, a loyal Patriot of sound mind and body, do … do make this my last will and testament.”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>BYFORD</speaker><content>Theodore Rose was an 18th century stone mason of some renown, but it’s more than a will. Keep reading, here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> “So I passed to them, still living, this key, which marks the way to our great secret enshrined within the city." And this letter is the key to finding it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Where did she get it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>BYFORD</speaker><content>She didn’t say, but according to the date and seal it was written in 1798.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And the Latin phrases? What do they mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>BYFORD</speaker><content>Well, I translated some of them for her. They’re riddles of some kind. This one says, “ A world turns between the heavens and the ash heap.”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>They’re not riddles. They’re clues. Clues leading to some great Masonic treasure. And this last line could be why she was murdered.  My Latin is pretty rusty, but I think that means, “peril and woe to him who follows this path with the dark heart”.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Beckett.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>So that pattern of scars on our monk’s dome was from a procedure called stereotactic brain surgery.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, can that get us an ID? Because medical records are confidential.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Prison records aren’t. I took a shot that the guy did some time. Nineteen men in the system had this surgery, but only one had scars that were an exact match to the monk. Benjamin Wade. He got surgery to remove a tumor while doing a stretch at Greenhaven for an attempted murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Hear that, Castle? Our suspect is an ex-con. A felonious monk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hey, Beckett. I’ve got no current address on Benjamin Wade, but he did have an apartment in the Bronx before he got sent to the joint.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, check it out. See if anyone knows where he is now.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I don’t think anyone here can give us a line on Wade. Local police says this whole place has been taken over by squatters and crack dens.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Look at this place. I’m going to get hepatitis just breathing the air in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>This is it. It’s where Wade used to live.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Home crap home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>NYPD.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Police!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>NYPD, don’t move!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Benjamin Wade, you’re under arrest for murder.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Recognize her, Mr. Wade?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And this is you, stalking her shortly before she was killed. You care to explain?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Maybe he took a vow of silence. You know, silent but deadly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Assuming he’s a real monk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>WADE</speaker><content>Actually, I am a monk. I just learned to think before I speak. I joined the Franciscan Order of Perpetual Hope after I left prison.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>This monastery that you’re a part of, does it happen to be in Washington Heights? Because that’s exactly where we found Susannah Richland, and … given your record …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>WADE</speaker><content>I’m not that guy anymore. After my brain tumor I had a spiritual awakening. Found a purpose.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Then what were you doing in a crack house?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>WADE</speaker><content>Was tending to the lost. I wasn’t stalking this woman. I was – I was trying to protect her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Protect her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-11"><speaker>WADE</speaker><content>I found her in the monastery chapel. She was kneeling by the prayer candles. Said the place was special to her family. So I left her to pray in peace. And this guy shows up. Brown long hair, glasses, he’s wearing this hat. Starts asking me questions about her. Wants to know what she’s doing there. He’s upset. He seems aggressive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mr. Wade, that’s you following her. Not some other guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-13"><speaker>WADE</speaker><content>I thought that he was going to go after her. So I followed her until she got into a cab and then I came back to the monastery.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Really?  Okay. Describe the cab.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-15"><speaker>WADE</speaker><content>It was a cab.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>License plate? Medallion number.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-17"><speaker>WADE</speaker><content>I don’t remember. It was a Prius, maybe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>There are hundreds of those. A good storyteller uses details. That’s what sells the lie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-19"><speaker>WADE</speaker><content>It’s not a lie. There was an ad for Wicked on top of it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Wicked. That’s nice. It’s precise, Freudian, little detail. But still a lie.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So here’s what’s not a lie. Just called the Franciscan order? Turns out Benjamin Wade really is a monk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And our murderer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Now we just need to prove it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Wait, you guys are on the same page about this guy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Not exactly. I think he’s guilty because of his contact with the victim, the stalking, and his history of violence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I think he’s guilty because of his contact with the victim, the stalking, and his role in a sinister conspiracy involving Freemasons.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I can’t believe you’re really buying into that letter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I can’t believe you aren’t! I did a little research into the author of our letter, Mr. Theodore Rose. Did you know he was a 33rd degree Master Mason?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So that makes him what, like a Freemason black belt?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Way better than that. He was a patriot spy. He wrote codes and cyphers during the American Revolution. Meaning, this letter could be the key to finding the great secret of the Masons, enshrined somewhere within the city.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why, because you want it to be?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Partly. And because it’s the only story that makes sense. A shadowy brotherhood guarding Rose’s secret for all eternity. Susannah got too close, so they sent their monk assassin to kill her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-13"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah, about that. Wade’s lawyer’s here. He says we need to charge his client or let him go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content> We don’t have enough to charge him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why don’t we try to keep him until we do. Put Wade in with a sketch artist. Have him describe that guy that was supposedly stalking Susannah. That’ll buy Castle and I enough time to tear his alibi apart. And just to cover our bases, you look into that cab that Wade described.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-16"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> Really? You want me to track down a cab off a banner ad for Wicked?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Impress me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-18"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>You know, there are times I wish she’d stayed in DC.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>BROTHER SILAS MORA</speaker><content>I’m sorry, Detective, but you’re wrong. Brother Benjamin was in his quarters at the time you say this young woman was killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And can anyone else verify that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>MORA</speaker><content>At least seven other members of our order saw him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And what exactly is the mission of your order?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>MORA</speaker><content>To care for those in need. To live by and share the teachings of Christ.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I think you left out the part about protecting a great secret.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>MORA</speaker><content>I’m afraid I don’t understand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Don’t you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>MORA</speaker><content>No, I don’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ah … thank you … so much for your time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Thank you for your time? That’s it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, until we get the statements from the other seven witnesses.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Look, they’re all going to tell you the same thing. Don’t you see? These monks, they’re in it up to their hoods.  Unless … unless they’re not protecting a great secret and they’re actually trying to find it, too. Because, like the Ark of the Covenant, it is a source of ultimate power.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, these monks took vows of poverty, chastity, and obedience. I don’t see them trying to take over the world.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>World.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Theodore Rose’s letter. There’s that one clue in Latin. Uh …  … “the world turns between the heavens and ash heap”. In Latin the word for ash heap also means altar. The heavens are depicted in that stained glass.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And the altar is right underneath it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So the clues led her to this chapel. But why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The prayer candles. So this must be where Wade said he found Susannah kneeling. Castle, look. There’s something carved in that base stone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s the symbol she drew on her hand. So these other clues …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-22"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Must lead to other places where the symbols are hidden. But what are they for?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-23"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Listen to this.  “For Gods and men alike doth lame Hephaestus strike.” I know what that means. I know where that is!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-25"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah. Hephaestus was the Greek God of blacksmiths. His forge was in Mount Etna. There’s a blacksmith shop right here in lower Manhattan called Etna’s Forge. It’s been there since the 1700s. I know because I was there with … Alexis. It was a field trip. Third grade. But that’s – that’s gotta be it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-26"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Our victim was killed with a sword. If there’s an old blacksmith’s shop that could be our crime scene.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-27"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>A clue trail to a Freemason secret the people would kill for. This case just keeps getting better.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So maybe what Benjamin Wade actually did that night was follow Susannah to this blacksmith’s shop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Castle, we don’t even know if she was here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, she was here, all right. On the verge of solving the puzzle when her life was cut tragically short.  This is the place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I never knew this was here.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Wow. This is incredible. Shouldn’t there be a docent or some sweaty guy hammering metal standing around?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah.  Hello? Is there a smithy here about? We have travelled many a mile –  – is this annoying you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah.  You know what? I’m going to check in back. Why don’t you look around here. If this is our crime scene there might be signs of a struggle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oooh.  Have it, want it, need it, got it, need it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>KENNY</speaker><content>You should not have come here looking for the sign, for only death awaits you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well now, that wouldn’t happen to be a double edged saber with a crenellated hilt, now would it?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>KENNY</speaker><content>You have trespassed into secrets beyond your comprehension. You will pay with your life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay, okay, but just … before you kill me there’s one thing you should know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>KENNY</speaker><content>And what is that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I am really good at this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You’re not so bad yourself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Who are you and what do you know about the last will of Theodore Rose?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>KENNY</speaker><content>For two hundred years my people have guarded the secret. It’ll go with me to my grave. And yours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Now who are you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-9"><speaker>KENNY</speaker><content>It’s not important who I am. The win is yours. The sign shall be revealed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s the symbol from Susannah’s board. She was here. It was you. You’re the one who killed her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-11"><speaker>KENNY</speaker><content>Whoa, wait a minute. You won, man. You can put the sword down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Not until you tell me who you are and why you killed Susannah Richland.  Beckett!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-13"><speaker>KENNY</speaker><content> I think there’s been some kind of mistake here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No, no, no. No mistake. Susannah was stabbed through the throat with a double edged saber. By you or one of your people.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-15"><speaker>KENNY</speaker><content>I’m sorry, I’m a little lost here. Did they change the script? ‘cause if they did, they didn’t tell me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Script.  What script?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-17"><speaker>KENNY</speaker><content>The scavenger hunt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle. What’s going on?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>A scavenger hunt? So the clues?  The symbol? It’s all just a game?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>KENNY</speaker><content>A fundraiser. For the New York Historical Institute. The clues lead to historic buildings where the players collect these old symbols. They hire actors like me to interact with the contestants. I usually work Renaissance Faires.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Was this woman one of your contestants?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>KENNY</speaker><content>Yeah. She came through here …  … a couple days ago. She was killed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, with a saber almost exactly like the one you were using.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>KENNY</speaker><content> That was a stunt weapon. It’s harmless. They all are. I didn’t kill anybody. I’m just an actor. I wasn’t even working here last night. Look, please. Call the New York Historical Institute. Talk to Nolan Burns, the director. This is all just a game.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>NOLAN BURNS</speaker><content>Of course it was just a game. Every year more and more historic New York buildings are torn down. And as director of the Historical Institute I was looking for a fun way to raise awareness.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mr. Burns, these symbols that Susannah Richland took pictures of, are those also a part of the game?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>BURNS</speaker><content>Yes, these are all symbols I used in the game. Looks like she found them all. She might have won.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Is it possible that someone could have killed her to get a competitive edge?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>BURNS</speaker><content>The prize money is $2500. Some of the contestants spent more than that in travel expenses.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Could these symbols mean something else? Something dangerous?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>BURNS</speaker><content> Not that I’m aware of. I do know they can be found on buildings dating as far back as the 1700s, which is why I used them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s just – our victim had this letter on her, from an 18th century Freemason named Theodore Rose. In it he speaks of a great hidden secret.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>BURNS</speaker><content> To be enshrined in the city. The letter was part of the game. We had it handwritten on parchment. One for each contestant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>But Rose is real. He had a penchant for clues and cyphers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-11"><speaker>BURNS</speaker><content>Exactly. He brought some authenticity. And the fact that he was a Freemason and a friend of George Washington’s made Rose the perfect person on whom to base the game. So I drew from his writings and the rest I pulled from Freemason history. But none of this is real. I don’t see how any of this would lead to someone’s death.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Regardless, I’m going to need the names of all of the contestants.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-13"><speaker>BURNS</speaker><content>You’d have to check with the event planning company, Games Ultra. They handled the registration.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I can’t believe all this time it was all just make believe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, you didn’t really believe that this was going to lead to some great Freemason treasure, did you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No. Of course not. That would be foolish.  Now if you’ll excuse me, I’m going to go home to wallow in what is perhaps the most disappointing day of my crime solving career.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay. I’ll come by later and try to cheer you up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Did we get the list of contestants from Games Ultra?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yep, and the contestant applications had to include a photo. Take a look at this dude.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What about him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, check out the sketch that our monk gave us of the guy that he says was following Susannah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s the same guy.  Okay, so … what do we know about Tom Stevens?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, his name and address are bogus. Everything on the application is. None of this information is real.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>He has to be the guy who killed her. He was at the monastery. And why else would he sign up with a fake name?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, his name might be fake, but his money real.  And there you go. He paid with a check. If we can trace that payment …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>We might be able to ID him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>All right, see where Games Ultra keeps their accounts and hit that bank first thing in the morning. I want this guy found.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Richard? Richard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’m sorry, what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>What is all this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Just some … game.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Well, you might want to pay attention to the real world for a moment. Alexis is furious with you over your behavior at dinner the other night and I must say, I agree.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>C’mon, it wasn’t that bad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>You insulted her apartment, you made fun of her boyfriend’s career –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Mother, he’s counting bees.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Yes, and it is important to him, as Alexis is important to him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I just don’t even understand. Why is she even with him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-11"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content> This is what she wants. Now will she want it next week or next month? Who knows? But this is what she wants today, and if you want her to be a part of her life, then you are going to have to change your point of view.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You’re right, Mother.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-13"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Course I’m right. Good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Point of view.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>This isn’t a game. This isn’t a game at all.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No luck. The bank says Mr. Stevens paid with a check, but it was a cashier’s check. There’s no way to trace it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hiding his identity, following our victim just before she died. This had gotta be our killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Okay. I finally tracked down that cab that our victim got into. The one with the banner ad for Wicked on top?  At first I had to call the theater where Wicked was playing. They directed me to a PR firm who then sent me to an ad agency who sells space on the top of cabs, five cabs had –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Did you talk to the cabbie or not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yes. Yes, I did. The cabbie confirmed that he picked up Susannah in Washington Heights at 10:10PM.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So our monk was telling the truth. Okay, where did the cabbie take her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>That’s the odd part. He didn’t take her anywhere.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What do you mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Susannah just had him drive around the neighborhood for forty-five minutes and then dropped her back off at the chapel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That doesn’t make any sense. Why would she go back there the same night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’ll tell you why. Because Susannah realized it wasn’t just a game.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, please don’t tell me that you’re still on –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No, no, no. Just listen. Burns told us that he based the game on some of the writings of Theodore Rose. Now, what if Rose’s clues were real and actually lead somewhere? What if Susannah figured that out?  Here are all our symbols. They didn’t seem to relate to each other, until you add this one. The one Susannah drew on her hand. The one she found at the chapel the night she was killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>They all fit together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The final piece. Without it the other didn’t fit. That’s why the killer scraped it off her hand. He didn’t want her or anyone else to be able to figure it out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-16"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Okay, so the pieces fit together. What do they mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> I don’t know. But does this shape look familiar? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yes it does.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Amazing, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah. But what does it mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It means that this isn’t part of any game. All those symbols put together indicate this carving. It has to have some kind of significance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle … look at this.  Each one of these symbols has a small letter next to it.  R … O … S … I.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Rosi? Maybe it’s supposed to be his name: Rose.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No … that’s an I. Um … maybe it’s roi, like French for king? Or soir for evening …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No, wait.  Earth, air, water, fire, ether in the center. In Medieval alchemy these are the five elements that make up the universe, but there’s an order of importance: earth, air, water, fire. Put the letters in that order it’s O … R … I … S.  Oris. Latin for mouth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’m just kidding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I can’t believe you fell for that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>There is something in here, though. Hang on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Susannah was here. This is our crime scene.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>There’s our murder weapon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, look at this.  These marks are fresh. Someone was trying to get inside it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Susannah must have come to the chapel that night and figured out how to get in here, just like we did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Except the killer found her before she was able to open the sarcophagus.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> What do you think’s inside?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I don’t know, but someone thought it was worth killing for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay, okay. Just like everything else we’ve been doing, we need to solve a clue to open it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, look at the world.  It’s just like the one in the stained glass above the altar.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>“The world spins between the heavens and the ash heap.” … ashes to ashes. The coffin could be the ash heap.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Which means …  … there. Those are our heavens.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-24"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The world turns.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-25"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>1792. These are the half-dimes Professor Byford just told us about. These are the first coins minted by the US Treasury. These are worth a fortune!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-26"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Now we have our motive for murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-27"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Just one of these went for auction last year. 1.5 million dollars. There’s gotta be a thousand in here. Do you have any idea what that’s worth?  I just told you what it’s worth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-28"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What was that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-29"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>If I had to guess, I’d say something bad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-30"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No! No!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-31"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oops.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, put the bag of coins back in the coffin. Maybe it’ll open up the door again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Good idea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Rats. This is not my idea of going to the chapel with you. You have a cell signal?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, it doesn’t look like it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well then, the letter was right. “Peril and woe to him who follows this path of dark heart.” This is it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, we’re not going to die in here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You saw how thick those walls were. They’re made of stone. We can yell and scream all day long. No one’s going to hear. It’s not like they stocked up this place with supplies. And what’s going to happen when we get tired of eating candle wax?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, we’re going to get out of here. There has to be a way out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay, yeah. You know what? You’re right.  This is just Theodore Rose testing us. There’s got to be another clue. Another puzzle. Something to do with his name. What if – what if it’s an anagram?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Theodore Rose … is … head or toes. No. Theodore Rose … he do rooster.  That’s inappropriate. Okay, Theodore Rose, Theodore Rose. Deer shot oreo. Oh, they didn’t have Oreos in the 1700s.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, there might be another way out of here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’m all ears.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Susannah’s killer knows that the half-dimes are still in here. Eventually he’s going to have to come back to get them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He must be someone who knew they existed in the first place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Someone who knew all of this was real.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And who better than the person who wanted everyone to think this was just a game? Nolan Burns.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Nolan Burns. The director of the Historical Institute.  Castle, I’ve got bars.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Finally.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-19"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>S’up, Beckett?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Espo, you need to get to the chapel now. And tell Ryan to pick up Nolan Burns.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mr. Burns, you left out a few details the last time we spoke.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>BURNS</speaker><content>I don’t know what you mean.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>BURNS</speaker><content>You found them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So it wasn’t just a game.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>BURNS</speaker><content>No. That letter we gave the contestants was based on an actual letter I found hidden in a building I was renovating. I tried to follow the clues myself, but I couldn’t solve them all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You set up a scavenger hunt to solve clues through crowdsourcing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>BURNS</speaker><content>I never thought anyone would get hurt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Not hurt, Burns. Murdered.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-9"><speaker>BURNS</speaker><content>Yeah, but not by me. I swear. I told you. I was at home with my family the night she died.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You also told me that you didn’t know Susannah. I spoke with your assistant. You met with her three months ago. How did you fail to mention that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-11"><speaker>BURNS</speaker><content>Because I knew how it would look!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And now it looks even worse. Now, why did you meet with her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-13"><speaker>BURNS</speaker><content>Because I hoped she could shed some light on the Rose family history. You know, something that might help solve that last clue. But that was it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Wait a minute. Go back. Susannah was an accountant. Why would she know anything about the Rose family?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-15"><speaker>BURNS</speaker><content>Because. She was a direct descendant of Theodore Rose. The legend of the missing half-dimes was family lore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Family lore.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>HENRY</speaker><content>Hey. They said you found something out about my cousin’s murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We did. We just have to go over a few things first. Now according to her phone records, she called you more frequently over the last few months. Is there any reason why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>HENRY</speaker><content>I got the feeling she was lonely.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And did she ever mention Theodore Rose?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>HENRY</speaker><content>No. Why would she?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So you’re familiar with the lore. The missing half-dimes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>HENRY</speaker><content>Yeah, sure. It was a big family myth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Except it wasn’t. Susannah actually located the coins. They were in a hidden crypt. That’s where she was killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-9"><speaker>HENRY</speaker><content>That’s terrible. Do you know who did it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Most likely someone who knew was she was looking for. CSU found two sets of DNA in that crypt. One was from Susannah, one was from her killer. Now, on a hunch I had them compare the two. And the results indicate that Susannah and her killer were related.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>CSU also found a synthetic hair found in a wig, not unlike this one.  You signed up for the game under a false name. You used a disguise so you could track her progress. It’s over, Henry. We know it’s you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-12"><speaker>HENRY</speaker><content>My mom’s in assisted living. I work hard but I barely get by. Those half-dimes were going to change my life. But Susannah said that she was going to find them and then just give them all away. Said they were part of history. That they belonged to the people. She called me that night with the good news. And I tried to talk her out of it one last time. We argued.  And the next thing I knew …</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, I was looking through the records and I found out there have been several Rose family weddings in that chapel. Susannah had even been there once, years ago. She must have remembered seeing that stained glass window.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s how she was able to figure out that last clue when no one else could.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>And why Henry scraped it off her hand. So he could be the only one to ever find it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So what’s going to happen to the half-dimes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, they were found in the chapel, so they belong to the monastery.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Put the monks' vow of poverty to the test.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, they’ve already passed that with flying colors. Because of the historical significance of the coins they’re donating them to the Met.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hmm. You know –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Oh, here we go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>- it’s believed that George Washington had those half-dimes minted for Martha Washington’s silver. Back then, before the Revolution, it was illegal for anyone but a king to make money. So those coins were worth a lot more than just their silver. They were actually more of a declaration of independence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well then, it’s right that they’re going back to the people. Just like Susannah wanted.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Speaking of independence… I’ve gotta go see Alexis.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hi. Can I come in?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content> We can talk here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Look, I’m … sorry. About how I acted.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Being sorry isn’t enough, Dad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Then what can I do? What can I do to make this right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-6"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Do you know I found out you had proposed to Beckett?  Over the phone, with Gram. While I was in Costa Rica.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> This is about Beckett?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-8"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>No. But I was hurt you didn’t tell me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Look, I was going to tell you. It just … it just happened.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-10"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>I know it did. And I don’t know if it’s a good idea or if she’s really the one, but you know what? I accept it. You know why? Because she makes you happy. The same way Pi makes me happy. All I want is the same thing I’m giving you. Acceptance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay then. I accept him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-12"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>No you don’t. Because it’s not about what you say, it’s about what’s inside. I know it’s there now and I don’t want Pi to feel that from you. And I don’t want to feel that, either.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Look … I’ll work on it. I will.  In the meantime, how about we go out for some makeup ice cream, okay? My treat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-14"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>No. I need time to stop being mad. And you need time to figure out a way to be okay with this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-15"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>I’ll see you later, Dad.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>