<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>


<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>RICHARD CASTLE</speaker><content>What if we got married on the Cyclone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>KATE BECKETT</speaker><content>The rollercoaster at Coney Island?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>C’mon! How much fun would that be?  And talk about an appropriate, if not slightly on the nose, metaphor. A bride and groom together, side by side, as they go through the ups and downs, the twists and turns, and the loopty-loops of life?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, I love you. But I will not marry you on a ride or up in space or on a slide.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I bet Dr. Seuss got married somewhere fun.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yes. His wife’s living room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>How many people do you think can fit in one of those rollercoaster cars, anyway? Twenty, thirty?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s a good point. We should determine exactly whom we are going to invite.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Yeah. Good idea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That way we can determine exactly how big a rollercoaster car we need to build.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Or how big of an actual venue we need. Either way, I’ll go and get the paper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’ll get a pen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And I will get the phone.  Beckett.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You know, there’s a good argument for keeping the list really small. Just immediate family.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>This argument doesn’t have something to do with a certain amusement park ride, does it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’m being serious. Getting married is an intimate act and our ceremony should reflect that intimacy.  And that way we can all fit in one car. Ryan, how do you feel about rollercoasters?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>KEVIN RYAN</speaker><content>Ooh, make me nauseous. Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> No reason.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Who’s our victim?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Peter Cordero, 26. According to the super he lives alone. He’s a futures trader at J.P Harding, the Wall Street investment firm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And how was he killed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Uh, single GSW to the chest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It looks like his own future got traded.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, not without a fight first. Who found the body?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, that’s an interesting question. At 10:03PM a woman made a 911 call from a payphone down the block. But she refused to leave her name.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>A payphone down the block? But how would she know she was dead, unless –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Unless she was in the apartment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>LANIE PARISH</speaker><content>Well, lividity places the time of death between 8 and 10, so if the 911 call came in at 10: 03 …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She could be our killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Esposito’s checking security cam footage. Hopefully we caught her on tape.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Now, is it just me or is it odd that our victim is wearing a suit jacket, tie, pants, shoes … but his shirt is unbuttoned?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>It’s odd, all right. And look at this.  His shirt was on and buttoned when he was shot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So our killer unbuttoned his shirt after he was dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Yep.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The killer was looking for something. A pricey necklace.  Ooh, a bunch of cash strapped to his chest like Wolf of Wall Street.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-23"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>There’s something else. I didn’t find any defensive wounds. So if there was a fight out there, I don’t think this guy was in it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-24"><speaker>JAVIER ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yo, Beckett. There are no security cameras in the lobby, but I found on in the liquor store down the street. It got a shot of that payphone right when that 911 call came in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-25"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, canvass the neighbors. See if anyone saw her in the building.  Did you talk to next of kin yet?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-26"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, the guy didn’t have any immediate family, but he did list a cousin in Queens, a Maria Cordero, as his in case of emergency.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-27"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>All right, bring her in. Let’s see if she recognizes the woman in the photo. Castle and I will go to his place of work and see what they know there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-28"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Right.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>MARIA CORDERO</speaker><content>No. No. I’m sorry. I don’t know her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Maria, did your cousin say anything about having a girlfriend?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>MARIA</speaker><content>No. He said he didn’t have time. Work was his life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Were the two of you close?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>MARIA</speaker><content>Peter was like my brother. When he was 10 his parents died in the big earthquake in Venezuela. My parents adopted him and brought him to the States.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Did Peter say anything about having any enemies?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>MARIA</speaker><content>No. Peter was a sweet guy. He never forgot where he came from, not like those privileged, silver-spoon guys he worked with. He was a scholarship kid, so everything that he got was through hard work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>When did you talk to him last?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>MARIA</speaker><content>A few days ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>How did he seem?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>MARIA</speaker><content>Stressed, actually.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Did he say what about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>MARIA</speaker><content>No … I – I don’t know. When I asked him he said something happened at work, but it wasn’t anything he couldn’t handle.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>J.P Harding Investment Bank. This place is either the engine of capitalism or the poster child of greed and corruption, depending on which paper you read.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Maybe the invisible hand of the market killed Peter. It would explain the lack of defensive wounds. You know, prep school buddy of mine came to work here after college. He made a quarter of a billion dollars before he was 30, retired, and bought an island.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Wait, he owns his own island? We should definitely invite him to the wedding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Excuse me?  Hi, I’m Detective Beckett. We need to speak with Peter Cordero’s boss. Jamie Burman, I believe?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>RECEPTIONIST</speaker><content>Can I tell him what it’s regarding?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>JAMIE BURMAN</speaker><content>Killing. Are you capable of it? Because if you are, I will make you rich. Goldman just poached Consolidated’s pension account from us this morning. So I am offering a bounty.  Neal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>NEAL</speaker><content>A million dollars. To the first son of a b*tch at this table to poach an account back from Goldman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>It’s open season, guys. Open hunting season. I want you to make them bleed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Excuse me.  Excuse me, Mr. Burman.  Detective Beckett. Could we have a word, please?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>I told you SEC pricks to talk to my lawyer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I’m not SEC.  I’m NYPD. Homicide.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>Homicide?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>I apologize for the theatrics, Detective, but in this world it gets results.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And here I thought the stories of Wall Street excess were exaggerated.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mr. Burman, I understand that Peter Cordero reported directly to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>Yes. He was my best commodities trader. And one of the nicest guys you’ll ever meet, in this part of the world, at least. Do you have any leads?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Uh, just one.  Do you recognize this woman?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>No. I’m afraid I don’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well according to Peter Cordero’s family, he was having some trouble here at work. Do you have any idea what that might have been?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>No idea. In fact, he was having one of the best months he’d ever had.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What about his clients? Any problems there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>No. Pete was a rising star. His clients loved him. But …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>But what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>Last week I was taking the stairs to the 65th floor – my version of exercise – and I saw Peter in the stairwell with this guy who looked like a gangbanger. All tatted up his neck, a big scar on his cheek. Not the kind of guy you’d ever see down here. And he was handing Peter a package about yay big . When Peter saw me, he looked guilty as hell. So I just kept walking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And you didn’t ask him about it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>Yeah, I did later. But he said it was nothing, so I just let it go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You saw a gangbanger in your stairwell and you just let it go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>This is a high stress environment, Detective. We don’t ask a lot of questions about what our people do to … to get through the day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay. Do you think you can describe him to a sketch artist?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-18"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>I think so.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Great. I need the names of all of Peter’s associates here at work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-20"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>Of course.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Lanie’s got something for us.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Still no indication of defensive wounds, but I did find this when I checked his nails for DNA.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Numbers. 7 2 3 5 9 8?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>He wrote in in pen, I’d say four or five days ago. But that’s not why I called you. Look at this.  On his chest, next to the Y incision.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Look at what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>It’s subtle, so subtle I almost missed it. But I think it explains why his shirt was ripped open. You see this grainy material?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>It’s adhesive residue. In fact, there’s a residue pattern from his belly to his chest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Adhesive?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Looking at the pattern, I’d say your Wall Street wolf was wearing a wire.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>A wire?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yes, sir. We believe our killer removed it from the victim’s body after shooting him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Do we know who he was wearing a wire for?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We’re checking with other branches of law enforcement right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>What about this woman who called in the murder? Have you been able to identify her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know, no one in Cordero’s life seems to know who she is and we have no idea where to find her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I – think she just found us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Oh lord. I’d say your case just got a lot more complicated.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What is it, sir?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>They’re from the US Attorney’s office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You know them?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Not the woman from the photo, but the woman with her is Elizabeth Weston, the US Attorney for the southern district. She also happens to be my sister.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>ELIZABETH WESTON</speaker><content>Victoria. It’s been awhile.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Yes, it has.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content> Who is this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>STEPHANIE GOLDMARK</speaker><content>I’m Stephanie Goldmark, assistant US Attorney. We’re here about the Cordero murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Oh, well that’s funny. Because we have a few questions about that ourselves.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Starting, Ms. Goldmark, with why you didn’t identify yourself when you made that 911 call from the pay phone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>Because I instructed her not to. I couldn’t afford to compromise our investigation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What investigation?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>Is there somewhere private we can talk?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>All right, Elizabeth. What’s this all about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>Your victim was a confidential informant for my office in an ongoing criminal investigation of J.P Harding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Which is why Cordero was wearing a wire.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>GOLDMARK</speaker><content>Yes, and since J.P Harding is on the 65th floor we couldn’t monitor it live. Cordero put it on every morning and turned it in every night, along with the attached recording device.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Only last night he didn’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>GOLDMARK</speaker><content> I went to his apartment to see what happened. That’s when I found him. And the wire was gone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>We think that there was something key to our investigation on that wire and that’s why he was killed. So where are you on leads?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, uh … ballistics is running the slug, but right now the only lead is this sketch provided by Mr. Cordero’s boss, Jamie Burman.  It’s of a man he saw with our victim.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>Well, I wouldn’t put much credence in that sketch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Why? Why is that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>Because Burman is the target of our investigation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Jamie Burman, head of J.P Harding?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>We’ve been trying to mount a case against him for years. Insider trading, securities fraud. We know he’s doing it, we just haven’t been able to get proof.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>GOLDMARK</speaker><content>Not without getting inside. Burman’s too careful. Then last month we caught a break. Peter Cordero was found with a baggie of cocaine during a stop and frisk. With his priors for possession when he was a teen he was facing five to ten.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>You got Cordero to play ball?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>He jumped at an immunity deal. He had already gotten valuable information on his wire recordings, but yesterday he was scheduled to meet with Burman one on one. He was going to push him to open up about some of his deals.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-17"><speaker>GOLDMARK</speaker><content>Cordero may have pushed too hard. We think that Burman made Cordero in that meeting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So you think Jamie Burman is somehow responsible for Cordero’s death?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-19"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>Well, if Burman knew he had incriminated himself on tape –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He would go to any length to get it back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-21"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>Victoria, this investigation is ongoing and exposing it to Mr. Burman or anyone at J.P Harding would break federal statutes. But I thought that this something that you and your team needed to know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-22"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>I’d certainly say so.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-23"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>So I trust that you will keep my office in the loop if there are any … significant developments. Is that clear?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-24"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Of course.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-25"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Sir, I didn’t – I didn’t know you had a sister.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-26"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Oh, well … now you do.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>US Attorney for the southern district. That’s a really big deal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Why hasn’t Gates ever mentioned her before?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I don’t know, but there was definitely a subtle chill between the two of them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>A subtle chill? More like a polar vortex. I’m guessing something happened between them in the past. Something deeply personal that Gates does not want us to know about.  I’ll give you a dollar if you ask her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Come on! Aren’t you curious?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, but I like my job too much.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey, uh … so there might be something to the US Attorney’s theory. I checked Cordero’s calendar. He was scheduled to meet with Burman at 5PM yesterday and whatever they talked about, it got heated.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>How do you know that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>According to building security, the two of them left shortly after and seemed to be in the middle of a fight.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>Yeah, Peter and I had words yesterday, so what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So you didn’t tell us about that when we talked this morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>Because it wasn’t relevant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>How is it not relevant? The video shows you leaving together. Two hours later he’s dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>It’s not relevant because I didn’t kill him. Honestly, Detective, what would be my motive?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What exactly were the two of you arguing about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>A business deal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You looked pretty worked up for a business deal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>There was a lot riding on it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What was the deal?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>Client confidentiality, Detective. I’m not at liberty to discuss it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You had a meeting with Peter before that. What were you speaking about then?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>Other financial matters.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What kind of financial matters?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>Sensitive ones! Any discussion of which, even with law enforcement, would be considered insider trading. So unless you have a subpoena –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Who else was at the meeting?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-17"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>Just the two of us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And what did you do after you left the lobby?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-19"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>We walked up Lafayette and parted ways around Spring.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What time was that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-21"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>Around 6:15.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-22"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Where were you between 8 and 10?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-23"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>At my usual table at Le Cirque. Feel free to check.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-24"><speaker>NEAL</speaker><content>It’s time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-25"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>Now, if you’ll excuse me, I have a conference call with the Fed. Oh, and if you want to talk to me again, Detective, call my lawyer.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Le Cirque confirms that Burman was there from 8PM ‘til 10:25. It couldn’t have been him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Because a guy like Burman isn’t going to get his hands dirty. He’s going to hire someone. No, your sister’s right. Burman’s behind this.  Speaking of your sister –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content> Let’s not.  If Burman is behind this, he will do everything he can to protect himself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Knowing that the Feds are watching him he would be careful to cover his tracks. It’s going to be next to impossible to trace this back to him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So all we’re really sure of is that the sketch he gave us is a load of fictitious crap meant to send us in the wrong direction.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>It’s not as fictitious as you think. I just got the ballistics back on the bullet that killed Cordero. Striations match the slug that was pulled from a robbery shooting at a bodega in the Bronx three months ago. The detectives couldn’t make a case, but their three best suspects were gang members, including this guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Same guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Same gun.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hector Nunez?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, runs the South Bronx territory of Los Caballeros gang. Priors include assault, attempted manslaughter, and conspiracy to distribute cocaine.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>MARIA</speaker><content>No, you’re wrong. Peter had nothing to do with cocaine. He hated drugs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you know he was arrested last month for possession?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>MARIA</speaker><content>That’s impossible. I know Peter. He’d never use that stuff.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Are you sure, Maria? Because he was seen receiving a package last week from this guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>MARIA</speaker><content>No. No. It can’t be.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You recognize him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>MARIA</speaker><content>Hector Nunez. He was Peter’s best friend growing up. But then he got mixed up in a gang and he tried to drag Peter in, too. Afterwards Hector changed. He became dangerous. Peter cut ties with him over a decade ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Can you think of any reason he’d be back in Peter’s life?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>MARIA</speaker><content>Hector was a devil. Peter would have never gotten mixed up with him again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>MARIA</speaker><content>Unless … he didn’t have a choice.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>This is a long way from Wall Street.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>This doesn’t make any sense. If Peter was into drugs, he had enough money to get them from downtown. Why would he risk getting them from someone he knew was dangerous?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>There it is. El Baile Club.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, unofficial headquarters of Los Caballeros. Stay close. If Hector’s as dangerous as advertised things might get a little hairy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hairy’s my middle name.  It sounded a lot better in my head.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Are you sure this is the right place? Those guys don’t look very dangerous.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What about those guys?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ah. You mean the heavily armed ones.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We’re looking for Hector Nunez.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Beckett.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hector Nunez?  Detective Beckett, NYPD.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>HECTOR NUNEZ</speaker><content>Detective shouldn’t be here. You could get hurt. It’s a dangerous neighborhood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah well, maybe I should take you down to my neighborhood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>NUNEZ</speaker><content>Let me save you some time. Whatever it is, I didn’t do it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And I suppose you’ve never heard of a Peter Cordero, either?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-11"><speaker>NUNEZ</speaker><content>What about Peter?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He’s dead.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>NUNEZ</speaker><content>Who did this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well we were thinking you. …  … might be able to tell us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>NUNEZ</speaker><content>I’d never hurt Peter. He was my best friend. When we were friends and the gang wanted to take him, I wouldn’t let them. I knew he could do better.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So how did he end up shot and killed with your gun?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>NUNEZ</speaker><content>Something was going on with him. He called me last week for the first time in years. Said he was into some deal that was going to make him rich. But it was dangerous. In case someone really needed to protect himself, he said he needed a weapon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You’re saying you gave him that gun?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>NUNEZ</speaker><content>Well he said he couldn’t buy one himself because he was being watched all the time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Was that what was in the package you gave him in the stairwell?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-9"><speaker>NUNEZ</speaker><content> Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The deal that he was into, was it drugs?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-11"><speaker>NUNEZ</speaker><content>Not drugs. Money. Something to do with bank accounts.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Bank accounts?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-13"><speaker>NUNEZ</speaker><content>Last Thursday night he came to me, said he needed one last favor. He wanted me to take an envelope to the manager of some bank in Midtown. Suisse Federal or something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Why couldn’t he just do it himself? Why did he need you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-15"><speaker>NUNEZ</speaker><content>He said he couldn’t be seen at the bank. It was too risky.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What was in the envelope?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-17"><speaker>NUNEZ</speaker><content>He said something about transfer instructions. It was sealed, but there was a bank account number written on the outside.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you remember the number?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-19"><speaker>NUNEZ</speaker><content>I wrote it down in case something went wrong.  I guess it did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Not the same six digit number that was on his hand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-21"><speaker>NUNEZ</speaker><content>After I took the envelope to the bank I called Peter at work to confirm it was done. That’s the last time we talked.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hector’s alibi checks out. He was at City of Mercy Nursing Home visiting his mom when Peter was killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Mysterious financial transactions, a deal so dangerous he needed a gun? Seems to me there’s a lot more to your sister’s star witness than she knew.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Than she knew or than she chose to tell us about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Sir?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yo. Talked to the manager at Suisse Federal. He confirmed that a bank account with those numbers exists. But he refused to give out any information on it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Did he at least acknowledge it was Peter Cordero’s account?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>He couldn’t. Because he didn’t know himself. It’s a numbered account, set up for privacy, so the only way that anyone can access it is with a password.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So there’s no way to know what Cordero was doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Unless …  Six digits? Seems kind of password-y to me.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, read it to me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>7 2 3 5 9 8.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Come on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>We’re in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Castle, you’ve done it again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>What’s it say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The balance is zero dollars.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Zero dollars? That doesn’t seem very dangerous.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It feels like the end of a treasure hunt where you open up the chest and it’s just full of sand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-10"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Wait, go to the day Mr. Nunez claims he did the transfer. March 21st.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh my God. 25 million dollars.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Whoa. Looks like some expensive sand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>It looks like it came into the account the day before at 8:34 in the morning and then Hector transferred it out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>A secret 25 million dollar transfer that got him killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-15"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>What the hell was Cordero into?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Any luck?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No. I just talked to the head of Suisse Federal Bank. Given international banking regulations, there’s no way to tell where that money came from or where it went.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Or if the money is even Cordero’s. He could have been moving it for someone else.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Sir, if this transaction is somehow responsible for Cordero’s death and we can’t track it then we may never be able to find his killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>There may be another way.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>25 million?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>That’s right. And your informant went to a great deal of trouble to keep it secret.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>And you have no idea where the money came from?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>No, but odds are it’s what got him killed.  Elizabeth, if you know anything about this …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>Of course I don’t know anything about this.  You don’t believe me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Do you blame me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>I didn’t know. And given the lengths he went to hide the transaction, he clearly didn’t want me to know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Okay, fine. Then I’m going to need access to Peter Cordero’s wire recordings.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>For what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Because there may be something on those tapes that’s relevant to his murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-11"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>We went through them. If there was anything on there we would have heard it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-12"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Not if you weren’t listening for it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-13"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>I’m sorry, Victoria, but those wire records are privileged part of a confidential investigation. I can’t give you access.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-14"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Can’t, or won’t? Do you think I’m blind? Bringing down someone as big as Burman, you’d be able to write your own ticket. The mayor’s office, attorney general. Everything you always dreamed of. But you need Cordero’s testimony. And if he was involved in anything dirty while acting as a witness, it would jeopardize your whole case. That’s why you won’t give us those tapes. Because you’re afraid of what we might find.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-15"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>Taking down a shark like Burman would send a signal to every fraudulent actor in the financial markets. I have to think about the greater good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-16"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Oh, is that what you tell yourself so you can sleep at night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-17"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>You could never play the game, could you? It’s why you’re stuck behind a desk instead of running the entire force down at 1PP.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-18"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>I am not stuck anywhere. And I will never, never apologize for doing my job to the letter of the law.  Now, I’m going to need those wire recordings. Or do I have to go over your head?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-19"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>Anything you find, you bring it to me first. Do you understand? I will not have you screw up another one of my investigations?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Let’s not put her on the list.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> I feel bad for Gates. My sisters can never work together. I tell you, when the two of them went at it, oof.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I wouldn’t mind going at it with Gates’s sister.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Oh yeah?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Mmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>How would you like having Gates as your sister-in-law?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I think I got something.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So on March 21st, Peter Cordero’s wire picked up a phone call from Hector Nunez to confirm that the transfer was done. The call came in at 9:25AM.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s pretty much what Hector said.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, but listen to the next two calls that Peter makes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>He’s saying “I’m calling on behalf of Armando Garcia. Want to make sure that his money was received. Can you confirm the amount?” Then he says “thank you” and hangs up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Who is Armando Garcia?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>We checked with J.P Harding, they don’t have any clients by that name.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So it wasn’t company business.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No. Now, listen to the second call.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>PETER</speaker><content>Is he in? This is Peter Cordero calling.  Hey, everything’s taken care of, but we’re running out of time. We need to get this done in the next couple of days. Is that going to be a problem?  Good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>“Everything’s taken care of.” That must be about the 25 million dollars.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-11"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>But what exactly was getting done in the next couple of days? And how did it get him killed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We need to find Armando Garcia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-13"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah. Unfortunately it’s a pretty common name. There are hundreds of Armando Garcias in the US alone. It’s going to be hard to narrow it down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Unless we can find out who he was calling. At 9:25 Peter would have been at work. He would have made those phone calls from his desk phone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-15"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>If we can get those phone records they could tell us what he was involved in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-16"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>I’ll put in for a warrant. Hopefully we’ll get it by morning.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You know, I was thinking about Gates’s sister and it got me wondering: do you have any family I don’t know about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I don’t think so.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Good. Because this intimate wedding of ours –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh no. You too?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>How bad is yours?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I’ve got over a hundred.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> I’m at three hundred … over that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Four hundred?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, to be fair I am world famous.  –ish.  Look, it’s a first draft. It just needs some editing. Brutal, ruthless editing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, Michael Connelly? You haven’t seen him in over a year. And do you not remember what he wrote about your last book?  No. I think we’ve got our first edit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well I have to invite Connelly because if he finds out that Jonathan Kellerman made the cut, and I have to invite Kellerman because I have to invite Wes Craven and Stephen King.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, but we’ve got to start somewhere.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, I think I know where.  Aunt Theresa? Really? After what she posted about me on Facebook?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She took it down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What are we going to do? We can’t have five hundred people at the wedding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-17"><speaker>MARTHA RODGERS</speaker><content>Hello, you two.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ah, help has arrived in the form of a neutral third party. Someone who was born to be brutal and ruthless.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-19"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Thank you.  Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-20"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Ah hah. Still working on the invite list, I see.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yes, actually. And would you mind joining us?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-22"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Love to. Let me get my list. Oh, you know, I had no idea how many people I needed to invite until I wrote them all down.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Good news, I crossed referenced my mother’s list with my list. We have three names in common.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Wow. Three names. That’s … great. That takes us from what, 585 to 582? There’s got to be a better way to cut this down. Ryan, you guys kept your wedding small. What was it, like a hundred people?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah. That’s all we could afford.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>How did you … contain the list?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> I have a lot of relatives that hate me now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>So the warrant on Cordero’s phone finally came through. Whoever this Armando Garcia is, it has something to do with Venezuela.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s where Peter was from.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, that first call confirming the 25 million? It was made to a bank in Venezuela.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>The second call was to the Venezuela consulate right here in the city. It was a direct line of a senior official there, a Luis Delgado.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Clandestine wire transfers, a high ranking consulate official, all circling around the mysterious Armando Garcia. What was Cordero doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I don’t know, but I can’t wait to find out. Swiss bank accounts, secret money transfers. It’s got international intrigue written all over it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>VENEZUELAN DIPLOMAT</speaker><content>It was just a simple passport request.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>A passport request?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>VENEZUELAN DIPLOMAT</speaker><content>Yes. That’s why he called.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What about the money?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>VENEZUELAN DIPLOMAT</speaker><content>I’m afraid I don’t anything about any money.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Really? I suppose you’ve never heard of Armando Garcia, either?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>VENEZUELAN DIPLOMAT</speaker><content>Armando Garcia? Yes, of course I’ve heard of Armando Garcia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You have?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You have?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-10"><speaker>VENEZUELAN DIPLOMAT</speaker><content>That’s who I got the passport for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Wait, I thought that the passport was for Peter Cordero.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-12"><speaker>VENEZUELAN DIPLOMAT</speaker><content>Yes. Peter Cordero, Armando Garcia. It’s the same guy.  When his aunt and uncle moved him to New York he changed his name to fit in. But his birth name was Armando Garcia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> He was sending the money to himself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You said he was requesting a passport. A Venezuelan passport?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-15"><speaker>VENEZUELAN DIPLOMAT</speaker><content>Yes, of course. Cordero applied to reestablish his Venezuelan citizenship and we were more than happy to oblige.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Under the name Armando Garcia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-17"><speaker>VENEZUELAN DIPLOMAT</speaker><content>That’s right. But um … there was something odd about his request. He asked to pick up the passport in Mexico City.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mexico City? Did he say why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-19"><speaker>VENEZUELAN DIPLOMAT</speaker><content>No. But he was supposed to get it yesterday, at our embassy there. He had booked a flight from Mexico City to Caracas that night.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>He was running away?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Not just running away. Changing his identity completely.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>He never intended to testify. He was just stringing my sister along until he could escape.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>All he had to do was drive to Mexico. Once he boarded that flight to Caracas under his new identity, paid for with a new credit card, Peter Cordero would cease to exist. Your sister would never find him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>But he wasn’t going to leave empty handed, so he made one last desperate deal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The night he was killed, he was preparing to disappear forever along with the 25 million.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-7"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>You just don’t conjure 25 million dollars out of thin air. It came from somewhere.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And given the circumstances, nowhere legal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-9"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>If you’re right, it’ll destroy my sister’s case. All his testimony will be tainted.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So what do you want us to do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-11"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Find the truth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>In order to do that, we need to know where the money came from. And there’s no way to find out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-13"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Uh … maybe there is. You know that secret Armando Garcia credit card? You know, the one he used to buy the plane tickets? We found another charge on it for a computer station he rented at an internet café.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>He was there the exact same time that 25 million showed up in his account.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So whatever he was doing, it was related to the transfer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-16"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>That café has security video. If we can get a look at the computer screen or Peter’s fingers on the keyboard maybe we can figure out where that money came from.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-17"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>And why he was killed.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Sir, uh … you okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Ah … just trying to figure out how to tell my sister her case is compromised without her blaming me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why would she blame you? I mean, you’re just doing your job.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>There’s a history.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-6"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>1998. I had just been made head of Internal Affairs. Elizabeth was in the DA’s office. We called ourselves the dynamic duo. At the time Elizabeth was closing in on a heroin ring in east New York and they had an undercover inside. His testimony was key to the case, but …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He was dirty?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-8"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>He skimmed a few eight balls off the very boss Elizabeth was building her case around. When my office caught him reselling it, she came to me. Begged me not to file charges. Asked me to think of the greater good.  I did my job that day, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-9"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>It hasn’t been the same between us since.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>The security video is in.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>There’s Cordero.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>But the angle is over the monitor. We can’t see the screen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Or the keyboard. There’s no way to tell what he’s doing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Wait a minute. Wait. Who’s that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Take a look at the time code. It’s right around the moment the 25 million got into Cordero’s Swiss bank account.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>It’s him. He transferred the money to Cordero.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-7"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>A covert transfer from an untraceable IP address paid for under an alias. These people look extraordinary measures to keep from being discovered.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Zoom in.  Freeze it.  Wait, that’s Cordero’s boss. That’s Jamie Burman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Why would Burman secretly pay Cordero 25 million dollars?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Only one reason. Cordero must have told Burman about the US Attorney’s investigation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And Burman was paying him to throw the case.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>If Burman was paying Cordero to throw the case then the recordings from his wire were all lies. Burman was feeding the US Attorney’s office false evidence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>And if Elizabeth was building her case on that, she would have been torn apart by the defense.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Keeping her out of Burman’s business for quite a while, if not forever.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-4"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>All this time, my sister thought she was taking down Burman when he was really trying to take down her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The one thing it doesn’t explain, though, is why Cordero was killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-6"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Burman’s up to his eyeballs in this. You bring him in here and find out what he knows.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yes, sir.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>I’m afraid you’re mistaken, Detective. I didn’t transfer any money to Mr. Cordero. Certainly not 25 million dollars.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And yet the moment that you pressed that button 25 million dollars showed up in Cordero’s account.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>LAWYER</speaker><content>You have no evidence that account belongs to Mr. Cordero. Just as you have no evidence that money came from my client.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Then why were you with him in that internet café?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-5"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>They have good coffee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I think there’s a reason why you went out of your way to keep that transfer a secret. I think Cordero told you that he was being forced to be an informant for the US Attorney. And knowing that he would never be able to work again he struck a deal with you. 25 million in exchange for providing false evidence to undermine the investigation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-7"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>What investigation?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know exactly what investigation. And when you found out that he wasn’t going to finish the job, that he was going to leave town and take your money with him, you had him killed. And then you took the wire you knew he was wearing to cover up any recorded evidence of the murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-9"><speaker>LAWYER</speaker><content>That’s all wild speculation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-10"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>Not to mention you have your facts wrong.  You said Peter was wearing his wire when he was killed? I’m afraid that’s not possible.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So you knew about the wire. You admit you were in on it with him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-12"><speaker>LAWYER</speaker><content>Jamie –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-13"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>It’s not illegal to know. And I guarantee you, you will never link me to that payment, so you’ll never be able to prove witness tampering. But yeah, I knew about the wire. And Peter wasn’t wearing it when he was killed because he had already left it for the Feds at the dead drop at Lafayette and Spring.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>How do you even –  The walk that you took together. You were with him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-15"><speaker>BURMAN</speaker><content>I saw him go into the mailbox store and put it into one of those boxes.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="34"><utterance uid="34-1"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Thank you for coming.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-2"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>Of course.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-3"><speaker>GOLDMARK</speaker><content>There’s been a break in the case?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yes, actually. New information has surfaced about Peter Cordero’s murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-5"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>In fact, it seems someone in the US Attorney’s office lied about Cordero not leaving his wire at the dead drop the night of his death.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-6"><speaker>GOLDMARK</speaker><content>No one lied. I went to the drop myself. It wasn’t there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-7"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Elizabeth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-8"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Tell her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-9"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content> Stephanie, if Peter never turned in his wire, how did that day’s recordings end up on your computer?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>See, even though you erased them, the tech department here was able to recover everything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-11"><speaker>GOLDMARK</speaker><content>I don’t know what you’re talking about.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-12"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Standard procedure was to turn them over for analysis the next morning, but you listened to those tapes that night and you heard something you weren’t supposed to. At least not until Cordero was gone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-13"><speaker>PETER</speaker><content>I came to the US believing in the American dream, so I worked hard and tried to be honest in a corrupt government, plants drugs on me, threatens to destroy my future, all because you need someone to testify? How am I supposed to still believe? I did everything I could to play by the rules, but no one else does. So by the time you hear this, I’ll be gone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We brought in the cop that busted Cordero.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He confessed to planting the cocaine. On your orders.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-16"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>Why, Stephanie?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-17"><speaker>GOLDMARK</speaker><content>You said you needed someone on the inside. To make the case against Burman., For the greater good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-18"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>No. Not like this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>When you heard that recording and found out Peter was leaving, you knew it would all come out. So you went to his place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-20"><speaker>GOLDMARK</speaker><content>I went to try and talk to him. But he wouldn’t listen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And then you saw his gun and you made sure that his story would never get out. And then you made it look like he was killed for that recording.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="35"><utterance uid="35-1"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>Detective Beckett, Mr. Castle. I would like to commend you for your exemplary work in the face headwinds from me and my office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh, thank you. But we were just doing our jobs. Following our Captain’s lead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Did you manage to track down that 25 million?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-4"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>Yes. It turns out that Mr. Cordero donated a large portion of it to rebuild his hometown, the one that was destroy in the earthquake that killed his parents.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Are you going to try to recover it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-6"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>Well it’s very hard to reclaim funds one they’ve left the country.  I think that we have better uses for our resources. I should be going, but thank you again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-7"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>What about Burman? Do you still have a case?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-8"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>Well, not the one that I thought, but at least I won’t embarrass myself in court presenting evidence that is untrue.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-9"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Then Burman paid 25 million for nothing. I bet that hurt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-10"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>Probably, but it’s not enough. We will build our case the right way. It may take some time, but we’ll get him. Thank you, Victoria.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-11"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>For what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-12"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>For doing your job so well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-13"><speaker>WESTON</speaker><content>So I know it’s late and you probably want to get home, but after today I could really use a drink.  And a sister.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-14"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Me too.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="36"><utterance uid="36-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You know, in the end Gates’s sister wasn’t that bad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Does that mean we have to invite her to the wedding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, what about that? Our lists?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, we can’t have that many people coming.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Agreed. So what do we do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I think we have to decide why we’re actually having this wedding. I mean, are we doing this not to insult hundreds of people or are we doing this for us?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, for us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well then why don’t we just take a minute and write down the names of all the people that absolutely, positively have to be there. No matter what. To make us happy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>One minute?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s not much time. What if we forget someone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well then they shouldn’t have been invited in the first place .</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Let’s do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>All right. Are you ready?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yep.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>One minute … and go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You stopped writing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So did you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Of course, I’m going to have to invite my mother. And Alexis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah. And my dad and Aunt Theresa.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Right.  Espo. And Ryan, who’ll bring Jenny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mmmhmm. Lanie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-24"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Lanie. I’m going to have to invite the poker group.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-25"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yep. Maddie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-26"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Gates.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-27"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ooh, and Gates’s family.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>