<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>


<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>RICHARD CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh my God, ice cream? Are you trying to kill me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>ALEXIS CASTLE</speaker><content>At least you’ll die happy.  Kate?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>KATE BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh, no, thanks. I couldn’t Not after this amazing meal that you guys just stuffed us with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>MARTHA RODGERS</speaker><content>Oh, darling, I’m sorry, dessert is not optional. Not after I traipsed all over town to find Richard his flavor of ice cream.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Potato chip fudge?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Yes!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Beckett, dig deep. Come – you would not quit at mile twenty-five of a marathon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know what? Why don’t we take a break and you and I do dishes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Don’t even think about it. Gram and I have it covered.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You are not letting them do dishes after they just cooked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>They want to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You’re seriously milking this whole ‘I’ve been missing for two months’ thing, aren’t you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>They are glad to have me back. And if fussing over me makes them happy –  - enjoy it. Like you ought to be enjoying this potato chip fudge ice cream sundae. It’s got that whole salty/sweet thing going on. It’s just – just like me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’ll – get – yeah, I’ll get it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Beckett’s phone.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Look, I know that you’ve only been back for a few weeks and we’re all still trying to process it, but, I’ve gotta say, Alexis waiting on you hand and foot – it’s just a little odd.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You know what’s really odd? An ice cream truck in the middle of nowhere? There’s no kids lining up to buy Bomb Pops around here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, this couldn’t have been the driver’s route.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>KEVIN RYAN</speaker><content>Not even close. I just got off the phone with the owner of the ice cream truck, Sergei Vetochkin. The victim’s his son, Anton, 22. They found him behind the wheel around 5PM.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Is nothing sacred? I mean, who kills an ice cream man, a symbol of childhood innocence?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Maybe someone wanted his money.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Except that today’s cash receipts were still in the van.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>LANIE PARISH</speaker><content>And whoever did this shot him at close range. Two GSWs to the chest with powder burns.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>JAVIER ESPOSITO</speaker><content>We figure the shooter boarded the truck and shot Anton, knocking him back into the shifter. It went into first and that’s why the truck rolled here. The killer probably bolted out the back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Anyone see it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>We’ve got unis canvassing for witnesses but it’s not exactly an area where people hang out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And what about street cams?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Coverage is spotty. We’ll get really lucky if we get a hit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What was this kid doing here in the first place?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>SERGEI VETOTCHKIN</speaker><content>I don’t know why our son would be in that neighborhood. That’s – that’s not where we do business.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, is it possible that he was involved in something that would take him down there? Something dangerous?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>SERGEI</speaker><content>No. Anton was a good boy. Never got in trouble.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Were there any troubles on his route? Anything unusual going on in his life?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What school did he go to?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>SERGEI</speaker><content>Since he was a boy in Abkhazia he loved to draw.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>NATALIE BARNS</speaker><content>Yeah, there was definitely something wrong. I’d never seen Anton like that before.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Could you tell us what happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>NATALIE</speaker><content>Yeah, I’d given the class an assignment and Anton was working at his station like everyone else and all of a sudden he started shaking like he was terrified.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Because of what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>NATALIE</speaker><content>I don’t know. Well, he ran out of the room, but I saw him later in the parking lot getting into a car with some guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What guy? Can you describe him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>NATALIE</speaker><content>No, it was too dark. But I – I do remember the car. It was bright green. An old Camry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Did you happen to get a license plate?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>NATALIE</speaker><content>I – I got a 3, an E, and a K.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>You said this all started when he was at his station. Can we take a look at what he was working on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>NATALIE</speaker><content>Um, yeah. I have to log you into the system.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>NATALIE</speaker><content>What the – his portfolio is gone and all of his projects have been deleted.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Did Anton delete them? Why would he do that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>NATALIE</speaker><content>I have no idea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>It’s CSU.  Ryan.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ryan?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey. CSU got us a lead. See how this cabinet door is open. Just like in these crime scene photos? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay. So?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>So when the cabinet door is closed –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>There’s blood spatter on the door panel behind it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Which means the door was closed when Anton was shot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yep. Now, see –  – this smear of blood on the inside edge of the door? CSU said that this came from a finger, so somebody grabbed the door from the inside, pulling it open.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>If someone was in there when Anton was shot –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>BECKET</speaker><content>They saw our killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>A witness.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah, not only that. I think our witness might be a kid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>They left that on the inside of the cabinet. It’s a permission slip for a class trip. No usable prints on it, but it does have today’s date.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Kennedy Elementary. It’s less than a mile away. Assuming an afternoon dismissal, Anton was shot at 5PM –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Someone from that school was in this van when Anton was killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Someone from Mrs. Ruiz’s second grade class.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>PRINCIPAL SILVA</speaker><content>I can’t imagine it’s one of Mrs. Ruiz’s students. Why would they even be in that area alone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, we’ll know more once our youth officer’s done talking to them. Now, what time did Mrs. Ruiz’s class let out yesterday?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>PRINCIPAL SILVA</speaker><content>At 3PM. And each child was picked up by a parent or authorized guardian.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay. And I’m going to need a list of all of their names so we can determine where they were at 5PM.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>PRINCIPAL SILVA</speaker><content>Of course.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>DETECTIVE MIRANDA DANIELS</speaker><content>Detective Beckett? Mrs. Ruiz and I talked to all the students. None of them seems to be your witness.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Except one of them has to be.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know, maybe we should talk to them again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>DANIELS</speaker><content>If they’re afraid to come forward that’s not going to help.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>PRINCIPAL SILVA</speaker><content>Or perhaps they didn’t see anything. Either way these children shouldn’t be subjected to endless questions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, I understand, but we have to find this witness.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>DANIELS</speaker><content>In cases like this, a child is often more likely to open up to somebody who’s not an authority figure: a classmate, a friend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So … basically we’re looking for someone who won’t intimidate them. An adult presence, in the classroom, that eight year olds will view as a peer. Someone that they can consider one of their own?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>PRINCIPAL SILVA</speaker><content>Okay, but where would we find someone like that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Got it.  Easy.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Thank you, Mrs. Ruiz, for letting Castle spend time in your classroom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, then we apologize for the imposition, but we do need to figure out who this witness is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yes, but being 90% kid myself I have an ability to get into the minds of children.  And I have the perfect plan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I appreciate your concern, Leslie – may I call you Leslie?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Excellent. I’m sure I’m more than capable of handling anything these little charmers can throw my way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>In this case, an eraser.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey, what do you got?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>We chased down that partial plate that Anton’s teacher gave us. That car she saw? It looks like it’s registered to a retired cop, Clark Jaffe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>A cop?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah. Anton placed a call to him that night from the payphone outside the college.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay. Bring him in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>That’s going to be a problem. Jaffe’s dead. Shot to death.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He was shot, too? When?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yesterday. About eight hours before Anton. And I ran ballistics. It’s a match. It’s the same shooter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Okay. I’m on my way.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hey, everybody!  Attention, everyone. Attention. Hey – guys.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Neat trick.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Right.  Good morning, class! Does anyone here know what a writer is?  Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>EMILY</speaker><content>A writer writes stories.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s exactly right. And who here knows a writer?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content>This is boring! Mrs. Ruiz said I can show and tell my instant camera.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>JACK</speaker><content>Mr. Castle, aren’t you a writer?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Well as a matter of fact, I am.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>JACK</speaker><content>Are you famous?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, I don’t know if I’d use the word famous. Some people –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content>My dad says your books suck.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He started it!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yes. Yes, I have a plan.  Aside from me, does anyone here know another writer?  Tell you what. Everyone look to your left.  You’re looking at a writer. Except for you guys on the end, you’re looking at a wall.  We are all writers. If you can tell a story, you can write a story.  So … let’s do that right now. Let’s write a story. It can be about a little boy or a little girl, just like you. It can be as silly or as scary as you want it to be.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>EMILY</speaker><content>Can I write about having a tea party?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Of course you can.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>SOPHIE</speaker><content>Mr. Castle? Is it okay to make some things up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Of course, yes. You can make things up. Or you could, um, you could write it based on something that happened in real life.  Is everyone ready?  And go!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We found a link between our two vics?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Other than Anton getting into Jaffe’s car that night? Not so far. And Anton’s never been in trouble with the law.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You talk to Anton’s parents?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, they’ve never heard of Jaffe. I’m telling you, these guys, they lived in different neighborhoods. They moved in different circles.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> They drive off together and then the next day they both end up dead? They’re connected. We’ve just got to find out how.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I’ve got something else. After Clark Jaffe was killed someone tossed his place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The killer was looking for something.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Thank you. That’s very kind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I was – I just – you don’t like me very much, do you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, I don’t. Not directly. But an experience that powerful is going to find a way to express itself and end up on the page. Even the wildest fantasies are based on a kernel of truth. As a master storyteller, I’m able to separate the make believe from the telltale details of thinly veiled fact. You mark my words, Mrs. Ruiz. Somewhere in this pile is the key to identifying our witness.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I followed up on Jaffe’s car. There’s no GPS, no EZ-pass, there’s no way of finding out where he and Anton went that night. Okay, what about you on financials?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>For an ex-cop, the guy lived like a monk. So did Anton, which is part of our problem. The kid had no cell phone, no credit cards to pull. There’s gotta be a connection between these two guys. I’m just not finding it. But here’s what I don’t get. What’s a 22 year old ice cream man doing with an ex-cop anyway?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I may have a lead on that. I was looking into the ice cream truck. It was ticketed last week up on Marble Hill, which is nowhere near Anton’s route.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So…?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>So I checked in to Clark Jaffe’s financials. Jaffe’s credit card shows that he parked at a meter the exact same block on the same day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s not a coincidence.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>This is traffic cam footage of Anton’s truck that day. Now watch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>He goes into that shipping store. What’s he doing in there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I have no idea. But I scrubbed all the footage. This is from an hour earlier.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>A green Camry.  And that’s Clark Jaffe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Going into the same store.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So what were the two of them doing?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I found it!  I think I found our witness. Right here. It’s Jack. He wrote a story about an evil giant, which, from a child’s perspective, is how the killer would seem. He said that the giant spoke in a loud, angry voice, said mean things, and promised he would hurt someone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yes, but in this story the giant had a gun.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Keep moving! Move up! Cover me!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>JACK</speaker><content>Got him!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Nice work! Wait a minute …  … I think I see more bad guys ahead. Uh oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>JACK</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s a giant. And does he? Yeah, he does. He’s got a gun.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>JACK</speaker><content>Oh no, get down. He’s going to shoot it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You think?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>JACK</speaker><content>He did last time. He said, “I’m gonna shoot.” Then he did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Last time, like in your story?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>JACK</speaker><content>Yes. He shot his gun. Bang, bang! And then the other guy was bleeding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Only, it wasn’t a story, was it, Jack? It really happened.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-12"><speaker>JACK</speaker><content>I was scared. I closed my eyes until the giant disappeared.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hey, man. You were very brave.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-14"><speaker>JACK</speaker><content>That’s not what my brother said.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Your brother was there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-16"><speaker>JACK</speaker><content>He said, “Don’t be a chicken, it’s just a movie.” Then he changed the channel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The giant was on TV?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-18"><speaker>JACK</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-19"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content>Mr. Castle wet his pants! Mr. Castle wet his pants!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh. No, no. It’s just – the ground was wet.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>CLERK</speaker><content>Yeah, Anton and Mr. Jaffe. They come in here a lot.  Uh, Anton rented a PO box here about six months ago. Box 552. And he shared it with Jaffe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>They were sharing a PO box?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>CLERK</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What kind of mail were they getting?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>CLERK</speaker><content>That’s the thing. They weren’t getting any mail. At least, not that I ever saw.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Then why did they need the box?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>CLERK</speaker><content>All I know is they both came in twice a week to check it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Together?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>CLERK</speaker><content>No. Usually about an hour apart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>They were using it as a dead drop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, but for what?  When was the last time you saw them?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-12"><speaker>CLERK</speaker><content>I saw them both last week. But Anton came in yesterday. And he seemed a little worked up after I told him about the phone call I got.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What phone call?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-14"><speaker>CLERK</speaker><content>Some dude with a Russian accent called and asked me who owned box 552. Anton’s box. I told the caller we don’t give out that kind of information. But when I mentioned the call to Anton, he flipped out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-15"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So Anton knew this guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-17"><speaker>CLERK</speaker><content>I guess so, because he went in to total panic mode. Said he had to use the phone. But I couldn’t let him use it. It’s against company policy, so he just raced out of here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What time was that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-19"><speaker>CLERK</speaker><content>Three o’clock.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay. Thanks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>3PM? That’s two hours before Anton was killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-22"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Sounds like this Russian dude was coming for him. Who do you think Anton was trying to call? Jaffe?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Or someone else connected to all of this. Look, Anton didn’t have a cell. So if he really needed to make a call, he’d go nearby.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-24"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I’ll canvass all the stores near here, see if anyone let Anton use their phone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-25"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Great.  And school’s almost out. I’ll get ahold of Castle and see if he’s gotten any closer to finding our witness.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Uh, no breakthroughs yet, but the good news is um … it looks like they’ve accepted me as one of their own.  Okay guys, give me the wallet. That was a gift.  Ow. Right in my –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Wait, what is going on over there? Is there a problem?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No, everything’s fine. I’ll talk to you tonight. Okay, ‘bye ‘bye.  Okay guys, very funny. Give me back the wallet now.  Mrs. Ruiz, a little help here?  No?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>EMILY</speaker><content>Mr. Castle?  Are you okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, yes, I am. I’m fine. Thank you, Emily. Very kind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>EMILY</speaker><content>I know how it feels. Sometimes bad things happen to me, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>They do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>EMILY</speaker><content>Uh huh. Really bad things. Things I didn’t want to tell Mrs. Ruiz when she asked me this morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, things like what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-10"><speaker>EMILY</speaker><content>Like yesterday, I was –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-11"><speaker>EMILY</speaker><content>Will you be here tomorrow?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You can count on it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So Esposito confirmed with Emily’s parents that her 14 year old brother was supposed to be watching her that day, but he was playing video games and he didn’t check on her for hours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So she could have sneaked out. It is her, Beckett. I knew it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Which is why we should have talked to her at her place last night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And risk intimidating her? No, no, this girl – she’s ready to open up to me. We have … a special connection.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Really?  Should I be worried?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Only that I’m going to solve the case before you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Where do you think you’re going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Um … second grade?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-10"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Not without finishing your breakfast.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I ate most of it and I just – I’m late.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-12"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Come on, Dad. Just one more bite.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Alexis, I do not have time –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-14"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Now, don’t forget your lunch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay, you’re right. It’s weird. I’ll talk to her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>But right now, I’m late for a tea party.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Thank you so much. Oh, that’s plenty. Did you make this tea yourself?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>EMILY</speaker><content> Uh huh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I have to say, it’s excellent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>EMILY</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No, thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>EMILY</speaker><content>Do you want some sugar?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Actually, I’m trying to cut back. Do you have any low calorie fairy dust?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>EMILY</speaker><content>Uh huh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Perfect.  Mmm… delicious, thank you very much. And thank you for spending recess with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>EMILY</speaker><content>You’re welcome. Do you want to build an ice palace?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s only my favorite thing to do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Here we go. That’s nice.  You know, Emily … do you remember yesterday? You said that something really bad happened. Something –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-13"><speaker>EMILY</speaker><content>You’re making the wall too high.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh. Sorry.  Is that better?  You said it was something that you didn’t want to tell Mrs. Ruiz about. Do you think maybe you’d want to tell me?  Okay. You know, you could, if you wanted. It would just be one princess to another.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-15"><speaker>EMILY</speaker><content>Because princesses help each other?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Because princesses help each other.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-17"><speaker>EMILY</speaker><content>It’s about Jason.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Jason … the kid who makes faces Jason?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-19"><speaker>EMILY</speaker><content>He’s a bully. He says mean things and pulls my hair. This morning, he stepped on my foot. On purpose.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Emily, do you know why people do mean things?  Because it makes them feel strong. Really though, you and me? We’re the strong ones. We just keep our strength inside. So sometimes we forget it’s there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-21"><speaker>EMILY</speaker><content>Like sometimes I forget I have gum in my pocket.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Exactly. So, next time Jason does something mean, you just use that strength and just let it go. When he sees he can’t upset you, he’ll stop bothering you. Okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-23"><speaker>EMILY</speaker><content>Can I go out and play now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-24"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Of course. I’ll take care of these dishes and finish the palace.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-25"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Go ahead. Gloat. Maybe this was a dumb idea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-26"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I guess I am, aren’t I?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-27"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Thank you …  … Leslie?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-28"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Right.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content>She punched me in the nose!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>EMILY</speaker><content>It was my inside strength. I let it go, like Mr. Castle said.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content>You told her to hit me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What? No, Jason –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content>I’m going to tell the principal!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I – that was –</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>PRINCIPAL SILVA</speaker><content>Mr. Castle, I’m sure that this is being blown out of proportion. But I’ll be candid. Jason’s parents are two high powered lawyers with a zest for litigation. We found out a while ago that it’s best not to upset them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So what are you saying?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>PRINCIPAL SILVA</speaker><content>We gave this experiment a fair shot. But now we have to move on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Principal Silva, please. It – I just need a little more time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>PRINCIPAL SILVA</speaker><content>I wish that I could believe that, Mr. Castle, but have you made any progress in identifying this supposed witness? Any progress at all?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Nothing pops with these financials. If Anton and Jaffe were doing anything illegal with that PO box, they weren’t making much money.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Clark Jaffe put in thirty years, he retired with commendations and a spotless service record. Why would someone like him break the law?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> I’m asking the same thing about Anton. What we really need is Castle’s witness.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yo. Canvass got a hit. The owner of a bodega near that mailbox store said that Anton came in all desperate to use the phone. The guy let him make a call.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>To whom?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>To this guy. Dmitri Kalenkov. He emigrated to the US in ’03 and is rumored to be an enforcer for the Bratva.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Russian organized crime?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Wait a minute. The guy who called asking about the PO box, wasn’t he Russian, too? What if that was Dmitri and he’s the one that took out Jaffe and Anton?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Maybe they were involved in something illegal and whatever it was stepped on Russian mob turf.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So Anton called Dmitri to smooth things over.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>And ended up taking two in the chest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Thanks, LT. Organized crime just got a current address on Dmitri.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>NYPD!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Dmitri Kalenkov!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>NYPD!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hands up, hands up!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>NYPD!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hands up, Dmitri!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Oh, that smells good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Found him. It’s Dmitri.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>He’s been shot. Been dead at least a couple of days.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey, Beckett? Check it out.  Electrical cable? Car battery? Leads?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He was tortured first.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Well, someone might have been tortured here, but it was Dmitri.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Are you sure?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>The only injury I see besides bullet wounds is a blunt force trauma to the back of the head, and by the look of the contusion I would say it was made by that broken chair arm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So if Dmitri wasn’t tortured, maybe he was the one doing the torturing. It fits the profile of a mob enforcer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Which means whoever was tied into that chair broke free, overpowered Dmitri, and then shot him.  How long has he been dead?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>I’d say at least three days.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So Dmitri was killed before Jaffe and Anton.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>And most likely by the same shooter. Same two taps to the chest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, thanks, Lanie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why kill a mob enforcer, an ice cream man, and a retired cop? What were they mixed up in?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I don’t know, but it’s starting to look like a Russian thing with Anton, Dmitri, the guy who called the mailbox store.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, touch base with organized crime again. Let’s see if there’s a conflict in the Russian community.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-13"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey. That was Anton’s parents. Someone just broke into their apartment and tossed the place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Just like Jaffe’s place was tossed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The killer’s after something. Something that our victims had.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-16"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah, but what?</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Bye! Bye, sweetheart. ‘Bye Fiona. ‘Bye June. ‘Bye Sophie. ‘Bye Sarah. ‘Bye. Have a good one, buddy. Jack, you make sure you keep your guard up on that battlefield, all right?  All right.  ‘Bye sweetheart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>GIRL</speaker><content>‘Bye.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>EMILY</speaker><content>You’re leaving?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, yeah, Emily, I’ve gotta go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>EMILY</speaker><content>Is it because I got you in trouble?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, no. No, Emily, that’s not your fault. I’m always in trouble.  Come here.  You make sure you use your princess powers for good, okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>EMILY</speaker><content>‘Bye.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>‘Bye, guys!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Thank you very much, Mrs. Ruiz.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I appreciate that.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>SERGEI</speaker><content>I could not believe what I saw. When my wife and I got back from lunch the door was kicked in and the place was torn apart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Do you have any idea what they were looking for?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>SERGEI</speaker><content> In Anton’s room the ceiling vent was pried open and on the floor, right below it, I found this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Passports?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>They’re blank.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What was Anton doing with these?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>SERGEI</speaker><content>I’ve never seen them before today. What was my son involved in?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> He was studying graphic design. Do you think he was forging passports?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mr. Vetotchkin, I need to ask you. Do you recognize this man?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-10"><speaker>SERGEI</speaker><content>Yes, that’s Dmitri. Dmitri Kalenkov.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And how do you know him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-12"><speaker>SERGEI</speaker><content>He and my son grew up together, back in Abkhazia, before the war. Was Dmitri involved in this, too?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I’m sorry. Just one moment.  Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Beckett, you need to come down here. I found something.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, whoever put this in your pocket –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Is sending me a message. Our witness is reluctant to come forward, but when they saw I was leaving it forced their hand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Have you tried just asking who drew it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I don’t want to scare them off. But I have a plan.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>EMILY</speaker><content>I’m Emily. Who are you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I’m Kate. I’m Mr. Castle’s … friend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>EMILY</speaker><content>Do you like to play princess with him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Uh … … sometimes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>EMILY</speaker><content>Are you two getting married?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>One day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>One day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, so what are we looking for?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>A drawing that looks like it could have been made by the same kid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, these are second graders. I mean, don’t their drawings look the same?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I imagine they won’t need much prompting when we confront them. This has clearly been eating away at their delicate little psyches. Given the chance to unburden themselves –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>All right. Who is our sensitive little soul?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-13"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content>Hey! Mrs. Ruiz! Why are you going through my desk?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Jason?  You’re the witness?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content>I’m not talking to Mr. Castle. He’s a jerkface.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Okay, you know what? He’s the jerkface.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He’s eight years old. You’ve been here for a day and a half and you already have a nemesis?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>How was I supposed to know he’d be the witness?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Jason, honey, I want you to know that you’re not in trouble, okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content>Duh. All I did was draw a picture.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Exactly. But I know that you want to tell me all about this picture. Except jerkface over there –  – he thinks you’re scared and that we should call your mom to come pick you up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-8"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content> I’m not scared!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Told ya.  So listen, I need you to tell me everything that you remember seeing while you were hiding in this ice cream truck.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-10"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content>I – I can’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Jason, believe me. It’s going to feel a lot better letting it out rather than keeping it in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-12"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content>No. I can’t because I wasn’t there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You weren’t?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-14"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content> But I know who was.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Who?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-16"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content>I’m not supposed to tell.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Jason, listen. We just want to help you. Okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-18"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content>It was my sister.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay. Does she go to this school, too?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-20"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content>She’s a grown up. We have different dads. I stay with her when our mom goes out of town.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So you gave her your permission slip that day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-22"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content>She dropped me off, then she said she had to meet her friend, the ice cream man. When she came home she was crying. She told me never to tell anyone where she went or something bad would happen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What’s your sister’s name?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Natalie Barnes!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>We’re going to need you to come with us.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>NATALIE</speaker><content>I was never in Anton’s truck.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I know that you were, Natalie. Listen, whatever you are scared of, I will protect you. But you have to tell me the truth. And you have to start with those passports that you helped Anton forge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So you were involved.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>NATALIE</speaker><content>We were just trying to do something good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Who do you mean by ‘we’? You, Anton, and Jaffe?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>NATALIE</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Tell me about the passports.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-8"><speaker>NATALIE</speaker><content>Anton’s route covered Brighton Beach. And there were a lot of Russians there. And he’d seen so many of them come here with the promise of a job and then their papers would be taken and they’d be forced to work in sweatshops or – or worse and Anton was trying to get them back home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Which they couldn’t do, not without the right documents.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-10"><speaker>NATALIE</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And how did Jaffe fit in to all of this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-12"><speaker>NATALIE</speaker><content>Well, Anton heard that Jaffe had a connection that could get blank passports, and Jaffe worked Brighton Beach as a cop, so he knew what was going on and – and he was sympathetic to the immigrants.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And you were the one with the high-tech design software. That’s why Anton took your class.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-14"><speaker>NATALIE</speaker><content>When I found out what Anton was doing I – I decided to help because I …. I wanted to make a difference.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I don’t understand how this got anyone killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-16"><speaker>NATALIE</speaker><content>The other night Anton was making a passport in class and he saw the photo of the client. And he recognized the man, it was this – this terrible man from his past.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Who?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-18"><speaker>NATALIE</speaker><content>Anton called him Polkovnik. Anton was terrified of him. He said that this Polkovnik once tried to kill him. But Anton said that he had to – to show the picture to a friend of his, just to be sure. Some guy called Dmitri.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Natalie, what did you see in that van?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-20"><speaker>NATALIE</speaker><content>Anton had left a message for me to meet him in his ice cream truck. Away from his usual route. And when I got there he said that Jaffe was dead. And that this man had killed him and that he was afraid that we would be next if we didn’t run. Well then, Anton saw him coming so he told me to hide. And I watched. I watched as Polkovnik gunned Anton down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You see his face?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-22"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Can you describe him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-23"><speaker>NATALIE</speaker><content>Yeah, I can do better.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Wait, are you saying she’s got a picture of Polkovnik?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, in an envelope at her apartment, along with other information on him. Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Because we looked into this guy, Polkovnik.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Suffice to say, he’s wanted for more than just three murders.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Here in New York?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>No, in the Abkhazian region of Georgia ten years ago. He’s wanted by the World Court for war crimes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>He was a militia leader. Committed atrocities, wiped out villages, including where Anton and Dmitri lived. That’s why they fled. Interpol’s been after this guy ever since.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>They got a tip Polkovnik was in New York so they’re tightening the net. Only one problem – there’s no pictures of this guy, so no one knows what he looks like.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>And he wants to keep it this way, so when Dmitri tried to take justice into his own hands Polkovnik killed him. Then he tracked down Jaffe and Anton and killed them, too. He knew that they could ID him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s what he was looking for, the picture that Anton was going to use on his passport.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>A passport that he desperately needs to get out of this country.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, that photo’s at Natalie’s place. Let’s go.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He’s been here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Natalie said it was in the bedroom dresser, bottom right drawer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s not here. He must have found it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> It’s not in the drawer, Natalie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-5"><speaker>NATALIE</speaker><content>The photo was in an envelope. I hid it in an old camera case.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Wait. Jason said he stayed here because his mom was out of town.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Natalie, the – the camera case that you put the envelope in, was it for a Polaroid camera?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-9"><speaker>NATALIE</speaker><content>How’d you know?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Because Jason brought it to Kennedy Elementary yesterday for show and tell. That photo is in Mrs. Ruiz’s classroom right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We get that photo, we’ll get Polkovnik. Come on.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="34"><utterance uid="34-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>The FBI’s been notified. They have agents on the way and their tactical units are sweeping the area around Natalie’s apartment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Where are we on the APB?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Ready to go. And the Feds want to get this on the evening news. All they need is that photo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yep. They’ll have it in five.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="35"><utterance uid="35-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, which one’s Jason’s desk?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Right here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Got it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Behind you!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> You okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah. I’ve taken worse. In this classroom, as a matter of fact.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="36"><utterance uid="36-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Cupcake stampede! Come and get them, guys.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>There you go. One for everyone. Help yourselves. This is just a little thank you to say what a wonderful time I had with all for you. There you go. You’re welcome. I’m going to miss every one of you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-3"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content>Even me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yes Jason, even you. What do you say? Truce?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-5"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content>Yeah, truce.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>All right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>It looks like your nemesis isn’t ready to call it a truce just yet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah. Especially not when he sees what I put on his back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Leslie? One for you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Actually, we have something else for you as well.  This is a medal of outstanding service from the NYPD for your invaluable help with tracking down our witness.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She’s agreed to testify. And with her help, our three victims, along with many, many other people, will finally get justice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Are you kidding? You put up with Castle for two whole days.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No faces. That’s right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-15"><speaker>JASON</speaker><content>See you later.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Later, J. That’s me … </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What’s wrong?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s Alexis texting me. “Be sure you come home right after school.” How’d she even know I was here right now?  She put one of those tracker apps on my phone!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Um, Castle … this is getting a little out of hand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah. I’m going to have to deal with this.  And I think I know how.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="37"><utterance uid="37-1"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Dad, what took you so long? School ended hours ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Alexis, sweetheart –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-3"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>I’m been really worried.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yes, I know. And I think I know why. Because I disappeared. But I’m back now and I’m not going anywhere. I’m here to stay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-5"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>I just keep thinking I’ll lose you again or something terrible will happen. I know it sounds crazy –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No. No, it does not sound crazy. I would feel the same way. Matter of fact, I did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-7"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content> After Paris.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>After Paris. I couldn’t let you out of my sight.  But I know that you consider yourself the adult of the family –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-9"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>For good reason.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>For very good reason. But … but part of being an adult is realizing you can’t always protect the people you love.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-11"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content> Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-13"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Being an adult really sucks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah. And you’ve spent way too much time having to be one. So …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’m ordering you to be a kid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-16"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Don’t you think I’m a little old for that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I am not too old for it, so you are definitely not too old for it. Don’t you think we should at least test them out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-18"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Where do you want to go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-21"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>I don’t know. Ice cream?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>How about pizza? After this case I might be off ice cream for a while.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-23"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-24"><speaker>THE END</speaker><content>CASTLE</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>