<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>


<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>EMPLOYEE</speaker><content>Oh my God. It’s Lance Delorca.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>RICHARD CASTLE</speaker><content>Really? This was in fashion in the ‘90s?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>KATE BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah. I used to rock that in school with my Doc Martens.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You do realize we have a full range of All-Clad at home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>This one’s my favorite. My Nonna used to make me scrambled eggs in it when I was little.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Gotcha.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, so, I’m going to leave the rest of this kitchen stuff here for when my cousin Sophia moves in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You know, I don’t think I’m going to miss this place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What do you mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, the floors creak, we can hear everything Mr. Kubiak does in his bathroom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You never said anything about it before.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It doesn’t matter now. You’re moving out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Beckett.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Thanks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, sure. I’m fine.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>JAVIER ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Which can’t be said for our dead guy. An usher was closing up last night around 11:30, saw someone fleeing the scene. That’s when he found the body.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Did he say what that someone look like?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Just a figure in a dark coat. As far as our vic goes, there’s no wallet, no ID, no cell. But the usher thinks he might be –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Lance Delorca.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Who’s Lance Delorca?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He’s that guy! He’s one of the biggest action heroes of the 1980s and a huge role model for my youth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay. Well, he does look a little familiar.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>A little? He’s the star of all the Hard Kill movies. Ex-Navy Seal Zen master Rico Cruz? With the catch phrase “Time to hit Cruz control”?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, I was never a fan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>KEVIN RYAN</speaker><content>Me either. What’s he done lately, anyway?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Beat leukemia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, he hadn’t acted in years. Suffered a couple setbacks due to drugs and alcohol, had some box office flops, but … Lance lived in LA. I wonder what he was doing in town.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And at this theater. Did he come here to watch one of his own movies?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content> The usher said no. And there was no ticket stub found on the body.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>LANIE PARISH</speaker><content>There is perimortem bruising on his hands and torso. Castle’s idol must have gotten into a fight not too long before he died.  Cause of death is clearly strangulation by ligature.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>A narrow ligature, from the looks of it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Made by a thin wire tied to two wooden dowels. CSU found this in a dumpster.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>A garrote? Who would use one of those?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-20"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Special forces will sometimes, when they want to kill quietly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The bigger question is how they got the drop on Lance Delorca.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-22"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Uh, Lance played an action hero, Castle. Doesn’t mean he was one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-23"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Au contraire, mon frère. Lance was born in Spain where, before he became an actor, he was a member of the CNI, the Spanish Intelligence Agency. He was black ops. This man was a lethal weapon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, well …. Not lethal enough.  Have CSU take a look at the murder weapon for prints. I’ll get ahold of his next of kin. We’ll see if they know who might have done this to him.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>LANCE DELORCA</speaker><content>Every man has his price, El Jefe. Name yours and we can end this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>There he is. Lance Delorca as Rico Cruz, squaring off with El Jefe, the ruthless drug lord, played by Henry Booth. See, in this scene El Jefe has just abducted a brilliant but buxom archaeologist from a dig in Cartagena. Now Rico is trying to pay him ransom to get her released.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> “… I’ve got your zero, Rico. You need backup, just say the word.”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>BROCK HARMON</speaker><content>And I’ll take them all out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I was raised by a single mother. Hard Kill was how I got my brotime.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>That explains so much.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Mmhmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s Rico’s partner in all the Hard Kill movies. Booker Dane, played by Brock Harmon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, the guy from The Indestructibles movies, where all the badass action heroes band together for one last mission.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Before they die of old age?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hey. That’s a great film. And so was the sequel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>El Jefe’s henchwoman, played by Brock’s wife, Naomi Duvray. The one in the black.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>KAT KINGSLEY</speaker><content>Hands off me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>NAOMI DUVRAY</speaker><content>Shut up!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>HENRY ALLEN BOOTH</speaker><content>There she is, Mr. Cruz. Your precious archaeologist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>The redhead, she’s an archaeologist? That strains credibility.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-18"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, in a good way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hard at work investigating, I see.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-20"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Uh, actually, I just called TSA and Lance flew into town two weeks ago. We’re still trying to run down where he was staying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-21"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And I had CSU take a look at that garrote. There’s no prints or DNA, but it’s made out of a high-strength monofilament.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And I found the next of kin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-23"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>The archaeologist?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-24"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah. Lance married the actress. Her name’s Kat Kingsley.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-25"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I know what her name is. While you were having your B-movie festival, I tracked her down. She’s in New York. She’s shooting a film and she’s on her way in now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-26"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>She’s coming here? I had her poster on my wall for like –  – about a minute.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-27"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-28"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know, maybe you should sit this one out, Castle.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>KAT KINGSLEY</speaker><content>This doesn’t seem real, like it’s just a … bad dream.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ms. Kingsley, do you know of anyone who would have wanted to harm your husband?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>KAT</speaker><content>No. Of course not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And when was the last time you talked to him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>KAT</speaker><content>It was a week ago. We tried to meet for lunch, but it never worked out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>A week ago? You two weren’t staying together?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>KAT</speaker><content>We were getting a divorce. I saw Lance through his cancer treatment, but after all the years, the highs, the lows, neither of us had anything left. I mean, it was amicable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you know what he was doing in town?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>KAT</speaker><content>He was shooting a film with his old partner, Brock Harmon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What film?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>KAT</speaker><content>The next Indestructibles movie. Brock’s directing. In fact, Lance was staying with him, so if there was trouble Brock would know about it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>This is so cheesy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ah …  … and by cheesy she means amazing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Come on. Behold the miracle of cinema.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The real miracle is how a girl like that’s hanging out with a bunch of guys old enough to be her grandfather.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s Serafina, the mixed martial arts star. She could beat all those guys to a pulp.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Who’s that guy? Didn’t you make me watch a movie with him in it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Rolf Magnus. He’s a Nordic bodybuilder and a card carrying member of Mensa.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> I don’t know, Castle. Maybe I just like the old school guys. You know, like Eastwood, Bronson, McQueen. Real actors.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, well then check out Clay Biggs. Graduated top of his class at Julliard, in contrast to Brock Harmon, who made his on-screen debut as a pornstar known as Brock the –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>BROCK HARMON</speaker><content>Cut! That’s a cut!  Steve, get me something that works or get a new job.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mr. Harmon. Detective Beckett. This is Mr. Castle –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hi, Mr. Harmon. Huge fan. Huge fan.  I – I’m – it’s an honor – honor to meet you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>The honor is mine. I’ve passed many an hour in the john reading your books.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We’re here about Lance Delorca.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Ah. Sad day for me. And my family.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>NAOMI DUVREY</speaker><content>Here you go, darling.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Oh, thanks, babe.  If you’re a fan of mine, you’ll know my wife, Naomi Duvray. And her jewelry line, too, I hope. She just launched the spring collection.  It’s nice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You were just outstanding as El Jefe’s henchwoman in Hard Kill. I was – </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-20"><speaker>NAOMI</speaker><content>That is so sweet.  I had a mean roundhouse kick but I wasn’t much of an actor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-21"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Well, never stopped me.  Oh, this is my son, Trey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-22"><speaker>TREY</speaker><content>Good to meet you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Um, Mr. Harmon? Could we speak privately?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-24"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Oh. Sure.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Transplant from a bone marrow donor. That’s what put Lance in remission, saved his life. He knew he’d been given a second chance. He got sober, cleaned up his act. That’s why I gave him a part in the movie. This could have been his big comeback.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So we understand that he was staying with you? How did he seem?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Quiet. Secretive, I’d even say. Lance was always a man of few words, but even fewer this time out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And idea what he was doing on the Lower East Side last night at 11:30?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>I didn’t even know he was in town.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You said he was staying with you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Right. Lance wrapped last week. I was told transportation took him straight from the set to the airport.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, well, my detectives will need to speak with the driver. Along with anyone else that Lance knew.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Of course.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Um … what exactly happened? How’d he die?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Um… he was strangled. With a garrote.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Does that mean something to you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>You know, Lance was CNI, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Spanish Intelligence. But what does that have to do with his murder?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Everything. He was a CNI assassin. That was his signature. He killed people with a garrote.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Which is why it was used to kill him. Lance was murdered because he’s the Spanish Jason Bourne.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why, Castle? Because a B action movie star in a kimono said so?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Because it makes sense. Lance was drawing on his experience as a ruthless CNI operative to play action heroes. But his shadowy past caught up with him. Maybe it was revenge for a hit he did back in the day. Kill him the way he killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, he left CNI thirty years ago. Why would his past catch up to him now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>CAPTAIN VICTORIA GATES</speaker><content>Mr. Castle might just be right about CNI.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ah hah! How – how am I right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Esposito and Ryan are off interviewing folks on the set. But before the left they got on to something. They pulled Lance’s phone records and the day he died he made a phone call to Interpol in Spain, to the office of one Enrique Gomez.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What does Gomez have to do with CNI?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>According to his bio, Gomez used to work there, at the same time Lance Delorca did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So Lance reaches out to another ex-agent and he’s killed with a garrote? Mark my words: this case is going to lead us into a labyrinthian world of deceit, villainy, and international espionage.  This is better than one of his movies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>After what I saw it’d have to be.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Yeah, thanks.  Update: I contacted Interpol to track down that guy Lance called, Enrique Gomez. Well, it turns out Gomez is here in New York for a meeting at the UN.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Where was he last night at 11:30?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>On a redeye in from Madrid. He arrived early this morning so he’s not our killer, but Interpol will send him over for an interview. He might have insight on the murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, I talked to CNI to ask them about Lance’s time there. About missions that he was involved in, enemies that he might have had, and they are stonewalling me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Intelligence agencies like CNI avoid disclosing information on their employees. But I do have contacts in the State Department. Let me just ask around.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Great. I’ve reached out to my guys in Washington as well.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey, Beckett. I think we’ve got something from that movie set.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>We talked to the driver who took Lance to the airport.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Only that’s not what he did. Lance asked the driver to drop him off at some seedy hotel on Broome Street.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And he didn’t want anybody to know about it. He paid the driver a hundred bucks to lie and say he dropped Lance off at JFK.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why would he go to this hotel?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, that’s where it gets weird. The unis we sent to canvass said that Lance had rented a room there for the past week.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Under the name Rico Cruz, his character from Hard Kill.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Um … okay. Have unis check for security video at the hotel and uh … let’s round up any of Lance’s personal effects from his room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Thanks, LT.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>You know, I don’t understand. Why would Lance leave Brock Harmon’s Fifth Avenue digs to go stay in a flophouse?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And without telling anyone? He’s definitely up to something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hey! A Hard Kill DVD. Looks like Lance was trying to relive the old days.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> “Time to hit Cruz control.” Maybe that’s what I need.  Time to meet hard justice. Time for prison time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, you keep working on that, bro.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Time to pay the bill for doing the kill.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Okay, on second thought: don’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey. Building schematics?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>There’s a bunch of weird stuff in this box.  A soldering iron? Blue craft paint? A microphone? A USB drive? Both empty cases? It looks like he was building something. Like a recording device.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>And then he added stickers to it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Stickers? What the hell is that about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I don’t know. But the 2 and 5 are missing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Huh.  Trey. Hey, this must be Trey Harmon, Brock Harmon’s kid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Why would Lance call him?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>TREY</speaker><content>He wanted to ask me about the New York club scene. That’s my thing. I’m a club promoter. But I kind of shut him down, to be honest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Why’s that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>TREY</speaker><content>After the cancer he got sober. No way was I going to help him fall off the wagon and start partying again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> Huh.  Do you recognize this? Think it might be the floor plan to a club?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Come on! I barely touched you!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>TREY</speaker><content>I don’t know. I can barely tell what that is. Did Lance have this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah. And we don’t think that he wanted to party. Did he explain to you why he was interested in clubs?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>TREY</speaker><content>Not really. He just said that there was something that he needed to take care of.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>There was something he needed to take care of. I have a theory!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Great. Because right now I could use one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s a classic action movie plot device. Lance, his black ops day long behind him, decides to go on one final mission: to vanquish his old nemesis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Which would be?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s a rival assassin. Who was once his best friend, but then betrayed him and - or actually … a Blofeld style supervillain who killed Lance’s wife and then disappeared.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, but Kat Kingsley is still alive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No, Lance’s other wife from his tragic but secret CNI past. Now, I admit I’m a little sketchy on the details of the mission and the nemesis, but … bottom line is, Lance embarked on a mission. The years caught up with him, he had lost his step. So he was dispatched by another operative who was younger, quicker, and deadlier.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And possibly female. Tory screened that security cam video from the hotel and found this.  That’s Lance, leaving through the hotel lobby on his last day on Earth.  And ten seconds later, this woman goes after him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s her! That’s the operative. She’s wearing a dark coat, just like the person who left the crime scene. She must have trailed Lance from the hotel, then moved in for the kill.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She’s blonde, but she might be wearing a wig. Take a look at her sunglasses and the way that she’s angled her face away from the camera. She didn’t want to be ID’d.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>She may have gotten her wish. Tory said there’s not enough here to run facial recognition.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know, she’s wearing an earring. See if Tory can do something with that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Enrique Gomez is on his way up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Maybe he knows who she is.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>ENRIQUE GOMEZ</speaker><content>Nope, I don’t recognize her.  I’m sad to learn of Lance’s death.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What was your relationship with him, Mr. Gomez?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>GOMEZ</speaker><content>We were close as young men. Less so recently.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yet he called you just before he died? Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>GOMEZ</speaker><content>He needed a bodyguard. Somebody he could trust. And I know such people. But none of them were available on such short notice, so I couldn’t help him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why – why would Lance need a bodyguard?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>GOMEZ</speaker><content>He didn’t tell me. I didn’t ask.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You think maybe he was going on one last mission? Perhaps his CNI past was coming back to haunt him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>GOMEZ</speaker><content>Oh, that would be rather unlikely.  You see, Lance didn’t have a CNI past.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why is everyone saying that he did?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-11"><speaker>GOMEZ</speaker><content>Well, we grew up together, but I was the one who went into CNI. And when Lance came to America he asked to use my backstory to make himself more … mysterious and interesting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’m – I’m sorry. Are you saying Lance Delorca wasn’t a CNI operative?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-13"><speaker>GOMEZ</speaker><content>Before he started acting he was a goat herder in the Pyrenees.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey. So … Enrique Gomez’s story checks out. And with his authorization, CNI confirms that Lance Delorca was never an agent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> My hero was a liar. And a goat herder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yes, well, despite this deeply personal betrayal … we still have a murder to solve.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>How? We’re back to square one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Not necessarily. I mean, there’s still the mystery woman who followed Lance from the SRO.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>TORY ELLIS</speaker><content>She may not be a mystery any more.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Is she a goat herder?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Oh my God.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>TORY</speaker><content>I didn’t get anywhere with the earrings; they’re too common. But that got me focused on her ear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, what about it? It looks normal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>TORY</speaker><content>It is, but ear biometrics – size, shape, configuration – are almost as unique as fingerprints. An entire field of study is devoted to the subject.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Earology.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Earology.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>How did you know that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>FBI seminar.  So, you used her ear to identify this woman?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>TORY</speaker><content>Yes. By isolating the ear and running it against the mug shot database. When nothing popped I ran it against photos of women who had any connection with Lance Delorca. The computer analyzed thousands of images and finally found a match with a 99.2% probability that it’s this woman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s Kat Kingsley.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Lance was killed by his soon-to-be ex-wife?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hey. So we heard Kat Kingsley was here.  Whoa! Now that is a sexy outfit for an interrogation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s her costume. They took her right from the set of her movie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Man, she is really –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hot?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>- holding up well.  What’s the movie?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s direct to video. She plays a female Indiana Jones.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>She’s an archaeologist again?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So do you think it would be weird if I asked her to sign this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>When? On her way to jail?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It would mean so much to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What would her motivation be for killing Lance?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, seems her divorce was a tad messier than she lead us to believe.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So, what role are you playing now, Ms. Kingsley? Not the grieving widow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>KAT</speaker><content>I need to get back to set or they’re going to shut down production on Raiders of the Nubian Temple.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, well, you’ve got bigger problems than that. So I talked to Lance’s lawyer and he said that your divorce was anything but amicable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>KAT</speaker><content>We’re actors. We’re passionate people. Things got stormy at times.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Because you wanted the Malibu house and he didn’t want to give it to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>KAT</speaker><content>That home has sentimental value to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Along with monetary value. I mean, after twenty years it’s worth … eight million dollars. And with Lance out of the picture it was all yours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>KAT</speaker><content>You think I killed my husband?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You tried to before. Remember the incident where you discharged a firearm? At him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-10"><speaker>KAT</speaker><content>I was cleaning it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I know bad acting when I see it. This is you, Ms. Kingsley, following Lance hours before he was killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-12"><speaker>KAT</speaker><content>I was not following him. He asked me to meet with him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And he told you to wear a disguise?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-14"><speaker>KAT</speaker><content>I couldn’t be seen with him after the gun thing. We were told to avoid contact. But Lance begged me. He needed cash. Two hundred thousand dollars.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He asked you for a loan?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-16"><speaker>KAT</speaker><content>His assets were all tied up with the divorce. I inherited some money, he knew I had access to it. It wasn’t a loan. He sold me his half of the Malibu house.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Are you telling me that he traded you four million dollars for two hundred thousand?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-18"><speaker>KAT</speaker><content> How could I pass up a deal like that? I have a promissory note to prove it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why did he need the money?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-20"><speaker>KAT</speaker><content>He said he need to set something right. That he wanted to live up to the characters he played, I think? I wasn’t really listening. I just wanted him to sign over the house. I’m just being honest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, fine. If you’re being honest then why don’t you tell me this: we have a witness who saw a dark figure fleeing the crime scene. Was that you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-22"><speaker>KAT</speaker><content> Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Do you want to elaborate on that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-24"><speaker>KAT</speaker><content> Lance called me that night. From a payphone, I think. He said he was in trouble. And that people were after him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-25"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What people?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-26"><speaker>KAT</speaker><content>He didn’t say. But he asked me to pick him up at this theater playing Hard Kill. That it would be easy to find. He sounded so desperate. But when I got there, he was dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-27"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why didn’t you tell us this before?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-28"><speaker>KAT</speaker><content>I panicked! I’m trying to restart my career. I just knew how it might look.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-29"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, that’s because it’s exactly how it does look.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, not to me, it doesn’t. I don’t think she’s our killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, she’s just an innocent archaeologist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>My opinion is not affected by her skimpy outfit. I’m speaking as an objective investigator. Someone who has set their personal feelings aside.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Along with your poster?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Who told you? It’s Ryan, wasn’t it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, Kat Kingsley admitted to being at the crime scene.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, when she didn’t have to. Why admit to that if you’re actually guilty?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>To make herself look not guilty. Look, she had motive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>But parts of her story still check out: the promissory note, the withdrawal from her bank for two hundred thousand dollars. Lance said he needed the money to set something right. He needed to live up to his onscreen persona.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yes, according to our murder suspect.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So here’s Lance, meeting with his bone marrow donor. Perhaps surviving leukemia changed him. Drove him to become a better man, a man more like the hero he portrayed. That’s why when he registered at the hotel he did so as Rico Cruz. Because he became Rico Cruz.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What does that even mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That despite being an ex-goat herder with no black ops training, Lance took on a mission.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh, okay. So we’re back to one last mission now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Why else would he have the schematic, or the listening device, or why would he need a body guard?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>To protect himself from Kat Kingsley.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-17"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah, except for her story is still holding up. That call she says was from Lance came from a payphone six blocks from the movie theater.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>All right, canvass for witnesses that saw Lance or anyone else by that payphone. And if he was in trouble, as Kat said, let’s find out where he was coming from.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-19"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>We’ll get into it, but we might not have anything until the morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> You told her about the poster?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-22"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I didn’t know it was a sec-</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I don’t know, maybe it’s the way that he said it that struck a nerve.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Well, tact isn’t exactly the man’s middle name.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, but it’s my place, you know? It’s not Castle’s. Who cares if he never liked it? I mean, I don’t know why I got so upset.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Because. To him, this is just an apartment with creaky floors. But to you, this is where you rebuilt your life, where you solved your mother’s murder. Where you fell in love.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, to the best apartment ever.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>To the best apartment ever.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>So we struck gold on that canvass.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Someone saw Lance using the payphone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>No. But they saw him before that, running like hell from an alley.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Which leads us to this security cam video right here. You’ve gotta see it to believe it.  These four guys have got Lance cornered.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, this can’t be good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Who are those guys?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I don’t know, but it makes you wonder what Lance did to have them come after him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Four thugs against an aging Lance Delorca? I don’t know that I can watch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Did you see that? What Lance just did? That belongs in one of his movies! He annihilated them!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, not for long. Half an hour later someone annihilated him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ah, well … right. But at least this explains the phone call. When Lance called Kat Kingsley and said “I’m in trouble, people are after me”, this is what he was talking about.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And whoever these guys are, they must have caught up to him. We find these guys, we’ll find our killer.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We can’t ID any of these guys off of the surveillance video. Tory says that the image quality is too poor to run facial recognition or ear recognition.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The key is finding out what happened to Lance before he wound up in that alley. Something that required two hundred thousand dollars and a listening device. But whomever he went up against sent those four sides of beef after him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And after seeing the ass-whooping they got I checked nearby hospitals. Turns out that an ambulance was called to that area during our time window. They brought a heavyset dude to the ER. He was unconscious, bruised, and had a possible jaw.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>All right, let’s go talk to him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>We can’t. He woke up and checked himself out of the ER before they could even get his name.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Does the hospital have cameras?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I’m glad you asked that. This guy –  – definitely looks like a guy from the video.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>What a second, I know that guy. Yeah, from the film set. He was dressed in Afghan garb. Brock Harmon barely tapped him in the face and he screamed like a baby.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Perhaps because he has a broken jaw?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>AD says his name is Ernest Howe. He’s playing ISIS militant number twelve.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Not for long. You know what time it is? It’s Ryan time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Please. Just stop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Name’s Ryan and I hate lyin’.  Ernest Howe! NYPD.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>We’re here to talk to you about Lance Delorca.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>ERNEST HOWE</speaker><content>Yeah, it’s a bummer that he died.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Got a little problem with your jaw there, Ernest?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>ERNEST</speaker><content>A little TMJ.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Are you sure it’s not from that little altercation you got into the other night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-10"><speaker>ERNEST</speaker><content>Look, I don’t want any more trouble.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Oh, you’ve got trouble. Ryan trouble.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-12"><speaker>ERNEST</speaker><content>I don’t know what that means.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>We have you on video. You and those three mooks attacked Lance and he put the hurt on all of you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-14"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>But not enough hurt, because one of them killed him. Judging by your little trip to the ER, it wasn’t you. So why don’t you give us the name of your buddies, Ernest, and whoever put them up to this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-15"><speaker>ERNEST</speaker><content>You’ve got it all wrong. Those guys did this to me. I was on Lance’s side. He hired me to be his bodyguard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-16"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Why would Lance need a bodyguard?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-17"><speaker>ERNEST</speaker><content>He had a meeting at Club Drift. He wanted backup. He brought a briefcase. I think it had money in it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-18"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Who did he meet there? And what was the money for?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-19"><speaker>ERNEST</speaker><content>I don’t know. They made me wait downstairs. But the meeting? Ended quick. All of a sudden four security dudes hustle us out and accuse Lance of wearing a wire.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-20"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>A wire? Why would he be wearing a wire?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-21"><speaker>ERNEST</speaker><content>Well I didn’t exactly get a chance to ask. The last thing I remember is a guys’ foot flying across my face.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Maybe Lance was wearing a wire. That would explain the microphone and the USB drive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Nah. Ernest said that security didn’t find a wire and there wasn’t one on Lance’s body.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>But … let’s say he was all wired up with a briefcase of money. What the hell was he doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>It’s like Lance was running some kind of half-assed sting operation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Maybe he was. I spoke narcotics. The club that Lance went to is a major hub for drug sales, run by a guy that you’re familiar with, Castle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Is that – is that Henry Allen Booth?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>El Jefe from Hard Kill?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He made a career out of playing drug dealers and then he quit acting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And then he began living the part. Apparently he spent so much time with drug dealers, researching his roles, that he actually became one. Narcotics hasn’t been able to make a case against him, though.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>This is just like Hard Kill. Where Rico Cruz took down El Jefe. Only now it’s one actor taking on the other actor, but the other actor actually happens to be a drug dealer!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>But again, why would Lance do this? Why would he go after Booth?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I don’t know, but it’s so meta!  We should really talk to El Jefe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh, believe me. We will.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>HENRY ALLEN BOOTH</speaker><content>Yeah, sure. I met with Lance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>BOOTH</speaker><content>Old times. He wanted to share a drink. Relive the glory days.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Just out of the blue?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>BOOTH</speaker><content>Why not? Hard Kill did a solid for both of us. Even after all these years not a day goes by where some middle aged dude doesn’t see me and shout “El Jefe!”. I suppose I shouldn’t complain. That role bought me this club.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We hear that it did more than that, Mr. Booth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>BOOTH</speaker><content>So the movie drug dealer becomes a drug dealer, huh? It would be a good story, if it were true. That being said, I don’t discourage it. A good fiction can do wonders for one’s reputation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’ve learned that every good fiction contains a kernel of truth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What happened to the briefcase that Lance brought to the meeting? The one with two hundred thousand dollars in it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-10"><speaker>BOOTH</speaker><content>Lance had no briefcase.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And I suppose your guys didn’t chase him out of here and then attack him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-12"><speaker>BOOTH</speaker><content>Doesn’t ring a bell.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>We have video.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-14"><speaker>BOOTH</speaker><content>Not of my guys. You’re welcome to check. I doubt you’ll find any of them here. And since your next question will be where was I that night, I’ll save you the oxygen. There are about twenty people downstairs that can attest that I never left the building after Lance left. I didn’t kill him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay. Thanks for your time.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>“Thanks for your time”? Beckett, he was lying. About the money, about the meeting, about everything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Of course he was lying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So why didn’t you push harder. Why didn’t we check his alibi?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Because. We didn’t need to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Since when?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Since I figured out what the numbers five and two meant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The missing numbers from the sticker sheet?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The number 52 was on a slot car in Booth’s collection. A blue Shelby Cobra, to be exact.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s what Lance was building. He put a listening device inside a replica of Booth’s cars.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He must have switched them out when they had that meeting.  Which means that car was recording everything in that office. Including why Lance was there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And why Booth had him killed. We need to get that slot car.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We will. We just need a warrant first.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>I don’t understand. You’re telling me you can’t get a search warrant even though that son of a b*tch Booth is behind this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Not unless we can proved evidence that ties Booth to Lance’s death. And right now we can’t even prove that the two of them met. Look, Mr. Harmon, we were hoping that you could help us with this. Did Lance tell you he was going to the club? That he was going to talk to Booth?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Lance never said a word to me about Booth or the club. Nothing. Hell, I thought he was in LA. I wish I could help you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, you know what? We’ll keep looking for the men that attacked Lance. We’re not giving up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Castle.  How did Lance know to bug a slot car?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh.  Booth and his collection were featured in Slot Zone magazine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Huh. So you really think the proof of who killed Lance is sitting in that little blue Shelby Cobra?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, it doesn’t matter if we can’t get a warrant. Too bad Rico Cruz isn’t around. He’s find a way, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-9"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>So you .. .you’re a pretty big fan, huh?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Of Hard Kill? Ah … I was an average, ordinary fan. Not like I had the Hard Kill pajamas.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-11"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Say, the gang and I are going out for drinks later tonight. How’s you like to come with us?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-12"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Castle?  Hey.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You are never going to believe what just happened. Brock invited me to go drinking with The Indestructibles. Me! With them!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>But you told them that you couldn’t because you’re in the middle of a case, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No. What? No! I just – what – isn’t it okay if I –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, you really think that I could stand between you and your boyhood dream.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You are my boyhood dream.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Aww.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, you and drinking with the Indestructibles.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You don’t always have to keep talking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’m going to – I’m going to go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I don’t know what I’m going to wear!  I’ve gotta get ready!</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>All right. Okay. Well, you guys, you have no idea how excited I am to …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You guys just come from set or something?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Son, we came straight from hell. Let’s roll.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So um… what’s going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>CLAY BIGGS</speaker><content>No warrant is going to stop us from getting our hands on evidence to put away Lance’s killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Somebody takes out one of our own, we take him out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, guys. Hey. Listen. If your plan is to go to the club and steal that slot car, no, that would – that would taint the evidence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>ROLF MAGNUS</speaker><content>Actually we can compel the DA to consider it, since the car technically belonged to the victim, Lance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You really are a genius, aren’t you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-7"><speaker>ROLF</speaker><content>And also, none of us is an agent of the law.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-8"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>It’s one of the reasons I chose you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-9"><speaker>SERAFINA</speaker><content>And because you’ve been in Booth’s office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-10"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>You’re going to help us find that slot car.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No. No. No, no, no, no. Guys.  My wife is a cop. If I do this, she’ll kill me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-12"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content> “Oh, my wife’s going to kill me.” Is that what Rico Cruz would say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No. But what if we get caught?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-14"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>We’re not going to get caught. We’re The Indestructibles. Tense up, guys. It’s show time.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>The plan is simple. Once we get to the club, Serafina, Clay, Rolf, go in through the main entrance, take your positions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Serafina, alert us when you have eyes on the rear door.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-3"><speaker>SERAFINA</speaker><content> Falcon is in the nest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-4"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Clay. You and Rolf create a diversion to draw Booth down to the bar.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-5"><speaker>CLAY</speaker><content>Young fella, young fella. We’re doing bottle service. You got some of that Angel, you know, the champagne?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-6"><speaker>BARTENDER</speaker><content>Sure so. Just going to need your credit card, Mr. Biggs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-7"><speaker>CLAY</speaker><content>If you know who we are then you know we haven’t paid for a drink since Reagan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-8"><speaker>BARTENDER</speaker><content>Sir, Angel’s a grand a bottle. You understand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-9"><speaker>ROLF</speaker><content>Sir, we’re here to toast our fallen comrade. That Booth too cheap to pay respects?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-10"><speaker>BARTENDER</speaker><content>Mr. Booth?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-11"><speaker>BOOTH</speaker><content>Yeah?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-12"><speaker>BARTENDER</speaker><content>Got some old friends of yours at the bar. You should come down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-13"><speaker>BOOTH</speaker><content>All right, I’m coming down.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Once El Jefe’s on the move, Serafina, you’ll unlock the villa gates.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>CLAY</speaker><content> Prairie dog is on the plain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>And Castle and I will go for the goods Hard Kill style.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-4"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Always check.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="34"><utterance uid="34-1"><speaker>BOOTH</speaker><content>I’ve got to get going. Great seeing you, man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-2"><speaker>ROLF</speaker><content>Whoa, whoa, whoa. Where’re you going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-3"><speaker>CLAY</speaker><content>Hey, hey, hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-4"><speaker>BOOTH</speaker><content>You know what? Whatever you want, on me. Enjoy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-5"><speaker>CLAY</speaker><content> Abort. Abort. Prairie dog pulled a boomerang.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="35"><utterance uid="35-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I got it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-2"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Booth’s on his way back up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-4"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-6"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content> Prairie dog is in the burrow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Prairie dog is going to kill us. We’re going to be killed by a prairie dog –</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="36"><utterance uid="36-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’m starring in my own action movie.  This is the best night ever.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-2"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Go!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="37"><utterance uid="37-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You’re telling me that this was handed to you by a concerned citizen?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Uh … yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>This is probably one of those times I shouldn’t keep talking. For both our sakes.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="38"><utterance uid="38-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The recording you are about to hear will provide incontrovertible proof that Henry Allen Booth ordered the murder of Lance Delorca.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Sound's not working. Hang on a second. This was –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Headphones? Aren’t you going to let me hear it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And reward you for your semi-illegal behavior?  I think not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I – fine. I’ll put it on speaker.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Seriously? Because if it wasn’t for me we wouldn’t even –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Lance just walked into Booth’s office. They’re exchanging pleasantries. And … they’re getting down to business.  Oh my God.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What is it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh … my God.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What are they saying? Please, just tell me what they are saying!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>This is so not what I expected. Oh my God.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="39"><utterance uid="39-1"><speaker>TREY</speaker><content>So what’s this about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Trey, how well do you know Henry Allen Booth?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-3"><speaker>TREY</speaker><content>Well, if someone owns a club it’s my job to know them. I met him through my dad. They did a few movies together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>In fact, Booth invested some seed money so you could become a club promoter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And as a promoter, you had access to all the clubs in the city. Booth used that access to sell drugs in those clubs. Or so we’re told by Narcotics.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I don’t hear you denying this, Trey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-7"><speaker>TREY</speaker><content>I didn’t know about the drugs at first, and once I did it was too late. He owned me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Let me guess. Booth said you could buy him out, but at a price he knew you could never afford. What was it? Two hundred thousand dollars?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You didn’t tell your parents about any of this, did you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-10"><speaker>TREY</speaker><content>I wanted to make my own way. Not have Brock Harmon come to the rescue.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>But Lance found out. He tried to buy out Booth. Pay your ransom, just like Rico Cruz did in Hard Kill.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-12"><speaker>TREY</speaker><content>And I begged him not to. This wasn’t some movie. I knew that Booth wasn’t going to let me go and Lance couldn’t just walk in there with a bag of money and fix things. But suddenly he wanted to be a hero. I told him he was going to get us both killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>But he only got himself killed. Trying to save you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We have an audio recording of Booth from that night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-15"><speaker>TREY</speaker><content>How?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Lance bugged his office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>After Booth kicked Lance out of his office he sent his men after him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Lance gave them a beat down worthy of an action hero. That’s when Booth made this phone call.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-19"><speaker>BOOTH</speaker><content>Trey. Your pal Lance was here. I think you know why. He’s on the run somewhere near that theater playing Hard Kill. He’s your problem now. You need to take care of him, to make this right. Or I’ll take care of you. You do that, Trey. Get it done.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You were so afraid of Booth that you killed Lance in order to save your own skin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-21"><speaker>TREY</speaker><content>I would never do that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-22"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>It sounds like that’s exactly what you did do. Now, what happened after you hung up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-23"><speaker>TREY</speaker><content>I freaked. I called my mom. Told her everything. The whole story. She said to lay low, that she’d call a lawyer. And the next morning Lance was dead. I figured Booth’s guys got to him. Look, I was at my office all night. I slept there. The cleaning crew saw me. I swear to you, I did not kill Lance. And I don’t know who did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-24"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Tell me, Trey. Why would Lance go through all this trouble to help you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-25"><speaker>TREY</speaker><content>I don’t know. He just said that the cancer really woke him up and uh … after this was over there were some things that he wanted to tell me.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="40"><utterance uid="40-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So the cleaning crew confirmed Trey’s story. He is not our killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, maybe it was one of Booth’s men. We still haven’t ruled them out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey guys. I just found something very interesting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The identity of the killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>No, not that. You know how Trey said that Lance’s cancer woke him up? Well, I just spoke to his doctor. When Lance got the name of his bone marrow donor – to thank him – he found out that there was a second donor who was a very close match.  Check out that name.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="41"><utterance uid="41-1"><speaker>NAOMI</speaker><content>Have you released Trey yet? He had nothing to do with this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Actually, Trey has everything to do with this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-3"><speaker>NAOMI</speaker><content>I’m not sure I understand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>When Lance needed a bone marrow transplant, Trey gave a sample to see if he could donate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-5"><speaker>NAOMI</speaker><content>We all did. It was the least we could do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Except Trey’s sample was nearly a match. Lance must have had his suspicions, because he ran a paternity test on that sample.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Trey was his son.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He would have been conceived during the filming of Hard Kill, which was inconvenient since you were already married to Brock.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We spoke to your doorman, Naomi. He said that you didn’t come home until well after midnight the night that Lance was killed, so where were you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-10"><speaker>NAOMI</speaker><content>I didn’t kill Lance, if that’s what you’re suggesting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You’re more than capable of it. You don’t just have a mean roundhouse. You hold two black belts.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-12"><speaker>NAOMI</speaker><content>Okay, you need to leave.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We matched the wire. The wire that you use for your jewelry line, like the necklace that you’re wearing right now, it’s an exact match for our murder weapon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Trey told you that Lance had something important to tell him. You knew the truth would come out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-15"><speaker>NAOMI</speaker><content>Lance would have destroyed everything. My marriage, my family, everything that I spent almost thirty years trying to build. I couldn’t let him do that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-16"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>What’s going on?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="42"><utterance uid="42-1"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>You might be interested to know that Henry Allen Booth was just arrested by Narcotics.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I thought they couldn’t make a case.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-3"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Well, they couldn’t. But when Trey learned the truth about why Lance really did all this, he stepped up and decided to testify against Booth. So, good work, Detective Beckett. Mr. – Castle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-4"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Don’t stay late. You can finish the paperwork in the morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Thank you, sir.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Wow. Looks like Lance managed to vanquish his nemesis after all. An ending worthy of one of his movies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know, maybe we should watch Hard Kill tonight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>In his honor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I was just going to suggest the exact same thing. We’re starting to think alike now!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> That is horrifying. Okay, go cue up the movie, open up a bottle of wine. I’ll be home in a bit. I’ve just got a stop to make first.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, if I’m thinking what you’re thinking and it’s to pick up a sexy archaeologist costume, don’t worry.  I’ve already got the whip.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="43"><utterance uid="43-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="44"><utterance uid="44-1"><speaker>THE END</speaker><content>CASTLE</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>