<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>


<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>RICHARD CASTLE</speaker><content>So what do you think? This feels different, doesn’t it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>KATE BECKETT</speaker><content>What does?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Rolling up to a crime scene as a married couple. We’re like Nick and Nora Charles.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ooh, like McMillan and Wife.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hart to Hart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Turner and Hooch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Turner and Hooch aren’t even married.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, but you still remind me a little of Hooch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So … morning blend? Did this just happen?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>KEVIN RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah. A jogger found him about an hour ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>LANIE PARISH</speaker><content>Which is about the time he died. Needless to say, it’s pretty obvious what killed him. Gunshot wound to the head.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>JAVIER ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Him being Paul Reeves out of Queens. We’re running down next of kin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Anyone hear the shot?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>No. And there’s no video coverage in this area of the park.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Killer probably knew that. He took Reeves' phone, cash from his wallet, and probably waltzed right out of here. It looks like a mugging gone wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, there’s no signs of struggle. If this was a mugging and he didn’t put up a fight, why risk shooting him? Especially in broad daylight?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Singed fabric. Nobody heard anything because the killer used a backpack or a cloth to muffle the shot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And then took the victim’s phone and cash to throw us off track.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>This wasn’t a mugging. This was deliberate murder.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>BRENT REEVES</speaker><content>That just doesn’t make sense. Paul didn’t have an enemy in the world.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, how much do you know about your brother’s life? Were you close?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>BRENT</speaker><content>Very close. In fact, Paul had been staying at my place for the past month. He was waiting to close escrow on a condo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Was having a coffee in the park something he did often?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>BRENT</speaker><content> He never went to the park. He hardly ever left the office. Paul was a complete workaholic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And what did he do, exactly?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>BRENT</speaker><content>He was an investigator for the government. The GAO. I don’t know much more than that. He really couldn’t discuss his job.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Was he having any troubles at work that you’re aware of?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>BRENT</speaker><content>Not trouble, exactly, but … last night we had a beer. Paul said how a crucial meeting had come up that he was worried about.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What kind of meeting? I mean, with whom?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>BRENT</speaker><content>He didn’t say, but he had gotten a disturbing call from someone involved in one of his cases. I mean, he said …  - that meeting. I think that was supposed to happen this morning.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>What exactly did Paul investigate?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Like defense contractors billing five hundred bucks for a hammer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So if someone was fleecing Uncle Sam he could cancel their contracts?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Did anyone ever pressure Paul to back off a report or investigation?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Be that as it may, we need the files of all his active investigations.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Paul Reeves had over twenty open cases and he was taking on some major players. A hospital chain that defrauded Medicare, a lab at Latham Pharmaceuticals cited for lax storage practices, and a company that sold the VA defective medical equipment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I feel the heavy hand of conspiracy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, well, what else is new?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Consider this: Paul uncovers a nefarious scandal, rife with corruption and financial skullduggery in connection with a federal contract. But with millions of dollars at stake, the greedy contractor, determined to stay latched on to the federal teat, lures Paul into a meeting in the park where he has an assassin silence him, thus Paul’s findings never come to light.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And I don’t suppose that you have a particular case of Paul’s in mind, do you? Or proof? Or suspects?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No. But I will once you identify who met Paul at the park.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I might be a step closer to that. Do you remember how Paul’s brother mentioned that a meeting had just come up?  Well, I looked into Paul’s phone calls for the last forty-eight hours. One of them stood out.  An incoming call to his office at 11:04 yesterday morning. The call lasted less than a minute and I traced it to a payphone on the lower East side.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Try and find out who made that call.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>TORY ELLIS</speaker><content>This is street cam video of that payphone, 11:04 yesterday morning. This is the man who called Paul Reeves.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Tory ran the image and got a match on his face.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Jared Stone, misdemeanor computer trespassing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>TORY</speaker><content>Otherwise known as hacking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Stone was an Occupy Wall Street activist who hacked into a major bank, releasing their emails, which reflected poorly on their business practices.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So why would a hacker like Jared Stone kill a GAO investigator?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He wouldn’t. That story doesn’t make any sense. But this one does: using his vaunted hacking skills, Jared Stone is the one who uncovered the nefarious scandal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So we’re back to a nefarious scandal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yes. See, he wants to blow the lid off of a scandal, so who better to call than intrepid investigator Paul Reeves. Because, wait for it … Jared Stone is a whistleblower. And Paul Reeves was murdered because of what Jared Stone told him. Which … which actually means he could be in danger now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>You have to admit, Castle’s theory is surprisingly logical.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yes. And it’s conveniently unburdened by evidence. Nevertheless, let’s bring Jared Stone in for questioning and let’s take a look at that footage of the payphone for the past two weeks. If Jared Stone talked to anyone, I want to know who it was.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yo. I may have an address on Jared Stone. I ran his emails. He rented a place on the lower West off Craigslist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So what’s going on with married life, huh? How is that? The whole family thing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Sarah Grace. She’s – she’s growing up, changing so fast. I’m just trying to hold on to every second.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What kind of dad do you think I’d be?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>You’d be great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, even growing up with no role model?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, you know, the thing of it is, is you know what it’s like not having a father. You’d make sure your kid never felt that way.  You and Lanie, huh?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No. She likes things how they are. But you know. Maybe I’m ready for more than that. You know what I’m saying? Move forward.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Did you hear that? That sound?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>No. What’s that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>That’s my biological clock ticking. Tick, tock. Tick, tock.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>We were having a genuine, honest moment here. And you had to ruin it by being a jackass.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hold on. Slow down, slow down. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>That’s Jared Stone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hang tight here. I’ll follow him on foot, make sure we don’t lose him.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hey, bro.  Yeah, followed him down into the subway. I’m looking for him now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>What, you lost him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No, I didn’t lose him. I just … don’t have visual contact.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>That’s kind of splitting hairs, isn’t it? Look, I’ll head down there and I’ll –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No, you stay there. I’ll – wait, I see him. He’s at my 12. He’s moving fast. He’s scared, like someone’s after him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>If someone is, you better get to him before they do. Whoever killed Reeves may be gunning for Stone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>He’s boarding the 7th Ave express.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>All right, I’m on the train with Stone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>OFFICER MARISA ARAGON</speaker><content>You’re holding an uncapped marker and you’re telling me you were not about to tag this subway car?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>DUSTIN</speaker><content>Yes.  I mean, no.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>I’m need to see some identification. I’m going to have to write you up for this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Jared Stone?  Hey. You’re not in trouble, bro, but –  – look, I’m just here to talk to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>Put your gun on the ground. Now!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>Put your gun on the ground, now. Do it!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>Kick it over to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>Step back.  Nobody else move.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Nobody’s moving, man. I just came here to talk to you. I’m on your side.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>No, you’re a blunt instrument. A tool of the one percent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Look, nobody’s hurt yet. It’s just a big misunderstanding. So why don’t you lower that weapon and we can walk right out of here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-20"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>Oh, is that really possible?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-21"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>It is. Yeah. You just have to put the gun down, Jared.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-22"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>What the hell is that? Are you on the phone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-23"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>Everybody shut off your phones and get on the ground, now!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-24"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Javi? Javi!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>Stay down, don’t move, and nobody gets hurt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>BELLA</speaker><content>This cannot be happening.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>TY</speaker><content>Please. Look, don’t do this. Okay? Don’t hurt my wife.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>GRANT GERBER</speaker><content>Or the rest of us. Let’s be inclusive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hey. Everybody just stay calm. All right? We’re all going to be fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>You’re not in charge. I am.  I pulled the emergency brake. Why hasn’t the conductor come over the intercom yet?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I don’t know, maybe he –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>Shh!  You feel that? That’s movement. Like people are getting off the train. Evacuating. How do they know?  Who were you on the phone with?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Just a friend, man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>What kind of friend? Is it another cop? Was it a cop? Huh?  I can hit redial if I want.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, he was – he was NYPD, but that doesn’t mean anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>Shut up! Look, everybody just stop talking, okay? I’ve gotta think.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>He took my service weapon? How did I let him do that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hey, it could happen to anybody. Okay?  I’m Javier. Javier Esposito.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>Marisa Aragon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>GERBER</speaker><content>Jared.  May I call you Jared? Grant Gerber, salesman by trade. Which means I’m a listener. I listen, learn what people want so I can give it to them. Let me do that for you, Jared. I want to help you get what you want.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>I think you’ll get your chance.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>CAPTAIN VICTORIA GATES</speaker><content>I’ve just been informed that Jared Stone, a person of interest in the Paul Reeves case, drew a gun on a subway and took hostages, including Detective Esposito. At this point, it’s not clear why Jared Stone …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hey, if anybody can handle it, Espo can. Why would Stone take hostages?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Right now, our sole priority is to gather any and all information on Jared Stone so the hostage rescue team will know who we’re dealing with. All intel comes to me so I can forward it directly to HRT. They should be on the scene right now.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>CAPTAIN BIGALOW</speaker><content>Detective Ryan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yes, sir.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>BIGALOW</speaker><content>Captain Bigalow, HRT. What’s the intel on your suspect?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Sir, he’s a hacker and Occupy Wall Street activist. It’s all sketchy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>BIGALOW</speaker><content>What about your boy Esposito? Is he someone we can count on? He’s solid?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>He’s as solid as they get.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>BIGALOW</speaker><content>Roger that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey, Beckett. I’m sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Kevin, no one could have seen this coming.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>No, no. He’s my partner. I should have never let him go in there alone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We’ve gotta focus on getting Javi out of there. So once you brief HRT just head over to Stone’s apartment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Leave the scene?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Look, there’s nothing that you can do that HRT isn’t already doing. And if we want to help Javi out, then the best thing that we can do is find out who Jared Stone is and why he is doing this. And some of those answers might be at his apartment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Okay. I’ll check it out and let you know.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Kate! Is it true? What they’re saying?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Listen, he has been in worse scrapes than this and we are going to get him out of there, I promise you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Detective Beckett? Doctor Parish? We’ve got eyes on Esposito.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Where’s this coming from? I didn’t think the MTA had cameras in the subway cars.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>TORY</speaker><content>They don’t. The train is part of a pilot program for video security. This is on a separate feed so it took me a while to find it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Wait, if this is on a separate feed –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That means that we can see Stone but he doesn’t know that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Which gives us a tactical edge. I’ll make sure HRT knows about this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>At least Javi’s not down there alone. There’s another cop with him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, between the two of them they might be able to defuse the situation.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>Kind of a weird time for him to be hitting his playlist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>He’s trying to calm himself down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>Because he’s about to do what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I might need you to back me up. Can you do that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>What’s your play?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Talk to him. Try to get him see the light, then disarm him if I get the chance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>I should talk to him. I’m the one wearing the Kevlar.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, but I’ve already got a rapport with the guy, so…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>A bad rapport. I know what this is. I’m just a transit cop. You gold shield guys always acting like you’re better than us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>We are better than you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Mr. Stone!  Permission to speak?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-12"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content> Go ahead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-13"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>That’s far enough.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Look, whatever went down between you and Paul Reeves, this is only going to make it worse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-15"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>This wasn’t supposed to happen. Not here. This wasn’t part of the plan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-16"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Then we can come up with a new plan. One where you walk out of here. You can still do that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-17"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>It’s too late. Police are already involved. Now there’s no turning back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-18"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You have to turn back, Jared. Because if you don’t, here’s what’s going to happen. HRT, that’s the hostage rescue team, will wait for you to get weak and tired. And a dozen highly trained guys, armed to the teeth, will breach this car. And trust me when I tell you, they will not play. You’ll be lucky to get off one shot before they drop you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-19"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>HRT won’t come near me. Not once they know I have this.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Oh my God. A suicide vest?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>His left hand. That’s a dead man’s switch. He lets go of that …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Clearly Jared Stone is not a whistle blower.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He’s a terrorist wearing an explosive vest. This was a planned attack.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>I’ll contact Homeland, see what they have on him. Keep working intel on Jared Stone. Obviously this man is not at all who we thought he was.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Jared, what are you doing, man?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>It’s kind of self-explanatory, isn’t it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Look, I know you’re an activist and you’re all about taking on the one percent, but do you see anybody like that here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>GERBER</speaker><content>Look, I may be a salesman, but just so you know, I am not a big earner. Okay? I am barely scraping by.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Jared. They are working people. Your people. You don’t want to hurt them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>You’re right. I don’t. But I will. If I have to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>Take a picture. Text it to HRT.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I need you to tell me everything you know about Jared Stone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>LANDLORD</speaker><content>Just that he wanted the apartment for two weeks, so I rented it to him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Did you meet the guy? Talk to him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>LANDLORD</speaker><content>Just when I gave him the key. And told him that I did not permit wild parties.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>LANDLORD</speaker><content>What’s this about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Comb through every inch of this place. Look through all this papers, personal items. Anything that can tell us who Jared Stone is or what he’s up to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>LANDLORD</speaker><content>Excuse me, gentlemen. But could I ask you to remove your shoes? The carpet is brand new.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>LANDLORD</speaker><content>Just a thought.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Homeland doesn’t have a file on Jared Stone. Neither does NYPD Counterterrorism.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Why would Stone blow up the subway? I’ve been reading his posts on income inequality. He’s a little pedantic, but he’s an armchair revolutionary. He’s not a man of action.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Maybe he became radicalized somehow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The Taking of Pelham 1, 2, 3 could not have been his plan. He must have been heading someplace else when Esposito stopped him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He was.  Stone was set to attend a wealth management seminar with fifteen hundred people at the Tremaine Hotel. That’s where he was going when Esposito came along.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>The 7th Avenue express would have taken him right there. And if he was after one percenters this seminar would be a target rich environment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Sir, he also had a backup target. He had seats to an opera at the biggest theater on Broadway. Nineteen hundred seats.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>He was going for maximum casualties. And he’s willing to kill himself in the process. I’ll pass this on to HRT. Oh. One more thing. Tory ran video on that payphone. Stone did use it before. He called the Maldives last week. Twice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The Maldives?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Who was he talking to?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-11"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>The cell phone he has is no longer active. We can’t track it down.  Oh.  Gates.  HRT is asking what kind of pizza does Esposito like?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Uh .. pineapple, olives, and double jalapeños, sir.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-13"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>I’ll pass it along.  Uh, pineapple …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Since when does a hacker, who, by his very nature, tends to live his life virtually, morph into a suicide bomber? Stone has no history of violence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You think something happened to trigger him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I don’t know, but there’s a piece missing here somewhere. How does a GAO investigator fit into this? The calls to the Maldives? Has Ryan turned anything up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No. So far no word.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Excuse me. This receipt from two days ago for the shredder. Did you buy it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>LANDLORD</speaker><content>No. I don’t even know where that came from. It really doesn’t fit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Then Stone bought it.  Excuse me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>He’s shredding documents. Okay. We need to bag this up and take it back to the precinct, put it back together. Find out what Stone was trying to hide.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>So how’d you find me? How’d you track me down?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>Do you know about White Knight?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What’s White Knight?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>That’ll be the negotiator. You want something, right? Now’ll be the time to ask for it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>Hello?  Yes, it is.  Hello, Bob. You’re the negotiator?  I’m fine. Yeah, yeah. They’re all fine too.  Uh, let me ask.  Is anybody hungry?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>BELLA</speaker><content>I’m always hungry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>GERBER</speaker><content>So am I.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content> Yeah, um … everybody could use some food right about now. Um –  – well you do that, Bob.  My demands? Do I have demands? Yeah. I got one. You listening? I want Erin Wilson released from prison. You call me back when you have a plan to make that happen.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s all he said?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Who the hell is Aaron Wilson?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Well, if we want to save these people we need to find out.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, let’s find who this Aaron Wilson is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Wait a minute.  Castle, it’s a woman. E, R, I, N. She’s serving seven years in federal prison for felony computer trespassing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So she’s a hacker, too?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Court records show that she hacked a database at the New York Federal Reserve looking for proof that the Fed colluded with big banks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What’s her connection to Stone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>It looks like Jared Stone was an accomplice. But the US Attorney didn’t have enough to charge him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So they were partners in crime. Erin went to prison, Stone didn’t. That’s why he wants to get her out. He feels guilty. That would also explain the Maldives.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What do you mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s a non-extradition country.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey guys. You need to see this.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>What was in that shredder was about two pages of text. So far we’ve been able to assemble a few random words like “monitor” and “surveillance”.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, what do you think it is?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>It’s some kind of letter. But I don’t think that Stone was the one who wrote it. Take a look at this phrase that we assembled just now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> “Read, memorize, then destroy.”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>It’s not like he would write that to himself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So they’re instructions. Now we know Stone was working with other people. Maybe this is all about Erin Wilson. Maybe she’s the one behind all of this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle and I will look into Erin Wilson and we’ll dig deeper. We’ll also see if we can identify any associates that Jared might have had.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>We’ll keep piecing this together here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Guys, everyone down there is counting on us.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hey. Who’s Erin Wilson?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>She’s my soul mate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, why didn’t you give Bob more to go on so he knew who you were talking about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>I want to keep him off balance. Maintain control.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You get that tip off the internet? ‘Cause it’s not a very good one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What’s White Knight?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>Tell me your plan for Erin.  What the hell is taking so long, Bob? Getting her in prison didn’t seem to take any time at all.  Bob, shut up. Shut up! Listen to me. I want her flown to the Maldives.  Yeah, well, I’m telling you now, Bob. Okay? I want her flown to the Maldives and in a half an hour I want your plan on how to make that happen, are we clear?  Yeah, Bob. Food would be great right about now.  No, don’t send any cops.  I don’t care if they’re unarmed, Bob. I don’t want any police near this car. Just drop the food.  Then set it on the edge of the platform! I’ll send somebody to get it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>You. The husband. Go. Get the food. I know you’ll come back.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Just got bad news. Called the prison. Spoke to Erin Wilson.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She’s Stone’s girlfriend. She didn’t seem to know about his plan to break her out until just now. What about you? Anything on Stone’s known associates?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Stone may have lived online, but he wasn’t very social. He started a “Free Erin Wilson” website but didn’t seem to interact with any of the users.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He had to have interacted with somebody. Tech scrubbed his computer and found a hidden directory that they think contained private correspondence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>From whom?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Contents were thoroughly erased. The only thing left was the name of the directory. White Knight.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>TY</speaker><content>Okay, who’s next?  We’ve got double cheese, pepperoni, mushroom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>Uh, right here.  Thanks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>You doing okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>TY</speaker><content>Veggie with eggplant and garlic. Pineapple, olives, double jalapeño.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>That’s for me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>Really? We’re trapped in a subway car. I’m not sure you should eat that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>You going to eat that thing or just gaze at it in wonder?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I don’t understand. Why does HRT want to breach?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>In their assessment, Stone is trapped with no good options and no way to carry out his original plan. They believe the longer this goes the more likely he will do the unthinkable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Why not see how things play out with Erin Wilson?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>HRT thinks the Erin Wilson demand is a ruse. Stone is playing this card to buy time, work up his nerve.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>If they bust in, what’ll keep Stone from blowing that vest?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Esposito will. He’s in on it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Won’t Stone see HRT coming?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>TORY</speaker><content>Yes, if they approach via the tunnel. But they’re dropping onto the train from above, through the subway grates.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>When?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-10"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Soon. Any moment now.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>Are you sure we shouldn’t tell the others?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No. They’ll get nervous and Stone will pick up on it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hey, why did you become a cop?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content> Got out of the Army. It’s what made the most sense.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Me too. You miss the service?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>Some parts. Not others.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Married? Kids?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-8"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>No. Don’t do this, okay? Don’t try to take my mind off of what’s coming. I don’t need anyone holding my hand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You know, you’ve got a chip on your shoulder the size of Stonehenge. I was just trying to get to know you a little bit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-10"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>Oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>See that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-12"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>Sure did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>The next flicker is go time. You clear on the plan?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-14"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>Don’t worry about me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-15"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>I can feel vibrations. They’re on the train.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-16"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>You pull your people back now or everybody dies. Now! I know they’re here.  Don’t screw with me, Bob! Or I will pull my hand off this trigger right now!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-17"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>How am I supposed to trust that they’re gone, hmm? You just tried to send stormtroopers into a subway car full of people, not knowing where they are or where I am …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-18"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>Wait a second.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Don’t worry. He’s going to be okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>I know. I know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>How is she?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, at least when she could see Javi she knew he was okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>We’ll get Espo back. The key is finding out who Stone was working with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The answer’s probably in that White Knight directory, but so far tech hasn’t been able to recover any of the data.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well then, we’ll … revisit the victim. Looking into Paul Reeves’ investigations is what led us to Stone. Perhaps it’ll lead us to the others as well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Tory, let me ask you something. The video from the subway, before it cut out, did you record it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>TORY</speaker><content>Of course. All streaming video is archived automatically. Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Could you show it to me? There’s something I’d like to see.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>These are all twenty of the case files Paul Reeves was working on. Here’s a summary of those cases. I figured we’d just go through these until something points to Stone or to Erin Wilson or anything else we’re dealing with here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, I’ll start. Uh … the first one is that pharmaceutical lab cited for losing samples of a flu virus.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Not ringing any bells. Moving on to a medical chain that knowingly implanted defective artificial hips.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey guys. That document? I think it’s a playbook. Stone’s following it to the letter. Take a look at this sentence fragment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> “… demand Erin Wilson’s release from prison then hang up.” More instructions? I mean, how is that telling us anything that we don’t already know?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>You’ll see. Now take a look at this one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> “I demand Erin be flown to a non-extradition country.”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>But that instruction comes later on in the document, which is exactly how Stone played it. First he demanded her release and then he brought up the Maldives.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That doesn’t make any sense. If Stone wanted Erin Wilson freed from prison then why would he wait to mention the Maldives until later?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>For the same reason he asked about Erin Wilson’s release without explaining who she was. Stone is stalling. He’s playing for time. Something else is going on here. Something big.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-11"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Kate, I need to show you something.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>I noticed something when I was watching earlier, so I went to watch this whole video. We have a problem. A new problem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>This is Stone back when he was just holding them all hostage. This is him later –  – and later.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>His asthma’s getting worse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>It’s not just his asthma. It looks like he has fever and chills. It’s only a matter of time before he’s not able to think clearly. The man is sick and he’s getting sicker with flu-like symptoms.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Flu-like symptoms?  Castle, that case. Paul Reeves was investigating a missing flu virus. This is all connected somehow. It has to be.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>Once I hear that she’s in international airspace, I’ll surrender.  Because I’m giving you my word.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Stone’s not looking too good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-3"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>Hey, exactly how long is that going to take? Huh?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>He passes out and releases that switch we’re all dead. We’ve gotta make a move.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-5"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>Bob, Bob, Bob. That’s not acceptable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-6"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>Same plan as before?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-8"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>When?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>He gets distracted when he puffs on his inhaler. Next puff we go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-10"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>Look, those are my conditions. Once I hear from Erin that she’s free, I swear I let everybody go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-11"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>Don’t worry, everyone. It’s almost over.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-12"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>Ah! Stop! Please!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Secure the switch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-14"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>I’m not done yet. I’m not done yet!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-15"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Go, go, go, go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-16"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Good job.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-17"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey, Javi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-18"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What’s up? We took down Stone. Nobody’s hurt, everybody’s fine. It’s over.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-19"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> It’s not over, man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-20"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What? What do you mean, it’s not over? I don’t want a ticker tape parade or anything like that, but did you not just hear what I said?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-21"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Listen, Javi, this is about more than just a suicide vest. The CDC turned up a lethal variant of the H5N1 virus in Stone’s apartment. It’s a hot zone. Stone’s infected. And everyone around him might be, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-22"><speaker>DUSTIN</speaker><content>I got the door open. I got it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-23"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Close that door! I said, close it now! Nobody leaves the train!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Sir, how is Esposito?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Well, he and the others were transported to the hospital. But they’re in isolation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What’s the prognosis?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-4"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Now, this particular strain of H5N1 is lethal and can be spread through airborne contact.  But there is a vaccine. It’s been given to the passengers and it can knock down the virus even after exposure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So he’s going to be okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-6"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Doctors are optimistic. And the CDC is retracing Stone’s steps to identify who else he was in contact with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>This guy’s like an evil version of Typhoid Mary. The suicide vest, the demands? All about exposing people long enough to get them infected so they’d spread the virus.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-8"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Well, it could have been far worse if he had made it to that seminar or the opera. In proximity to all those people? He could have caused an epidemic. But I’m still not clear. How does our shooting victim fit into all this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Paul Reeves was investigating the lab where a sample of H5N1 went missing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>We think he figured out that Stone had stolen the virus, which is why Stone lured him into the park and killed him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>But sir, there are still questions, like who Stone was working with and why he did this in the first place, so we need to go and talk to him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-12"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Well, you better hurry up, because I hear he’s not in good shape.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yes, sir.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="34"><utterance uid="34-1"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>You’re not the priest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, but I can take your confession.  We know you had help, Mr. Stone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>White Knight. Who is he?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-4"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>Someone I met through the Free Erin site a few months back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What was his real name?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-6"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>I don’t know. We bonded over Erin. Over how to get her out. He was a strategic thinker and I wasn’t, so he helped me with the plan. I never would have detonated that vest. I just – I just needed some leverage. I love Erin. All I wanted was to see her free.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>More like you wanted to get people sick.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-8"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>What do you mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You tried to start an epidemic by spreading your deadly virus. Erin was just a sideshow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-10"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>What are you talking about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The opera, the seminar? Hundreds of one-percenters in close proximity? That was the perfect environment to spread your disease.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-12"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>It – disease? No, I – I was trying to find the best spot to make my stand for Erin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Then why did you call Paul Reeves?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-14"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>White Knight just said that it was part of the plan. I – called Reeves to tell him about some meeting at the park. I didn’t even know who he was.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The seminar. And the opera. Where those White Knight’s ideas, too?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-16"><speaker>JARED</speaker><content>So I was set up. Somebody used me. This thing I have – I may have given it to other people, too?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="35"><utterance uid="35-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay. That is not how I imagined that conversation would go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>If Stone’s telling the truth, then he’s the fall guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He was groomed, turned into a vector for the virus, and manipulated into spreading it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Which means this all connects to Paul Reeves' investigation of the lab where the virus came from.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="36"><utterance uid="36-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Stone was deliberately infected. The CDC confirmed that someone turned his asthma inhaler into a virus delivery system.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Question is, who came up with that idea?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, the answer’s gotta be connected to this lab that Paul was investigating.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I think it is. Beckett, take a look at this.  The lab from which the virus went missing, Latham Pharmaceuticals? They’re the same company that makes the vaccine that Espo and the others got.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Which is why they had samples of H5N1 in the first place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Right. But as part of his investigation, Paul was looking into production orders of the vaccine, specifically this one for ten million units of the vaccine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, there were only a thousand reported cases of H5N1 worldwide.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So why would Latham suddenly order up ten million vaccines?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Unless they knew there was going to be an outbreak.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I think Paul was asking the same question.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="37"><utterance uid="37-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ms. Jarvis, thank you for taking the time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, not yet. But we do have a few questions. Now, do you know why he was investigating Latham Pharmaceuticals?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And Latham developed a vaccine for a rare, but deadly flu virus, didn’t they? I mean, a flu so rare that the vaccine just sits on the shelf.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>They do with a little help.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You recently converted all your assets to Latham stock. Why is that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>It became my concern when you tried to start an H5N1 epidemic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>With the help of someone gullible. Someone you could easily manipulate. Like Jared Stone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Your husband was one of the prosecutors who put away his girlfriend, Erin Wilson.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So when you needed a patsy you knew just where to look. And then your colleague, Paul, when he saw that huge vaccine order, he started digging.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And when you saw that he was getting closer to the truth, you eliminated him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Actually, we can. We found the emails you wrote in your cloud account. Under the user name White Knight?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We also arrested a Latham executive with whom you were colluding. He admitted to his role and he cut a deal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And he threw you under the bus.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You could have infected and killed millions of people, Ms. Jarvis, and for what? So you could drive a nicer car? Buy a bigger house? Was this all just because of money?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You better find a good one.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="38"><utterance uid="38-1"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hey. So I uh … I hear everybody’s good to go, clean bills of health.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-3"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content> This time yesterday catching the flu was the least of our problems.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You did all right down there. I don’t care what they say about transit cops.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-5"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>Mmm. What they say about gold shields is even worse, mostly because it’s true.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>We make a tight team.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-7"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>Bonds forged in the heat of battle. You know how it is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-9"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>I wasn’t straight with you. I have a five year old son.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Uh … you said that you didn’t have a family. Why hide that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-11"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>I didn’t want you worried about me being a mom down there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content> You are a piece of work, Marisa.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-13"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>Who’s Lenny? Or is it Lanie?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>How do you know about her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-15"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>On my last tour an IED blew out my eardrum. I got pretty good at reading lips. You were saying her name before you took down Stone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-16"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, I don’t … I don’t remember that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-17"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>Who you think of in that moment? It has weight. Don’t trade what’s real for something that isn’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-18"><speaker>ARAGON</speaker><content>I’ll see you around, Javi.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="39"><utterance uid="39-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, it’s not every day you come across someone who makes a suicide bomber look like the good guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So I talked to the hospital. Jared Stone will make a full recovery, though clearly his troubles aren’t over yet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah. Unless he goes to the same prison as Erin Wilson. Because in the end, Jared Stone was driven by the most primal of emotions. Love.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Except he could have picked a better way to express it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey. Look who’s here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What’s up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hail the conquering hero.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Man, you had me scared.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>That’s because you’re a wimp.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Oh. Well, okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, well, I guess that makes me a wimp, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-14"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Got any of that left over for me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-15"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Javi, I was worried sick. I thought that –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-16"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I know what you thought. But I’m here. I’m back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-17"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>All right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I hate to interrupt, but I have a brilliant idea. How about we all go to the Old Haunt, huh? Drinks on me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Come on. We’ll take the subway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Too soon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-21"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Too soon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Please accept this as a token of my apology.  Am I on the wrong track here?</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>