<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>


<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>ABBY SMITH</speaker><content>Hey. I need to be at the club by 11, so I can’t really talk.  Uh, skip it. But everyone who’s anyone is going to be there.  I know. Look, I’ve really got to go. But I’ll be thinking about you. I’ll take a pic and send it to you to prove it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>ABBY</speaker><content>Hello? Is someone there?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>MARTHA RODGERS</speaker><content>Excellent. Now, mmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Vibrate. Vibrate, vibrate, vibrate!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>RICHARD CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Now, breathe in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I think – I think that’s – my vocal chords are about as warmed up as they’re going to get. Thank you so much. I thought you said you were just coming to watch, anyway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Well, that was the plan. But then I discovered my expertise was needed.  And don’t miss his forehead, honey. It’s shiny.  What about this jacket, dear? Did you choose –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yes, I’m good. I’m – you know, I picked it out myself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Because -</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Thank you. You know, I’ve done this before, Mother. I know exactly what I’m doing. Thank you.  You want to put just one more? Layers. Stack them right up on top of there. I think it’ll be great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>There’s a boy over there filming you with his phone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, that’s just behind the scenes stuff.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah. It’s all part of the campaign. Just tapping into that whole 360 degree digital media environment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Ah hah. Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>MO</speaker><content>Okay, Mr. Castle. We’re ready.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Excellent.  Want to go sit with Mo?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Oh! Mo!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>All right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>CAMERAMAN</speaker><content>We’re rolling.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>MO</speaker><content>And, action!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hi. I’m Richard Castle. Are you looking for a bone-chilling, spine-tingling thriller full of twists and turns? If you are, look no further than my latest novel, Raging Heat. Why don’t you download your copy today, because whether you get it on the download, buy a hard copy, or just listen to the audio version, I promise you, it’ll keep you hooked until the very last word.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oops.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>KATE BECKETT</speaker><content>That must have been kind of embarrassing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It was a minor blow to my ego. After that I had to channel my inner Castle, but once I did … nailed it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Wow. You nailed playing yourself. That’s impressive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Mock if you will, but pretty soon you’re going to see my image splashed across multiple platforms. It’s going to be Castle 2.0. It’s going to be Castle in the cloud.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Wait a minute. Multiple platforms? I thought that this was a TV commercial.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No. Better. It’s a web-mercial. And once it drops in a few days, my publisher assures me that both Raging Heat and I will go viral. It’s time I let technology wrap me in its warm, lucrative embrace.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Huh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Gentlemen. Is there an elevator? Is this a walk-up? Hope it’s an elevator.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>JAVIER ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Victim’s name is Abby Smith. She’s 23 years old. A maintenance worker found her early this morning. We’re dealing with something messed up here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>LANIE PARISH</speaker><content>You got that right, starting off with these stab wounds.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>They’re round. What was the murder weapon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Hard to tell. A knitting needle, maybe. An ice pick. Your guess is as good as mine. Her attacker knew about anatomy. He pierced her carotid and her subclavian arteries. She bled out in minutes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Which means our killer might have had a medical background.  You know, there are no signs of forced entry. Do we know how this killer came in?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>KEVIN RYAN</speaker><content>Well, we’re not really sure, but he definitely wanted Abby to know that he was here.  She was texted this photo at 10:33, right around time of death.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The killer sent this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> Right before he murdered her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He was watching her. And then he sent that to terrorize her. This was personal.  Well, so much for the warm embrace of technology.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Is there any way to trace the text?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, we’ll try, but it was sent from a burner phone. Um, meanwhile we’ll check with the neighbors, see if they saw anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, and talk to friends and family. If this was personal they might have an idea as to who was behind this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, why don’t we start with this guy.  Carlos. She was on the phone with him right before she received the text message. Judging by their call history he looks to be the boyfriend.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>CARLOS VILLEGAS</speaker><content>I can’t believe this happened. I should have been there to protect her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>We have to ask you, Carlos. Who else had a key to Abby’s place?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>CARLOS</speaker><content>Nobody. Just the landlord.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You know if she was expecting any visitors?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>CARLOS</speaker><content>No. She was actually heading out to, uh … Club Doom. She had booked a personal appearance there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Uh … Abby was a celebrity?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>CARLOS</speaker><content>She was huge on social media.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So was she an actress or a singer or what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>CARLOS</speaker><content>No, she posted pics on Snappamatic. You know, the photo sharing app? Snappamatic reviews, she called them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And that got her personal appearances?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>CARLOS</speaker><content>Yeah, and sponsors, too. Especially when she had half a million followers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>What did Abby review, exactly?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>CARLOS</speaker><content>They were like, joke reviews. She came to New York to be a comedian, and um …  … this is how she hit it big.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> “These gyros came right back up. That’s a two-for-one special you don’t want.”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>CARLOS</speaker><content>This pic went viral and overnight she was a star. With follows and fans, all this attention, I felt like I was losing her. Like there was no room left for the two of us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Do you think she had any stalkers?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>CARLOS</speaker><content>If she did I’m not sure she would have told me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-18"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Did any of these reviewees get upset about the pictures she posted?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-19"><speaker>CARLOS</speaker><content> Actually, yeah. There was guy. He made threatening calls.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-20"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>What was his name?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Edward Han. He’s an acupuncturist. His cell phone records show that he called Abby a dozen times in the days before her murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And who better than an acupuncturist to kill with accurate punctures? Perhaps with a giant needle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And he has the anatomical training to know where to strike.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Not to mention a beef with Abby.  Check this out. This was posted all over the place and I bet it put a damper on Han’s practice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> “Do not let this guy poke you.”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I don’t get it. Posting dumbass photos all over the place? How does she have a fan base? How did this become a career?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Welcome to the sharing economy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>More like oversharing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Really? And you’re opposed to all photos of oversharing women?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>That’s … different.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey. Han’s starting to look good for this. One of Abby’s neighbors saw him at her apartment yesterday.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>At her apartment? Doing what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Screaming at her. Threatening to “make her pay”. Until she slammed the door in his face.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So maybe he went back to get the last word.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>EDWARD HAN</speaker><content>I never went back. I admit I was at her apartment and I may have said those things, but –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You were angry about this review.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>HAN</speaker><content>Review? That bimbo was never even a client. She posted that picture and my walk-ins dropped off. Her little joke was costing me my business!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah well, in our business we call that motive. Where were you last night at 10:30?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>HAN</speaker><content>Off drowning my sorrows. I swear to you, I did not do this. But I know who did. She had a stalker.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, I know. We’re looking at him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>HAN</speaker><content>Not me! That’s what Abby thought, too, that I was stalking her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And why would she think that? Maybe because you were calling her all the time, showing up at her place?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>HAN</speaker><content>Abby said someone had been following her for the last month. But I didn’t track her down until a week ago. So the stalker couldn’t have been me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mr. Han, do you have evidence that this other person actually exists?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>HAN</speaker><content>There’s a note. On a postcard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What note?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>HAN</speaker><content>A threat she got that day. She waved it in my face. She accused me of slipping it under her door. Whoever left that note, that’s who did this. It has to be.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Han’s alibi checks out. Bartender said he was well into this fourth Mai Tai at the time of the murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>On reflection, it’s just as well.  From a storytelling standpoint. I mean, “Do not let this guy poke you” - and then the acupuncturist stabs her with a giant needle? It’s just a little too obvious.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Which means we’re looking for someone else with motive, but so far no one sticks out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Maybe Abby’s family has some insight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>They don’t. She wasn’t very close to them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>It looks like Han was telling the truth about that threat. CSU found this postcard in Abby’s dresser drawer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>“The brightest stars burn quickest.”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>She got this and on the same day she was murdered?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Is this a fingerprint?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No, that’s a smudge. But it might mean something. The lab says that it’s wood varnish.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey guys. Check this out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I was looking through Abby’s followers and one of them posted pictures of her on their account.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Crime scene photos?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>But not ours. The killer took these photos before we got to the crime scene.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> “This star’s 15 seconds are over.”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Whose account is this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>User name is … Netslayer.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>He kills her and then posts her picture. Why would he do that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Tear down the victim? Add insult to injury? “This star’s 15 seconds are over.” Maybe that’s why he killed Abby, because she’s a web celebrity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Or he wants to become one himself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Abby did have half a million followers. Killing her would give him an instant high profile.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Or he could just be using social media to hide his true motives for killing her. Either way, maybe these photos can help us find him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, I’ll get with Tory. We’ll analyze the photos, see if we can pull some images off the reflections.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>All right. And I’ll go through his account, see if he posted anything else that would help us ID him.  Where are you guys going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Straight to the source. Maybe Snappamatic can give us an idea of who he is or where to find him.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>KENT WILDER</speaker><content>Actually, ID’ing and locating users are two things we just can’t do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Can’t? Or won’t?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>OREN WILDER</speaker><content>Can’t. Snappamatic was designed for privacy. It runs on a software platform that anonymizes all of our users.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> I bet that was a real selling point for the killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>OREN</speaker><content>Look, no one is more upset about this than we are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I bet Abby Smith was.  One of your users killed her and you’re trying to tell me that you can’t help us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>KENT</speaker><content>We’re trying. Evan’s combing the guy’s account but all you need to register is a valid email address.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>EVAN</speaker><content>Which isn’t valid anymore, by the way, so no help there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>OREN</speaker><content>What we can do is suspend his account so he can’t post.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Uh, well the reason he’s posting in the first place is because he wants attention. He needs to communicate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Exactly. He likes to share, so let him. Maybe he’s going to share something that he didn’t intend to. Now, take the pictures down but leave the account up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>OREN</speaker><content>We’d rather not have the Snappamatic brand associated with a murderer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>It already is. It’s our pipeline directly to the killer. The account stays open.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Consider the bright side, gentlemen. The traffic for your site will be through the roof.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>EVAN</speaker><content>I think I got something.  I was digging through the metadata and found a geotag anomaly on one of the pictures.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What kind of an anomaly?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-17"><speaker>EVAN</speaker><content>Okay, so the geotag holds GPS coordinates, usually of where a photo was taken.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Usually, but not always?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-19"><speaker>EVAN</speaker><content>Not if the camera loses its GPS signal. In that case, the geotag is assigned when the photo is uploaded.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So the killer lost his GPS signal, didn’t notice –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And then when he posted his photos onto Snappamatic he accidently revealed his location.  What are the coordinates?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Tory plotted the longitude and latitude of the geotag and we got an address in downtown Manhattan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And what’s there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>It’s a vintage furniture store.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Wood – wood varnish! That explains the smudge on the note!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, let’s get the names of everyone that works there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>We already did. It’s a one man shop owned by one Bill Garrett. It turns out he used to be a cop until he had a nervous breakdown. And get this – he worked in the cyber division.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Which means he would know his way around the web and social media.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Bring him in.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Bill Garrett! NYPD! Keep your hands where we can see them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>On your knees. You know the drill.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>BILL GARRETT</speaker><content>Getting brought in here is no way to treat a fellow officer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mr. Garrett, we found these when we searched your shop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>I refinish furniture. Of course I have awls.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Awls that match the stab wounds in her neck?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>If you think I murdered this girl you’re out of your mind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We also found this cell phone. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>I keep it for emergencies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Emergencies. Like uh … snapping photos?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You see, even when you delete them they can still be recovered.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>All right, what is this? I didn’t take those.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Then how did they end up on your phone? And why were they uploaded to Snappamatic using your wifi network?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-12"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>I don’t upload photos. I don’t even go near the web unless I have to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And then there’s the text to Abby, and the wood varnish on this note, which we’re going to trace right back to your shop. It’s over. Your best bet is to cut a deal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-14"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>This is a mistake.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Working cyber unit must’ve taken its toll. It must have been difficult, seeing the darkest side of the web. That must have changed you. Maybe that’s why you left and did what you did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-16"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>I didn’t do anything. And I quit cyber because a frat boy date raped a girl, posted the photos online, and then got away with it, so I flipped out and I put him in the hospital.  I did not hurt this girl. I do not know her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Where were you at 10:30PM?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-18"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>I was at home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>With who?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-20"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>Nobody. I was alone.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>This was just posted to the Netslayer’s account.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s you guys arresting Garrett.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Wait, what’s this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> “Wrong suspect, NYPD. I’m still here. What will I do next?”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So either Garrett was framed –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Or somehow he pulled this off to make it look like he was framed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Whoever this is, he just took this to a whole new level. He’s taunting us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>More pictures are coming in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Body parts?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Body parts, sausages, a date? What the hell is this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> “The game is on.” That’s a challenge. Those are clues.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Clues to what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>His next murder.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Body parts … sausage … November 12th. Body parts being made into sausage. Human sausages … in November.  I’m not getting anywhere with this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> And you’re sure?  Okay. Thanks.  Garrett’s alibi checks out. He activated his alarm system when he got home last night and no one entered or exited until morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So the killer set him up just to toy with us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>CAPTAIN VICTORIA GATES</speaker><content>Detective? The news media’s calling for comment. 1PP wants to know what we think this is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>We’re not sure. This could be a clue as to his next victim or victims. Each image could represent a different person.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Or it could be a pictogram where the images add up to a message.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Tory’s trying to analyze each image, find their sources. But we think this collage is from one photo of a woman, Caucasian, in her 20s.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>So she could be our next target.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And given the killer’s behavior, she’s most likely someone with a high internet profile like Abby Smith.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yo. So we ID’d that grill as a Fowler. We’re checking into anybody named Fowler who might be big on social media.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-11"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>And that date. November 12th. Any special significance?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, for starters, it turns out it is World Pneumonia Day. But we’re also checking into any news events, births, and deaths that occurred that day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>If it even is a date. 11-12-13 could be part of a number sequence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-14"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yes, Castle. We’re also looking into that, as well as anyone Garrett put away while he was in cyber.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-15"><speaker>TORY ELLIS</speaker><content>Detective Beckett?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>TORY</speaker><content>I was able to identify one of the images.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>TORY</speaker><content>It was cropped from this photo of a food blogger named Mary Fuchs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Where did you find that photo?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>TORY</speaker><content>She posted it on her Snappamatic feed a few days ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So Mary Fuchs is a Snappamatic user just like Abby Smith.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>She could be next. We need to find her and bring her in here.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>MARY FUCHS</speaker><content>I don’t understand. Why would someone post part of my picture?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ms. Fuchs, do these images mean anything to you? Or this date?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>MARY</speaker><content>No. I mean, I don’t think so.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What about Abby Smith? Do you know her? Do you have any connection to her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>MARY</speaker><content>I’d never even heard of her until it was all over the news that she died. Is whoever killed her after me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, has anyone been following you? Have you received any threatening messages?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>MARY</speaker><content>No, nothing like that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You’re a blogger, right? What do you blog about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-9"><speaker>MARY</speaker><content>Uh, German cuisine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>German cuisine?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-11"><speaker>MARY</speaker><content>I’m German, so I review German restaurants. And I post recipes for classic dishes like strudel and the bratwurst I’m grilling in the picture.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So your Snappamatic page says that you have –  – 47 followers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-13"><speaker>MARY</speaker><content> Yeah. I think that’s pretty good, considering I just joined last week.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I don’t get it. Killing put the Netslayer onto the big stage. Taunting the police about it just turned on the Klieg lights. Why target a no-name like her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Maybe he’s trying to send a message that no one’s safe. Not web-celebs or obscure German food bloggers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, you better add artists to that list as well. Tory just ID’d another one of our images.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Is it from Snappamatic?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah. From the feed of a painter named Daniel Leek. The image is from a photo he took of one of his pieces. See, the expiration date is cropped from the top of this milk carton. But Leek’s pretty low on the Snappamatic totem pole. He only has about two thousand followers. Heck, my blog has more than that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You have a blog?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah, yeah. The Ryan Report. It’s the musings of a homicide detective?  You haven’t read it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No – I – oh, The Ryan Report. Yeah. I thought – because I didn’t –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, in spite of Leek’s following, let’s try to get him in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well … that’s going to be difficult. He’s at an art opening in Seattle. He doesn’t live in New York.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>If he lives in Seattle how is he a possible victim?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He’s not.  Rotten fruit, expiration date …  What’s the name of that painting?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-13"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Uh … “Spoiled”, I think.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I know what the clues mean.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Expiration date on spoiled milk. Plus grilled bratwurst equals … spoiled brats.  That’s the message. That’s what the images mean, leading us to …  Seriously? Anyone here besides me a consumer of vapid online magazines?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, all right. Spoiled brats, as in –  – “The Spoiled Brats of Snappamatic” feature article from two weeks ago. It’s all about rich kids who post pictures of their extravagant lifestyles on Snappamatic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s the key to solving the case. The killer has given us a pictogram – as I predicted – pointing us to that article.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, maybe, but what about the third image? The collage?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>This is it! This is the photo. Those are Tatiana Fisher’s body parts from this photo that she took with her boyfriend Cam Magani. He posted it on his Snappamatic feed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Spoiled … brat … Tatiana.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>She has over a million followers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Going after her would raise the killer’s infamy to new heights. She’s the next victim.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Tatiana Fisher, NYPD. We’ve been trying to get a hold of you and Cam Magani. We have reason to believe that you might be the Netslayer’s next target.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>TATIANA FISHER</speaker><content>That’s insane. He wouldn’t dare.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, maybe not. But we need to take you back to the precinct.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>TATIANA</speaker><content>I’m not going anywhere with you. I have a party on Fire Island, so…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Ma’am, this is a potentially dangerous situation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>TATIANA</speaker><content> Did you just call me ma’am? Look, I’ll make it simple for you, okay? Can you force me to go with you? Yes or no.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>TATIANA</speaker><content>Well then. Bye bye.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Wait, Ms. Fisher – Ms. Fisher.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Please. Just give us a –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>TATIANA</speaker><content>Oh my God, Cam!</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>NEWS REPORTER WOMAN</speaker><content>The internet is abuzz today with news of a serial killer stalking social media.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>NEWS REPORTER MAN</speaker><content>The representatives of Snappamatic, the online photo sharing app, have released a statement saying that they are cooperating with authorities.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>NEWS REPORTER WOMAN</speaker><content>Socialite Cam Magani’s body was found murdered in the vehicle you see behind me. Magani may be the latest victim of Netslayer, the mysterious online figure who claimed responsibility of Abby Smith, then posted gruesome images of body. With the city and internet roiling with fear, many are asking, who will this serial killer strike next and when will authorities stop him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>This guy is getting exactly what he wanted: attention. And it’s making him bolder, so where do we stand?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Sir, it looks like the killer hid in the back seat of Cam’s car, waited for him to get in, and then slit his throat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>How did he get in the car?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, we’re not sure, but CSU found plastic fragments inside the door lock. It might be from a lock pick.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So far there’s no prints or DNA and all we know for sure is that the killer was right handed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>And we paid too high a cost for that knowledge.  Detective? Bring me some good news before we lose another one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yes sir.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I can’t help but think if only I had figured it out sooner maybe he’s still be alive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>It wouldn’t have mattered. The game was rigged from the start. We never had a chance. The killer just wanted us to think we did. And now the Netslayer’s going to gain more notoriety and more followers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He already has. He’s at over half a million so far and earning thousands more by the minute.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-14"><speaker>TORY</speaker><content>Detective Beckett. Two more pictures just came in. Something different this time.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>TORY</speaker><content>This one was uploaded first. Proof of death, I guess you’d call it.  Then he sent this one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, it’s us before the first crime scene.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> “NYPD is on the case. Feel safe New York? You shouldn’t. I’m not done.”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He’s been watching us from the beginning. The guy’s been ahead of us the whole time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Detective Beckett? A word.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>1PP saw that picture, too. And they called me, concerned, about your commitment to this case.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>BECKTT</speaker><content>Sir, they’re taking that photo out of context.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>The truth doesn’t matter, Kate. It’s a public relations problem now. The killer just turned you into the poster child for these murders not being solved.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So … what? They want to take me off the case?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>I told them no. I won’t let our suspect sabotage this investigation by manipulating the narrative. So go home, clear your head. You get back here and you take his ass down.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>This is why I hate social media. Once something is out there you have no control. People can take a private moment and create their own context. I mean, we weren’t even investigating the murder yet and they made us look like we were bad cops. Or worse. Like we didn’t care.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Come on, Beckett, it’s the internet. No one’s going to take that picture seriously.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>1PP did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Look. It’s going to blow over, okay? With millions of items being posted every minute this is but a blip on the net continuum.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know the problem with anonymity? There’s no accountability. It empowers cowards to become bullies, just like this guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> You know what? Most bullies started out as victims themselves. Maybe this guy is lashing out on the internet because it was used against him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>He was a victim of a cybercrime.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And Bill Garrett was a cyber-cop. It can’t be a coincidence that the killer targeted him. We’ve been looking at people Garrett put away –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>When we should have been looking at victims of his cyber cases. Okay, I’ll get ahold of Garrett, I’ll have him look into his old case files. Our killer’s got to be in there somewhere.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Still, how did he get into Garrett’s shop to plant the evidence? Or Cam’s car?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I’ll tell you how. With a key. A key that he made.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>A 3D printer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah. Remember the fragment that we found in the lock of Cam’s Rolls Royce? Well, they’re PLA. It’s a bio plastic used in 3D printing. CSU found PLA in the locks at Abby’s apartment as well as Garrett’s shop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>How could the killer make a copy of the key without the original?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>It turns out all you need is a picture. When Cam bought the Rolls, he bragged about it by posting a photo of the key that anyone could then digitize. So, just as the killer did, I uploaded a photo to the printer and –  – voila.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Outstanding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>If by outstanding you mean horrifying. The killer snapped a photo of this key and then made a 3D duplicate of it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Welcome to the future.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Still, I’ve gotta get one of these.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Is there any way of finding out where the killer got his?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, we’re checking. But between brick and mortar and online stores we’ve got hundreds of vendors.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, this explains how he got Cam’s key but not Garrett and Abby’s.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>CARLOS</speaker><content>Abby never posted photos of her keys. And she was careful. It’s not like she left them lying around.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Did she ever valet park her car?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>CARLOS</speaker><content>No. She didn’t even drive it, except to get out of the city.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Any of her friends have keys to her place?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>CARLOS</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>She never let anybody crash there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>CARLOS</speaker><content>Actually … Abby used to rent out her apartment online. Through a travel site.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>The people who stayed, how’d they get her keys?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>CARLOS</speaker><content>She’d leave them under a loose brick on her stoop.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So I’ve been running the people that rented Abby’s apartment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why would anyone let complete strangers stay in their place?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>TORY</speaker><content>Extra money.  After this I don’t think I’ll be doing it anymore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So all the renters checked out except for one guy who booked and never showed up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>TORY</speaker><content>This is from an ATM across from Abby’s apartment on the day he was supposed to stay there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Turns out a guy did show up. Check this out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>He took a picture of her key. It’s the Netslayer. It’s gotta be.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-8"><speaker>TORY</speaker><content>It’s too far away and too low res to blow up, but watch this as he walks away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-9"><speaker>TORY</speaker><content>There.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And now we have a face.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Okay, where are we on finding this man?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>We’re distributing his picture. So far none of the victim’s families or neighbors recognize him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Sir, I’d like to release his photo to the press and social media.  Let’s turn the tables on this guy. He’s trying to hide, but someone out there’s going to recognize his face.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>You’re right. And that someone is me. I was going over these case files when the officer showed me his photo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Who is he?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>His name’s Adam Lane.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>You arrested him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>He wasn’t a criminal when we met. He was a victim.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And do you have any idea where he is now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-10"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>I haven’t seen or heard from Lane in six years. It took me a minute to recognize him with that fake beard he’s wearing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-11"><speaker>GATES</speaker><content>Okay. I’ll get ready to release Adam Lane’s name and picture to the media.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>There’s no current address for Lane.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Try to find one. Reach out to his family and anyone else that knows him.  In the meantime you need to tell us everything you know about Adam Lane.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>Lane was in high school back then. It was a cyber-bullying case.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Who was bullying him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>He was taking a shower when this meathead football player, Tim Witherspoon, stole his clothes. Now, this had happened to Lane his whole life, but this time he went ballistic. There he was, buck naked, screaming at Witherspoon in the locker room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I think I know where the cyber part comes in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>Yeah. Witherspoon secretly recorded it and posted it on his MySpace page.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So he was publicly humiliated.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-7"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>Yeah, but it wasn’t just the humiliation. After the video, the kids turned on him. They inundated him with these awful, hateful emails.  And no one was held accountable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-9"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>The cyber-bullying laws at the time were weak. I got him to take the video down but I couldn’t convince the DA to press charges. I should have tried harder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What happened to Lane?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-11"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>Everyone had their breaking point, right? Quit school, withdrew from life. It ruined him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And now he’s getting revenge by going after the popular kids on social media.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-13"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>And targeting me because I didn’t protect him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Not just you. All of us.  Did he have any friends? Was there anywhere he liked to hang out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-15"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>No, he was a loner. Computer geek. He didn’t have any friends. That’s pretty much all I know.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey. I’m having no luck tracking down Adam Lane. It looks like he went off the grid. No tax returns, no driver’s license, no job except for a stint at a funeral home three years ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That must be how he knows about anatomy. What about his parents?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Uh, father wasn’t in the picture, mother died about a year ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hey, get this. I ran down Tim Witherspoon, Lane’s bully. Turns out, he’s dead. Unsolved homicide. He was stabbed in his apartment ten months ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s right after Lane’s mother died. Maybe that’s what triggered him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So he murdered Witherspoon, took his revenge, but that wasn’t enough for him. Where did Lane and his mom live?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, the apartment sold when she died, but they lived on Avenue C at East 5th.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>That’s the Lower East Side. Ever since we released Lane’s photo we’ve had multiple tips that he’d been seen in that area.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>An antisocial kid like Lane who’s never made his way in the world is going to stay with what’s familiar. The Lower East Side’s the only neighborhood he’s ever known.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Who bought his mother’s place?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>An old Russian couple. But the basement is a rental unit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Who wants to bet Lane’s still living there?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Adam Lane, you’re under arrest for murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What’s so funny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>ADAM LANE</speaker><content>You’ll see.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Beckett.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>We got a problem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What’s the problem? We’ve got Adam Lane in custody.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, he’s got people in custody, too. It just showed up on the Netslayer feed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What people?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Oren and Kent Wilder from Snappamatic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>They’re about to be his next victims.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> “Like me or I die”. It’s a popularity contest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And Kent is losing. These guys' photos update every five seconds along with their votes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>They’re both attached to electrical leads.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>They probably lead to a power supply controlled by a computer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>That countdown started at one hour. Once it reaches zero …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Whichever brother has the least votes gets his heart stopped.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Or they both do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> It's the ultimate attack on social media.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>And us. He wants us to feel powerless. Those guys are going to die even though he’s in custody.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Not if we get to them first.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>In 37 minutes? How are we going to do that? They’re in front of tarps. There’s no background detail. These guys could be anywhere. Maybe even in separate places.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Go to the Snappamatic offices. Maybe they’ll help us track down the source of these photos now that Kent and Oren’s lives are at stake.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What are you going to do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I’m going to make Adam Lane talk.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>ADAM</speaker><content>So who’s ahead? Oren or Kent?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Time isn’t just running out for them, Adam. It’s running out for you as well. Your one and only window of opportunity is about to close.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>ADAM</speaker><content>I have nothing to say.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Look, I’m not going to lie to you. You are going to prison. But if you tell me where Kent and Oren are then you can still control what kind of prison.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-5"><speaker>ADAM</speaker><content>What’s the expression? Three hots and a cot?  Works for me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah well, you’re not going to be saying that if you get sent to the super max unit, where we put our most dangerous and violent inmates. You’ll be on lockdown there 24/7 for the rest of your life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-7"><speaker>ADAM</speaker><content>It can’t be any worse than high school.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Really? And you think that you were bullied? Well prison is going to take you places that you can’t imagine. A guy like you? Young, teachable?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-9"><speaker>ADAM</speaker><content>It doesn’t matter. I already have what I want.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And what do you think you have?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-11"><speaker>ADAM</speaker><content>A legacy. The internet is permanent. The Netslayer will live forever. I’ll be mentioned in the same breath as Manson and the Zodiac and … if I commit a murder while in police custody, while looking you in the eye, I could argue I did them one better. And there’s nothing you can do to stop me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Adam, you need help. You’re sick. Let me get you –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-13"><speaker>ADAM</speaker><content>I’m sick?  Nobody had to follow me. No one has to vote for Kent or Oren. But they can’t help themselves. They want to be a part of it. They have to watch. So … who is really sick?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="34"><utterance uid="34-1"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>He wasn’t always like that. If I could go back and do it over again …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You didn’t make him this way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-3"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>Yeah, but I didn’t stop it. And now I can’t stop these two guys from dying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>If anyone can break him, it’s Detective Beckett. And there’s still a chance Snappamatic can help us.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="35"><utterance uid="35-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>How’re we doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-2"><speaker>EVAN</speaker><content>Coding’s not like flipping a switch. It takes a little while.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>We don’t have a little while, Evan. We have –  – fifteen minutes to find these guys.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-4"><speaker>EVAN</speaker><content>I’m going as fast as I can. Kent was working on a software patch that would disable the program’s privacy protocols.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>And if we disable the protocols we can track where these photos are coming from?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-6"><speaker>EVAN</speaker><content>Yes.  I mean, in theory. The thing is, we’ve never done it before. I don’t know if it’ll work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Our canvass didn’t turn up a single witness to the abduction. We’re nowhere, bro. Tell me you’ve got something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>About to find out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-9"><speaker>EVAN</speaker><content>Okay.  Let’s do this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>What happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-11"><speaker>EVAN</speaker><content>The system crashed. We’re locked out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, get it back up! We’ve got fifteen minutes before these guys are dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-13"><speaker>EVAN</speaker><content>It takes twenty minutes to reboot.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="36"><utterance uid="36-1"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>What just happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Whatever they were trying didn’t go well. The site just crashed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-3"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>So there’s no way to trace those feeds of Oren and Kent? And that timer will just keep counting down until one of them is dead?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It’s all up to Beckett now.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="37"><utterance uid="37-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Adam, just answer one question and it might save your life. Where are Oren and Kent?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-2"><speaker>ADAM</speaker><content>If you cops were capable of doing your jobs you’d know. And looking back, maybe none of this would have ever happened.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Look, a horrible thing was done to you. But how is killing two more people going to fix that? How is that going to heal you? It won’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-4"><speaker>ADAM</speaker><content>It will. Don’t you see that I’ve already won? I’ll tell you what: admit that I won and I’ll give you a hint. I’ll give you a change to find Kent or Oren before ­– </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Fine. You won.  Now give me the hint.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-6"><speaker>ADAM</speaker><content>Changed my mind.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="38"><utterance uid="38-1"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>Seven minutes left. She’d gotta make a move, shake him up somehow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>She will.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="39"><utterance uid="39-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Netslayer. That’s evocative. I could – I could see how you would pick that. I picture a hooded figure, in all black, tall, muscular, maybe carrying an axe. But you know what I don’t picture, Adam? What nobody pictures?  You.  You think that you won? You haven’t. Everyone else has.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-2"><speaker>ADAM</speaker><content>What do you mean, everyone else?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Everyone who ever bullied you, whoever hurt you. Belittled you. Who thought that you were weak and worthless and small. And you know what, Adam? They were right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-4"><speaker>ADAM</speaker><content>No, they weren’t. I am not any of those things.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You’re all of them. And worse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-6"><speaker>ADAM</speaker><content>I am what people made me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You were born this way, or your mommy made you, but Tim Witherspoon and the rest of the kids at school? They didn’t break you. You were already broken. They only sensed what you were and what you were about to become. So you know what? In a way their bullying wasn’t enough.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-8"><speaker>ADAM</speaker><content>How can you say that to me? I’m the victim here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And you’re always going to be the victim. You think that hiding behind a user name and killing is going to change that? That won’t get you respect. You’re always going to be the same pathetic loser that you always were.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-10"><speaker>ADAM</speaker><content>I am not a loser!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And when you abducted Kent and Oren, I bet the two of them looked at each other and thought, “Are we being punked here?”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-12"><speaker>ADAM</speaker><content>Believe me, they didn’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>They think it’s a joke.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-14"><speaker>ADAM</speaker><content>They’re afraid. They’re - they’re terrified.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>They’re sharing a laugh right now about you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-16"><speaker>ADAM</speaker><content>They are not laughing!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="40"><utterance uid="40-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>She just got them to say that they’re together.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="41"><utterance uid="41-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh, they’re laughing. They’re laughing right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-2"><speaker>ADAM</speaker><content>Well, not for long. That clock will hit zero and their screams will echo off the tiled walls as they take in their last breath of stale air and then? They’ll both fry.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="42"><utterance uid="42-1"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>Tiled walls and stale air? That was how he talked about the locker room at his school.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Where Witherspoon put him on the video. He’s bringing this thing full circle. What was the name of that high school?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-3"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>Harding High, but they moved to a new campus. The original building is shut down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Beckett!</content></utterance>
</scene>


<scene id="43"><utterance uid="43-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Javi, the wires!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="43-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content> You okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="43-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> You okay?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="44"><utterance uid="44-1"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>I just wanted to say thanks for letting me pitch in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="44-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Are you kidding me? We couldn’t have done this without you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="44-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, Oren and Kent are alive because of your help.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="44-4"><speaker>GARRETT</speaker><content>Well, it’s always good to get a win.  Well, see you around.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="44-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>See you around.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="44-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>See you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="44-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know, there used to be some finality to all of this. You take a photo, dump it in the box, and you never see that face again. Not anymore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="44-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, Adam Lane is going to be on the news every night. He’ll be on the web for weeks. Months. Geez, years. Ironic that by catching him we’re giving him exactly what he wanted. More followers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="44-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, after this case I think I’m ready to unplug. Stay off the internet for a while.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="44-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yes, but before you do, we have one last piece of internet business.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="45"><utterance uid="45-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Come in, you guys. Come in. Right this way. Right this way! After you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="45-2"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Okay. Ah ha!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="45-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>All right. My publisher just sent me the link for the web-mercial for Raging Heat.  Prepare for greatness in three … two … one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="45-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hi. I’m Richard – I’ve got gum. I’m going to put my gum out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="45-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hi, I’m Richard Castle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="45-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hi, I’m Crichard Rastle.  Hi, I’m Richard Castle. Hi, I’m Richard Castle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="45-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hi, I’m Crichard Rastle.  I’m Richard Castle. For a spine-tingling, bone-chilling adventure, Raging Heat. For a spine-tingling, bone-chilling adventure, Raging Heat. For a spine-tingling, bone-chilling adventure, Raging Heat. For a sp – . It’s not an adventure. It’s a thriller. Why don’t you download your copy today? Hi, I’m Richard Castle. Hi, I’m Crichard Rastle.  I’m Richard Castle. Hi, I’m Richard Castle. Hi, I’m Crichard Rastle.  I’m Richard Castle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="45-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> What the hell was that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="45-9"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Dad, you’ve gotten over a million hits.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="45-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> A million people have seen that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="45-11"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="45-12"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>It’s gone viral, darling. Isn’t that what you wanted?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="45-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Not like this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="45-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Don’t worry, Castle. It’ll blow over. This is but a blip on the net continuum.  But … we so need to watch this one again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="45-15"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="45-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="45-17"><speaker>THE END</speaker><content>CASTLE</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>