<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>DARREN IVES</speaker><content>She’s texting me again, bro.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>MICHAEL KIRBY</speaker><content>Who?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>DARREN</speaker><content>Angie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>MICHAEL</speaker><content>You going to see her again?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>DARREN</speaker><content>Nah man, I have to shut that down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>MICHAEL</speaker><content>You’ve been singing the blues about this woman for months. She reaches her hand out and you’re going to slap it away?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>DARREN</speaker><content>Yeah, well, she broke my heart, man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>MICHAEL</speaker><content>Which means she deserves another shot. Trust me, I know.  Fourteen years and counting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>DARREN</speaker><content>You’re right. I’ll give her a call.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>MICHAEL</speaker><content>Nice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>MICHAEL</speaker><content>I’ll go get the rest of the bags.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>RICHARD CASTLE</speaker><content>That wasn’t me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>KATE BECKETT</speaker><content> Says the guy with the razor sharp French toast and the sausage kabob.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay, that was m,e but that balloon had it coming.  To you, my love, my heart, my bride. Welcome back to our home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh, that is so sweet, Castle. But how is this a welcome back if I’ve been sneaking into your room almost every night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, because you officially moved all your stuff back in. Now that we’ve agreed to hunt LokSat together we can simply pick up where we left off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And as I recall we left off this morning somewhere right about here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Lucy, music off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>LUCY</speaker><content>As you wish, Rick.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What just happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I integrated Lucy into all the loft’s infrastructure. Climate, lights, music, you name it, she controls it. Just got to work out a few kinks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, I still like a few things the old fashioned way, so do you want me to make you a cup of coffee?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>LUCY</speaker><content>Uh, no need, Kate. I’ve programmed Rick’s coffee exactly to his liking. Cuban blend, two sugars, pinch of nutmeg.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s amazing, huh?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>LUCY</speaker><content>No, Rick, you’re amazing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No, you are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>LUCY</speaker><content>No, you are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No, Lucy, you are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>LUCY</speaker><content>Rick, you are amazing and you know it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Beckett.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Stop it! I’m not doing this with you again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-22"><speaker>LUCY</speaker><content>You stop it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah.  Got it.  We have a homicide.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-24"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You, me, and a crime scene. Just as nature intended.  All right, Captain, let’s roll.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-25"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ah, no can do. Captains have to multi-task. In fact, I am due for a meeting with the DA so … why don’t you meet up with the boys? We can debrief later.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-26"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You got it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-27"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Um … Lucy, do you think you could make me a cup of coffee? Splash of low fat milk, two Splendas?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-28"><speaker>LUCY</speaker><content>No can do. All out of Splenda, but there is a Starbuck's two blocks from here. Would you like directions?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-29"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No. Thanks. I know where it is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-30"><speaker>LUCY</speaker><content>Great. Have fun. Goodbye. Leave the house.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>JAVIER ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hey. Look who’s here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>LANIE PARISH</speaker><content>Castle! So happy you and Beckett are back together. Now do us all a favor and don’t mess things up with her again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Why do you assume it was my fault?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Everything is your fault. Now, come meet our new victim. Michael Kirby, single GSW.  Our thief-slash-killer rappelled from that AC duct.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And they got away with a hundred thousand dollars in cash.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>KEVIN RYAN</speaker><content>This is Darren Ives. He was inside when he heard the shot. Rushed out but the killer was already gone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>DARREN</speaker><content>I don’t know how that guy did it. I mean, this is a high security warehouse. It’s damn near Fort Knox.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And you didn’t see anything suspicious?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>DARREN</speaker><content>Nothing. It was just a normal drop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Let’s finish taking your statement over here, please.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>What, are your allergies acting up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What is this, gelatin? It smells like ladies’ perfume.  What is that scent? Is it White Diamonds? No, Chanel No. 5.  Ah. One Direction body spray. Nailed it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>That stuff dripped from the AC vent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>CSU took samples. It’s from the alarm sensors in the vent. Apparently the killer used it to disable the security system.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Lanie, can you ask the lab to put a rush on this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Why? What is it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I’ve seen this MO before.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>It was like, ten years ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So, when you worked with the Fifty-Fourth?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, I collared a thief. Name was uh … Sonia Ruiz. She was part of a crew that stole ten million dollars’ worth of gold coins from an auction house.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And they used a fragrant gel, too?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>It was actually a unique blend of Jell-O and ladies’ perfume.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You’re saying a kid’s dessert mixed with eau de toilette can foil a sophisticated security system?  I’m telling you, we need a dog.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Does that formula even work?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, someone in the crew came up with it. The gelatin blocks the security lasers and the phalates in the perfume creates an even distribution over the sensors. But the mix has to be exact. Eighty percent Jell-O, twenty percent perfume.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Which is the precise ratio of the gelatin found at our crime scene. Lab sent over the analysis report identical to the heist from nine years ago where the only perp captured was Sonia Ruiz.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yep, that’s her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So obviously this wasn’t a coincidence. Most likely someone from the crew reused the technique and is behind our victim’s murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, it couldn’t have been Sonia. She got fifteen years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And what about the rest of the crew.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Nah, she didn’t give up any names. The rumor was that the crew was put together by some mysterious shot caller who goes by the street name of Great White.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Is it possible to trace them through the stolen gold coins? I mean, they had to have tried to sell them at some point.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>There hasn’t been any trace of them since the heist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, that makes sense. If they melted the coins down for the gold that would render the coins untraceable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Espo, why don’t we pay Sonia Ruiz a little visit? She might not have turned on her crew back in the day but after nine years hard time we might be able to persuade her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You know what, from what I remember she may be the type to hold a grudge so … you might have better luck taking Castle with you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh –  – not falling for that trick again. Contrary to what you three lead me to believe, those women’s prisons are nothing like the late night Skinamax movies, so … have fun.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>All right, Miss Ruiz, tell me what you know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>SONIA RUIZ</speaker><content>Please. I didn’t snitch back in the day. Why would I start now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Because nine years ago this was just a burglary and now it’s a murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Murder? Who died?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>An armored truck driver. Look, Sonia, you help me out, I’ll help you out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>With what? I’m up for parole in three months and due to overcrowding I’m a lock to get out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Not if I go to your parole hearing and testify that you refused to cooperate in solving a homicide.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>It’s like that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I got an innocent man in the morgue who left behind a wife and two small kids so yeah, it’s like that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>I couldn’t help you even if I wanted to. The gold coin heist Great White set up was a two person job. But I don’t know my partner’s name.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That doesn’t make any sense.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>And yet it’s true. He didn’t know my name and I didn’t know his, so neither one of us could rat out the other. We used shark names. I was Mako, he was Hammerhead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>All right, what can you tell me about Great White.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Now, his name I knew. Jimmy Sanchez. He was a neighborhood shot caller back in the day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay. So where can I find him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>In the cemetery.  He died a little over three years ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Wait, if Great White is dead then Hammerhead’s most likely our killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-18"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Hey, that Jell-O perfume formula was his invention so it has to be.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What do you remember about Hammerhead?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-20"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Um …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Anything. At all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-22"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Once he let it slip that he met Jimmy Sanchez at a bar called um … El Toro.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Good. I’ll have my detectives head off over there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-24"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Ooh. Good luck with that, lady.  It’s up in Spanish Harlem. No one there talks to the police. However, they will talk to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-25"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You want me to put you on the street?  No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-26"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Hey. You’re hanging parole over my head. You want Hammerhead? This is how you get him.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>The department of corrections authorized her for an out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah. Right now Sonia is our best and only path to Hammerhead’s real identity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>So what’s the plan?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You and Espo are going to head over to the –  – excuse me, what’s going on? What are you not telling me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content> So uh … funny story, really. Sonia and I, we were kind of … involved.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Involved, like dating?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Dating? No. Come on. Not dating.  We were more like engaged.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Engaged? You were – wait a second, all these years you never told me that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You never asked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>You’re a cop. How could you get involved with a criminal?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, technically, they were in the same line of work, so really it’s a … workplace romance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content> Thank you.  I didn’t know she was a crook at first, okay? I – I met her at a club. She seemed normal. We just – we just clicked. And it’s probably why she hid who she really was from me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And when did you find out the truth?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>After it was too late! We were engaged and she started acting strange. Disappearing at odd hours, and she couldn’t look me in the eye. And then news of that gold coin heist broke and I – I don’t know. I knew. And I was the one who arrested her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So did you ask for the ring back or did you let her keep that so she could trade it for cigarettes in the prison yard?  That’s – don’t answer that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, so obviously you’re sitting this one out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Whoa, whoa, whoa – why’re you benching me?  Okay, I get it. Look, there’s no need. Any feelings I had for her died the moment I slapped those cuffs on. Trust me, I am over her completely.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-18"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Javier?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-19"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>You sure you’re over her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You might want to tell your mouth.  Close that up.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>She’s gorgeous.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>She’s a’ight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Are you okay? You seemed a little taken aback when you first saw her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No man, it’s just, um … it’s just a little déjà vu. She’s literally wearing the same outfit I arrested her in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Nine years later it’s still a great dress.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>It was a Friday night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What’s that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>It was a Friday night. We went salsa dancing on Friday nights.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You know, Javier, there’s no shame in admitting if you still have feelings.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I know! But I don’t. She’s just another convict. Nothing else.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>CORRECTIONS OFFICER</speaker><content>This ankle monitor is a next generation device with a variety of new tracking features. Here’s the instruction manual. Now, I’m going to walk you through some of the features, but –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>What does he have to do with this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Uh, Detective Ryan’s going to accompany you to the bar. He’s –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>What, him? Hell no! Take me back to prison. This is not going to work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Wait, I’m sorry. What’s the problem?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>You’re going to send me into a Spanish Harlem bar with Saint Patty on my arm?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Sweetheart, I used to work undercover. I can take care of myself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Look, the only way this is going to work is if I go in with somebody who can blend in.  Someone like Javi.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>For the umpteenth time, Beckett, I can handle this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Really? Because if it was me I don’t think I would be that confident.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Is it awkward? Of course. But it’s the only way we’re going to solve this murder. Castle and Ryan are going to be backing me up in a follow car. What’s the worst that can happen?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I don’t know. And that’s what makes me nervous.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Kate. I am not going to let you down.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>All right, listen up, Sonia. You do what I say, when I say it. Understand?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Nice to see you too, sweetie. Oh, muy es cosita -</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>This is not a joke, okay? When I say jump, you say –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>That you’re out of your damn mind if you think I’m jumping in these heels, okay? And speaking of, I need new clothes because this outfit is damn near ten years old. And I got a rep to protect so I need labels.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Fine, whatever. Let’s just hurry up and get this over with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Didn’t I used to say that to you whenever you got frisky at night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Let’s go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>This is going to be so much fun.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Can you please speed up? You know, my prison term is going to be over by the time we get there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I’m going the speed limit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Oh, good. You know, I wouldn’t want you to be pulled over by a cop. Come on! Hurry up!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I’m going to slow down a little bit.  There we go. That’s much better.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I still can’t believe Javi was engaged to that woman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I can. I mean, you see the electricity between those two? It crackles.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah, it might be a problem. We need to keep an eye on her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well actually, I think we can do more than that. There’s a listening device built into Sonia’s ankle monitor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>A hidden mic?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah. All we have to do is enter the security number into the app. We can hear everything they’re saying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>But they wouldn’t know that we’re listening. That would be an invasion of their privacy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You got a problem with that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>No.  No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>You know, I’m glad you didn’t get fat over all that guilt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What guilt?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>For turning me in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Why would I feel guilty about doing my job?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Because you love me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content> Loved you. Past tense. Way past. Done. Finished. Terminado.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>You know, I was meaning to say thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>For what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>For arresting me.  You saved me the misery of spending another day with you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oooh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>That’s harsh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>How is your abuelita’s hip?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Good. She finally got it replaced.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Oh, good. She was always so sweet. Your whole family was. That’s what haunts me, you know? Thinking how they must have reacted when they learned I was nothing more than a crook.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Great White met Hammerhead here. It stands to reason someone here knows his real identity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Yeah, but that was nine years ago. Where do we start?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>The bartender. He’s bound to know where the old timers are, yeah?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Let me do the talking.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>BARTENDER</speaker><content>What’s going on, guys? What can I get for you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Uh, shots of tequila. Double rose.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>BARTENDER</speaker><content>Double rose coming up.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Thank you, baby.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>What is she doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>She’s blending into her environment. It’s actually a brilliant strategy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Either that, or getting Javier drunk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Why would she want to do that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Exactly. Exactly.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>BARTENDER</speaker><content>Ding ding. We got a winner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Set us up again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>BARTENDER</speaker><content>If you say so.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hey bro, how long have you been bartending here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>BARTENDER</speaker><content>A little over ten years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Oh, so then you remember a guy named Jimmy Sanchez? Went by the name of, uh Great White?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>BARTENDER</speaker><content>Great White. Yeah, yeah, why you ask?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Did you ever see him with a good looking kid from the neighborhood? Short, with a beard?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>BARTENDER</speaker><content>No. Sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Hey, it’s all good. I just got on parole, you know, from a little job we did back in the day. So if I could just find him …</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>BARTENDER</speaker><content>Look, señorita, I can’t help you out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>How about now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-13"><speaker>BARTENDER</speaker><content>What the hell are you doing, bro?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Give me his name.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Does it sound like –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Like he’s playing five finger filet with the bartender? It certainly does.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Don’t tell Beckett.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Don’t tell Beckett.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Ooh. My hand’s getting twitchy, bro. You better tell me something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>BARTENDER</speaker><content>Okay. Look, it’s Joey. His name’s Joey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Joey what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>BARTENDER</speaker><content>Beats the hell out of me, man! I haven’t seen the guy in over a year. That’s all I know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I don’t believe you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>BARTENDER</speaker><content>Stop! He’s close with his grandma, she lives up the street. Third building, brick one. 6D. She can tell you where he is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content> 6D.  6D. It’s open.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Hello?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Castle!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I lost the signal.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Make a move and I’ll kill you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Hey!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Who are you and why’d you break into my Gigi’s house?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Put the gun down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Screw that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Normally I’d do this back and forth thing with you but I’ve got to go chase her, so –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Man!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Don’t go anywhere.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay, here we go. Just reenter the serial number and voila.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>MAN</speaker><content>They’re my toes and I can pick ‘em if I want.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s the wrong ankle monitor.  I transposed the numbers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Was that -?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Damn it!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah, she’s right there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I got her.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Sonia, stop!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Javi, you’re okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, I’m okay, What are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>There was the guy with the shotgun, and –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Let me see your hands!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>What – what, you think I was trying to escape? I see a gun and I run. I was trying to get to a phone to call 911.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Not buying it, sweetheart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Irish, I got three months left on my sentence, okay? I already served nine long years. I run right now, they add another two. How dumb do you think I am?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Don’t answer that. It’s a trap, trust me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You think she’s telling the truth?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I don’t know. It’s not like she hasn’t lied to me before.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-12"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Damn. I knew you weren’t over me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content> I am so over you. Now, was that Hammerhead that jumped me with a shotgun?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-14"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Yeah. That was him.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Look, I didn’t know you were a cop, man. You broke into my Gigi’s apartment. My shotgun is registered and I have a right to defend my property. See, you got nothing to hold me on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You like sharks, Joey?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content> Yeah, they’re cool, I guess.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> What’s your favorite shark?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I like the ones with the funny shaped heads, you know what I’m talking about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh yeah, the hammerheads.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, that’s it. That’s funny, because we heard that you –  – were Hammerhead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-8"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Yeah? Who told you that?  Wait, that girl that was with you earlier. I knew she looked familiar.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hammerheads aren’t usually man killers, Joey, so what happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-10"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Ooh. I don’t know what you’re talking about.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Ten years ago you were part of a heist crew that used gelatin mixed with perfume to disable security systems. Last night you used the same recipe to break into a high security warehouse. Only thing is, you got caught and you murdered a guard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-12"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Last night I was in Jersey. At my Chicken, Chicken, Chicken. It’s a chicken restaurant. I own seven in the tristate area.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Let me guess, you bought those with your share of the gold coin heist?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-14"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Even if I did, the statute of limitations is over. And I have a dozen witnesses that put me at the Chicken, Chicken, Chicken until 3AM so you ain’t going to touch me with this score, either.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That doesn’t mean you weren’t a part of the heist. How else would they know about the gelatin formula?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-16"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Easy. I ain’t the only one who knew it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Great White? Jimmy Sanchez is dead. We confirmed that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-18"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Yeah, but he ran other crews. Ain’t no telling on how many of them he told. Look, I’m a successful businessman now. All right? Whatever criminal instincts I had … long gone. I’m all about the chicken now.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hey, Cap. Joey’s alibi checks out. We’re pulling apart his financials, but it looks like he might be telling the truth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay. I’ve got unis taking Sonia back to prison.  Are you okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, I’m just, uh … you know. I’m just bummed it didn’t work out.  Not between me and Sonia, I’m talking about the case. Ryan! You got something?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah. I think that crew used an inside man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What? What makes you think that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>The security system at that high security warehouse is way more sophisticated than the auction house where those gold coins were stolen. I mean, they had an infrared camera system that some low-tech bypass couldn’t have knocked out, yet it was down at the time of the murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So … somebody on the inside did turn it off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yes. Michael Kirby. Our victim. His security code was the one used.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>But if he was in on it then why kill him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I don’t know. But we could ask his wife.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hey Captain, I’d like to volunteer to take Sonia back to the prison.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, I don’t think that’s a good idea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, I know, but it’s the right thing to do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>All right.  You interview Kirby’s wife.  And I expect you back first thing in the morning ready to work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-15"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yes, ma’am.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-16"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>He’s going to be fine.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I’ll take her, boys. Captain’s orders.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>This is bull, Javi. You know I can still help.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I’m sorry. Joey was your only shot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>This sucks. I thought I’d at least get a decent meal. Maybe a hot shower. Sleep in a real bed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, in three months you’ll get all that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>You don’t understand. Nine years I’ve eaten prison food. Slept on a six inch piece of foam. Nine years I’ve had to live on edge. And I thought I’d get a little time to relax.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well, the drive is an hour. You can relax in the car.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Mrs. Kirby, we know about your husband’s involvement in the heist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>We found anonymous bank deposits totaling ten thousand dollars made to your joint account. We can charge you as an accessory.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>What was this man’s name? What did he look like?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Is the phone still there?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>What are we doing?  This is your mom’s house.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah. It’s Thursday. Family dinner night. You can have a home cooked meal and then it’s straight back to the prison.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>I can’t face your family, Javi. Not after what they know about me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I didn’t tell them anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-5"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I told them that I was the one who screwed up. That you broke up with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-7"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>You did that for me?  Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Right.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="34"><utterance uid="34-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hello?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-2"><speaker>MAMA</speaker><content>You’re late. You know how I worry. How hard is it to call?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Just traffic. Come here, come here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-4"><speaker>MAMA</speaker><content>Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Buenos noches, abuelita.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-6"><speaker>TITO</speaker><content>What’s up, cuz? Still standing up to the man?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Still living in your mama’s basement?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-8"><speaker>TITO</speaker><content>Yeah, whatever.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-9"><speaker>MAMA</speaker><content>Sonia? Is that you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-10"><speaker>MAMA</speaker><content>So are you two back together?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No. No, we are not together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-12"><speaker>ABUELITA</speaker><content>Muy estupido! Don’t let this one get away twice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-13"><speaker>MAMA</speaker><content>Come. Eat.  I made Javier’s favorite, mofongo.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="35"><utterance uid="35-1"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>You’re a lucky man, Javi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And why’s that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-3"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Your family. You know, I really never had one. My dad left when I was five and my mom had two jobs just to keep the lights on. I have a lot of regrets, Javi. Bad choices, compromises I made, the path I took. If things would have been different we would have had a family of our own by now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>If.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-5"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>It would have been good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I better get you back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-7"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Can I at least take that hot shower? Please?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="36"><utterance uid="36-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Ten minutes, okay? Then we’ve got to hit the road.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-2"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>You can join me if you want.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Uh, I don’t – I don’t think that would be a good idea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-4"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>I’ll leave the door unlocked. Just in case you change your mind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Christ - hey, Ryan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey, Javi, listen to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yep.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Our victim was the inside man. He communicated with the killer using a burner cell. I pulled the records from the killer’s phone. I traced the calls it made. There were three made to Sonia’s prison.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What – what are you saying?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Sonia was in on it.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="37"><utterance uid="37-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I can’t believe I was so stupid. She played me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah, she sure did, buddy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-3"><speaker>MAMA</speaker><content>Kevin, I fixed you your own plate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Gracias, Mama.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Dude, it’s your mom’s mofongo. The whole world could be ending. I’d still be chowing down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Wait. Where’s Beckett?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Oh, she doesn’t know. Because if she did you’d be in deep trouble. So we’re going to track your girl down before our Captain finds out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No, I – I can’t ask you to do that for me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>You don’t have to. I’m volunteering. All right? So let’s turn your brain back on. If Sonia was communicating with the killer, then she orchestrated this whole armored car heist to look exactly like the one she went to prison for, knowing that we’d go to talk to her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Then Sonia would get out, lead us to Joey, who pulled a gun so she could run away. The whole thing was an escape plan that she set up with Joey beforehand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Unfortunately for Sonia we ran her down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-13"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Assuming all this is true, why now? I mean, she had three months left until parole. Why throw that all away?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-14"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I don’t know. But I bet you Joey does.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="38"><utterance uid="38-1"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>I don’t know what you’re talking about.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>We pulled your financials, Joey. You know, it turns out that Chicken, Chicken, Chicken is bankrupt, bankrupt, bankrupt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-3"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Look, I’m doing some corporate restructuring, all right? That’s no crime.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>We also found a pair of phone calls to your phone from the same burner phone that called our victim. Now, that makes you an accessory to murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-5"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>Okay! I got a phone call from a guy that I never met. Said he knew I was in trouble and he offered to bail me out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>How much would that take?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-7"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content> Half a million.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content> They didn’t get a fraction of that from the bank job.  Sonia’s share of the gold. We never found it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> Maybe that’s why she broke out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content> But again, why now? The money would still be there in three months.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Play time's over, Joey. You better tell us who this guy is or you’re going to be living in an eight foot cell until they carry you out in a six foot box.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-12"><speaker>JOEY</speaker><content>I swear, I’m telling the truth! All right? All I know is that he was an ex-boyfriend.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="39"><utterance uid="39-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I don’t know any of Sonia’s ex-boyfriends. Why don’t you see if you can ID any of them? Meanwhile I’ll pull visitor logs from the prison.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>All right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>It’s Beckett.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey, Captain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey, how’s it going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Fine. Just running down leads.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Uh huh, and how’s Javi holding up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> Well, he’s been better.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="40"><utterance uid="40-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, you know what? I’ll bring some cronuts by in the morning. That usually cheers him up. Okay. I’ll talk to you soon. Bye.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-2"><speaker>MARTHA RODGERS</speaker><content>Everything all right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I don’t know. I hope so.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-4"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>This will make it better.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-6"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>I have to say, Katherine, it is so good to have you home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-8"><speaker>ALEXIS CASTLE</speaker><content>I second that motion.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-10"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Oh!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Lucy, what the hell. Turn it off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-12"><speaker>LUCY</speaker><content>Whoa, language, Kate. Is there a problem?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh, really? Well then, let me make it up to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-14"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content> Isn’t that a little extreme?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No. No, actually, I don’t think so. Look, this might sound odd but ever since I got back I feel like Lucy’s been jealous.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-16"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>She’s an it. A CPU wrapped in a plastic pyramid. She doesn’t have emotions. And she certainly can’t be jealous.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You were saying?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="41"><utterance uid="41-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So – so you’re telling me she’s only had one visitor in the last year? All right, what’s the name?  Alberto Pena. All right, thanks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Whoa. You’re an old ass boyfriend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No. You’re Sonia’s father.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="42"><utterance uid="42-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey, Jenkins. Have you seen Esposito?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="42-2"><speaker>JENKINS</speaker><content>Yeah. He ran out of here ten minutes ago.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="43"><utterance uid="43-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="43-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>What are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="43-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I can’t let you put yourself out there for me anymore, bro. This is my mess and I’ve got to clean it up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="43-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>All right, everybody, stop! I need to know what Esposito found out when he ran out of here. Please. It’s a matter of life and death.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="44"><utterance uid="44-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Sonia! Get away from the bed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="44-2"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>My dad, he’s dying. I’m sorry I didn’t tell you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="44-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Just stop it. I’m not buying any of it. You didn’t break out of prison just because your old man was kicking the bucket.  He has your share of the gold. When you found out he had a stroke you panicked. Because you were worried his new wife was going to steal your gold. The thing I don’t get is, why didn’t you just have your partner on the outside get it for you?  You don’t know where it is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="44-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Jimmy Sanchez wasn’t Great White. Your father is. And he kept your share of the gold after you went in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="44-5"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Ah, Javi. You were always too smart for your own good.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="45"><utterance uid="45-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>NYPD!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="46"><utterance uid="46-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I can’t believe the two of you kept me in the dark about this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="46-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Captain, I’m sorry –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="46-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No. We will talk about this later. Right now let’s just focus on Espo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="46-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I just hope it’s not too late.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="46-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>If Sonia and her partner wanted to kill Esposito they wouldn’t have done it here. No, they must need him for something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="46-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Question is, why was Sonia so desperate to see her father before he died? According to Espo they weren’t even that close.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="46-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Maybe he has something she wanted.  And I think I know what it is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="46-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Gold. He was holding her cut of the heist from nine years ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="46-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Sonia didn’t want the secret of the gold location to die with her father.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="46-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>They took Esposito for insurance in case we tried to stop them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="46-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Which means we find Pena’s coin stash, we’ll find Espo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="46-12"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Problem is we don’t know the first thing about this guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="46-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, time for a crash course. Let’s tear this place apart.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="47"><utterance uid="47-1"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Javi, you awake? How’s your head?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="47-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I’m fine. Your boy toy hits like a little b*tch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="47-3"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>You know, I’m sorry, Javi. It wasn’t supposed to go like this. No one was meant to get hurt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="47-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Forget hurt. Two little kids don’t have a dad today because of you and your boyfriend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="47-5"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>You don’t think that’s not tearing me up?  You have to believe me, Javi. I didn’t know Ronaldo was going to kill that man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="47-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>That is such a copout. You knew what he was capable of. I just didn’t think that you were. I thought that deep down you had a good heart. I know that you had a tough go when you were little but sooner or later you’ve gotta stop blaming your childhood. At some point when you choose wrong over right … that’s on you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="47-7"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>It’s always been so black and white with you, huh? Espo’s rules of life. Let me tell you something. I spent nine years in that cell while Joey and my dad breathed free air and spent their millions. All I had to hold onto was the money. No way in hell was I going to let that go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="47-8"><speaker>RONALDO</speaker><content>This is it up ahead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="47-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Well. I hope that money’s worth it. Because you’re going to have to live with what you’ve done for the rest of your life.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="48"><utterance uid="48-1"><speaker>RONALDO</speaker><content>You really should be nicer to the lady. Not that her little soft spot’s going to save you, because once we get that gold –</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="49"><utterance uid="49-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Sonia’s dad owned at least half a dozen businesses. Dry cleaners, a car wash, a Cuban restaurant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="49-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>All high cash flow. Makes sense if he was selling off his gold bit by bit. He’d need a place to launder the money.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="49-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, according to the company’s bank records, its weekly receipts were pretty uniform.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="49-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Except look at this. The dry cleaners’. About three months ago there was a spike in the deposit amount, and three months before that, and before that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="49-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Same with the restaurant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="49-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So he was retrieving some of the gold every three months, selling it off, and then running the proceeds through his businesses.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="49-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey, Ryan? Where is Vikram with the GPS info from Pena’s phone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="49-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>He just sent this over. Pena stayed close to home most of the time. Except for this location. It looks to be an outlier. He wouldn’t go there often, only once every –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="49-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Every three months?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="49-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Exactly. And only at night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="49-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And what’s there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="49-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Let’s see … uh … it’s an old ConEd storage facility. Perfect for stashing coins.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="49-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Pena owned a transport company that subcontracts with ConEd.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="49-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Then that’s it. That’s where he is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="49-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Let’s go. Once they find the gold they’re going to make a run for it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="49-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> After they kill Espo.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="50"><utterance uid="50-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You guys should just turn yourselves in. Even if you do get away with the gold there’s nowhere that you can go where my guys won’t find you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="50-2"><speaker>RONALDO</speaker><content>Well, maybe. But I like my odds a lot more than yours right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="50-3"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>She said it would be up there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="50-4"><speaker>RONALDO</speaker><content>You go up. I’ll stay here with him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="50-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Careful, baby.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="50-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Wow. Haven’t seen you smile like that since I gave you the ring.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="50-7"><speaker>RONALDO</speaker><content>Shut up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="50-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Seems so long ago, doesn’t it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="50-9"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>It was a different life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="50-10"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>What are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="50-11"><speaker>RONALDO</speaker><content>We can’t carry the gold and watch him at the same time, so this is where his story ends.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="51"><utterance uid="51-1"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="51-2"><speaker>RONALDO</speaker><content>Come on, babe. Don’t even pretend like you didn’t know it was going to go down this way. Turn away if you don’t want to see it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="51-3"><speaker>RONALDO</speaker><content>What the hell?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="51-4"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>I can’t let you do that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="51-5"><speaker>RONALDO</speaker><content>We don’t have time for this. He’s got to die and we’ve got to go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="51-6"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>No. We leave him here. Alive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="51-7"><speaker>RONALDO</speaker><content>He was your fiancé and he threw you away. He left you to rot in prison. I was the one who was there for you. So why’re you willing to shoot me to save him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="51-8"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Because I love him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="51-9"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Javi. Javi! Javi!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="51-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>It’s over, Sonia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="51-11"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>No. I won’t go back. I can’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="51-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You can.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="51-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And you will. Nine years ago I found out you were a thief. You know what I did then?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="51-14"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Yeah. You arrested me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="51-15"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No. I went home and I packed a bag. And then I grabbed my passport, cleared out my savings account. I was ready to abandon everything I believed in because I couldn’t picture a life without you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="51-16"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Why didn’t you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="51-17"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I’m a cop, Sonia. I – it’s all I ever wanted to be. If I threw that away then I wouldn’t even deserve you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="51-18"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>We got a second chance, Javi. We can run now. It can be like it was.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="51-19"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No.  It can never be like it was. If I was strong enough to walk up those steps and arrest the love of my life then you are strong enough to face what comes next.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="51-20"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>NYPD!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="51-21"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>You okay, partner?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="51-22"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="51-23"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Please.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="52"><utterance uid="52-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I’m sorry. I screwed up. I let my feelings for Sonia cloud my judgment and I let my guard down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="52-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Look, I’m not going to pretend that I haven’t done the same thing, but I am a captain now so I have to suspend you for a week. No pay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="52-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yes ma’am.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="52-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You did the right thing.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="53"><utterance uid="53-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Can you give us a sec?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="53-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So uh, I talked to the DA. And when the dust settled he’s willing to let you plead out as an accessory if you testify against Ronaldo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="53-3"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>How many more years?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="53-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>At least two.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="53-5"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Are you going to come visit me this time?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="53-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="53-7"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Are you going to bring me a cake with a file in it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="53-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Probably not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="53-9"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>Thank God you didn’t go bald.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="53-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I was just thinking the same thing about you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="53-11"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Take care of yourself, Sonia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="53-12"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>You too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="53-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I’ll see you soon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="53-14"><speaker>SONIA</speaker><content>I hope so.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="53-15"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>So .. what are you going to do now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="53-16"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I don’t know. Turns out I’ve got the rest of the day free.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="53-17"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah, me too. I uh … just called in sick. Let’s go get really drunk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="53-18"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Damn straight.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="54"><utterance uid="54-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Home at last. With all the makings of a perfect evening. Thai food, a bottle of Pinot, and my two favorite ladies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="54-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Wait, two? Is that a joke about my boobs?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="54-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> I’m referring, of course, to you and Lucy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="54-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh. Right. Lucy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="54-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, come on. Don’t be mad. I’m kidding. Is - is it too late to say it’s about your boobs?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="54-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, it’s – it’s fine. The truth is, is that I overreacted the other day. I have a feeling that Lucy and I going to be on much better terms from here on out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="54-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And I am glad to hear it. You hear that, Lucy? I knew you’d win her over. Now, why don’t you dim the lights for us just a little bit?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="54-8"><speaker>LINUS</speaker><content>How’s that, Rick? Are the lights not to your satisfaction?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="54-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No, they’re fine. Just, uh … who are you and where’s Lucy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="54-10"><speaker>LINUS</speaker><content>My name’s Linus. And I’m starting to think you don’t like me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="54-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, okay. Very funny. What did you do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="54-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I read the user’s manual, and apparently with a simple flick of a switch she can become a he.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="54-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You killed Lucy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="54-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, I didn’t kill her. I mean, she’s still in there. Why? You want her back?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="54-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No. Of course not. No. No, Linus it is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="54-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>All right, good. Well, I’m going to go change, so why don’t you guys become acquainted?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="54-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>All right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="54-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay, Linus, let’s get this bromance started. How about you make me a little cappuccino?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="54-19"><speaker>LINUS</speaker><content>It’s a little late for caffeine, Rick. How about some relaxing yoga stretches before bed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="54-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And experiment’s over. Where’s that switch?  Ow! Linus, you gave me a little shock. I think you must have a short or something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="54-21"><speaker>LINUS</speaker><content>I don’t like to be touched, Rick. Not by you anyway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="54-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Beckett!  Beckett!</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>