<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>LARS</speaker><content>This is what you wanted.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>LARS</speaker><content>Now please, let me go.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>RICHARD CASTLE</speaker><content>Whoops.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>KATE BECKETT</speaker><content>You know, once you clean that up maybe we could go for a, um, round three?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Whoa.  You do not have to tell me twice. Or should I say, thrice?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>MARTHA RODGERS</speaker><content>Good morning my darlings!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Mother, I really wish you’d call before you came over.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Well, I don’t want to risk interrupting you two lovebirds in the middle of you-know-what. And it looks like I have interrupted you in the middle of you-know-what.  And with a melon. My, my. Not judging, but … room temperature.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Mother, what – what is it that you want?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>I want for my son to grant me a very simple wish. Now, it seems that my publisher says that for my self-help book to make the best-seller list I need a celebrity endorsement.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>And not just any celebrity endorsement. The endorsement of endorsements.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Mother, I would be happy to write something for your book.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Oprah. I need Oprah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Uh, do you even know Oprah?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No, I do not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content>Well, you must know someone who knows Oprah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>If I promise to try, will you leave?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>MARTHA</speaker><content> Poof, I am gone. Oh, you know, it’s so funny, darling. I have that same negligee but of course it’s in the little tiger print so it’s –  Well, resume your lovemaking, darling.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Uh –  – Beckett. Oh!  Ryan and Espo have caught a crime scene. Want to join them?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Why? Got a crime scene right here. My mother just killed the mood.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>KEVIN RYAN</speaker><content> Yeah. Okay, baby. I’ll call you later. Reception’s terrible in here.  Hey. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Early morning or late night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Both. Jenny can’t sleep, which means, in her crazy nine month pregnant logic, out of solidarity, I’m not allowed to sleep, either.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, could be worse. You could be granted the eternal sleep, like your victim, whose name is –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>JAVIER ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Lars Cross. He’s a sonar technician for an oil exploration company.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah, Chesapeake Energy. Apparently he was doing an overseas job for them in Turkey but he got fired for missing too much work. According to his passport he only got back to the States three days ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>If he was just fired, how could he afford all those wonderful new toys?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>That’s nothing. He’s got a brand new Porsche 911 downstairs that he apparently paid cash for. And he just leased a safe deposit box at a bank down the street.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, Detectives, I deduce that our victim’s sudden influx of cash had something to do with the fact that he –  – has no head?  Dude, seriously. Give a guy a heads up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>LANIE PARISH</speaker><content>Make way, Castle!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ugh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Time of death between 10PM and midnight. Lars was strapped to that chair with duct tape. Perimortem bruising indicates that he was tortured before the killer decapitated him with –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Schwing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> A Turkish scimitar?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Ah! I checked, no fingerprints. It’s from the victim’s collection.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Apparently Lars was really into the Middle East.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>A region known for its sordid history of beheading and yet, Lars was beheaded here in Manhattan.  Hmm. Perhaps Lars made the mistake of telling the king the ending of the story, am I right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>1001 Arabian Nights.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Truly, I am shocked. How is it that none of you know the story of 1001 Arabian Nights?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-20"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>We weren’t nerds in high school.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Fair enough. Lucky for you, class is now in session. In the story 1001 Arabian Nights, a jealous king would sleep with a new young maiden every night, then have her beheaded so no other men could have her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-22"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>So … it’s a story about a misogynistic serial killer?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-23"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No. Well, yes. But no. In the story, to stop the bloodshed, a young maiden by the name of Scheherazade wove a fascinating tale for the king, but she refused to tell him the ending, forcing him to keep her alive until the next night, so she could finish the story. She told him a new story every night for a thousand and one nights until finally the king married her.  Which really says a lot about the power of a good storyteller.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-24"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yet tells us nothing about why our victim was killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-25"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Or does it? Our victim was tortured because the killer, like the king, wanted something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-26"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, our victim’s sister is meeting me in the precinct. Maybe she can shed some light on what that thing was.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-27"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I pulled a warrant for Lars’s new safe deposit box, see if there’s a clue as to what our killer was after.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-28"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, this is Oprah’s assistant. Um … I’ll take this. You guys … head out without me.  I’ll … be heading … to the precinct in just a little while.  Guys, these are comedy gold. Seriously.  Hello?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-29"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Not funny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-30"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hang on, I can’t hear you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-31"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>I know.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Are you getting any reception?  Thank you. Hello?  Yes.  Well actually, it’s not about one of my books. It’s about my mother’s.  No, I only wish I was joking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>Are you a cop?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Geez!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>I don’t recognize you, and I’ve lived in the building for years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’m actually with the cops.  I can send you the manuscript?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>I know who the killer is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Can you – can you – hold – hold on one moment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>It was Lars’s ex-boyfriend, Mark. Last night around nine Mark was banging on Lars’s door. Said Lars owed him money and that he better pay up or else.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hang – hang on.  You – can I call you right back?  Hello? Hello?  Shoot. All right, where were –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Wait. Where’d she go?</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Ms. Cross, your brother appeared to come into a great deal of money upon his return to the country. But we checked his financials and there’s no record of where it came from. Do you have any idea?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Did he have any enemies? At home or abroad?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Even his ex-boyfriend Mark?  According to Castle, a neighbor overheard Lars’s ex yelling outside of his apartment last night.  Did your brother owe him money?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Lars never paid him back, did he?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>So Mark, you used to date Lars. Well, according to these reports he called the cops on you over a dozen times in the past year.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>MARK</speaker><content>I sometimes get overly dramatic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>MARK</speaker><content>What can I do? I am a Pisces. But I am over Lars. And I moved on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Not according to a witness who saw you threatening him last night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>MARK</speaker><content>Oh, yes. I threatened him. A lot. All right? I gave him twenty grand to get his degree and what thanks do I get? He dumps me and leaves the country. And now he’s back two months later rolling around in a Porsche. So … yeah. I went a little mental.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Sure. If by going a little mental you mean torturing and killing your ex.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>MARK</speaker><content>What? Lars is – is dead? Oh my –  You think I did it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>MARK</speaker><content>No. Lars was the love of my life. I could never just – look, Lars was alive when I left him. I swear to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>What time was that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>MARK</speaker><content>Nine thirty. I Ubered uptown. I met some friends and drank away my sorrows until 2AM.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>All right, let’s just, uh, suppose that you are telling the truth. What happened at Lars’s?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>MARK</speaker><content>He let me in, apologized for everything, and said he just needed a day to get the cash to pay me back.  Wait, he was telling the truth?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The truth about what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>MARK</speaker><content>He was acting all paranoid when he came back from Turkey and his partner thought he had double crossed him -</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hold on, hold on. What partner?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>MARK</speaker><content>I don’t know. I don’t know, honestly. I just thought he was making it all up so that he wouldn’t have to pay me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-18"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, I bet that pissed you off, huh?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-19"><speaker>MARK</speaker><content>Wha – no! Well, yeah, but I didn’t kill him. All right? I just took his laptop as collateral.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-20"><speaker>MARK</speaker><content>Is that why he was killed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-21"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>We’re going to need that laptop.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Mark’s alibi checks out. He was telling the truth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So what do you think Lars was smuggling?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, he was in Turkey, which is the heroin pipeline from Afghanistan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hmm. No. Wasn’t drugs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Why not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Because Lars was beheaded by a scimitar. No, the storyteller inside me craves an explanation far more –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Farfetched?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Pirate’s booty? Cold fusion? Alien cadavers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No. Those are all ridiculous theories. Did you say alien cadavers, though? Because I saw a documentary once –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey Castle, um, what was the name of that woman you interviewed? Lars’s neighbor?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, I didn’t get her name.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I think my unis forgot to put her statement in this file. I swear, most of my time is spent checking people’s paperwork.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You’re suffering from a little buyer’s remorse. Yeah, it’s one of life’s cruel jokes. You get exactly what you wished for, only to find it wasn’t what you wanted at all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, I love being a captain. It’s just sometimes it feels like I’m more of a kindergarten teacher.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I’m sorry you gotta –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I just broke this case wide open.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Actually I did, so I’ll go first.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-20"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No, I think I’ll go first. Mine’s bigger than yours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-21"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>You wish, pal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-22"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Guys? Play nice. Indoor voices. Espo goes first.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-23"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>See? She knows. So, I opened Lars’s safe deposit box and found four hundred Gs.  Gots to be drug money. Beat that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-24"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Easy. I got Lars’s encrypted laptop from Mark, found out what he was smuggling and it wasn’t drugs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-25"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-26"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No. Lars wasn’t a drug dealer. He was a tomb raider. Ryan, can you zoom in on that, please?  I’ve seen that symbol before. Yes, um … at Lars’s apartment. You remember there were all those books on 1001 Arabian Nights? I think that symbol was on one of the books.  Yes! Here it is. The seal of Solomon.  “The seal of Solomon was believed to be imbued with mystical powers, including the ability to seal genies into lamps. In the tale of Aladdin and the magic lamp, Aladdin finds a lamp containing a genie in a cave. Many people believe this cave was actually King Solomon’s tomb, which is most likely located near the border of Syria and Turkey.”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-27"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You guys? You know what this means?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-28"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Oh please, no.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-29"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Come on! The money, the Porsche? Lars wished for them and his wishes were granted –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-30"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> And here we go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-31"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>- by a genie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-32"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Lars found Aladdin’s lamp!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Perfect! Thank you, Diane.  Guys.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Look at this. These books from Lars’s apartment on 1001 Arabian Nights. They all have handwritten notes in them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>This one has maps drawn in it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>This one has his theories on where King Solomon is buried.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>These books are his research that he used in conjunction with his skills as a sonar engineer, to unearth King Solomon’s tomb.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah, we’re with you on that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>And to find the lamp with the magical genie in it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>That’s where you lose us, Castle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>The only thing magical about that lamp is the millions of dollars that private collectors are willing to pay for it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Come on, Castle. You don’t really believe in genies, do you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I believe, until I hear a more viable theory as to where Lars got all that money, that this is the best theory that I’ve got.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So a genie is your best explanation?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Not that Lars sold one of the items in Turkey before smuggling the rest back here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Okay, that’s – pretty good theory.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Or that Lars double crossed his partner and that’s probably where all the cash came from.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Fine, that’s a good theory, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>No, no, no, no. That’s – that’s better than good. It explains why the killer tortured him. If it was his partner then he would have wanted to find out what happened to the antiquities.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>We’ll look into Lars’s time in Turkey, see if we can dig up a connection to his partner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-20"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-21"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>For my money it’s whoever took those pictures.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-22"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What’ve you got there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-23"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The woman who wrote this book, Dr. Marion Baker, she’s a professor of Middle Eastern literature at Hudson University. We should go talk to her. Knowing more about the lamp will help us know why Lars was killed for it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-24"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You just want to find out more about genies and wishes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-25"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-26"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Fine. Go ahead. Meet with Dr. Baker. Maybe she can talk some sense into you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-27"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Your wish is my command.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-28"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Smoke! And he’s gone.  Okay, now I’m gone.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>MARION</speaker><content>King Solomon’s tomb. Remarkable. It’s arguably the greatest discovery in the last fifty years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Now this, Dr. Baker, is what I need your expertise with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>MARION</speaker><content>Certainly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>MARION</speaker><content>Well, you see these grooves? They indicate it was a wheel made lamp versus the mold made ones that became so popular in the fourth –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Fascinating, Doctor. But can you skip ahead to the part where King Solomon seals a genie inside of it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>MARION</speaker><content>Did Sidney put you up to this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>ALEXIS CASTLE</speaker><content>Who’s Sidney?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>MARION</speaker><content>The schmuck I beat out for tenure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Dr. Baker, I do not know Sidney. This is not a joke. I am very serious.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>MARION</speaker><content>But you’re acting as if you believe in genies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Doctor, it’s not an act.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>MARION</speaker><content>Well, the story of Aladdin and the magic lamp is a romantic metaphor. Nothing more.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Of course. But what if, and I’m only saying what if, the legends of genies were based in fact?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>MARION</speaker><content>Well, I certainly hope it isn’t. Genies are frightful creatures.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You’re saying they’re not the cheeriest sixties housewives or singing blue cartoons?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>MARION</speaker><content>I’ll put it to you like this: in Arabic they use the same word for demon as they do for genie. They’re dangerous, capricious tricksters who appear and disappear in gentle breezes or a whirlwind of dust.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Now what if the master of the lamp is killed before the wishes are granted?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>MARION</speaker><content>Well, then the masterless genie would be separated from its lamp.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Like a Japanese Ronin samurai.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-20"><speaker>MARION</speaker><content>Exactly. But the genie would be forced to wander the Earth until a new master rubs the lamp.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-21"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Tell me more, Dr. Baker.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-22"><speaker>MARION</speaker><content>Oh, sure. For the low, low price of $19.95. Buy my book.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-23"><speaker>MARION</speaker><content>You don’t give your stories away for free, Mr. Castle, and neither do I. So uh –  – if you’ll excuse me I have a class to teach.  Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-24"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-25"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Dad, what are you thinking?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-26"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Lars found the lamp and clearly he rubbed it. That makes him the genie’s master, right? But if no one has rubbed the lamp since and I were to discover it? That would make me the genie’s new master.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-27"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Okay. Let’s just pretend that all this is real. You do realize that if Lars was the genie’s master it didn’t work out so well for him in the end.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-28"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What are you saying?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-29"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Be careful what you wish for. It might just come true. And in this case it might just get you killed.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>I could really use a genie right now. I would wish that my kid was already born and sleeping through the night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Bro, fatherhood has made you so damn boring. If I had a wish? I’d use it to become the top MMA fighter in the world. And take home a different hot chick every single night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Okay, now that I think about it, I would wish that I could be a Broadway star. Play Jean Valjean in front of sold out crowds, win a bunch of Tonys.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You’d wish to wear tights and sing show tunes for a living?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>You’d wish to wear Speedos and grapple sweaty men for a living.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And hook up with a different hot chick every single night, don’t forget that part.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>You know what I wish? That my detectives would actually get some work done for living. While the two of you were on fantasy island I found a lead.  Mike Harlin. He’s a surface driller for Chesapeake Energy. That is the same company that Lars worked for. He was also on the same plane as Lars from Turkey to New York.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>He’s got to be Lars’s partner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I pinged his cell phone. It’s disconnected.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>He’s making a run for it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>And if he tortured the location of the antiquities out of Lars –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Then there’s a good chance that he’s going to grab them and try to disappear for good.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Alexis?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You broke into my office?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>No. The redhead let me in. So I could wait inside.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You went through my desk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>To look for a pen to write you a note. Wow, you are a very distrusting person.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yes, I get that way when I’m lied to. I don’t know who you are but you sure as hell aren’t Lars’s neighbor. I’m calling the police.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>If you do I’m out that door.  And you’ll never know how powerful of an ally I can be.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>All right, you’ve got one minute to convince me. Go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>My name is Lindsay Dillon. I’m a journalist researching a story about looted antiquities. A source in Turkey hinted that Lars might have discovered King Solomon’s tomb. So I decided to keep tabs on him. That’s when I overheard the fight he had with his ex-boyfriend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> So why not tell the police? Why lie?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>Because when you’ve got a dead body, a story about stolen relics turns from a back page snoozer to a front page lead –  – just like that. And though I wanted to be helpful to your murder investigation –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>If you made an official statement every reporter would hear about your story and you’d lose your exclusive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>See? I knew you’d get it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That doesn’t explain why you broke into my office –  – unless you have another lead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-17"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>We’re both writers. Let’s help each other out. Only you’ve got to keep me as your anonymous source. Deal?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Deal. What’ve you got?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-19"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>Lars was working with a guy named Mike Harlin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah. We know about him already but he’s missing. Unless you know where he’s been hiding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-21"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>No. But I do know that Harlin used an alias while in Turkey.  Al Aiden.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>This is great. I’m going to call this in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-23"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Al Aiden.  Aladdin. Yeah, that’s cute.  Beckett! Hey, I have a lead for you. It’s the –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-24"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Wait a second.  Stop that woman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-25"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>What woman?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-26"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The – the blonde woman. The woman who just –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-27"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>How did she get past you?</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, Cap. Front desk confirmed an Al Aiden checked into room 57 this morning. We’re on our way to the room now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Mike Harlin?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>MIKE</speaker><content>Whoa!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>NYPD!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey! Away from the window! Now!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>MIKE</speaker><content>Okay, okay!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Get on your knees right now!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>MIKE</speaker><content>Chill, man!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Interlace your fingers behind your head.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>MIKE</speaker><content>All right.  I knew she’d lead you to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>What are you talking about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>MIKE</speaker><content>The genie, man. She’s out to get me.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>MIKE</speaker><content>Genies are evil. And their wishes bring about nothing but misery.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ah hah. I see what’s happening here. The uh, wandering Ronin genie is angry with Harlin for killing her master. That’s why she prevented him from finding the lamp.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yeah, Castle, the man is either delusional or he’s laying the groundwork for some BS insanity plea.  What’s your excuse?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Let’s talk about Lars and how you chopped his head off with a sword.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>MIKE</speaker><content>No, no, no, no, no. I didn’t kill him. Okay? I was at my mom’s birthday party when he got murdered.  Man, check it out! I’m sure whoever took Lars’s head off is coming for mine next.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Really? Why is that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>MIKE</speaker><content>I know too much. Me and Lars, we met on the job in Turkey. Okay? And then one day, after our search for oil pockets, Lars came to me. He was all excited.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Because he found the location of King Solomon’s tomb and you used your skills as an excavator to help him dig it up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>MIKE</speaker><content>No. No, it wasn’t that easy. We needed money to do it safely. Okay? So Lars, he found some guy. He offered us two hundred and fifty Ks, each, in cash, to do the dig.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>MIKE</speaker><content>The catch was if we found something, well, Lars had to ship it to the guy who was here in New York.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Okay, so who is this financier?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>MIKE</speaker><content>I don’t know. Look, the money was too good so I didn’t ask any questions. I – I wish I did, though. Because opening that tomb was the worst thing that could happen to us. I mean, the moment we took that lamp? That genie unleashed its vengeance, man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You can’t honestly be trying to tell us that you saw a genie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>MIKE</speaker><content>No. But genies can choose to appear or not to appear to anyone they want.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s true. Professor Baker told me that. And she’s a doctor, so …</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>MIKE</speaker><content>Guys. I didn’t believe in genies, either. Okay? Until my life fell apart. I found my girlfriend in bed with my roommate. And then I stayed with my mom and my mom accidentally threw out the duffle bag with my two hundred and fifty Gs. You know? And when I think that things, they – they can’t get any worse? I found out that Lars got his head lopped off and now that genie, that crazy, evil genie is after me, man. I know it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Okay Harlin, I’m going to have to get you off the crazy train that you’re riding on right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah. We know that the shipment got screwed up and you suspected that Lars double crossed you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>MIKE</speaker><content>What? No. No, Lars did not double cross me. He got double crossed by the shipper. Okay, well, really the smuggler. You can’t just walk past customs with priceless relics and expect no one to notice, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>So Lars hired a guy back in Turkey to ship the items back.  What was his name?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>MIKE</speaker><content>I don’t know.  I do know. Hold on! I do – I do know that he lied to the shipper. Okay? He told them it was just mining equipment. The only thing was that someone from his crew jimmied the crate and found the artifacts.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Let me guess, the shipper started seeing dollar signs?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>MIKE</speaker><content>Yeah. And then he demanded four hundred grand, in cash, just to release the shipment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>That explains the cash that we found in Lars’s safe deposit box.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Right, but how the hell did Lars get his hands on four hundred thousand bucks?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ah … don’t – don’t say that he wished for it.  He probably got the money from the financier. Wait, wait. But the one thing that doesn’t make sense is if Lars already had the extortion money then why did the shipper kill him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ah … don’t! Do not say that it was to gain control of the genie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I wasn’t gonna.  Okay, I was.  But there is another possibility. Maybe the shipper kept the treasure for himself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, then why torture Lars? I mean, what information could he possibly want if he already had the artifacts?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey guys, any leads on who the financier is?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No, whoever paid for Lars and Harlin’s tomb raiding made sure to cover their tracks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, Harlin’s alibi checked out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Which means that this mystery shipper is our prime suspect.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>If he was extorting Lars he’d have plenty of motive for murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay, check in with customs. Let’s get a list of all the ships that have come in from Turkey in the last week. If we can track down those antiquities that should lead us to the killer.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey. You okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No. I’ve been doing some digging into that mystery blonde.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Uh … you mean the reporter?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>She is no more a reporter than she was Lars’s neighbor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What? She lied to you again?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>This is the real Lindsay Dillon, a 65 year old black woman living in Tallahassee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ugh. So what’s the blonde’s angle?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I wish I knew. She lies out of one side of her mouth, helps with the investigation out of the other. It just doesn’t make any sense.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Well, for all we know she could be working with the killer, trying to steer us in the wrong direction.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Twice! She just vanished on me.  Vanished on me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Appearing and disappearing at will. Being both deceptive and helpful. They mystery blonde is Lars’s Ronin genie, wandering the Earth waiting for someone to find her lamp. She’s chosen to appear to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-13"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s it. I’m cutting you off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No, no, no, no. She’s giving me clues, Beckett. She wants me to find the lamp. I think she wants me to be her new master.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And you know what I think? You need to call me the next time you see her so I can question her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’ve gotta come up with a wish list. Oh my God, I have so many. How am I going to whittle it down to three?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-17"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That’s funny, I just have one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>What’s that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>That my man would stop talking about being some skeezy blonde’s master and would start talking about taking his wife to bed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh … well, I don’t need a genie –  – to grant that wish.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yo hey, Captain. So we cross checked customs records with the date that Harlin said Lars shipped the antiquities.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>One ship left port that day in Istanbul. And the only cargo that it dropped off in New York was a shipment to this man. Yuruk Sezen. He runs a rug import business with a storefront in SoHo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So obviously he’s our shipper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah, we’re headed there now. Hopefully he still has the antiquities.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Including the magic lamp.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Uh … guys? Guys? If you find that lamp and Castle’s not there I’m never going to hear the end of it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>We’ll have him meet us there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay. Great. Oh, hey, hey!  Can you make sure that he gets dibs on the first rub, please?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Mmmhm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Great. Thanks. I owe you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Ugh. I can’t believe I said that.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>NYPD.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>NYPD.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Are you in here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Clear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I’m clear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Clear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Looks like Yuruk’s skipped town.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Why’re you playing with the carpets?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’m checking if they’re magic.  Think about it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Guys? This carpet’s bleeding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-11"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Déjà vu.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Check out these bruises. Just like Lars.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Duct tape on his chest, wrist, and ankles. Someone must have tied him up, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So apart from the fully detached head, the MO is identical to Lars: tortured then killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Well, clearly Yuruk’s not our killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, the true killer must have tortured Lars to get to Yuruk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Then tortured Yuruk to get to those stolen antiquities.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>This body is still warm. The killer was just here. Castle, go call for backup.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Wait for them out front.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Right.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Hey, Beckett. No, right now they’re securing the back. All right, we’ll be here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The genie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ah hah! I knew it was you!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You – you are not who I thought you were. I’m so sorry. Have a lovely day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ah … my back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>PHOEBE</speaker><content>I’m going to need that back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Sure. Let me just dust it off for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-8"><speaker>PHOEBE</speaker><content>Ah ah ah. Hands.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-9"><speaker>PHOEBE</speaker><content>Travis, hurry it up. We’ve got company.  Who the hell are you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Nobody.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-11"><speaker>PHOEBE</speaker><content>What are you doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-12"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-13"><speaker>PHOEBE</speaker><content>So you’re nobody doing nothing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Pleased to meet you. I would love to chat, but uh, you are obviously busy with whatever clearly legal endeavor you’re engaged in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-15"><speaker>PHOEBE</speaker><content>You a cop?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Not a cop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-17"><speaker>PHOEBE</speaker><content>Good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-18"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Whoa … whoa! What – what if I was a cop?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-19"><speaker>PHOEBE</speaker><content>Either way I’m going to kill you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You shoot me, I drop this, and it breaks into a million pieces.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-21"><speaker>PHOEBE</speaker><content>It’s okay. I’ve got a dozen more.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>But do they have a genie?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-23"><speaker>PHOEBE</speaker><content>What are you, five years old? I’m sorry, pal. I’ve gotta do what I’ve gotta do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-24"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I really wish you wouldn’t!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-25"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You are a genie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-26"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>Come on!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-27"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>The lamp! But your lamp! It’s yours!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-28"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>Leave it!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-29"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Couldn’t you have just flown us out of there on a carpet?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-30"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>What are you talking about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-31"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You can’t make carpets fly?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-32"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>Can you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-33"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’m not a genie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-34"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>Neither am I.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-35"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s something a genie would say, because they’re liars and tricksters.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-36"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>By that logic any liar could be a genie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-37"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, I’ve caught you now and you’re not going anywhere. The cops are right over there and you’re going to tell us everything you know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-38"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Come on!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>We put a net over the neighborhood. The truck and the treasure were gone. And because you didn’t get a license plate we have little chance of finding them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>It all happened so fast.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Oh, right. And yet, you did have time to –  – creep over to the lamp, examine it, get held at gunpoint, rub the lamp, make a wish upon the lamp, and have a genie appear in a puff of smoke and knock the woman thug over the head with a two by four.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You forgot the part where it was dark and super dusty.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Castle, you’re just lucky that Lanie was able to pull DNA off Yuruk’s body.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Did she manage to get a match?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>No. But she was able to determine that the killer was a female.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Most likely the woman holding me at gunpoint.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Or your magical blonde genie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>The one only Castle’s seen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So neither of you believe me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>No, bro. I do believe you. Actually, I was able to ID the genie based on your description.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Good work!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-14"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Laugh it up, you guys. I still have two wishes left. I’m not above using them for evil.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-15"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Dad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Ah! Alexis. Good. Great. Tell these guys I am not crazy for believing in a genie. And before you answer, remember I spent six months making an extra lunch for your imaginary friend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-17"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Really?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-18"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Guys, I was seven.  But you’re not crazy. The mystery blonde is real.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-19"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-20"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>But she’s not a genie.  Her name is Genevieve Sutton. She has an office on 2nd Avenue. She’s listed as a security consultant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-21"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>A fixer, by the sounds of it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-22"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>And how did you get this info, Alexis?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-23"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Well, after Dad left I dusted his desk for prints. Got a little help from Hayley, who ran them through the DMV database and voila.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-24"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>So she’s not a genie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-25"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-26"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Genevieve is short for genie. I mean, seriously, if she can grant wishes, a driver’s license, that would be a piece of cake.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-27"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Uh huh. But why would a genie want to do that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-28"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Oh, seriously. Who cares?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-29"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Make believe time with Castle is over.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-30"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>We’re going to bring in Genevieve and find out the real story.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-31"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-32"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Someone need some ice cream?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-33"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content> Me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-34"><speaker>ALEXIS</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You may have everyone else fooled, but not me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle, let me in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I am your master. I command you to tell me the truth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Castle!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Are you a genie or not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>Can you let her in? Because you’re seriously weirding me out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I’m going to take that as a maybe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-9"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>I apologize, but his behavior is the least of your worries. You are accused of two homicides and connected to the theft and trafficking of millions of dollars in antiquities. So your best bet is to start talking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-10"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>Look, I didn’t kill anyone. And I was trying to keep the relics from falling into the wrong hands. And I would have, too, if I hadn’t had to save your reality-challenged husband.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-11"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I prefer fantasy-augmented.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Um, what do you mean by wrong hands?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-13"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>Lars was hired to excavate the antiquities in order to protect them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hired by who?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-15"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>An anonymous benefactor. Let’s call him Mr. X. With the Syrian conflict threatening to spill over into Turkey, Mr. X became concerned that Solomon’s tomb would be destroyed, or worse, looted, and the relics sold to fund terrorism.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>And you know all of this, how?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-17"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>Mr. X retained my services in order to ensure Lars recovered the artifacts from Yuruk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>But instead Lars ended up dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-19"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>Unfortunately. The night that Lars was murdered I was pulled away on a false lead. When I got back the cops were everywhere, so I targeted Mr. Castle as a way to learn what the police knew.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I don’t suppose you got the license plate of that truck as you were saving me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-21"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>No. But I did before I saved you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>State police has found the truck.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Tapped into a live feed from a rest stop outside of Rye.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey, babe. Sorry, it’s not really a good time right now.  What? Uh, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I will be right there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Um … hey guys? Jenny’s having the baby.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>That’s awesome, man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Yes, great! Go! Go!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Call me, bro.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-9"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Yeah!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-10"><speaker>DISPATCH</speaker><content>Captain, what’s your status?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-11"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>This is Captain Beckett. Is there anything in that truck?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Genevieve said that there would be twelve.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-13"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>I bet I know which crate is missing.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Where’s the lamp, Phoebe?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You’ve got one chance to help yourself here. Now, we know you didn’t kill Yuruk. Traffic cams put you and the truck on the other side of the city when he was murdered.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That makes you and Travis little more than the hired help.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So I’d do myself a favor and start talking. Beginning with who you delivered the lamp to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>PHOEBE</speaker><content>I might be hired help … but I ain’t no rat.  I want a lawyer. I know my rights.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>DNA confirms that our killer’s a woman, but someone with resources and connections. Not this flunky.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>A killer who knew Lars. A woman who would risk losing the entire shipment for the ultimate prize: the lamp.  And I know just the person to lead us to it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Dr. Baker, thank you again for coming to see us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>MARION</speaker><content>How could I resist when you told me you found the genie from Aladdin’s lamp?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>That was a little bit of a white lie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yeah. See, we were looking back over Lars’s school records from Columbia. It turns out he actually audited a class of yours at Hudson University a few years back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>MARION</speaker><content>I have hundreds of students every year. I’m afraid I can’t remember all of them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That’s strange. Your TA remembers that you and Lars would meet regularly during your office hours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-7"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>In fact, he said that you guys met the morning that Lars returned from Turkey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-8"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Now Lars, I’m sure, shared the discovery of the lamp with you knowing that you of all people would appreciate its value, but what he wasn’t counting on was your professional jealousy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-9"><speaker>MARION</speaker><content> Why would I be jealous?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>You’ve been searching for King Solomon’s tomb for over fifteen years. We talked to the dean of your department. He told us about your obsession. How it ruined your marriage and nearly destroyed you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-11"><speaker>MARION</speaker><content>That is not true.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-12"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Because you never found that tomb.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Now that must have been a bitter pill to swallow. Knowing that Lars used all of your hard earned research to find something that you never could. And now he was going to get all the fame and fortune that you never would.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-14"><speaker>MARION</speaker><content>Mr. Castle, you really do have an overactive imagination. You could no more prove that story you just spun than you could prove that genies come out of lamps and grant three wishes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-15"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Actually, that’s not true. Uniforms searched your home. They found the lamp.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I guess you’re as good at hiding treasure as you are at finding it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-17"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Dr. Baker, you’re under arrest for the murder of Lars Cross and Yuruk Sezen.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>You better watch out, Castle. I may have to steal your blonde.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I still have two wishes left. All the rubbing in the world is not going to do you any good. Can I get a "that’s what she said"?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh … who’s that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Prince Khalid Hasheim of the Jordanian royal family. He’s here to bail out Genevieve.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Methinks we found our mysterious Mr. X.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Prince Hasheim, I’m Captain Beckett. This is Mr. Castle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-7"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Or perhaps we should call you Mr. X.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-8"><speaker>GENEVIEVE</speaker><content>Mr. X is my employer. He paid me to protect the contents of King Solomon’s tomb.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-9"><speaker>PRINCE KHALID HASHEIM</speaker><content>Right. Well, I don’t know this gentleman, but anyone who helps protect the history of my region is to be applauded.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-10"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Of course. So what’s going to happen to the antiquities and the lamp now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-11"><speaker>HASHEIM</speaker><content>Well, I’m no expert, but given the way they entered the country and their connection to a murder trial, they’ll be tied up in legal battles for years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh. I’m sorry to hear that. I am sure that Mr. X will be very disappointed considering that he worked so hard to procure them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-13"><speaker>HASHEIM</speaker><content>I don’t know about that, Captain. If one wished to keep priceless history safe from looters and terrorists there is no better place for them to wait out the conflict than in the basement of the Smithsonian.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-14"><speaker>HASHEIM</speaker><content>It was a pleasure to meet you both. Come along, Gennie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-15"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content> Here we go again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-16"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>That – she was – that -</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-17"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>So I just got off the phone with Ryan. There’s been some complications with Jenny’s labor.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content> Everything was normal, uh … until Jenny started hyperventilating. She lost consciousness. The doctors think it might be a, uh, amniotic fluid embolism.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>But they’re – they’re trying to stabilize her now so that they can deliver the baby.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-3"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>We’re here, bro. Whatever you need.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-4"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Thanks. Thanks. I should get back in there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-5"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Let’s settle in.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Hey. So, um … obviously I don’t believe in genies or wishes, but just in case I was wondering if you could use one of your wishes for Jenny and the baby.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I already did. Both of them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-4"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-5"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Hey. Uh … doctors, they stabilized Jenny and –  – she delivered a healthy baby boy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-6"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Yes!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-7"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>What’s his name?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-8"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>His name is Nicholas Javier Ryan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-9"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Aww.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-10"><speaker>ESPOSITO</speaker><content>Tell me you spelled it right on the birth certificate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-11"><speaker>LANIE</speaker><content>Aww, I want one too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-12"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>So if you see that genie again you mind telling her I said thank you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-13"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Oh, I think I’m done with genies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-14"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>What? Why the change of heart?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-15"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Well, because of you, of course.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-16"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh, really? So after eight years some of my common sense has finally rubbed off on you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-17"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>No. No, no, no. Nothing like that. Um … I have no need for genies, simply because I already have everything I could ever wish for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-18"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Right back at you, handsome.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-19"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Oh, wait. Um … so you wouldn’t even wish for a working lightsaber?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-20"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Nope.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-21"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Okay. Transporter? Like the ones in Star Trek? You would never have to fly again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-22"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I like flying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-23"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Huh. Time machine?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-24"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Only to go back and fall in love with you all over again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-25"><speaker>BECKETT</speaker><content>Wow. That was a good answer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-26"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>I know, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-27"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>Make way, Daddy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-28"><speaker>CASTLE</speaker><content>How’s Jenny?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-29"><speaker>RYAN</speaker><content>Uh, she’s exhausted.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>