<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Host</speaker><content>Welcome everybody, welcome to Amazing Discoveries!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Oh, oh! It's on again!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>You guys, can we please not watch this all right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>All</speaker><content>Shhhh!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Host</speaker><content>Folks, has this ever happened to you. You go to the refrigerator to get a nice glass of milk,  and these darn cartons are so flingin'-flangin' hard to open.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content> Oh, you said it Mike.  Aw! There's got to be a better way!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>And there is Kevin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Can we please turn this off?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Noo way, Kevin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>There is a revolutionary new product that guarantees that you'll never have to open up milk cartons again. Meet the Milk Master 2000.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content> Are you intrigued?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>You're flingin'-flangin' right I am!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>Keep in mind, he's never used this product before, you're gonna see how easy this is to do.  Go ahead.  This works with any milk carton.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content> Wow, it is easy.  Now, I can have milk everyday.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Well, it's official there are no good movies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Janice</speaker><content>Well, let's go to a bad one and make out. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>Perhaps, you would like me to turn like this,  so that you can bunny bump against my back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content> Hey!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Hey, man. What's up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Maybe you can tell me. My agent would like to know why I didn't show up at the audition I didn't know I had today. The first good thing she gets me in weeks. How could you not give me the message?!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Well, I'll tell ya I do enjoy guilt, but, ah, it wasn't me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Yes, it was! It was him! Uh huh!  Okay, it was me!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>How is it you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Well, it was just, it was all so crazy, you know. I mean, Chandler was in the closet, counting to 10, and he was up to 7 and I hadn't found a place to hide yet. I-I-I meant to tell you, and I wrote it all down on my hand. See, all of it. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Yep, that's my audition.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>See, now this is why I keep notepads everywhere.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Yep, and that's why we don't invite you to play.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Janice</speaker><content>What is the great tragedy here? You go get yourself another appointment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Well, Estelle tried, you know. The casting director told her that I missed my chance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>That is unfair. I'll call her and tell her it was totally my fault.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Pheebs, you can't do that. The casting director doesn't talk to friends, she only talks to agents.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>What a sad little life she must lead. Okay, ooh  .</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>What, what are you doing? What are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>No, no, no, I know, I know, ooh.  'Hi, this is Katelynn, from Phoebe Buffay's office. Um, is um, Ann there for Phoebe, she'll know what it's about.'</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-22"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Hang up, hang up. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-23"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content> 'Annie! Hi. Listen we got a problem with Joey Tribbiani, apparently he missed his audition. Who did you speak to in my office? Estelle, no, I don't know what I'm going to do with her. No. All right, so your husband leaves and burns down the apartment, the world does not stop.'</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-24"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Is anybody else scared?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-25"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content> 'Right, well look, um, if Joey loses this audition, that is it for Estelle. I don't care! Annie you are a doll, what time can you see him?'  I need a pen. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-26"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Get the woman a pad! Get the woman a pad! A pad! A pad!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-27"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>Oh, now you want a pad.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Carol and Susan</speaker><content> Hey!!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>There's my boy! Here's my boy! And here's his Barbi  What's ah, what's my boy doing with a Barbi?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Carol</speaker><content>He picked it out of the toy store himself, he loves it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Susan</speaker><content>He carries it everywhere, it's like a security blanket, but with ski boots and a kicky beret.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>Yeah, it's, it's, it's cute. Why, why, why does he have it, again?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Susan</speaker><content>So he's got a doll? So what? Unless you're afraid he's gonna grow up and be in show business.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Carol</speaker><content>This doesn't have anything to do with the fact that he is being raised by two women, does it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>You know what it's fine. If you're okay with the Barbi thing, so am I.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>Give daddy the Barbi! Ben, give, give me the Barbi. Okay, how 'bout, don't you want to play with the monster truck?  No. Okay, oh, oh, how about a Dino-soilder? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Ross, you are so pathetic. Why can't your son just play with his doll? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content> I gotta go to work. Has anybody seen my left boob?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>I love that movie. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>There it is. Joey, what are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>I'm sorry, it just felt nice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content> Joe. Joe! Answer the phone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Hey, I only got one good arm, you know. You should be doing stuff for me. Go get me a sweater.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Just do it! Okay, it's Janice and if I get it I'm going to have to see her tonight.  Oh, that's great I'm gonna have to see her tonight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>What's the big deal? Why don't you wanna see Janice?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Okay, last night at dinner, when the meals came, she put half her chicken piccata on my plate and took my tomatoes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>And that's bad because..., you hate chicken piccata?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Noo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>You didn't want to share your tomatoes, tomatoes are very important to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>No, it's like all of the sudden, we were this couple. And this alarm started going off in my head: 'Run for your life! Get out of the building!'</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Men are unbelievable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>What is it with you people! I mean, the minute you start to feel something, you have to run away?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>I know, that,  that's why I don't want to go tonight, I'm afraid I'm going to say something stupid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>Oh, you mean like that guy thing where you act mean and distant until you get us to break up with you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-20"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Hey, you know about that?!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-21"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Look what do I do? I wanna get past this, I don't wanna be afraid of the commitment thing. I wanna go through the tunnel, to the other side!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-22"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content> Where there is no fear of commitment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-23"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Do we have any...  Do we have any thoughts here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-24"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Well, I've never been through the tunnel myself, 'cause as I understand it, you're not allowed to go through with more than one girl in the car, right. But, it seems to me it's pretty much like anything else, you know, face your fear. It have a fear of heights, you go to the top of the building! If you're afraid of bugs.....get a bug. Right. In this case, you have a fear of commitment, so I say you go in there and be the most committed guy there ever was.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-25"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Amazingly, that makes sense.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-26"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>You think?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-27"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Oh, yeah. Go for it man, jump off the high dive, stare down the barrel of the gun, pee into the wind!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-28"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Yeah, Joe, I assure you if I'm staring down the barrel of a gun, I'm pretty much peeing every which way.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Oh, it's your audition from this morning. Can I use the phone again?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Sure Pheebs, you know, that's what it's there for, emergencies and pretend agents.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Come on baby, come on!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content> 'Hi, I have Phoebe Buffay returning a page. Okay, well, um, she's in her car I'll have to patch you through.'</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Very nice touch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content> 'Okay, go ahead.'  Um, hi Annie.  Fantastic!  You got it.  Oh, okay, um, 'Will he work for scale?' you ask me. Well, I don't know about that,  except that I do and he will. Great, oh you are such a sweetheart. I would love to have lunch with you, how about we have lunch next....  Op, went through a tunnel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Unbelievable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Thank you so much.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>It was really fun, I mean I've never talked on a car phone before.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>You were amazing, could you just do me this huge favor, you see there's this one other audition that I really, really want, and Estelle couldn't get me in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Oh, I don't know. I mean it was fun one time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Come on, please, it'll be just this one more, well actually it's two.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Two?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Yeah! Well, well really it's three. Please. You're so good at it. I love you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Okay, I'll do it, but just these three, right</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Nooo, four.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Janice</speaker><content>So, how come you wanted to eat in tonight?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>'Cause, I wanted to uh, give you this. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Janice</speaker><content>Ohhh, are you a puppy!  Contact paper! I never really know what to say when someone you're sleeping with gives you contact paper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Well, wait there's, there's more. See the contact paper is to go into your brand new drawer.  See, the drawer actually goes in my dresser.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Janice</speaker><content>Oh, you didn't have to do this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Yes, I did. Yes, I did. Because, you're my girlfriend, and that's what girlfriends should, should get.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Janice</speaker><content>Well, I gotta buy a vowel. Because, oh my Gawd! Who, would've thought that someday, Chandler Bing would buy me a drawer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Well, not me. But that's what's happened, and, ah, and, and there's more. We should take a trip.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Janice</speaker><content>We should?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Yep, we're a couple and that's what couples do. And, I wanna meet your parents. We should take a trip with your parents!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Janice</speaker><content> I don't think we need to, because you're tripping me out right now! Are you okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>I am, I actually am. I mean this is amazing. My entire life I have feared this place, and now that I'm here it's like what was the big deal. I could probably say 'Let's move in together.' and I'd be okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Janice</speaker><content>You probably want us to move in together?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>It doesn't scare me!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>Janice</speaker><content>Yeah, well, it scares me! I mean I not even divorced yet, Chandler. You know, you just invited me over here for pasta, and all of the sudden you're talking about moving in together. And, and I wasn't even that hungry. You know what, it's getting a little late, and I-I should just, um... </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Oh, no, no, no, don't go! I've scared ya'! I've said too much! I'm hopeless, and awkward, and desperate for love!!  Hey, Janice! It's me. Um, yeah, I-I-I just wanna apologize in advance for having chased you down the street. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Honey, this will help. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>So, I finally catch up to her and she says this relationship is going to fast and we have to slow down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Rachel and Monica</speaker><content>Uff.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>That is never good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Then I got all needy and clingy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Okay, wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute. Maybe it's not so bad. How did you leave it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>She said she'd call me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Rachel and Monica</speaker><content>Ohh! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Oh God.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>Welcome to our side of the tunnel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>This ice cream tastes like crap by the way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Yeah, well that's that lo-cal, non dairy, soy milk junk. We sort of, we save the real stuff for those really terminal cases.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>You know, when you start get screwed over all the time, you gotta switch to low-fat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Yeah, you do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>So, you don't think I'm terminal?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>Well, no, not at all, you're not terminal, you just, you just need some damage control.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Okay, okay. So, should I call her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>Rachel and Monica</speaker><content>Nooo!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>This is a very critical time right now. If you feel yourself reaching for that phone, then you go shoe shopping, you get your butt in a bubble bath. You want her back you have to start acting aloof.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-20"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>She has to know that your not ready.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-21"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Right. So, what you have to do is, you have to accidentally run into her on purpose. And then act aloof.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-22"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>So I'm not, not gonna lose her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-23"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Oooh, honey, you're not a total loser.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-24"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>I said, 'So I'm not gonna lose her?'</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-25"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Oh.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>Guess who's here. It's the toughest guy in toy land, Ben.  'A real American hero. I'm G.I. Joe!' Drop the Barbi, drop the Barbi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content> G. I. Joe! Cool! Can I play?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>Look Ben, it's a toy that protects U.S. oil interests overseas!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Joey and Ross</speaker><content>Go Joe!!!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content> Helloo! Oh! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Pheebs! There you are!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>No it's not, sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>But Phoebe, wait! Wait! Phoebe. Phoebe! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Oh, Joey! Oh, okay, see I didn't recognize you wearing, in those....pants.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Look listen, that TV movie I went in for? Did you hear anything? I think I got a shot at it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Yes! They called and you didn't get it! Okay, I mean you didn't get it, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>It's okay, these things happen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>But they shouldn't happen, you know what, you're, you're in a terrible, terrible business. Oh God, I don't wanna be the person who makes your face look like that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>I'm, I'm okay. See. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Oh, now you're sad and creepy, oh. You know what, I, I'm sorry I quit, okay, I just quit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>No! No, no you can't quit! You're the best agent I ever had! Look Pheebs, rejection is part being an actor, you can't take it personally.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Not personal, really, well they said that they never met an Italian actor with a worse Italian accent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>They actually said that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Yeah. Ooh God, there's that face again! See I can't do this job! I...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-20"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>No, no, no, see that's why you have to do this job, agents always lie. You know, Estelle just says stuff like 'They went another way', but this, I can use this.  I canna work on a new accent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-21"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Yeah okay, no if it helps you okay. Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-22"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content> You'll never get me, Joe!!! </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Janice</speaker><content> No, thank you.  Chandler!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content> Hello, Janice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Janice</speaker><content>What are you doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content> Oh, just a bit of shopping. How've you been?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Janice</speaker><content>Are you being British?!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content> No. Not anymore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Janice</speaker><content>Why are you shopping here? You don't live in this neighborhood. Were you here waiting for me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Yeah, huh. I'm just uh, you know I'm just picking up some things for a party. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Janice</speaker><content>Barley? What kind of party serves barley?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Well, I'm sorry if my friends aren't as sophisticated as yours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Janice</speaker><content>Where is this party?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Here in Chelsea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Janice</speaker><content>Who's party is it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>A woman's</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>Janice</speaker><content>What woman?!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content> Chelsea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>Janice</speaker><content>Okay, you know, one of two things is happening here. Either you're seeing somebody behind my back, which would make you the biggest jerk on the planet. Or, else you're pretending that you're seeing somebody, which just makes you so pathetic that I could start crying right here in the cereal aisle. So like which of these two guys do you want to be? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Can I be that guy?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Okay, so we got some more good rejections, lots of stuff to work on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Okay, shoot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Okay, um, oh, the zoo commercial.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>I didn't get it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>No. They said you 'Weren't believable as a human being.' So, you can work on that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Okay, what else?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Um, the off-Broadway play people said 'You were pretty but dumb.'</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Oh no wait, I'm sorry, that's 'pretty dumb.'</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Look, it's okay, no, no, no, really, look um, I really appreciate this Pheebs, but I think I'm gonna have to go back to Estelle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Yeah, well don't get me wrong, you're a better agent than she is, but at least with her I don't want to blow my pretty dumb brains out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Yeah, no, I understand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>You do, thanks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Yeah. Sorry. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Wait a minute.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-17"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-18"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Wait a minute, did you just make up all that stuff just to get out of being my agent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-19"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content> Oh, you caught me. I am so busted.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-20"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content> That's-ah what I suspected-ah.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>....And then I just, you know, threw the bag of barley at her, and ran out of the store.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>My God! Chandler, we said be 'aloof' not 'a doof'.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>I've actually ruined this haven't I? It's time for the good ice cream now, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Yeah, it is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>You know what, everything's gonna be okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content> Hello. Hi, Janice! Can you hold on for a second? Okay.  Okay, what do I do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Shhh...I don't know what to do, this is totally unprecedented.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>If-if-if we ever did what you did a man would never call.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Hello!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>Oh wait, you know what, I got it, I got it, pretend like you just woke up, okay, that will throw her off. Be sleepy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Yes, and grumpy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>What are you, stop naming dwarves!  Hello, Janice. Hi, I'm so glad that you called, I know I've been acting a really weird lately. And, it's just because I'm crazy about you, and I just got...stupid, and, and scared, and....stupid a couple of more times. I'm sorry.  Really?!  Really?!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>He's soo lucky, if Janice were a guy, she'd be sleeping with somebody else by now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content> I love you too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-16"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>Aw, it's soo unfair. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>Hey, I don't know what to tell you guys that's the doll he chose.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Susan</speaker><content>What'd you do, dip it in sugar?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>Look, G. I. Joe's in, Barbi's out. And if you guys can't deal with it, that's your 'too bad.'</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>What are you being such a weenie for? So he has a Barbi, big deal. You used to dress up like a woman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>Well, you used to dress up in Mom's clothes all the time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>What are you talking about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>The big hat, the pearls, the little pick handbag.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>Okay, you are totally making this up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>How can you not remember? You made us call you...Bea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content> Oh God.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>Susan</speaker><content>I've literally never been this happy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>Wasn't there a little song?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>Carol</speaker><content>Oh please God, let there be a song.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>There was no song.  There was no song!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-16"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content> 'I am Bea.'</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-17"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-18"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>'I drink tea.'</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-19"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>Okay, that's, that's enough. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-20"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>'....Won't you, won't you, won't you.... '</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-21"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content> Won't you dance around with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-22"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>A-ha!!! </content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Young Ross</speaker><content> 'I am Bea. I drink tea. Won't you dance around with....'  Ohhh! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>YoungMonica</speaker><content> Ross!!! </content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>