<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>And that's why, no matter what mommy says, we really were on a break.  Yes we were! Yes we were!  Come here gorgeous.  Oh! Look at you! You are the cutest little baby ever! You're just a... a little bitty baby, you know that? But you've got...  You've got big beautiful eyes... Yes you do... and a... and a big round belly.  Big baby butt! I like big butts.  I like big butts and I cannot lie / you other brothers can't deny / when a girl walks in with an itty, bitty, waist / and a round thing in your face you get... Oh my God, Emma... you're laughing! Oh my God, you've never done that before, have you? You never done that before... Daddy made you laugh, huh? Well, daddy and Sir Mix Alot... What? What? You... you wanna hear some more? Uhm... My anaconda don't want none / unless you got buns hon...  I'm a terrible father!</content></utterance>
</scene>


<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Hi!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Hey... hey listen... What do you guys know about investments?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>How come?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Well, I'm starting to make good money on the show and I'm thinking... I should probably do something with it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>What do you do with your money now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Well, I just tape it to the back of my toilet tank.  I didn't say that! It's in a bank guarded by robots!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Do you have any ideas?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Uh, yeah... This guy at work got me excited about going in on an emu farm. That'd be kinda cool huh? Pitching in on the weekends, helping to plant the emus...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>Joe... Emus are birds. You raise them for meat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>Joey, I think you should consider something a little less risky. I mean, I think in this market, real estate is your best investment. The Fed just lowered the rates and the interest on your mortgage is totally deductible.  That's right, I know some stuff!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Real estate, huh? Hmmm...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>My dad told me. They play golf together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Oh, well... Maybe I'll join them some time. I just hope the club doesn't slip out of my hand and beat the moustache off his face.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Hi!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Rachel and Monica</speaker><content>Hey!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Listen! You have to help me pick a dress 'cause I'm meeting Mike's parents tonight! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>Wow, the boyfriend's parents! That's a big step.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>They just gonna love you, just be yourself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>They live on the upper east side on Park Avenue!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Oh yeah, she can't be herself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Okay, so... all right... Which dress?  You can say "neither".</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Rachel and Monica</speaker><content>Oh God, neither!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>I'm sorry honey, but we're gonna take you shopping. It's gonna be fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Yeah, totally! You are in such good hands. And I'm so good with meeting parents. With the father, you know, you want to flirt a little bit, but not in a gross way. Just kind of like: "Oh Mr. Pincer, I can see where Wallis gets his good looks..."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>You went out with Wallis Pincer?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Uh, he took the SAT's for me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>I knew you didn't get a 1400!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Sssh yeah, well, duh! I mean...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>So... now... What about with Mike's mom?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Oh, with the mother, just... just constantly tell her how amazing her son is. Take it from me, moms love me. Ross's mom one time actually said I'm like the daughter that she never had.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>I just finished getting Phoebe all dressed to meet Mike's parents. She's so nervous, it's so sweet!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>Guess what? I made Emma laugh today.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>Yeah, and it was uhm... it was like a real little person laugh too. It was... it was like uhm...  Only... only not creepy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Well... well, what did you do to make her laugh? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>I uhm... Well, I sang...  well actually I rapped... Baby Got Back... </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>You WHAT? You sang... to our baby daughter... a song about a guy who likes to have sex with women with giant asses?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>But you know what, if you think about it, it actually promotes a healthy uhm... body image... because... even big butts or uhm... juicy doubles.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>Please don't take her away from me!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Catherine</speaker><content>Oh hi, come on in. I'm Catherine, the listing agent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Hi I'm Joey. This is Chandler.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>So how come Richard's selling the place? Went bankrupt? Medical malpractice? Choked on his own moustache?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Catherine</speaker><content>Actually, he is buying a much bigger place. It's got a great view of Central Pa....</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Is there anything we should know about the apartment?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Catherine</speaker><content>All the appliances are included. There is a lot of light, a new kitchen... I think you guys would be very happy here... </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>No, no, no, no, no, NO! No, no... we're not together. We're not a couple. We're definitely not a couple.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Catherine</speaker><content>Oh... Okay, sorry!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Well, you seem pretty insulted by that. What? I'm not good enough for you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>We're not gonna have this conversation again... Look at this place. Why am I so intimidated by this guy? Pretentious art, this huge macho couch. When we know all he does is sit around all day crying about losing Monica to a real man!  You don't think he's here, do you? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>You know what it is? It's a nice place but I gotta see, I don't know if I see myself living here. Oh, oh, oh, let me see...  Yeah, I could see it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>There's a tape here with Monica's name on it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Ooh! A tape with a girls name on it. It's probably a sex tape...  Wait a minute... This says Monica...  And this is Richard's apartment... </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Get there faster! </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>Wow! You look like... like my mom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>I'm wearing pantyhose!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>Great! Come on in! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Oh, thank you! Oh... Oh my God, you're RICH!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>No, my parents are rich.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Yeah, so... They gotta die someday.  HELLO!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>Mom, dad, this is Phoebe. Phoebe, these are my parents: Theodore and Bitsy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Bitsy</speaker><content>It's so nice to finally meet you!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>And you... Your home is lovely.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Bitsy</speaker><content>Well thank you, I'll give you a tour later. It's actually three floors.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Holy crap!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Bitsy</speaker><content>Phoebe, why don't you come in the living room and meet our friends?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Oh, try and stop me!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>Hey... Wh... What are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>Yeah, I'm sure they will, but you don't have to do this... I'm wanting them to get to know Phoebe, not  Phoebe...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>Well, come on...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>Theodore</speaker><content>Phoebe, these are our friends, Tom and Sue Angle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-18"><speaker>Bitsy</speaker><content>Phoebe, come sit. Tell us a little bit about yourself... So where are you from?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>God! God! This is not going well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>No, no, no, you're doing fine, really... Why don't you go talk to my dad?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Okay, okay, okay, okay... Still sure about me being myself?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>Absolutely! Or maybe just a little less pimp spit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>So Theodore... I uhm... I can see where Mike gets his good looks from...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Theodore</speaker><content>Oh... Well...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Yeah... And that physique! You must work out all the time...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Theodore</speaker><content>Oh no, not all the time... I do the best I can...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Yeah I bet! Look out! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Theodore</speaker><content>OH! OWWWWW! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Oh my God, are you okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Theodore</speaker><content>I recently had surgery.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>I'm so sorry!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Theodore</speaker><content>No, I'll be fine... I just should check the stitches...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>I really, really am sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>Theodore</speaker><content>How could you know. Why wouldn't you punch me in the stomach? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>Uhm... Did you just hit my dad?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Yes... I'm sorry, I've never met a boyfriends parents before...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>But, I mean, you have met... humans before, right? Look, why don't you go talk to my mom?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-20"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Yeah okay... yeah, your mom... okay... She looks nice, I can talk to her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-21"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>Yeah, you do that, and I go check my dad for signs of internal bleeding. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-22"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Yeah... Oh Bitsy, hi. Uhm... listen I just wanted to thank you again for having me here tonight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-23"><speaker>Bitsy</speaker><content>Well, not at all...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-24"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Also uhm... I just want you to know what a wonderful man your son is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-25"><speaker>Bitsy</speaker><content>Thank you, I think so too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-26"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Well, and you know, it really is a testament to how he was raised. Especially to you. Because he's very respectful of women.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-27"><speaker>Bitsy</speaker><content>Is he really?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-28"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Are you kidding. He is so considerate of my feelings and... you know I think... you'd also like to know that he is a very gentle lover.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-29"><speaker>Bitsy</speaker><content>E-e-excuse me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-30"><speaker>Bitsy</speaker><content>That's... my boy. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-31"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>Awesome!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>I'm not gonna watch it... I don't NEED to watch it... I mean, what good could possibly come from watching?  Well, we know I'm gonna watch it. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Hey dude, what's up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Don't judge me, I'm only human!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Did you take that tape?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>I had to! Okay, imagine you were married... and you found a tape of your wife in another guys' apartment... Wouldn't you need to know what was on it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>I don't know. Who'm I'm married to?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Some girl...!?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>She hot?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Yeah...!?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>How did she get me to settle down?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>All right, I'm gonna watch it... I mean look, it's probably not even what I think it is... And even if it is... It can't possibly be as bad as what I'm picturing in my head...  Can it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Guess I don't know. My experience: if a girl says yes to being taped... She doesn't say no to much else, I tell ya...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Then you're gonna have to watch it for me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Just for a few seconds, so I can know what it is... Please?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>All right, fine... But if I enjoy this, you have only yourself to blame... </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Why am I hearing cheering?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Well it's okay, its like... its just a football game.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Football? Just football?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>Yeah, see... you were all worried for nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-20"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>It's football... It's just football... This is great! This is the first time I've ever enjoyed football... It may be customary to get a beer...  What the...  What are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-21"><speaker>Joey</speaker><content>You don't wanna see what I just saw! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-22"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>What are you guys doing?  Oh my God, is that Richard? </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Okay... aahhh... Please laugh for mommy... Please? Please laugh for mommy...  Not funny huh? Oh so, is it... only offensive novelty rap? Or maybe just, you know, rap in general? 'Cause mommy can rap...  My name is mommy and I'm here to say / that all the babies are... Oh, I can't rap... All right sweetheart... This is only because I love you so much, and I know that you're not gonna tell anybody...  I like... big butts and I cannot lie... / You other brothers can't deny... / when a girl walks in with an itty bitty waist and a round thing in your face...  Yes! Yes! Yes! YES! Oohhhhh! Oh!  I like big butts and I cannot lie... / You other brothers can't deny... Oh Emma you're laughing! Oh you are, you really do like big butts, don't you. Oh you beautiful little weirdo... </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>Hey!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Oh you missed it. She was laughing. Oh it was amazing. It was amazing. It was the most beautiful, beautiful sound that...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>Oh I know, isn't it? Ooh... what'd you do to get her to laugh?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Oh! You know, I just... couple of things I tried ... I just sang a little doo... Itsy Bitsy Spider...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>You sang Baby Got Back didn't you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Nothing else worked. That girl is all about the ass...</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>...and then it goes back to the chorus... Smelly cat, Sme-lly ca-t / I-t's not your fau-lt. And that's the end of the song... I realise that you didn't ask to hear it, but uhm... no-one had spoken in seventeen minutes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>Phoebe writes lots of great songs. Wha... What was that one you sang the other night that everybody just loved?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Oh, Pervert Parade?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Oh, Ode To A Pubic Hair?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>Stop! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Oh God! Is that veal?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>Mom, I thought I told you... Phoebe's a vegetarian.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Bitsy</speaker><content>Oh!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Oh no, no, no, no... That's okay, that's okay... I mean, I'm... I am a vegetarian... except for veal... Yeah no, veal I love...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>Phoebe you don't have to eat...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>No, no, no, I actually it's any baby animals: kittens, fish babies... You know... especially veal... and this, this nice vein of fat running through it...  Hmmm... yummy  Hmmm... </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>So...? What do you think? </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>So you stole that tape from Richard's apartment?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Whoho ho... Listen to the judgment from the porn star!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>That tape was never meant to be seen by...  Joey I would feel more comfortable if I was having this conversation in private.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>Why in the world would you take this tape and and why would you watch it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Because that's who I am, okay? I'm sure a mature man like Richard could see a tape like that and it wouldn't bother him. Just'd be another saucy anecdote for him to share at his men's club over brandy and moustaches.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>Is all this about you not being able to grow a moustache?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>This is about you and Richard. He's clearly not over you. He keeps a tape so he can... look at it whenever he wants.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>Isn't that sad? I mean, can you see how pathetic that is? You shouldn't be jealous. You should feel bad for him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Oh, yeah, well, poor Richard. Y'... I can grow a moustache!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>Chandler, this is not our problem. We've got each other. That's all that matters.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Yeah, oh, but I just keep picturing you rolling around with him with your cowboy boots in the air...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>Cowboy boots? I've never worn cowboy boots in my whole life! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Oh, good, good. Play more, 'cause I wanna see how it ends.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>THAT'S NOT ME!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>What...? That's not you! Life is good again! Ride 'em cowgirl!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-16"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>That bastard taped over me! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-17"><speaker>Chandler</speaker><content>Is that a problem?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-18"><speaker>Monica</speaker><content>I-It's just so insulting! Big spring for a new blank tape, Doctor!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Theodore</speaker><content>I can't imagine what he sees in her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Bitsy</speaker><content>She actually makes me miss that pill-popping ex-wife of his.  Oh, hello dear...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>Hey, what's going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Bitsy</speaker><content>We were just chit-chatting. How's your friend?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>A little better.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Bitsy</speaker><content>By the way, do you know who's moving back into town? Tom and Sue's daughter Jen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Theodore</speaker><content>You remember her Michael, she's lovely and... well-behaved and... single.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>I'm not interested.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>Bitsy</speaker><content>Oh, please darling, let's be honest. You can have all the... sailor fun you want with that one, but... let's be real...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>All right, stop! You know, all Phoebe has done tonight is trying to get you to like her. And maybe that hasn't been clear all the time, but she did her best. And yeah... She's a little different than you are...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>Bitsy</speaker><content>Michael, a pimp spit in her mouth! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>So what? I mean if even I can get past that, it shouldn't bother you. And you don't have to like her. You just have to accept the fact that I do. I mean, if you even can't be civil to the woman I love...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>Bitsy</speaker><content>The woman you what? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Yeah... The woman you what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>The woman I love...  I love you... Which is probably something I shouldn't say for the first time in front of my parents... and Tom and Sue...Who are by the way the most sinfully boring I've ever met in my life...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-16"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>I love you too...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-17"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>You do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-18"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>YEAH...! How great is this...? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-19"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>Wanna get out of here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-20"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-21"><speaker>Mike</speaker><content>Mom, dad, thanks for dinner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-22"><speaker>Phoebe</speaker><content>I had a great time.  It was really top drawer. And here's something rich: thirteen bathrooms in this place... I threw up in the coat closet... Ta taaa...</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>She sweat, wet, got it going like a turbo 'vette.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>So fellas</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>Yeah!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>fellas</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>Yeah!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Has your girlfriend got the butt?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>Hell yeah!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>So shake it! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>Shake it!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Shake it! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>Shake it!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-12"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Shake that nasty butt...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-13"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>Baby got back </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-14"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>One more time from the top... I like big butts and I cannot lie, you other br... </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-15"><speaker>Ross</speaker><content>Rachel please! That is so inappropriate!</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>