<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>

<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>Do you feel the spirit?  And in the 39th year of his reign, Asa was diseased in his feet until the disease was exceedingly great, yet he didn't seek help from the Lord, but from the physicians. Now there is nothing wrong with seeing a doctor, but can a doctor heal through the power that Jesus gave his disciples? Men of science can walk through life with blindfolds never knowing that you or I could not take a single step if we were not uplifted by God.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>Agnes, thank you for letting me be an instrument of God's love for you.  In faith, all things are possible. My friends, I want you to let Agnes feel the wave of faith in this church here today, lifting her into God's hands.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>Come on, sister.  Praise Jesus! Thank you Lord! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Dad</speaker><content>Son!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>Dad, I think I need a doctor!</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> Did you remember my DVD player?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well if you wanted it, you shouldn't have left it behind when you moved out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>No I get it, it's a drag watching porn on VHS.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'll call you as soon as I'm done with it. That's if you ever get a phone installed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Ohh forget it, I'll come by and get it myself, err after work, Thursday?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Won't be home Thursday.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>No problem, still have a key; I can let myself in and out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I guess maybe I could bring in it tomorrow. After all, how many times can you hit pause at the part where Lindsay Lohan wins the spelling bee? What is it about girls who can spell?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>It's a math contest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What is it about girls who can count?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>It's poker night isn't it?  You said weeks ago that I could play. Stop making excuses.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Gotta go, building full of sick people.  If I hurry maybe I can avoid them.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>The abdominal series show no evidence of obstruction, what'd you have to eat?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>Chicken sandwich, we travel - lots of fast food.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>Thank you, I barely felt it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>You're welcome.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>God told me you were kind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>You talk to God?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Dad</speaker><content>God's presence often descends on Boyd to help him guide others.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>This been going on long?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Dad</speaker><content>Since he was 10.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>God told me I would meet a woman... err... healer... who was harboring vengeful thoughts about a man she works with.  That's God's job.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I'll keep that in mind. His urine is dilute.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Dad</speaker><content>What does that mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Could mean that for some reason his kidneys aren't purifying the way they should, which would let toxins accumulate in his body. We'll run the blood work and see what it tells us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>Thank you, I appreciate it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>God talks to him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>It's not psychosis, he's just religious. The only medical issue that showed up on the blood work is low sodium.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, you talk to God you're religious, God talks to you you're psychotic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>A lot of people experience their religion as something more than symbolic. That doesn't mean--</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>God ever talked to you when you were in the seminary?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-20"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content> No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content>God's loss, our gain. He's either psychotic or a scam artist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-22"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>He was actually err... really impressive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-23"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well yeah, with the burning bush and all, it's quite the show.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-24"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>He was intelligent, polite, dignified, he's not a typical 15-yr-old.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-25"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>And he told Cameron, God wants her to stop being pissed at me over the article.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-26"><speaker>House</speaker><content>God knows you stole Cameron's article?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-27"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>He knows she's harboring "vengeful thoughts".</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-28"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I'm over it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-29"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah. I can tell that from the Berlin wall of body language between you.  I'm shocked that he picked up on it. Low sodium - check for Addison's?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-30"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>No pigmentation and potassium levels are normal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-31"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Cirrhosis?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-32"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Liver feels fine, transaminases are normal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-33"><speaker>House</speaker><content> We should monitor his saline intake to correct the low sodium. No more than one mEq  per litre per hour. Let's push the patient history to see if there's any history of drugs or other delusions. I'll take care of it. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-34"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You're going to talk to a patient?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-35"><speaker>House</speaker><content>God talks to him. It'd be arrogant of me to assume that I'm better than God.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So, you're a faith healer. Or is that a pejorative? Do you prefer something like divine health management?  I thought God might have mentioned that I was coming.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>I'm ok with faith healer, Doctor House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh! That's a nice one, didn't even go with I see an 'H' and a medical coat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>The nurses talk about you a lot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Ah, don't believe them. I keep a sock in my pants. Faith - that's another word for ignorance isn't it? Never understood how people could be so proud of believing in something with no proof at all. Like that's an achievement.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>God's asking for our trust. You can't love somebody and not trust them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Trust has to be earned; can't trust someone hiding in a closet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>You don't trust anyone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You seem lucid, there's no confusion, no lethargy. What drugs have you been taking?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>Nothing. Erm... some aspirin, I get focused on something, I forget to eat and next thing you know I've got a hunger headache.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So aspirin and hospitals are ok. That's an interesting attitude for someone who's kept any number of people from getting medical help.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>Just because I believe in prayer doesn't mean I don't believe in germs and toxins.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That bottle's been opened before. You refilled it at the water cooler.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Dad</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>How often do you do that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Dad</speaker><content>Few times an hour, he likes to stay hydrated. You think germs might have gotten in?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I think water might have gotten in.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>We can adjust your pain meds.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Grace</speaker><content>Again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Suppose we increase your oxycodone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Grace</speaker><content>We both know the only reason I'm talking lucidly now is because I did not take my full dose this morning.  You've done your best. And I have been a good soldier; it's time we accept it’s over.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>What about the trip you were talking about taking? You've wanted to see Florence since you were a teenager, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Grace</speaker><content>Yeah, go now all drugged up. It's not exactly the trip I've been dreaming of.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Ok, but you're strong. You're dealing with this. And there is the right combination of pain meds out there, and we'll find it. Don't give up on us.  And don't be startled by the sound you're about to hear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Excuse me. I have a friend with boundary issues.  Can this wait 5 minutes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Is she dying?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Before the end of this consult?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>They could build monuments to your self-centeredness.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Patient, 15-yr-old, faith healer, hotline to God.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>What are his symptoms?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He is NOT a saint. He figures out what's going on in people's lives by watching, listening, deducing--</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You're worried about trademark infringement?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Then he passes on advice from God so he can watch them jump, it's a power trip.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-18"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Ah! And there the similarities end. Why is he here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I fear for the human race. A teenager claims to be the voice of God and people with advanced degrees are listening.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-20"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Majority of Americans believe in a personal God, what are his symptoms?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Massive cramps, low sodium, turns out he's been drinking water non-stop, God told him to purify his body.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-22"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Huge water intake would cause low sodium...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-23"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Which would cause the cramping, yeah I get it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-24"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>What? That's it? You solved it. You just brought me out here to rant because faith annoys you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-25"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Um hmm... he's all better. You know I get it if people were just looking for a way to fill the holes. But they WANT the holes; they wanna live in the holes. And they go nuts when someone else pours dirt in their holes. CLIMB OUT OF YOUR HOLES, PEOPLE!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>Go tell it on the mountain, that Jesus Christ is born...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Boyd?  Are you alright? Boyd!  Come on, let's go. Can you tell me your name? Do you know where you are? Boyd? Boyd?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>God doesn't want you to be afraid, he sent me here to heal you. You think he hasn't heard your prayers but he heard them all, even the ones you didn't say.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Sorry, Boyd come on; let's get you back to your room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content> In faith, all things are possible.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Let's go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>Lord, I call on you to relieve the suffering of your daughter and make her whole again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> Grace?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Hey, hey! What are you... what is this? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>He's just had a complex partial seizure, he's disoriented, he doesn't know what he's doing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> Well get him back to his room. Now.  Are you ok?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Are we certain he even had a seizure? Him singing and healing, he does it all the time, doesn't he?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Isn't it interesting that religious behavior is so close to being crazy we can't tell them apart?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>The repetition, the lack of affect and awareness, it was a seizure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Infection?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>No fever.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Could be Wilson's. Or maybe it's a glycogen storage disease.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Or a brain tumor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Or tuberous sclerosis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Hmm... how to settle this? We could ask our patient to ask God, or we could MRI his brain. Which way do you want to go? 'cos I'm open to all of them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> House! Why the hell did you let an unstable patient wander the hallways?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>His leash broke.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>The last thing a terminal patient needs is to hear somebody taunt them with a cure. She was... freaked, she was angry...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And now she's not freaked and angry, and you are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>She says she's 'feeling better'. Maybe not singing or dancing but she's feeling just a little bit happy for the first time in months.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Sudden drop in pain could create euphoria. You should let her have her vacation. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Oh, that's great. And when vacation's over, when she crash lands from all this denial, she was dealing with her illness. Now her expectations are rising and you're not the one who has to be there when all that false hope gets yanked out from under her. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Don't you guys have anything to do? </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>How long have you been healing people?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>You believe that's what I'm doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I'd... like to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>But you don't. Why do you always do things you don't want to do?  It's okay. I don't expect a real answer. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>God would probably want you to take the stick out of your butt and get over this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>If there is some higher order running the universe, it's probably so different from anything our species can conceive, there's no point in even thinking about it. But I doubt it gives a damn about my butt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>So you believe God might exist, but you don't think about it? It's the most important issue-</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I think penguins might as well speculate about nuclear physics! Why are we having this conversation?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>What? I'm curious.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>You cannot tell someone they're your colleague and not a friend, and then casually chat about the afterlife.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content> You actually keep score?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Your MRI results aren't done yet; go back to your room. No singing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>Well you would get a point for figuring why the low sodium, what are my guy's points for?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Your trick about the spat between Doctor Cameron and Doctor Foreman apparently impressed someone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>And the second point?  Do you think it could be because I... healed Grace? She's been back to see me, I like her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You like messing with people. That's why you're here now. Now maybe you think that your batteries are powered by God, maybe you don't. Either way, you enjoy what you do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>Yes. I like helping people. I get a rush when I see the look on their faces when they realize their burdens are gone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Hmm... but you make sure you're in the next state by the time the endorphins wear off and the arthritis comes back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>That doesn't happen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh, you do extensive follow-up studies?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>God told me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That's not fair. We were having fun; it's hard to keep sniping rationally when you throw a bomb like that in there. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>He spoke with me about you too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Forgive my enemies, never date a Taurus when Mercury's in retrograde, yeah, I learnt that one myself, the hard way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>God says you look for excuses to be alone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>See that is exactly the kind of brilliance that sounds deep, but you could say it about any person who doesn't pine for the social approval of everyone he meets, which you were cleverly able to deduce about me by not being a moron. Next time, tell God to be more specific.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-17"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>God wants you to invite Doctor Wilson to your poker game.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Don't talk to my patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>What are you talking about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You get all huffy when my patient stumbles into yours in the hallway but you got no qualms about chatting my guy up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>This is fun, it's like password. Keep talking; I'll jump in when I get a clue what the hell you're talking about.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>God knows about my poker game.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You think I told him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Either that or I start going to Church every Sunday. That would mess with my bowling league.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>House, aside from yelling at him to get back to his room, I have never spoken to your patient.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>MRI shows an abnormal area.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Tuberous sclerosis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>It's the right neighborhood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>It accounts for all the symptoms.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>All of them?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Leading cortical tubers identifiable. We can do this surgically.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Tell our patient congratulations. Soon his chats with God will be a thing of the past.  Tie goes to the mortal.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Did you know the Catholic Church keeps a doctor at Lourdes; he hears the same thing every day. But, out of the thousands of cases of people who've claimed to feel better, the Catholic Church has only recognized a handful as miracles.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Grace</speaker><content>But they do recognize a handful. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Well, they're a church. It's what they do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>Grace</speaker><content>Look, for the past couple of years, the world's been getting smaller. 8 months, 6 months...  I watch a trailer for a movie and I think, ‘am I going to be here when that comes out?’ and maybe there is still a horizon out there. You know, maybe I can make plans for a year from now. Two years. I like the view.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>The view is a lie, and if you believe it, you're going to crash so hard. Let me take new images of your liver.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>Grace</speaker><content>You can't accept that it could be true.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Well if it is true, you shouldn't be afraid of proving it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Tuberous sclerosis is a genetic disorder, causes small benign tumors to grow in various parts of the body. In this case the brain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>Dad</speaker><content>You said benign.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>They probably are but benign or not, they're not in a good location. We need to remove them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>Dad</speaker><content>You're talking brain surgery?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>His symptoms are getting worse which means the tumors are growing. Surgery will correct it all - the chemical imbalance, the seizures, the auditory hallucinations.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>Dad</speaker><content>Hallucinations?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Without the surgery, it's just going to get worse; might even be fatal. With the surgery, your son should be a perfectly normal 15-yr-old boy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>I'm not normal.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I need you to talk to my patient.  I'll get this one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Why do I have the feeling you're plotting world domination?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Moses is refusing surgery. You have a gift, people thank you for telling them they're going to die.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>If I can get him to agree to surgery, I want in on the poker game.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You would let this kid die just to get into a stupid game?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You'd let him die just to keep me out?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Hi. I'm Doctor Wilson.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>I knew they'd send somebody else.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Think God has a big mouth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>House.  Can I ask why you don't want the tumors removed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>God put them there for a reason.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You think God needs a telephone in your head to talk to you? Isn't he everywhere? It's not a long-distance call.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>This is the way God does things, through natural law. If he went around doing big flashy miracles all the time, nobody would need faith.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>How come everyone else needs faith but you just get the guy screaming his existence in your ear?  Your turn.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Do you think God wants you to die?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-10"><speaker>Dad</speaker><content>This is the way that the Lord often is with his chosen ones. He... he gives the most trials to those that he loves the most.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>How sweet. You abdicate your authority; avoid those tricky parental issues like whether to let him drive at 16, just let him die at 15.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-12"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>So you... believe your son is... umm... a saint? The way I understand it, one of the hallmarks of a saint is humility. Now someone with true humility would consider the possibility that God hadn't chosen him for that kind of honor. Well, he'd consider the possibility that... he just... had an illness. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You have a gift for manipulation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I listen, I have an actual conversation with people; which shockingly does raise the odds they’ll be co-operative.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That's what I'm saying. You read that kid; you manipulated the hell out of him.  Bring pretzels.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I know that knock. Use your key, I'm not getting up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Game's not 'til tomorrow night. Those aren't pretzels.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I took some images of Grace Palmeri's cancer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah...?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> Her tumor’s shrunk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Don't tell my patient.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I want all the records on miracle woman. Every test, every treatment she's ever had, every question she's ever answered in this hospital. Anything sent for previous doctors. Go back to neo-natal if you have to-  Which part of keep them away from each other confused you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>They're friends. She thinks he saved her life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Now we have obligingly offered medical proof that his delusions are true.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content> They've withdrawn permission for the surgery. I put the lawyers on it. Her tumor shrank?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm on it.  Tell Jesus that we need another 24 hours to normalize the sodium levels.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>It's already normalized.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Actually, tell Joseph.  Jesus will know you're lying. And I want you and Foreman and Cameron to go over every line of every file on that woman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Isn't he the one we're supposed to save?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The only way to save him is to prove that she is still dying.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>MRI machine checks out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Maybe the radiologist mis-charted which machine they used.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Checked both. This is insane, we're diagnosing a recovery.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>What about 6 months ago? Maybe there was a malfunction on her "before" pictures. Some shadow that made the tumor look bigger than it really was. I'll go see what I can find out. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Maybe it's a delayed effect from radiation. Sometimes it could take a while.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>She hasn't had radiation for 6 months.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Nowhere. Her records--</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>There's about a dozen appliances in every home that give off radiation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Dosages that wouldn't hurt a hamster if it was tied to the machine for a year.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>If the machine's operating properly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-12"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Sometimes remissions just happen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-13"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content> You think House will just shrug and say that if one of us doesn't check the home? </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Kings on nines.  Wilson! This is err...  Dry Cleaner, Tax Accountant, Guy from the Bus Stop. This is Wilson.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>Dry Cleaner</speaker><content>How come he gets a name?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Seniority.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Hello. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Find anything?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Do you have any idea how many electrical devices give off radiation?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>All of them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I'm going to be here all night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Everybody's a whiner. Be a do-er, not a me-tooer.  Raise.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>There's at least 4 different types of pain pills here. And an LED device.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'll raise your raise.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Keep looking.  Fold.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>Tax Accountant</speaker><content>You were bluffing. He knew you were bluffing. Your luck's changing tonight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>So did they find anything? Or are you going to have to accept the fact that every now and then, remissions happen?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>This call had better be worth my time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-12"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>This is what happens when it's not our patient. We don't know enough.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That's why you're there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-14"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>She's got a boyfriend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Unless you think he's radioactive...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-16"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>He could show up any minute! The honor of working for you is not worth a felony charge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Give me a minute </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-18"><speaker>GBS</speaker><content>I'm saying the odds of you having a straight flush are pretty low. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-19"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>House!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-20"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'll fold.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-21"><speaker>Dry Cleaner</speaker><content>Fold.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-22"><speaker>Tax Accountant</speaker><content>Fold.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-23"><speaker>GBS</speaker><content>I'm screwed, aren't I?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-24"><speaker>House</speaker><content>9 bucks for a straight flush.  He's not coming home. Relax.  There's nothing in this universe that can't be explained... eventually. Take this game. Only 2 people knew that you wanted in on it. I didn't tell him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-25"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I told you, I didn't tell him!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-26"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Why would you? No, the only person he's been getting all intimate and conversational with is your cancer chick. How would she know?  The subject of my poker game isn't likely to come up in the course of a patient interview. No, that's the kind of thing you mention to someone you're used to sharing the details of your day with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-27"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> Don't.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-28"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Your rabbi, guidance counselor, parent... she's not your mom, is she?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-29"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'm seriously saying don't. [His voice has a very serious warning tone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-30"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You've been having sex...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-31"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>So not the place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-32"><speaker>House</speaker><content>... with our miracle woman.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>Dad</speaker><content>Excuse me... may I talk to you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Of course.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>Dad</speaker><content>Umm... Boyd's getting dressed, he's ready to check out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>He can't check out without your permission.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>His sodium level still isn't normal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>Dad</speaker><content>I told him, he said that God said it was ok. He was fine. Could you talk to him?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Tell them my name isn't Wilson.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Most people in your situation just have their careers to worry about. You've got that and divine retribution.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Tell them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Tell me how it happened, I'll tell them whatever you want.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> She'd had a bad day - pain-wise. Her ride didn't show up to take her home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So you offered?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Yeah. She didn't have any groceries. She was too sick to go out I... figured I could afford... take a half hour and... pick her up a few things and...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Stay and make sure she's ok.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And never leave. You told me you got an apartment, but you moved in with her. You lied to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-11"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Tell them!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>His name is not Wilson, and he's screwed up worse than I am.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-13"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Ok, yes, I lied to you. I'm sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Half the doctors who specialize in oncology turn into burnt-out cases, but you - you eat neediness.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-15"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Lucky for you.  Thanks for the game guys, don't think I'll be coming back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're a functional vampire. Sure, you're heroic, useful to society, but only because it feeds you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>There's nothing worth stealing so don't even look.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You don't just have a fetish for needy people, you marry them!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-19"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Here we go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-20"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You mean it, and then time passes and suddenly they're not so needy anymore. Your fault. You've been there for them too much. They're getting healthy, independent, and that's just ugly. God you must be pissed at God right now for making her all happy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-21"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Why are you doing this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-22"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Because you're being stupid.  You know what you're risking by sleeping with a patient!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-23"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Oh that's crap! You're not mad because I'm risking my job. You're not even mad because I lied to you, you're mad because I lied to you and you couldn't tell!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-24"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, you got me nailed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-25"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Yeah, that's why you didn't want me in your poker game. Because when it comes to being in control, Gregory House leaves our faith healer kid in the dust. And that's why religious belief annoys you. Because if the universe operates by abstract rules, you can learn them and you can protect yourself. If a supreme being exists, he can squash you anytime he wants.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-26"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He knows where I am.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-27"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Think it’s yours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-28"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Yeah.  I'll be right there.  Jesus is spiking a fever. He's delusional.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-29"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Tuberous sclerosis doesn't cause fever.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-30"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-31"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'll drive.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Pick any random guy off the street, bring him in here, examine him exhaustively and you'll find at least 3 things wrong with him. This kid has tuberous sclerosis - a mild case.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>But his tumors are growing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>We assumed that the tumors were growing 'cos he's getting sicker, but he could have grown old and died and never known about them if he hadn't come here. We were looking for something; it's more or less in the right part of the brain. It's like we found someone standing over a dead body holding a gun. We arrested them, didn't look any further. Well sometimes, people really do just stumble into a murder scene.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>His fever's 103 and rising. If we don't do anything, he's going to be chatting with God face-to-face real soon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Fevers don't come from a long-term underlying condition. He's a garden variety religious nut who happens to have an infection. It's lumbar puncture time.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>No, no, God told me no more of man's medicine. If we have faith in him, he'll make me well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>It's just a test; we just want to find out what's wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>God knows what's wrong. God will take care of it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content> He's delirious and he's a minor. This is your decision, not his.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content> The kingdom of heaven is like a treasure hidden in the field... which when a man finds he hides… he buys another field…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Buy all the land you want, don't blow your brains out! You're watching your son kill himself! He's out of his mind with fever--</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>Dad! If your faith is weak, I will fail. I need you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>Dad</speaker><content>I'm sorry; you don't even know what's wrong with him. God knows the answer and I would rather leave it in his hands than yours.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Wilson, need you to do your thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You do know that I don't actually have magical powers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I have faith.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Better off trying to slip some antibiotics into a meal...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Which antibiotics? We don't know what infection he's got.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Go as broad as you can.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Forget it; our best hope is your silver tongue.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>What if it's not an infection?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Were you not paying attention when I was doing my murder scene metaphor?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>What if the tuberous sclerosis IS guilty? It had the guns in its hands, it was standing over the--</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It doesn't cause fever.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-12"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>It causes everything else. What if the fever's the innocent bystander? Fever could have been set off by something he picked up anywhere. Could have been a bug he got here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Or a bug he gave here. He gave it to your patient. That's why her tumor shrank; the virus went after the cancer first.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>For 200 years, there've been reports of wild viruses that target tumors. Early 1900's, an Italian medical journal wrote up a woman with cervical cancer who was injected with a weak strain of rabies, I've no idea why they did that but her tumor shrank.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-15"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You think he gave her rabies?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>One of the virus types most prone to go after cancer cells is herpes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-17"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Herpes encephalitis. It would fit. Seizure, low sodium, even the blurred vision and it would mean, if you're right, Grace's cancer is coming back. You're not going to be able to convince them. They don't want any more tests. They don't wanna--</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>They can't argue with the mark of Cain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-19"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>I'm not going to change my mind! No more tests! God knows the way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-20"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Ok, let's start with the shirt. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-21"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>What are you doing?  What are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-22"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm on a mission from God. If you won't let me undress you, then strip.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-23"><speaker>Dad</speaker><content>What's he doing? What's going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-24"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That woman you helped? You gave her a virus.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-25"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>She's healed, I have a gift!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-26"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Gift is jewelry, socks. What you have is herpes encephalitis. The only way you could have transmitted it is by scratching one of your own sores and touching another person.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-27"><speaker>Dad</speaker><content>Herpes... that's something you get from sex, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-28"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Either that or cold sores. Your kid got it from the sex.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-29"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>No, no, no sores  No, my body's clean, they examined me when I came in! No sores!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-30"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Herpes hides. You have an outbreak; it goes away, comes back, goes away.  Strip! Maybe you didn't have a sore when you came in but you've got one now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-31"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>Dad I've never ever--</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-32"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Do you ever wonder why a perfect child of God should feel so desperate to purify his body that he needed to scarf down a dozen gallons of water a day?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-33"><speaker>Dad</speaker><content>Boyd... is he right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-34"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>Dad, no! He's crazy! Help me! Doctor Wilson! Help!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-35"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>God said no medicine, no procedures. Taking off your clothes doesn't count as either of those. This one's your call.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-36"><speaker>Dad</speaker><content>Son.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-37"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content>Dad, you have to have faith in me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-38"><speaker>Dad</speaker><content>I have faith in the Lord. You, I trust; as much as you can trust a teenage boy. Take off your clothes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-39"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Relax. A few Hail Mary's, a little acyclovir, he'll be picking up angels again in no time.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Come in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content> My father told me I have to apologize to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You still hearing voices?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>Boyd</speaker><content> You're lucky. You go through life with a certainty that what you're doing is right. I know how comforting that is. Good luck. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're not going to give me my final point? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You knew it was me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Who else?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You don't think God should get a point knocked off?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>The tumor shrank.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Because of a virus! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-11"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Do you know what the odds are? She had to have the right type of cancer; he had to have the right type of virus, the exposure had to be--</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>She won the lottery.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-13"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You say won the lottery, he says... miracle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, the hand of God reached into this kid's pants, made him have sex so he could scratch the rash, stick his fingers into some woman's face, give her a few extra months. Come on, he's just another liar and manipulator.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-15"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> Well nobody's as perfect as you are. It is possible to believe in something and still fail to live up to it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So... how's your girlfriend?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-17"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>She got a little extra time out of this. Not a lot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>She didn't crash.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-19"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>No. She said she's happier when she believes in something bigger than she is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-20"><speaker>House</speaker><content>She still believes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-21"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Faith. She's going to Florence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-22"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're moving out? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-23"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-24"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You moving back in with me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-25"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I don't think that's a great idea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-26"><speaker>House</speaker><content>But we're ok?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-27"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> House, you are... as God made you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>