<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>
<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Inmate</speaker><content>Deep fried shrimp, and lobster. I never had lobster. What, do you boil ‘em or grill ‘em? Which one’s better? Ah, just get ‘em both. And I know I need a strawberry malt, and then there’s those chocolate donuts that come in a box?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Lawyer</speaker><content>We’ll do our best to accommodate. Tomorrow you’ll be moved to a holding cell. That’s where you’ll get your last meal.  You also have a constitutional right to the spiritual advisor of your choice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Inmate</speaker><content>Naw, I don’t need none of that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Lawyer</speaker><content>One last thing to think about: After I read the execution warrant, you’ll be given an opportunity to make a statement. You might want to take some time and think about what you want to say as your final words. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Inmate</speaker><content>Yo, Clarence! You hear that? A spiritual advisor of my choice!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>Don’t matter, you goin’ to hell anyway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Inmate</speaker><content>You think I’ll get another stay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>You should. Supreme Court said it ain’t right to kill retards.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Warden</speaker><content>Cut the chatter! Exercise time.  Be back in an hour. Enjoy. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Woman</speaker><content>Why did you hit me so many times, Clarence?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>You know why!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Woman</speaker><content>You could have stopped. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>You stabbed me in the back, man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>I never st –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>You couldn’t fight fair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>Like you did? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Guard</speaker><content>I had a wife and three kids.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>You are a sick bastard! Open the door! Open the door! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>Man 2</speaker><content>Hey! What’d I ever do to you, man? </content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>James</speaker><content>You can’t go in there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Who are you, and why are you wearing a tie?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>James</speaker><content>I’m Dr. Cuddy’s new assistant. Can I tell her what it’s regarding?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yes. I would like to know why she gets a secretary and I don’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>James</speaker><content>I’m her assistant, not her secretary. I graduated from Rutgers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Hmm. I didn’t know they had a secretarial school. Well, I hope you took some classes in sexual harassment law. Does the word “ka-ching” mean anything to you? I’m going in now. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Dr. House, we are in the middle of a meeting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What’s with hiring a male secretary? JDate not working out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>He is cute. Be careful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>She’s not like you. She can’t just walk into a bar and pick up her soul mate in twenty minutes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>I met Mark at a fundraiser that happened to be held at a –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You met me at a strip club.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>You were the worst two dollars I ever spent.  We’ll catch up later.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Stacy, it’s House. I know you can handle it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>Nothing to handle. He obviously wants to talk to you alone. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>If you have a problem working with Stacy you should have said so.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What was I supposed to do? Ask her to leave? That’s just rude. Death row guy. I want the case.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>How do you even know about him? You don’t have access to the hospital’s mainframe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, but “partypants” does.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>You stole my password?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Hardly counts as stealing; it’s a pretty obvious choice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-22"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Well, I have already assigned Death Row Guy to Dr. Nolo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-23"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Nolo? Well, I don’t want to say anything bad about another doctor, but… especially a useless drunk…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-24"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>You are addicted to pain pills.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-25"><speaker>House</speaker><content>But I’m not useless. Tell Nolo I’m talking over.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-26"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Dr. Nolo is a board certified cardiologist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-27"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh, good. I’m sure he’ll explore all the usual options for why a guy’s heart starts beating so fast it pumps out air instead of blood. Wait a second – there are no usual options!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-28"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>How badly do you want this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-29"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I will give you two more clinic hours this week.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-30"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Don’t bend over for the soap. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Just the heart, or the patient have any other complaints?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The patient’s not talking to anybody.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Where are we going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You are going to the clinic for two hours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Me? Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Talk to Cuddy. She’s got me going to Mercer State Prison, Capital Sentences unit, I don’t know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Aren’t there better ways to spend our time?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Good question. What makes a person deserving? Is a man who cheats on his wife more deserving than a man who kills his wife?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Uh… yeah. Actually, he is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What about a child molester? Certainly not a good guy, but he didn’t kill anybody. Maybe he can get antibiotics, but no MRIs. What about you? What medical care should you be denied for being a car thief? Tell you what: the three of you work out a list of what medical treatments a person loses based on the crime they committed. I’ll review it when I get back. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Warden</speaker><content>Your patient shanked one inmate his first month here, broke another one’s neck, nearly decapitated one of my guards…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Relax, I’ve got a great bedside manner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Warden</speaker><content>Too dangerous to house him in the infirmary. You don’t have to worry, we’ve taken every precaution. I’ve had my men clear from the cell all pens, paperclips and staplers. Any supplies that might be used as a weapon.  Open her up! For your visit, we’ve got him cuffed and shackled.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And yet, you’re staying out there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Warden</speaker><content> Uhp! You’re going to have to give me that. Wouldn’t want anybody to get hurt.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content> Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Cindy</speaker><content>Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I’m Dr. Cameron. How’re you feeling?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Cindy</speaker><content>Eh. Little cough, no big deal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Okay. What’re you doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Cindy</speaker><content>I just got a job at the university. They need a health clearance. Apparently I’m a little anemic, so they made me get some more tests.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Any family history of anemia?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Cindy</speaker><content>Not that I know of. My mom died of cancer when I was a kid, my dad’s heart gave out a couple of years ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Brothers and sisters?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Cindy</speaker><content>I’m afraid it’s a short family history. That’s it. I had a husband once, but… didn’t stick. My tests should be back, probably in that file.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Probably. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Cindy</speaker><content>Is everything okay?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Did you redo the x-ray?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Twice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Well, you don’t need a consult. You know the diagnosis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>All she has is a cough.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Bluish tinge to the fingernails, lips… he’s hypoxic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Warden</speaker><content>What’s that mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It means he’s not getting enough oxygen. You know how people say you can’t live without love? Well, oxygen’s even more important. He’s got fluid in his lungs, breathing rate of 50… he needs to be intubated and put on a respirator.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Warden</speaker><content>Don’t have a respirator.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Better get one in about an hour, or you’re gonna lose him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Warden</speaker><content>I’ll make out a requisition. The state’s already sentenced this man to die.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content> I think the state was a tad more specific about “how”.  This is Dr. Gregory House. I need an ambulance to pick-up at Mercer State Prison.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Warden</speaker><content>Wasted call, my men will stop them at the gate. No way a Death Row inmate leaves my prison, at least not through the front doors.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You work fast.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>So do you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Was that a shot?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>Yeah. It was easy once I convinced the clerk to take it to Judge Markem, she’s a sucker for Eighth Amendment arguments.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Stop, I’m getting turned on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>House!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Ruh-row!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>It was just a consult! You expect us to shut down an entire floor for this guy?!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Did you do something to your hair?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Stacy?!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>You said you cleared with her –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Come on. You’ve known me how long and you still don’t know when I’m joshin’ ya?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Take him back to prison. Now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, can’t. See, ironically I’m bound by this court order which your ace attorney got. I have to make him all better before shipping him back for the state to kill him. Is it just me, or is that weird? Anyway, we’re walking.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Somebody left this on my chair. It’s clever. Forces me to either deal with the file or never sit down again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Cindy Kramer. I told her you’d see her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You shouldn’t have told her that. She’s got metastatic squamous cell lung cancer, six months, tops.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Have you even looked at the x-ray?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, just guessing. It’s a new game. If I’m wrong, she gets a stuffed bear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>A spot on a x-ray doesn’t necessarily mean that she’s terminal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I love children. So filled with hope.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>It could be pneumonia. It could be sarcodosis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Could be, if she didn’t already have swollen hilar lymph nodes on the other lung.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Could we at least brainstorm for other ideas?  Thank you.  I still think it could be pneumonia and sarcodosis, but we should check for tuberculosis and definitely rule out congestive heart failure.  The five stages of dying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Exactly. Personally, I think it’s all just new-age crap, but from your tear-filled, puppy-dog eyes I think I’ve made my point. Now go tell Cindy Whatever-her-name-is that she’s dying.  Tachycardia, pulmonary edema, likely suspects?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content> The Death Row guy? That’s who you’re working on instead of Cindy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>God, I’ve got to learn not to beat around the bush. By dying, I meant no matter what we do. Very, very soon she is going to be dead. Is it still to subtle?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I took an oath to do no harm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, well, it’s not like they make you sign it or anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>We cure your patient, he goes back to Death Row. He goes back to Death Row, they kill him!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He stays here and we don’t treat him, he dies, and I still don’t treat Cindy Lou-Who.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Can we get on with this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, I knew I could count on your help for your homie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-20"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content> Exactly, I’m black. I sympathize for guys who grew up in the city kept down by the man. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Makes sense to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-22"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>It’s a bunch of crap. You can’t blame society for the fact that you chose to become a killer. The guy’s probably a heroin addict, that explains the tachycardia, which caused the pulmonary edema.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-23"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>How does an inmate on Death Row get his hands on heroin?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-24"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Are you serious?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-25"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The man knows prisons. When we’ve got a yachting question, we’ll come to you. Okay, drugs it is. Test his hair, blood, urine, the works. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Thanks for getting my back. I thought you seminary boys were against the death penalty.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I left the seminary.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Over their stance on capital punishment?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I’m against the death penalty in principle. In practice, however, watching a murderer die causes me a lot less grief than annoying my boss. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Guard</speaker><content>We gotta check you out before you go in.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Department of Justice statistics show that it’s a racially motivated form of punishment. Black defendants are ten times more likely to get a death sentence than whites.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Doesn’t mean we need to get rid of the death penalty, do we? It just means we need to kill more white people.  It’s okay, you’re in a hospital, we’re taking care of you. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>Water… water.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What’s the differential for being thirsty?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>He was just a little dehydrated, and out of his mind. We upped his saline drip, he’s fine now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Blood and urine tests came back clean, no sign of opiates in his system. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Don’t do that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>What, you have some House theory explaining heroin use despite a negative test?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Nope. Only I get to write on the board.  So it’s not drugs. What else can cause the heart to do wind sprints? You got the blood work back, any –  – thing out of the ordinary?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>His bi-carb is low.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, but which column? Could be the result of the tachycardia, could be the cause?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>It’s the cause.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Why, because you want it to be? Let’s see how well that works with your other patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>We’re just talking semantics here. We should put him on a bi-carb drip and send him back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Right, buff his numbers. Don’t bother trying to figure out the underlying cause. I thought you cared about patients.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Our job isn’t to make sure he can bounce his grandkids on his lap, our job is to get him healthy enough to go back to Death Row.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Our job is to diagnose him. What? Mommy and Daddy are having a little fight, it doesn’t mean we stop loving you. Now, go outside and play. Get Daddy some smokes and an arterial blood gas test.  Wow. That was impressive. Okay, what number am I thinking of?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>Were you trying to get me fired? If you didn’t want me working here, why didn’t you just say so?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I just don’t want you working right here, in my office. But anywhere else in the building is fine. It’s a big hospital.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-17"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>I’m a lawyer. You’re a jerk. There’s gonna to be some overlap.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>God, I hope that was a euphemism.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-19"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>Cuddy just reamed me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-20"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I hope that one means what I think it means.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-21"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>For trusting you! She figured when she hired me she’d at least have someone you couldn’t walk all over.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-22"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The number was six, by the way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-23"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>I need to know, can I trust you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-24"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If I hadn’t lied to you about Cuddy’s approval, my patient would be dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-25"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>Great. Now I know. Now we can work together.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I’m drawing some blood from your femoral artery.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>From my what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Runs through your groin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>You think you’re gonna stick me in the jewels with that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>It’s really closer to your thigh. Technically, at this point, it seems like your jewels are more for display purposes, anyway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>Hold up, hold up. Give me some pain killers, or something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Tough guy like you don’t need ‘em.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>Forget that, numb me up, man.  You got some gang ink? Let me see that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>It’s a Native American symbol. It means “the force of life.”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>That’s what you tell all these white dudes so they let you play doctor?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Yep. Got ‘em all fooled.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-12"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>For real, how a brother like you go from gang-banger to wearing a white coat?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-13"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>How’s a brother like you go from loving a woman to punching her skull in?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-14"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>Bitch stepped out.  Argh! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-15"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Sorry about that. Guess I didn’t use enough lidocaine.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Blood gas came back with a pH of 7.28 and decreased HCO3.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Which means two things. Most importantly, Cameron was wrong about the bi-carb, and less significantly, we have a new symptom. Anion gap acidosis. Who’s chubby? Come on, pretend he loves puppies. Pretend he’s a human being. What’ve you got?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I think we should reconsider drugs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>He already tested negative.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>That’s why I said reconsider. Back in juvie, I cut up oregano and sold it as pot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Is that how you put yourself through med school?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>What if Clarence thought he was taking heroin, but it was something else?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What “something else” could lead to anion gap acidosis?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Mudpiles.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, you don’t have to ask. Just wash your hands before you come back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-11"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Methanol, uremia, diabetes…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh, it’s a mnemonic. That makes sense, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-13"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Paraldehyde, INH, lactic acid –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Rewind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-15"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>INH?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yahtzee!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-17"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Drugs for tuberculosis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-18"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Nearly a quarter of the prison population is infected with TB.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Clever entrepreneur like Foreman here, chops up his meds, passes it off as heroin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-20"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>INH poisoning would explain all the symptoms.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Who wants to head over to the prison and find Clarence’s secret stash? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-22"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Fine, I’ll do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-23"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Great, Chase it is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-24"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I assume you have a reason beyond wanting to make me completely miserable?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-25"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You’ve got a prettier mouth. Better chance the inmates will open up to you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>Guy with bandages all around his face</speaker><content>Perhaps I’ll come out looking just as monsterous? I mean, isn’t that what I deserve? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>The man’s in a coma.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He didn’t mind. I asked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You’re getting crumbs all over him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Why do you think they put TVs in coma patients’ rooms, anyway?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Some people think they can still hear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So leave them a radio. His eyes are closed; who thinks they can see? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Do you know why people are nice to other people?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh, I know this one. Because people are good, decent and caring. Either that, or people are cowards. If I’m mean to you, you’ll be mean to me. Mutually assured destruction.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Exactly. You’re gonna eat these chips? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You gonna get to your point?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-12"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You need people to like you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I don’t care if people like me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-14"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>…Yes. But you need people to like you because you need people. Unless you think you can get the next court order yourself. If Stacy can’t trust you, you can’t use her.  And that’s not even dealing with the greater agenda –  of getting her to dump her husband and fall in love with you all over again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Look I know you’re friends with her, but there is a code. Bros before hos, man.  Crap.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-16"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>What is it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Death Row guy is dying.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Bradycardia. His heart rate’s dropped to 30, it’s not going to hold that much longer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Are you just waiting to call time of death, or are you gonna give him atropine?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Temporary fix?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Right. Don’t know why those diabetics are all hung up on insulin. They’re just gonna have to have to take more. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Atropine’s only gonna buy you a few hours! We don’t even know what’s wrong with him –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Just get out of here. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content> This is Chase.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Did you beat any confessions out of anybody?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I haven’t spoken to any inmates.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Does anybody do their jobs anymore?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I’ve decided Clarence’s life isn’t worth risking mine for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I appreciate your candor. Did you even go to the prison or are you just out playing polo?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I’m searching both Clarence’s cells. I figure, if he’s on something, it’s stashed somewhere.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Unless he finished it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Yeah, that’d be a shame. He could have shoved it anywhere, there’s envelopes stacked to the ceiling, bottles of copier toner, boxes of rubber bands </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Call it off. Come on back.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>What’s going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You’re dying.  A man deserves a last drink.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>You’re okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Thanks. That means a lot. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>Cindy</speaker><content>All the tests have been inconclusive?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Diagnostics is more of an art than a science.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>Cindy</speaker><content>Should I be worried right now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I work for one of the top diagnosticians in the country. We’re pouring all of our energy into figuring this out.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Thought you convicts knew how to drink. You’re at least three shots behind.  Now you’re four shots behind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>You better give me the next one or I’m gonna kill you. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>House –  I was just waiting for test results, I was…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Little busy right now. Getting my drink on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Unbelievable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>Oof. That’s the finest piece I’ve seen in ten years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I could’ve hit that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>And you didn’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Eh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>Then you’re the one that should be locked up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Tell me something, I’ve been trying to figure this out. Why does a guy –  – who’s on Death Row suddenly try to off himself? I know you drank that copier fluid. It’s not as visually dramatic as slitting your wrists with a homemade shiv, but it’ll do the trick.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-12"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>It just hit me all of a sudden. It was like, they tell me when to eat, when to sleep, when to walk, when to talk, everything. I had to take control of something, right? When to die, I figured that was as good as anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content> And that thought just came to you. Just like that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-14"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>Man, I told you. Twenty-three hours a – </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Mmm. Well, look. Here’s the good news. The copier fluid you drank contains about 90% methanol, which is very poisonous and you took more than enough to kill yourself. The bad news is the alcohol you just drank contains so much ethanol that it’s gonna bind with that nasty formic acid raging through your body, and you’re just gonna pee it out. Harmlessly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-16"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>Man, you are drunk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yes, I am. I also saved your life.  At least for now.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>Morning!  Your head hurt?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, you just have a very grating voice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>You always were a light weight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Why are you talking to me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>Can’t it be enough that I want to cause you pain? The patient’s okay now, you’re going to send him back?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Absolutely.  Can I trust you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>You used to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I still think the patient’s sick. I’m keeping him here. Now, either you can do your job and keep the hospital informed, or you can help me make sure the hospital is not informed and buy me some time. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Have you done a CT?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Yeah, I have.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>With contrast?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content> She’s done everything she needs to do except tell her patient that she’s dying. I told you, only I get to play with the markers.  Our prisoner has a new symptom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I’m not telling Cindy she’s dying until the diagnosis is confirmed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I’m not buying that CLARENCE is trying to take control of his life by suicide. Healthy people don’t kill themselves.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Healthy people don’t kill other people.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Guy just filed an appeal in a state that hasn’t actually killed anybody in about 30 years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>What if it wasn’t suicide? What if it was an escape plan? Drink enough methanol to get transferred to a hospital, try to escape from here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Excellent. Explains everything, except the symptom that got him here. His heart went nuts before he got stuck in that storage cell and chugged a toner martini. I think there’s something going on in his head. Check for intracranial lesions, brain infections, autoimmune diseases… do a CT, LP, full workup. State’s paying, so go nuts. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Where’d you get these scars?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>I got shived my first month in. After I healed up I got mines. You guys still think I’m sick?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content> Obviously.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>Why you care? Why don’t you just let me die?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Well, I’m different than you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>Right, you love me like your own mama. That’s why the nurse says you kicked her out when my heart nearly stopped.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Take a deep breath.  Any family history of mental illness?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>I always heard my pa was crazy; I never met the man. With my mom, it was the drugs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Any siblings?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-10"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>Got a brother, pretty much raised him on my own.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-11"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Inspirational story. He doin’ time, too?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-12"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>Hey. He’s a good kid. Don’t go judgin’ what you don’t know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-13"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>How’s his health?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-14"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>I haven’t heard from him since I went inside. Spent 16 years with him, changed his damn diapers. Can you imagine your whole life bein’ about the worst thing you ever did?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-15"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You killed four people. Somehow, making mac and cheese just the way he wants kind of loses its significance.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh no. Now you’ve left your entire body in my chair. What does that mean you want?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I need a segmental bronchoalveolar lavage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I take it the CT with contrast came back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>They’re not definitive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Biopsy would be.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Biopsy would be invasive and unnecessary.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And definitive. But you don’t want definitive, you want to hang on to your delusions as long as you can.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>A lavage could prove it’s not cancer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>But you need me to approve the procedure. Must be a bitch. The answer is no.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-10"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Why? Because it’s me? I’m over you. I’ve jumped on the bandwagon. I hate you, okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Great. Let’s treat her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-12"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>What is it? You won’t help Cindy but you’re obsessed with this piece of dirt! Are you just trying to prove that who someone is doesn’t matter, that all that matters is your stupid puzzle? Fine. Treat them the same. That’s all I’m asking. One test.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Wow, that is remarkable. According to those patchouli-oli selling new-agers, it’s supposed to be the terminal patient, but you’re going through the five stages. You just made a completely seamless transition from anger to bargaining. Cover two more of my clinic hours, and you can have your one procedure. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>No lesions, no aneurysms. Ironically, the mind of a killer looks completely normal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>If someone asks you to describe me to them, what’s the first thing you’d tell them?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Insecure. What are you asking?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Like, if you were setting me up on a blind date. Would you describe me to the girl as the black guy, a neurologist, car thief?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>This guy’s really getting to you, isn’t he?</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>There’s no sign of infection.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You’re gonna have to do the biopsy.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Your Death Row guy’s still here!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, sorry. Just gotta get him stabilized. Probably keep him on fluids for a few more hours, then off he goes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Oh yeah? ‘Cause I’m figuring that you still think he’s sick.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Figuring requires deductive reasoning. I’m figuring that you did no figuring. Stacy just ratted me out, right? So much for attorney-client privledge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>I’m the client, you moron. Stacy has a duty to this hospital.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>I’m sending him back to prison.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Whoa, can’t. Court order.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-9"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Court order says he has to be declared healthy. Doesn’t specify what doctor needs to make that declaration. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content> What is it, Clarence?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>My gut!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Would you describe it as a shooting pain? A throbbing pain? Or maybe an imaginary pain because you don’t want to go back to prison?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Where does it hurt?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>My gut, I feel like I’m getting stabbed! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, he’d know. Let me take a look.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Oh, so everybody lies except a convicted murderer. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I don’t think he’s faking this stuff. What do you think, Doctor? </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>I didn’t have any choice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, you had to tell Cuddy. She’s your boss, I get it. Hitler thought he was doing the world a favor, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>Yeah, pretty much on that same level.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Gandhi didn’t march the sea because his buddies asked him too, Pol Pot didn’t wipe out the teachers because he wanted to make friends.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>You’re not making friends right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I trusted you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-7"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>I know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Wilson’s a fool. I’m an idiot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-9"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>I had to do what I thought was right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It’s the only reason anybody does anything.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>The surgery went fine. They removed almost a foot of necrotic bowel. They’re shackling him and taking him to recovery.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I wonder. I wonder why Clarence killed that second inmate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Fine, I’ll bite. What the hell are you talking about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Everything we do is dictated by motive.  Why did he kill his girlfriend?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Because he’s a maniac!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Is that the reason he gave?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>She was cheating on him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Jealousy.  That gets him sent to prison, where he kills inmate number one. Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Guy attacked him first.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Revenge. Who’d he killed after that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-11"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Prison guard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Who had a file full of abusive complaints. Probably been kicking Clarence’s ass for months.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-13"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Clarence is just ridding the world of bad seeds.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Call that one “retribution”. Then he kills inmate number two. Anybody know why?  Nuh-uh. It’s not in there. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>All of a sudden I got to have a reason?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It’s an anomaly. Doctors love anomalies. Dark spot on an x-ray, bright spot on an MRI…. Killing that second inmate is the homicidal equivalent of blood in the urine. It doesn’t fit. I’m interested in things that don’t fit. Tell me why you did it. Your other victims you were almost bragging about. What was different about this guy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>It happened when I was in gen-pop. I was in the library, just readin’, and I started feelin’ real nervous. This guy was staring at me, I could feel his eyes digging holes in the back of my neck, it made me feel crazy. Sweat was pouring down my face. I could hear my heartbeat racing in my ears. I just raged out on the dude.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So what’s the differential for raging out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Excess testosterone, steroids –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Adrenaline –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Prep Clarence for surgery.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Care to share with the class.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh, come on. Do I have to spell it out for you? Pheochromocytoma. Actually, I’m not sure how you spell it.  But you said it yourself, adrenaline. Pheochomocytoma sits on top of the adrenal gland, randomly spits out oodles of the stuff. It’s perfect, it explains everything. The tachycardia, pulmonary edema, the vasoconstriction that caused the necrotic bowel –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Even explains how he had the strength to rip the rail off his bed. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>But pheo’s extremely rare.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I love rare. Set up an MRI. Where’s Cameron?  Like I don’t know.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Dr. Cameron? Could I borrow you for a consult?  Bittersweet thing about being head of the oncology department, I get CCed in all the biopsy results.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Yeah, I know. She’s terminal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Yeah. So I take it you were in there informing her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-4"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Well, I… I hadn’t exactly gotten around to that, but I was just –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Doing what? Making friends?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-6"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Cindy’s divorced. She doesn’t have any kids, no siblings, both her parents are gone –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>It’s not your job to be her friend. Do you understand? And it’s not worth it. She feels better her few final days, and you’re not the same, maybe for years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-8"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>You don’t think it’s worth it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I know it’s not worth it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-10"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>My husband w –  I met him just after he was diagnosed with terminal brain cancer. If I hadn’t married him, he was alone. When a good person dies, there should be an impact on the world. Somebody should notice. Somebody should be upset. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="34"><utterance uid="34-1"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>Pheo what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I don’t even remember. It’s just a fancy way of saying small, adrenaline-secreting tumor. Yeah, that clarified it for you. All you need to know is if I’m right, we can fix it. Just gotta to find it first. We need an MRI. It’s completely painless for most people.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-3"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>But not for me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I assume you got those tattoos in prison. Prison tats often contain inks with heavy metals. The MRI’s basically a giant magnet. It’d suck those metallic inks right out of your skin.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="35"><utterance uid="35-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Stop squirming. Don’t make us do this again. Big baby.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Still don’t see anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-3"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>Turn it off!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>There’s Waldo. Found it, Clarence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-5"><speaker>Clarence</speaker><content>Turn it off! Turn this damn thing off!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Keep him in there until you guys see it too. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Son of a bitch.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="36"><utterance uid="36-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Looks like they got the pheo out successfully. So what now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Clarence goes back to Death Row.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Just like that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He’s cured.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>That tumor caused random shots of adrenaline, which obviously led to the rage attacks that made him become a murderer in the first place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>My God, you’re right! Let’s call the surgeons, we’ve got to save that tumor. Put it on the witness stand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>We could testify at Clarence’s appeal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content> You smell that? I think that is the stink of hypocrisy. You wouldn’t even consider the notion that Clarence’s social upbringing was responsible for what he became, but now you’re sprinting to the witness stand to blame everything on a little tumor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>A person’s upbringing and their biology are completely different.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah. See, you only overcame one of them. Well, let’s just give Clarence a free pass, hmmm? Which, is probably going to piss off all those other pheo sufferers who managed to control their rage attacks and become lawyers, race car doctors, or even doctors. Removing that tumor puts a stop to those random shots adrenaline, it doesn’t absolve him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-11"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You want him to be executed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That’s not what I’m saying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-13"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Got an opinion?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Everyone’s got an opinion. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-15"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I, um, I think I’m gonna testify at Clarence’s appeal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You’ll do what you think is right. On your own time. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="37"><utterance uid="37-1"><speaker>Cindy</speaker><content>But it’s just a cough. </content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>