<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>
<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>MARINE 1</speaker><content>Take it Sarge, take it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content>Oh I'll take it! Baby babe  I'll meet you, same place, same time. Where we can, get together, and ease up, our mind. Do a little dance, make a...  Yo yo, turn that back on, turn it back on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>MARINE 1</speaker><content> Don't look at me cause you know I didn't do it all right? Don't look at me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content> Hey, you better have put fresh batteries in that like I told you to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>MARINE 1</speaker><content>I did Sarge, all right? The ones you gave me, I did, I put them in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content>Well then hit it or something. Otherwise,  you're all going to have to listen to me sing!  Son of a bitch!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content>Here.  Don't panic, and don't shoot us, don't die.  Got it G? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>Up and at em, you're supposed to be in clinic duty.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Yeah, like I could sleep down there with all the crying and coughing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content> Here. Ex-Marine. Thinks he has gulf war syndrome.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> There's no such thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>So he's been told, it hasn't stopped the unexplained fatigue, rashes and joint pain. And just so you know, he's the nephew of a benefactor I owe a favour, so you're going to take this case whether you like it or not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Why wouldn't I want to take the case?  The guy's tired and sore, it's going to be chapter one in my... </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content>Don't panic, and don't shoot us, don't die.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>You know him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Never met him before in my life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>Ok...Well you're about to. He's on his way here. Get your ass up and get your team together. You've got work to do. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>That's amazing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>No it's not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>It's not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I can play the harmonica with my nose, make a penny come out of a child's ear, or any other orifice for that matter; under the right circumstances I could bring two women into simultaneous ecstasy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>The right circumstance being their agreement to bill you on the same credit card.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>What I absolutely cannot do is dream about someone I've never seen before.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Just because you don't understand it doesn't mean it can't happen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>True, it can't happen because it can't happen!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content> Well maybe you didn't dream about this guy specifically.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Right, just some other guy who looks exactly like him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>No, you imagined some generic Marine then you placed his face in the dream after you saw the picture.  Sort of a coincidence mixed with a little déjà vu.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>There's no record of him ever coming into the clinic so I must have seen him before somewhere else.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Fine, you've known him since cub scouts. The more interesting question isn't what you dreamed but why?  I'm guessing you're longing for either a renewed relationship with your dad or a new relationship with one of the Village People.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>He was in the Navy not the Marines.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>I thought your dad was in the Marines?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>The guy in the Village People.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Actually he's only in the Navy when they sang, In The Navy. The rest of the time he's just in generic fatigues.  What? You brought it up!  You didn't flush.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I didn't pee.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Male, 34, just got out of the Marines after 2 years in Iraq. Admitted complaining of chronic fatigue, joint pains, intermittent rashes and sore throats. Thinks he has gulf war syndrome.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Why is he here instead of the VA?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Because he has a rich uncle that Cuddy is trying to avoid fellating and doesn't buy the VA's diagnosis of Nothing's-wrong-atosis. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>The VA is right, there's no such thing as Gulf War Syndrome especially in veterans who've never served in the Gulf War.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Different war, same place. Whatever was there in 1990 is still there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>That can send you home in a pine box but it still can't get you sick 3 months after you've gotten home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>What, so thousands of soldiers are lying about the symptoms?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>You send 700,000 people on a vacation to Hawaii some of them are going to come back sick, doesn't mean it was caused by snorkelling.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>He's right. Studies all show the same pattern of symptoms in veterans that were sent to the Gulf and those who weren't.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>That's it? You believe her but not me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Stick to your guns Chase. Just because there isn't a single unifying symptom doesn't mean there isn't something going on. Could just affect everyone differently.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>You think this guy has Gulf War Syndrome?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Course not. He's depressed and he's looking for a disability check. Most likely because he's just realised that knowing how to barter for sex in six languages and open a beer bottle with your eye socket are not the most marketable skills.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Why'd you take this case?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Because a good scientist continually questions his own theories and assumptions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Cuddy's making him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Now I'm making you. Do a full physical and recheck his blood for HIV, Hep C, Malaria, Schistosomiasis and T strain A. baumannii just to make sure the VA's dotted their i's and find out every hospital and clinic he's ever visited, every city he's ever lived in and... whether he's ever been on TV. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>TV?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> The problem could be neurological, everyone knows TV rots your brain. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content>It's usually the worst on my palms and the bottoms of my feet. I get these, black dots all over.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>I don't see anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content>It comes and goes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>You sure it's not just scrapes and bruises?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content>I know the difference between a rash and a bruise.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Sometimes it's harder than you realise to distinguish between the two. You obviously exercise.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content>My problems aren't caused by my workouts.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>But you do work out, and by the look of you pretty strenuously. That's not usually the case with patients whose principal complaint is chronic fatigue and joint pain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content>I was in the Marines for 12 years. I'm used to doing PT every day. Just because I can push through the pain doesn't mean it's not there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>We're not saying we don't believe you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content>The hell you aren't.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>We just need to be specific about what exactly the problems are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content>I sleep 10 hours at night, but I feel tired all the time. I constantly get coughs, rashes, sore throats. My knees and hips feel like someone poured sand in my joints. I get these weird tingling sensations in my legs, sometimes they're cold, other times it feels like my blood is boiling. Specific enough? Look I don't care what you guys call it, Gulf War Syndrome, Iraq fever or just crappy sickness X. I just want someone to figure out what it is so they can cure it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Except for the supposed pain in his joints none of the other symptoms he's complaining about are currently evident.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Besides low potassium, probably caused by him overhydrating after working out. His blood work's all normal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Low potassium could also probably be caused by the experimental vaccines and anti chemical warfare pills he was given before he deployed to Iraq. Not to mention the fact that whole country is littered with hundreds of tons of radioactive shrapnel from depleted uranium munitions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content> What did you go to medical school in France? There's no trace of uranium in his urine. He was given the vaccines and meds 2 years ago without any allergic or adverse reactions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Has he ever done any modelling?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>We forgot to ask. We should send his urine to the University of Leicester there's a professor there who's developed a more advanced screening technique for uranium.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>If the levels are too low for us to detect they're way too low to cause any damage.  Where you going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> This way. Did you find out about any television or other media exposure?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Do you really care or are you just trying to waste hospital resources to get back at Cuddy for making you take the case?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Of course I care, what a horrible thing to say. Do a Lexis-Nexis search and get a copy of his credit report.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Before or after we tell him to eat a banana and discharge him with a psych referral?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I say before. And I say in between give him a polysomnogram. Sleep apnea could cause chronic fatigue and paranoia. Find out where he went to summer camp. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Are you ok?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Yea just a little too much coffee this morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Were we... walking you to the bathroom?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> I wish.  Wilson was just in there. These guys know what I'm talking about. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>That's his third REM cycle and his breathing is completely normal, there's obviously nothing wrong with his sleep pattern.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>It's not uranium it's got to be some other sort of toxin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Or nothing at all. Do you really think there's something wrong, or do you just want Foreman to be wrong?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Both.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Well, it's not his sleep pattern. If you really think it's a toxin you can do a liver biopsy in the morning. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>We can't leave, if we don't monitor the whole test House won't accept the results, he'll just make us do it over.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>It doesn't take two doctors to monitor what's clearly going to be a normal polysomnogram.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Oh so you want me to stay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>You're the one that thought there was something wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>I never said it was a sleep disorder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>You want to flip for it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content> Just... go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Oh c'mon, don't be a baby. Fine, I'll stay.  You know what we could do... </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Why not? We're surrounded by empty rooms with beds in them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Yea and video cameras too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>So we turn them off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-18"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Yeah that's all I need is House or Foreman walking in on us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-19"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>We have the keys.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-20"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content> No, what if he wakes up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-21"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Alright.  Suit yourself. </content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> Damn it. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content>Hello? Is anybody out there? I think there's a problem in here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>What's wrong?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content>What do you mean what's wrong? You don't smell that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Nothing smells John.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content>Are you kidding me? It's disgusting!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>How long have you thought... Wait.  Open your mouth  The smell's not in the room, it's in your mouth. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>What's going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Good question.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>You were wrong about the nothing's-wrong-atosis, you can fake fatigue and joint pain but you can't fake bacterial vaginosis in your mouth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Where's his mouth been?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Says he hasn't performed oral sex on anyone for over a year.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Selfish bastard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Because he hasn't been with anyone since his last girlfriend dumped him after he deployed to Iraq the second time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Selfish bitch. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>We've ruled out HIV, diabetes and any other endocrine abnormality.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Could be autoimmune, Sjogren's decreases salivary flow creates a hospitable home for bacteria.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>No, his eyes and tear ducts are fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Who was his last girlfriend?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content> Yea we'll get right on that. Chronic fatigue, joint pain and opportunistic infection spells cancer, probably lymphoma. We should biopsy his tonsillar and submandibular lymph nodes</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Right about cancer, wrong about lymphoma. Unless you're simply hiding the fact that his lymph nodes are swollen. Get Wilson to biopsy his salivary glands. He's got parotid cancer, and see if you can get to the truth about who he's been dating, there's no way a Marine goes a year without getting some blood on his bayonet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>It's not an STD you just said...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Just do it. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>The antibiotics should at least relieve the infection, which will reduce the odour and taste in your mouth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content>Not soon enough.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>All right, you're going to feel a little burn. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content>You know I never even dipped. Chewing tobacco. Practically everyone in my unit did, but me. I was so paranoid about cancer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Well if it's parotid cancer it's very treatable if diagnosed early. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content>My mom had cancer, which is why I know that diagnosing cancer early means before there's any serious symptoms.  Certainly tastes like a pretty serious symptom you know?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>We'll know more after the test. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>If he was just trying to mess with Cuddy for wasting his time this would have stopped as soon as the patient started exhibiting actual symptoms.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>So the question is why is he wasting our time?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Or is he wasting our time?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>You think he's got a medical reason for asking for the guy's credit report?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>I don't. Where were you two when the guy woke up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Uhhh... we just... stepped out for a second.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>To do what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>To... get a coffee. We'd been up most of the night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>He's just pushing to make sure we get the complete history, obviously we're missing something or we'd have the answer. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>You didn't have any coffee when you came back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>All right already, we confess. You caught us, we snuck into one of the sleep lab rooms to have sex, we shouldn't have done it while we were supposed to be working and we're sorry, now can we move on? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>House would do Wilson before you'd do Chase.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>No you would do House AND Wilson before I do Chase. Now can we get back to work?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content> She did me once!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>She was stoned! </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Biopsy's inconclusive. I'm going to do a sialogram while we wait for the results from the additional blood work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>No hurry. Probably nothing we can do at this point anyway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Well if the cancer hasn't spread.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>He's spitting stink. You should focus on the living. I need a prescription.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>I just wrote you a prescription.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>For Vicodin, I need alfuzosin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>No you don't. You figured out where you met your Marine?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>What? Oh that, I haven't really thought about it. I can't pee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>You can't remember him can you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I can't pee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>So stop taking the Vicodin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I want to pee and not be in pain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Why don't you go to sleep?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I don't pee when I'm asleep.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Maybe you'll dream about him again and maybe he'll give you an address.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-16"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I haven't peed in three days.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-17"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>I read that REM sleep is the brain's way of working out problems.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-18"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Very useful, did you hear what I just said?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-19"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Yea you lied because you want to avoid talking about your obsession.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-20"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I'm not obsessing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-21"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Why don't you just ask him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-22"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> I haven't peed in three days!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-23"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>You'd be dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-24"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I'm not counting intermittent drips.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-25"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>You'd be in agony.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-26"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I passed agony yesterday around 4. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content> His mother, brother, uncle and best friend all confirm he hasn't had a date in over a year, which means it's not an STD. If you come up with something medically relevant, page me. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>What did you want me to tell him? The truth?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>No. You didn't have to be so convincing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content> Don't worry. I'll make it up to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>This is getting out of control.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Don't pout.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Our patient woke up with an infection while we were getting our rocks off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content> Do you want to stop?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>No. But I don't want to get caught either.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>You think I do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>You certainly didn't go out of your way to keep the volume down while we were in the sleep lab.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-12"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content> I couldn't help that... Why would I want to get caught?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-13"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Maybe you want to give House a reason to be jealous?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-14"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>I'm over House. All this is, is uncomplicated sex, don't try to make it more than that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-15"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>We're not doing it at work anymore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-16"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Fine.  Want to go grab some lunch?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>WOMAN</speaker><content> I think the pill is the way to go, we haven't had a condom break yet thank god, but it's bound to happen. Especially the way we've been doing it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>On a bed of nails?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>WOMAN</speaker><content>No he's not kinky. He's just insatiable. I can barely make it to any of my morning classes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> You smoke?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>WOMAN</speaker><content>No way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> Stop it! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>WOMAN</speaker><content> Sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Any history of hypertension? Blood clots? Strokes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>WOMAN</speaker><content>Nope. Besides my OCD I'm fit as a fiddle. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You have OCD.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-11"><speaker>WOMAN</speaker><content>Duh. Can't you tell?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Any other compulsions besides drinking massive amounts of water?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-13"><speaker>WOMAN</speaker><content>No. That's it thank god. My therapist says it could be a lot worse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You get up in the middle of the night to drink?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-15"><speaker>WOMAN</speaker><content>Yeah, every couple of hours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-16"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Then your therapist is an idiot. Unconscious people don't have OCD. They can however have diabetes insipidus.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-17"><speaker>WOMAN</speaker><content>That's impossible. I eat candy all the time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-18"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Different kind of diabetes. This kind is cause by a banged up pituitary. You're obviously more of a lover than a fighter I'm guessing either a car accident or... you cracked your skull on the balance beam.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-19"><speaker>WOMAN</speaker><content> How'd you know?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-20"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Easy, nice ass, no boobs, you got palms like a longshoreman. Wait here, you need a CAT scan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-21"><speaker>WOMAN</speaker><content>Oh my god.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-22"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Don't worry, just means you'll be taking two hormone supplements instead of one.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Ok, this time you're going to feel a little pressure, I'm inserting the contrast material.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content>Could you turn up the music?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Sure.  Looks pretty good so far.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content>Still can't hear it that well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Can you hear it now? John?  John? John can you hear me? </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Still no... relief?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I got relief. I just got no pee. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>If the pills didn't work you may need a catheter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You didn't come here to talk to me about my pee, what's going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content> He's got cancer all right, but it's not in his salivary glands, it's in his brain.  And it's bad, at least 6 tumours, maybe more. He lost his hearing, his sight's probably next.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Death is probably next.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>No way he could've grown all these in a week.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Any older, VA couldn't have missed all these.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Maybe they didn't miss them, just mixed them up. Switched his films with another patient's by mistake.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Maybe, but it means some poor sap's getting his melon sliced in the VA for no reason.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>This poor sergeant is going to be dead by the end of the week.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Where have you two been?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Lunch. Why, what happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Wilson's found some fast growing, illusive, or magic brain tumours. What did you find?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-9"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Nothing, he's telling the truth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-10"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>About what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-11"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>About everything. Where he's lived, who he's dated, besides forgetting to mention his dad's shin splints, his granddad's nosebleeds and to return a few rented DVD's, everything he's told us has checked out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-12"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content> You have them researching your dream?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-13"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Nope. I have them researching my patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-14"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>You had a dream about a patient?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-15"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>This poor guy's brain is riddled with tumours and you're checking his credit report?  C'mon, I need you guys. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-16"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Where you going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-17"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>To do my job.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-18"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>He's not your patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-19"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>He is now. Go home and go to sleep, maybe you'll dream the cure to late stage brain cancer.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>How is he?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>He's dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content> Oh god.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Least he will be in a few days. Question is why? The only explanation is that the VA hospital screwed up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>There was definitely no mix up I had them recheck.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Yes, why would a government agency lie to cover up a mistake? Might've caused the death of a guy they've been trying to kill for the last two years anyway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>They didn't lie  Did you just take two Vicodin?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>No, it was an antidepressant, I was told to take two every time you walked into the room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content> The VA scan of his brain. No tumours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Yes this has proved positive that someone didn't have tumours in his brain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-11"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>You see that bright spot below his left orbit. That is the titanium pin your patient had inserted 20 years ago. Unless you think the VA happened to mix up his scans with someone who had the exact same pin, they didn't screw up.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>You paged us?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Why didn't you send his urine to Leicester like I told you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Because you told me not to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Why did you choose that moment to listen to me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>You think depleted uranium might have something to do with his tumours?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Radiation's the only thing that will make tumours grow that fast.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>High doses of radiation. Even if he ate depleted uranium bullets for breakfast he still would have been exposed to less radiation than we've given him in the last two days.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Do it anyway.   And you, call his uncle back, find out if he ever brought his nephew to any hospital parties or fundraisers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-9"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>No. Not until you give me a reason.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Because... I'm your boss.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-11"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>A rational reason. Or at least admit that you don't have one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I've got a full bladder and I'm not afraid to use it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-13"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>But you are apparently afraid of discovering something that you can't rationally explain...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> SHUT UP! Do what you're told. Cuddy and Wilson may not have to listen to me but you do. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-15"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>What the hell was that all about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-16"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>I don't care. Which is why I didn't feel the need to ask him 8 personal questions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-17"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>I'm over him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-18"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Just making an observation.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>All right, ready whenever you are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>I'm ready.  Wait a minute. Zoom in.  I don't see it. You sure you got the right coordinates?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Yea she's in the right place. Go 10 millimetres above the ACPC line on the Z-axis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>NURSE</speaker><content>10 mil above ACPC on Z.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>It's not there anymore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Are you sure you got the gantry angle right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>NURSE</speaker><content>Yeah I'm sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>It's not there. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>It disappeared.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>6 tumours don't just disappear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Unless they were never there to begin with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>The VA didn't screw up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Maybe someone else did. Maybe it was Dr. Self-Righteous.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>I saw the tumours. There was no mix up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>Maybe there's something wrong with the portable imager in the OR.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Something that would cause it to show brain tissue in perfect detail but completely miss neoplastic tissue?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Then they were never tumours to begin with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>I told you I saw...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>No you saw something that looked like tumours. We all did. We were all wrong. Well maybe he doesn't have cancer maybe he has a brain infection that's causing multiple abscesses.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-12"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>That miraculously healed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-13"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>No, they were healed by the antibiotics we're giving him for the vaginosis in his mouth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-14"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>If it's an infection why didn't it show up in his blood work?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-15"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I don't know. Yet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-16"><speaker>NURSE</speaker><content>Dr. Wilson, we have a problem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-17"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content>What did you do? I can't feel my legs. I can't feel my legs! What did you guys do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-18"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>John, John, calm down. We didn't even operate.  Would this be a usual effect?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-19"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content>I can't feel my legs!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-20"><speaker>NURSE</speaker><content>It's not the anaesthesia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-21"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>John, John! We're going to figure out what's wrong with you, but first we need to know one thing. Have you ever appeared in any pornos?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Chronic fatigue, sore throats, rashes, putrid discharge of the mouth, multiple abscesses in the brain, hearing loss and last but not least lower limb paralysis. He's certainly given us plenty of clues.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>It's got to be some sort of infection.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>That's miraculously improving in his brain but getting worse in his ears and legs?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Could be an infection and cancer. Neoplastic syndrome could depress his immune system and cause the other symptoms.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Mm-hmm. You're basing this theory on the negative biopsy, the lymph nodes that aren't swollen or the tumours that were never there to begin with?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>And what are you going to base your theory on? His favourite restaurants?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>I was right. He's excreting depleted uranium in his urine. We should start him on an IV infusion of isotonic sodium bicarbonates.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>It's not depleted uranium.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>You're the one...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Who asked for the test when we were thinking cancer, we no longer are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Depleted uranium doesn't just cause cells to mutate it can cause cell death as well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Not spinal cord cells. At least not until the dose is high enough to kill all his other cells first.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-13"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>So you're saying the radioactive uranium in his urine is irrelevant?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> The sun is radioactive, the earth is radioactive, this hospital is filled with radiation. The issue is not where it is but how much there is, and what damage that amount could cause inside someone's spinal cord, as I've already stated quite clearly...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-15"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Got it, we're all idiots, what's your theory?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-16"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Give me your keys.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-17"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-18"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You ever tried riding a motorcycle with a distended bladder?  Keep him on antibiotics, check his hearing and paralysis every hour. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-19"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>So you basically want us to do nothing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-20"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>No... I basically want to do nothing. I want you to keep him on antibiotics and check his hearing and paralysis every hour. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-21"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Wait, you can't go home now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-22"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Actually I have to go home now. It's two days past my bedtime.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-23"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>House he needs your help.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-24"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>And I need sleep. Hey it's the brain's way of working out problems that the conscious mind can't solve during the day remember? </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content> No, nothing.  I'm going to die, aren't I?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>No, we're not. We should start treatment for the uranium toxicity like you said.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>But House...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Isn't here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>If House wanted to be involved in the case... </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>If he wanted us to start this treatment he would have told us to the last time you brought it up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>You have a better idea?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Then we're going with Chase's. </content></utterance>
</scene>



<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Tell him not to get the lines tangled. The infusion is slow we can't have any kinks in the lines.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content> I went to medical school too. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Keep your arms on your body, above your heart. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content> I can't feel my stomach.  I don't feel that.  I don't feel anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>The paralysis is ascending, if it keeps going we're going to need a respirator.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content>What? What are you saying?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Can you breathe? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content>No. Not yet.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>So, where were we?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>You have a nice night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>No. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>The paralysis is ascending. Last check it was nearly to his diaphragm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Tells us something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Means it's getting worse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Worse is something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Actually it tells us it's not the uranium.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Did we think it was?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>We started him on sodium bicarb to try and flush the uranium out of his system.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Great, now the fact that he's getting worse tells us nothing. Never thought it was uranium. For all we know uranium treatment is what's making him...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Sodium bicarb infusion wouldn't have any effect on...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>On what? Kind of hard to say what it would have an effect on if you have no idea what's there to affect.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-11"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>We had to do something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Well next time, go with something that has a chance of working.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-13"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Like what? Did you come up with some brilliant idea while you were warm and cosy in your bed at home?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>We need more information.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-15"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>How much more information could you possible want? We have a medical history going all the way back to his great grandparents. A non-medical history going...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-16"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>It's not enough.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-17"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>It's all we're going to get.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-18"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Want to bet?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>Who approved a sodium bicarb infusion?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Don't look at me, I was home in bed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>What's wrong?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>He's unconscious, his skin has lost all colour and his BP and hematocrit are plunging.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>He was only on the sodium bicarb...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>He's bleeding out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>He can't be bleeding out there's no blood in the bed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Fine, he's bleeding in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-9"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>There's no sign of bruising or internal haemorrhaging.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-10"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>The paralysis must have reached his diaphragm he's not able to oxygenate his blood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>He's not able to oxygenate his blood because he doesn't have any left. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-12"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>There's no evidence...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-13"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>The only thing that would explain...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-14"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>There's no reason for blood loss.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-15"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>There has to be a reason, he needs a transfusion. Get me four units of O negative stat! Now let's elevate his feet. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-16"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>He doesn't need a transfusion.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-17"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Nobody asked you.  In fact why are you even here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-18"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>Because obviously you need my help.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-19"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Get out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-20"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>House.  His blood obviously didn't just vanish...  What the hell is this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-21"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> Somebody must have spilled something.  Somebody else should be getting me four units of O negative stat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-22"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content> What the hell is that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-23"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>It's a urine catheter collection bag with a rip in it, what hell's it look like?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-24"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>What?  It's just urine. It's sterile. No one's getting me blood!  Why isn't anybody getting me blood?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-25"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>You're bleeding. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-26"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>House are you all right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-27"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Why are you even here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-28"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>I'm always here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-29"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>No you're not. There got to be a reason. There has to be. </content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>So, where were we?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>You have a nice night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Yes I did thank you. I'm guessing better than our patient. Probably due to his BP and hematocrit plunging. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>How'd you know? </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>The answer was staring right at us the whole time, as plain as the nose on our faces, or the nose on his face.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content>What's going on, what'd he say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>No hairs and cauterisation scars.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content> Which means?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>He had it cauterised.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>How could you know that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Because it makes sense, undoubtedly done to stop the same childhood nosebleeds that plagued his grandfather, undoubtedly because they were both born with Hereditary Hemorrhagic Telangiectasia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-8"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content>What's he saying?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I'm saying you got a genetic disease that is destroying your capillaries.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-10"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>That no one in his family has ever been diagnosed with before?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Not surprising, since the most common initial symptoms, skin rashes and nosebleeds, are often written off as the result of minor trauma or dry weather. But they can also be the result of his arteries and veins merging together. He obviously has AVM's.  An AVM near his spine caused the paralysis. AVM in his lungs prevented his blood from being filtered. Dirty blood caused the joint pain, fatigue and the infections in his mouth and brain. Nothing that a few surgeries won't clear up. Get MR angiograms of the aforementioned. The Marines weren't hiding anything, he was, or at least he forgot to mention his bloody tissue issue. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-12"><speaker>JOHN</speaker><content>What's going on, what'd he say?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Oh, looks like solving the case, solved your other problem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>There is no medicine like happiness, except maybe laughter, or rubber tubes shoved up your urethra.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>You cathed yourself?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>It's actually not that bad after the first... I don't know, 9 or 10 inches. Cath relieved the spasm. I'm as good as new.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Of course, just a minor spasm in a muscle you've been using multiple times a day without any problem for the past 45 years. Not a major side effect caused by the overuse of a particular narcotic painkiller.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> Yeah that was my thought too. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-7"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content> So, no reason to think about cutting back on your use of that particular pill.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Thank god. Actually it was a triple dose of the good stuff that allowed me to finally get some sleep and solve the case. The pills made all my dreams come true.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-9"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>You really got the answer in your sleep?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I got one in my sleep, the other one I got in the shower. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I've been thinking about you. You lied.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>I didn't lie, I simply chose not to share completely irrelevant facts.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Like the fact that you lied. No wonder I couldn't place his face. You were practically swallowing it on the dance floor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>I was not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Talk about the cool uncle, he donates the money while the nephew gets the write off. Of course by write off I mean he gets to put your ankles...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content> This is exactly why I didn't mention our one date over two years ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Because of my t-shirt?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-8"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content> Because you are an obnoxious ass. Because you would've spent the whole time...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>That's very smart, because this way I spent my whole time completely focused on the patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-10"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>How did you even remember him? We were only at that party for like 10 minutes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>What is this some new health plan? You service the Dean of Medicine and you get free health care for a year?  Why are you smiling?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-12"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>You remembered him because he made out with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-13"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I'm good with faces. So this plan, is it open to anyone? Is there a co-pay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-14"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>You're lousy with faces.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-15"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Don't make this about me, this is your humiliation. So how much for private room coverage?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-16"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content> Get over me. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-17"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Oh give me a break. You hired me...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-18"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>Because you're a good doctor who couldn't get himself hired at a blood bank so I got you cheap.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-19"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You gave me everything I asked for because one night I gave you everything you...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-20"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>Stop staring at my ass when you think I'm not looking, showing up at restaurants where I happen to be on a date and fantasising about me in the shower. That ship sailed long ago House. Get over it. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-21"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>If you're still referring to you ass I think that super tanker sailed would be a more precise metaphor.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Sorry, looking for an extra large trash can. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Since when does he clean anything up?</content></utterance>
</scene>

</script>