<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>
<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>You ok?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>AMY</speaker><content>Yes... my clip woulda veened.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>What the hell do you think you two were doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>AMY</speaker><content>We thought we heard someone in there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>You NEVER go in without authorisation!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>Captain this is all me, Amy just followed me in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>So torching your ass last year wasn't enough huh? You need to stop trying to prove how tough you are before you get yourself killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>Yes sir.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content> Go have the paramedics look you over.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>RANDOM FIREFIGHTER</speaker><content>C'mon Derek lets get this ladder to the 2nd story. Let’s go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>AMY</speaker><content>Derek! ... Derek!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>AMY</speaker><content>Derek.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>AMY</speaker><content>What's happening?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>I'm... freezing!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>I'm fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>ER docs don't think so. Your temperature is going up and down like a roller coaster. How old are these skin grafts?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>Last one was about six months ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>We're gonna run some tests and we'll get a consult with Dr House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>I'll be fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>You'll be doing what the doctor said, got it?  I'll check in later.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>AMY</speaker><content>Hey, the way you covered for me last night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>He's my brother; I know how to eat it from him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>AMY</speaker><content>I'm gonna stop by after my shift ok?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content> So where is this Dr House?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content> Speaking engagement.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Not guilty.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>JUDGE</speaker><content>And on the charge of gaining control of said medication by fraud how do you plead?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Not guilty.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>JUDGE</speaker><content>Very well, preliminary hearing is set for the 19th at 10am at which time I'll determine whether there is enough evidence to proceed to trial. The next case on the calendar People versus Williams charges assault 2nd degree with intent to cause injury...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>GEMEINER</speaker><content>You’re going to go talk to him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I was just going to ask him where he gets his haircut.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>GEMEINER</speaker><content> They have your signature, prescription log, a security camera video and a pharmacist’s sworn statement saying you stole the dead guy’s pills. You’re already looking at 10 years, you wanna add witness intimidation charge? Go ahead, ask him about his hair.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>He suffered 3rd degree burns over 54% of his body a year ago and arrived in the ER last night disorientated and shivering. Twelve hours, his temperature was bouncing between 96 and 102.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content> Why don't you contest the search of the pharmacy records?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Yeah you could argue it violated doctor-patient confidentiality.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Except that he wasn't the patient or the doctor, he was the guy who stole from the patient and the doctor.  This was the 3rd time he's been disorientated in the last 2 weeks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Running into smoke filled burning buildings can be a bit disorienting. Fortunately I have the cure, stop doing it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>He's not in a burning building anymore and he's still shivering.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>A hypothalamic tumour can cause vacillating temperatures.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>So could ER nurses who were too busy to notice that a patient likes both hot coffee and cold sodas </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>He tested negative for Hep C, TB, HIV, Lyme and his tox screen's clean.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>In case you hadn't noticed, not exactly in the mood to dance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>I'm not asking you to dance, I'm asking you to do your job.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>EKG showed arrhythmia, probably just a mild heart attack.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>No chest pain, smoke inhalation already explains the arrhythmia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>He was in the burn unit for six months and had multiple surgeries, could be a hospital acquired infection maybe MRSA.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Works for me, draw blood cultures start him on antibiotics, Vancomycin plus broad gram-negative coverage.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>If you called to see the design for my prison tatts, they're still at R and D.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>You need to talk to Tritter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Not according to my lawyer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>Your lawyer isn't going to be able to get the DA to drop the case, Tritter can.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Yeah, you know what else Tritter can do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>You're not impressing anyone. You may call yourself principled but what you really are is a stubborn adolescent idiot! This isn't his fault.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I'm not the one who--</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content> YOU used the rectal thermometer on him, YOU insulted him instead of apologising, YOU flaunted your drug use in his face and you REFUSED to accept a deal...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I accepted the deal!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>Not until after you stole a dead guy's pills.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Allegedly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>Tritter has been opening doors for you every step of the way and you keep slamming them shut. There are no more openings to give House, if you wanna stay out of prison you gotta make one for yourself.  It’s for Vicodin, You function better on it. Talk to him.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>MRSA is a bacteria that often infects hospital patients, the burns on your chest and arm exposed raw flesh that made you a wide open target.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>But the antibiotics will take care of it right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Depends on what strain it is, we will know more once we get the results back from these cultures.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>So this MRSA thing? Would it make everything look blue?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>He's seeing blue  where'd you get the script from?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Cuddy. Wanna know what I gave her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>MRSA wouldn't change his ocular palette.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Heavy metal poisoning could cause vision changes, particularly thallium.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>If it was thallium he'd be losing his hair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> So maybe it’s menopause.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>He's 28 years old.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Yes, his age is the reason it's weird that a MAN has menopause.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Male menopause, high oestrogen, low testosterone, explains temperature swings, disorientation, endocrinologically similar to female menopause but without the vaginas and mah-jong tiles. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content> Male menopause doesn't explain the vision.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Blue vision isn't a symptom, it's a side effect of Viagra, it’s right there on the label, which I have no reason to have read except that I'm a doctor, but then...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content> He's not taking Viagra.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You mean he didn't tell YOU he was taking Viagra, and I don't care how sick he is, trust me, he still thinks he's got a shot. Menopause causes temperature swings, limpness, limpness causes pills, pills cause the blueness.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>He's presenting no other signs of premature aging.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Aging's not the only cause, you said he's got burns to 54% of his body, sure it’s not 55%?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Burns to his genitals could cause testicular trauma.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Which could in turn cause...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Run a hormone panel, comes back positive pump him full of testosterone and send him home. And stop following me. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>Thank god my parents are dead, if my old man heard I had menopause I'd never live it down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>It’s nothing to be ashamed of, once these testosterone pills dissolve your system will be back to normal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>Yeah but till then I'm an old lady.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>AMY</speaker><content>Ok to come in?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>It’s not MRSA, he's not being isolated anymore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>Anyone not in a white coat is welcome.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>AMY</speaker><content>You're looking better, how you feeling?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>Good, it turns out I got some hormone thing, they're fixing it right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>AMY</speaker><content>You ok?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>Yea I think so I just... </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Derek you in pain?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>You need to get these out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>What's wrong?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>AMY</speaker><content> What's going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content> Looks like an allergic reaction.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content> Hold on we’re going to get you something to stop it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>No just take them out!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>You gotta calm down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>No get them out!  Get them out!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-20"><speaker>AMY</speaker><content>Derek! Derek let her go! Derek let her go!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-21"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>2mg of IV lorazepam stat!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>TRITTER</speaker><content>Complaint department's across the hall  I'm busy, can I just assume that you told me how unfair I'm being and...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> I'm sorry... You could throw a dart at all the adjectives between arrogant and unhinged and I'm sure you'd hit one that describes me. There's a reason I operate that way... I live in pain. Pain that on good days is merely intolerable and on bad ones will suck the life-force right out of you. Doesn't mean that I've handled this right, actually, means I was wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>TRITTER</speaker><content>Thank you. I know that couldn't have been easy for you to say. Even if you don't mean a word of it. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I'm sorry! You can hook me up to a damn polygraph.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>TRITTER</speaker><content>And I'm sure you'd pass. The thing is I've never been interested in what you have to say; all I care about is what you do. I'll see you at the hearing.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>It wasn't the medicine. Contamination and allergy tests both came back negative.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>And there's nothing to suggest a pulmonary embolism.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>And his EKG showed the expected tachycardia from the exertion of the attack ... and I'm fine by the way thanks for asking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Aggression comes on that fast, it's gotta have a neurologic basis. We should do a CT for frontal lobe tumour and an LP for meningitis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Great, have at it. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content> That's it, no challenging our theory, no tearing us down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>No need, you got it under control.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Where you going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Upstairs this time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>To do what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Check myself into rehab. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>Did Tritter offer you another deal?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Nope, this is all me. So no slaps on the back? Encouraging words...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>We are just trying to understand what this is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I hope this is me detoxing, otherwise I soiled a perfectly good pair of underwear last night for nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>So this is for real, this is not just a show for Tritter?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Absolutely it's a show for Tritter, and the Judge, unfortunately unless it's real, there is no show. Hey if it doesn't help my case at least I'll go to prison with heightened senses, all the better to enjoy my strolls around the yard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>VOLDEMORT</speaker><content>Going to need to check that stuff.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>When I lead the big patient rebellion, Voldemort here is the first to go.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>CT was normal, no frontal lobe tumour, LP was negative for meningitis, we're back to square one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>What about something vascular, polyarteritis nodosa.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Brain lesions would've shown up on the CT. Legionnaires explains the chills and temperature; altered mental status causes the aggression.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>We would've seen respiratory problems.  We're throwing darts; we need to go to House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>We need to deal with this ourselves.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>He can make the time, Derek's still his patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>The man's life as he knows it could be over. I'd think you of all people would wanna cut him some slack.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>We're treating a man who runs into burning buildings for perfect strangers. He didn't ask for what's happening to him. House did everything to himself, he's been cut more than enough slack.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Right now, House has more important things to deal with.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>WOMAN</speaker><content>That was the first time I'd seen him in months, I guess I was hoping he'd put his arms around me and tell me he understood, but he said he wasn't ready to forgive me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>THERAPIST</speaker><content>He may never be ready, you're doing the only thing you can do, keep trying. How about you Greg? You thought about how to fix things with people in your life?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>No need, people in my life have no expectations of me, makes all our lives easier.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>THERAPIST</speaker><content>Apparently not. The first step in recovery...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> Is admitting I have a problem, I've obviously already done that or I wouldn't be here. I've even embraced step 2, I've admitted there's a higher power, may not be a god per se... but that Andre the giant guy was powerful. Where I start to butt up against it is step 3, surrendering my will to this higher power. I'm sure Andre's ghost has my back and all but my free will, I never leave home without it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>THERAPIST</speaker><content>Kinda like your pills. If you could do this on your own I assume you wouldn't be here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> True.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content> Everybody lies.  His tox screen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>It's been clean every time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Exactly. It shouldn't be. He's had extensive skin grafts which hurt like hell.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Not everybody's House, people can handle pain without any medication.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-12"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>But they do have pain. This guy's worried about losing his job so he's hiding the pain. We find out where the pain is, maybe we find out where the problem is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-13"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Or he doesn't feel pain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-14"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Either way, it's something.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>When?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>NURSE</speaker><content>Two minutes ago pulse is 137, respiration 42.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>AMY</speaker><content>He was fine he was just telling me a joke...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Get her outta here!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>No fluid in his lungs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>O2 stats are 85, he's hypoxic were going to have to intubate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content> It's not his lungs! He's got marked ST elevation he's having a heart attack </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Pick a colour.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>VOLDEMORT</speaker><content> Medication time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> You are a ray of sunshine on a cloudy day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>He's stable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Won't stay that way, his blood test showed troponins and CK-MB up. Chase was right, he was hiding chest pain, he's been having a whole series of heart attacks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Heart attacks can't cause you to reach out and choke someone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Lack of oxygen to the brain causes disorientation, increased adrenalin causes rage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>More important question is what caused the attacks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Where you going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-10"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>To see House, we have a 28 year old with clean arteries, no valvular abnormalities, having multiple heart attacks. I'm not going to wait for Chase to give us another breakthrough.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Maybe we should go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>We don't have an answer yet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I'm fine by the way, thanks for asking! Whoever came up with buprenorphine to wean off Vicodin should be shot. And then stabbed in the eye  I think someone needs to adjust my meds!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>The heart shows no sign of inflammation or...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>The cause of the heart attacks isn't internal it must be external, something environmental.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>None of the attacks happened in the same place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Still must be something in common.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>First one happened in an apartment building fire.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Fire, water, smoke, oxygen masks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-10"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>The 2nd and 3rd ones happened here there's no fire, no water, no smoke.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-11"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>His clothes were all different he'd been cleaned.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>That's the what's, how bout the who's?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-13"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>His partner Amy was at all three attacks but...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Anyone else?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-15"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>People don't cause heart attacks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-16"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Well then you should be worried about proving me wrong.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Amy? Could you come with me please?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Anything new on my brother?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>We're not quite sure yet.  Could you come with me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>AMY</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>AMY</speaker><content>What's this all about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>I dunno, they wanted to talk to us together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>AMY</speaker><content>Derek!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>House was right.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>AMY</speaker><content>I don't get it, how could I be causing his heart attacks?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>You may be carrying an agent that triggered them. It could be anything. Mould spores, poisonous plant residues, something you picked up at a fire site. Until we identify the agent we can’t let you near Derek.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>AMY</speaker><content>I can't believe that I'm doing this to him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>You can't blame yourself for this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>AMY</speaker><content>You know how he got those skin grafts?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>He was trapped in a fire.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>AMY</speaker><content>We were clearing rooms in an office building fire, the ceiling collapsed and it cut me off from the rest of the group. I kept yelling that I was fine but Derek refused to wait for the team to clear the debris so he took off looking for another access point. He got caught in a back draft. He almost died because of me once. And now it's happening again.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You're not my mom, you don't have to keep checking up on me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>How you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Not bad, considering I just learned that I'm completely powerless.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>See this big fancy wing? It was built because this program works</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Faulty logic. This big fancy wing exists because some people with money think that it works. They wanna believe that they can buy a better world. This is nothing short of idealised despair, let people wallow in it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>I don't even know what that means.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>None of this means anything. It’s just nonsensical slogans and platitudes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content> Meaning takes time. It takes work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>What do you think I've been doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-10"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>You've been here for two days! Talk about wallowing in it. We all get it, we know how much pain you have. You're here to deal with that and get on with your life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Right! I should have an affair with a dying patient and move into a hotel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-12"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>You're a coward house. You find fault in everybody because you're afraid to look at yourself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-13"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Thanks, I was running short on platitudes, you can leave now. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>We tested Amy for about a dozen different agents but they all came back negative.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content> So she's not causing the attacks?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Derek, are you in love with her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>What does that have to do with anything?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Amy told me how you got those skin grafts, and the way you're always watching out for her, and I see the way you look at her  have you told her how you feel?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>She has a 6-year-old daughter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Women with daughters can still fall in love.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>I know, because she did, with my brother, they're engaged.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Broken heart syndrome, he's in love and it's killing him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Thought that only happened to 80-year-old widows.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Thanks to his menopause and oestrogen level he basically is an old woman, BHS is an acute physical response to an emotional experience, stress triggers a flood of catecholamines.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>That's a plain old stress cardiomyopathy, not a heart attack.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>But if you're too worried about losing your job to get it treated they can develop into full on heart attacks, you think it's a coincidence this started when Amy got engaged?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>No I don't, but now that you know the why what are you going to do to stop the how?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>I already put him on beta-blockers and nitroglycerin, no effect.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>We need to put him on antidepressants.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Not if you're right. Antidepressants would inhibit his autonomic nervous system, which would only speed up the heart attacks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>We could try propylthiouracil, slow down his metabolic rate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Thyroid effect would only weaken the heart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-12"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Only other option is blood thinners.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-13"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>This is not a fat guy with plaque-filled arteries and a swollen heart, he's a guy who's brain is trying to kill his heart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-14"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content> So buy him a girlfriend, make him happy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-15"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content> That might make YOU happy. The only thing that will make Derek happy is Amy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-16"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>So keep him away from her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-17"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>He has a myocardial infarction every time she walks in the room, what do you think will happen to his heart when we tell him he can never see her again?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-18"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>He needs a shrink.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-19"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Chase's idea is as good as any, I mean short of frying his brain and wiping Amy out, we're screwed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-20"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> We need Cuddy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-21"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-22"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>So you can tell her why you need to fry a guy's brain.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>The guy's heart isn't working and you want to shock his brain?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Electroshock therapy is the only way to erase his memories of Amy and stop the brain’s chemical attack on the heart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>This isn't 1940, the problem can be controlled with antidepressants.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Cameron. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Antidepressants would inhibit his autonomic nervous system, speed up the attacks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> LMNO, PTU, blood thinners, none of them would solve this problem. He's got a real-life harlequin romance in his head, were going to pull out the 1940s playbook. Bilateral electrodes, high stimulus sine wave intensity, turning that dial all the way to 11. It's basic brain chemistry, we interrupt protein synthesis altering the neurotransmitter system, the result, no memories, no Amy, no problem. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content> Go ahead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> You heard the lady, go plug him in  Am I really that pathetic? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>What are you talking about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>If I'd pitched electroshock therapy as a cure for broken heart syndrome any other time, you'd have dug in and maybe tried another 100 useless things first. So either you're actually beginning to trust me or... you just feel sorry for me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>You presented a reasonable argument. You were clear-headed and non-impulsive about it. You never once used the word moron. The rehab's working House.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>You'll still be able to perform routine functions like walking, talking, tying your shoes  the treatment targets the anterior cerebral cortex. It should only effect your experiential memories.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>So my parents, my childhood?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>If this works, you won't remember them, or your firefighting training.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>And Amy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Are you ok with that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>I wouldn't miss her right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Tell Amy how you feel, because if she loves you...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content> I won’t do that to her. Or to my brother.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>You're effectively killing who you are just to keep this secret.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-10"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>She doesn't love me.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>TRITTER</speaker><content> Caterpillar?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Lower intestine with ulcerative colitis.  You crash art therapy classes just for the adrenalin rush?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>TRITTER</speaker><content>Cuddy wouldn't get off the phone until I promised I'd come see for myself. I gotta admit, this move I did not expect.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Well don't tell anyone but the photos of smiling people in the brochures, it's just marketing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>TRITTER</speaker><content>Well you're obviously making an effort. So I suppose the next step is for me to talk to the DA.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Which you have no intention of doing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>TRITTER</speaker><content> No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>So words mean nothing, actions mean nothing, what the hell is left?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> You son of a bitch!  What about your words, your actions.  Gotta get House cleaned up, get him to show some humility, when it comes to actually doing something you prove that all you care about is bitch slapping a guy who refused to kiss your ass.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-10"><speaker>TRITTER</speaker><content>You ever trust an addict? You ever give one the benefit of the doubt? How many times did it work out for you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Yeah yeah yeah, I get it, so you were screwed over by your mother, your wife, your partner, but you keep sending them Christmas cards while you take it out on everyone else.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-12"><speaker>TRITTER</speaker><content>No more Christmas cards, no I learned. People like you, even your actions lie </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>I'm scared.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>I know, we're going to give you a muscle relaxant so your body doesn't convulse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>ANETHESIOLOGIST</speaker><content> Count backwards from 10.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>10...9...8...7... </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>What's your name?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>Derek.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-8"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Heart sounds good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-9"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Do you know what city we're in?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-10"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content> No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-11"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Would you be ok with a couple visitors?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-12"><speaker>BROCK</speaker><content>Derek, it’s me, Brock? I'm your brother, and when you get out of here you'll be staying with me. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-13"><speaker>AMY</speaker><content>I'm Amy. I'm your friend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-14"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>I'm sorry. But I don't remember either of you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>We've given him four rounds of electroshock, the charge made his voice a little higher but the EKG and BP are good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Going to give him his last round in the morning, then be at court for your hearing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Thanks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>I'm going to stay here, monitor Derek.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Thanks for the update.  My next condolence call is arriving, I'll see you guys tomorrow</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>I got you something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> Nice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>I figured it might help make a good impression on the judge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>It's not that nice... I had no business blaming you for any of this. I know you were just trying to help me, protect me, that's what friends do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-11"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content> Is this.... an apology?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Part of the program, if you don't like it I can stop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-13"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Not at all, it's just so... unfamiliar. Please, keep going.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-14"><speaker>AMY</speaker><content>He looks lost.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-15"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>It's going to take him a while.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-16"><speaker>AMY</speaker><content>Brock's pulling a double shift. He can't stand to see him this way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-17"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Derek's going to need him Amy; I know the timing isn't great with the wedding coming up...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-18"><speaker>AMY</speaker><content>What wedding?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-19"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Yours. You and Brock.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-20"><speaker>AMY</speaker><content>We're not getting married, we don't even date. Why would you think we're getting married? </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>VELEZ</speaker><content>When you first offered Dr House the chance to check into drug rehab how did he respond?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>TRITTER</speaker><content>He told me to get out of his office  I warned him that he could end up in prison and lose his medical license. If he was concerned he didn't show it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>VELEZ</speaker><content>So you continued your investigation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>TRITTER</speaker><content>Yes, which is what led me to the hospital pharmacy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>GEMEINER</speaker><content> Turn it off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> I told you never to call me when I'm on trial.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>The memories were false we fried his brain for nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Whatever was killing him before is still there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>We did an MRI  There's some slight hypoperfusion in the anterior cortex.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>VELEZ</speaker><content> What did you find when you checked the pharmacy logs?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>JUDGE</speaker><content>Hold on Mr Vickers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Thanks Your Honour  hard to hear.  You test for clotting time and LB function?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>GEMEINER</speaker><content>I believe this is a medical emergency Your Honour.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>His blood's normal and his heart’s pumping it up to the brain</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>But it's not all getting there, something's obstructing the blood flow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-10"><speaker>JUDGE</speaker><content>Dr House you were given adequate notice to make arrangements for your patients.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-11"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>There's no hyper-intensity to suggest a foreign body near the region, and no signs of infection or vascular malformation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>It's lower down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-13"><speaker>JUDGE</speaker><content>Dr House, hang up!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-14"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content> The cytology on the LP doesn't suggest a tumour.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-15"><speaker>JUDGE</speaker><content>Dr House! Now!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-16"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> Hang on a second.  Does your voice always get that high and annoying when you're angry?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-17"><speaker>JUDGE</speaker><content>Do you want to go to jail?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-18"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>No thank you.  Set him up for a selective vertebral angiography, I'm on my way. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-19"><speaker>GEMEINER</speaker><content>Dr House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-20"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>House, sit down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-21"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> Why? I'm bored, there's nothing I can say or do that's going to make a difference here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-22"><speaker>JUDGE</speaker><content>If you leave this room I will find you in contempt. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-23"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content> Get a recess. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Are you out of your mind?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>They said they wanted me there, but I don't think they liked me. His voice isn't high because of the electrical charges; it's another symptom of menopause.  His system keeps getting hit by women's issues, so let’s follow the pattern. What might obstruct the blood flow that's more common in women than men?  Is the catheter in?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Go back to court, we will let you know the results.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Shut up and wire him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> Centre the image in the interpeduncular cistern, keep it moving at 30 frames per second.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>You think the arteries are narrowing; you're going to need still shots which WE can do without you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>The problem is not how wide the road is, it's a guy with a squeegee on the sidewalk, flagging cars. That's what's causing the slowdown, we find him we find the problem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-8"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>He's wired.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Go!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-10"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Injecting the dye. Blood's in the capillaries.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> There! Mr Squeegee, spinal meningioma, pushing on the nerves to the vocal chords. Creates the voice change and that nerve just happens to live right near the meningeal branch of the vertebral artery, obstructs the blood flow to the brain, brain malfunctions creating false memories, memories cause love, love kills. And we didn't completely screw up; cleaning the slate bought us time to find the real problem. On the other hand, if we'd been better we wouldn't have needed the time. Schedule him for surgery, dig that thing out and he can start enjoying real misery instead of the fake stuff. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-12"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>House  I just heard that you apologised to Wilson.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-13"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Detoxing, I didn't know what I was saying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Excuse me  I have to go to jail. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-15"><speaker>VELEZ</speaker><content>What is your position at Princeton Plainsboro?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-16"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>Chief Administrator and Dean of Medicine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-17"><speaker>VELEZ</speaker><content>And you're responsible for oversight of the pharmacy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-18"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-19"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Sorry, didn't mean to interrupt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-20"><speaker>JUDGE</speaker><content>I hope you don't mind that we continued on without you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-21"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I said I was sorry there's no need to be sarcastic. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-22"><speaker>VELEZ</speaker><content>What is this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-23"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>That's our prescription sign out log from December 24th.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-24"><speaker>VELEZ</speaker><content>Does that appear to be Dr House's signature?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-25"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-26"><speaker>VELEZ</speaker><content>What has he signed for?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-27"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>A prescription for Oxycodone in the name of patient Larry Zebalusky.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-28"><speaker>VELEZ</speaker><content>And did the pills ever reach the patient?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-29"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-30"><speaker>VELEZ</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-31"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>He was already dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-32"><speaker>VELEZ</speaker><content>And Dr House knew this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-33"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-34"><speaker>VELEZ</speaker><content>So... Dr House had no legal or medical basis for acquiring that Oxycodone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-35"><speaker>VELEZ</speaker><content>Dr Cuddy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-36"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>He never got the pills.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-37"><speaker>VELEZ</speaker><content>It's his signature, the log is strictly controlled.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-38"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>Dr House did pick up a prescription but it wasn't for Oxycodone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-39"><speaker>VELEZ</speaker><content>It says Oxycodone, you testified...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-40"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content> I know. But it wasn't Oxycodone. Dr Wilson informed me that Dr House already tried to steal the pain medication of this patient. Which made it clear to me that Dr House was in a particularly vulnerable and desperate state. So I went to the pharmacy and I swapped bottles, Dr House only got a bottle with placebos.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-41"><speaker>VELEZ</speaker><content>I understand your impulse to protect a valued colleague.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-42"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content> I have it right here on the inventory report.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-43"><speaker>TRITTER</speaker><content> Your Honour she's lying she's obviously forged that report.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-44"><speaker>GEMEINER</speaker><content> In light of this new evidence...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-45"><speaker>VELEZ</speaker><content>If this is real why didn't she mention it earlier?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-46"><speaker>GEMEINER</speaker><content>I move to dismiss this case.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-47"><speaker>TRITTER</speaker><content>There is other evidence Your Honour.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-48"><speaker>JUDGE</speaker><content>Everyone shut up and sit down. Dr Cuddy why are you only now coming forward with this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-49"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content> I guess I just never expected it to go this far.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-50"><speaker>JUDGE</speaker><content> The witness is excused.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-51"><speaker>VELEZ</speaker><content>Your Honour you can't seriously believe...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-52"><speaker>JUDGE</speaker><content>Dr House please stand  my suspicion is your boss  my suspicion is you have better friends than you deserve. Rules and laws apply to everyone, you are not as special as you think. But Detective Tritter chose to make you so. Detective, I don't know exactly what's going on here, but I am sure that this man is not flooding the street with cocaine. I'm also certain that knowing Dr House, he must have done something to set you off but you're going to have to live with it. Given Dr Cuddy's testimony I'm not going to allow this to proceed to jury  case dismissed. Court is adjourned.  Dr House, you're still guilty of contempt for that little walk out earlier, you'll be spending the night in jail, and after that you’re going right back to your rehab, bailiff take Dr House into custody.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-53"><speaker>TRITTER</speaker><content>Dr House. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-54"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>So should I be looking for you in the shadows? Flinch every time a car backfires?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-55"><speaker>TRITTER</speaker><content>Good Luck, I hope I'm wrong about you. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>We got the meningioma. Your brain should start generating real memories again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>DEREK</speaker><content>What do I do when I get out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>You have people who love you, they'll take care of you... You start over. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>Surprised to see you're not spooning your way through the walls.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>So what do you say? How about a conjugal visit to celebrate?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content> There's nothing to celebrate House, you made me perjure myself -  fabricate evidence. You make everyone around you worse for being there. The only bright spot is that now I own your ass! When you get out of rehab, you're going to be pulling double clinic duty, giving lectures to students, helping me find donors and pretty much anything else I ask, you got it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content> Your buprenorphine. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You get these from the pharmacy or from Voldemort?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Voldemort, why? What difference does it...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-7"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content> That's Vicodin, he's been slipping you Vicodin?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>No... He’d be risking his minimum wage job to do that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-9"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>The whole time?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> My higher power said it was ok.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-11"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Nothing's changed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Nothing's changed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-13"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>The apology, you didn't need to do that to make this work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> Believe what you want.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-15"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content> Goodnight house, I'll see ya tomorrow. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-16"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Goodnight Wilson.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>