<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>
<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>Ladies and gentlemen, step around, step around, come on, gather ‘round, gather around, let me show you a little way to make a little easy money today, you understand what I’m saying? These are the blacks, don’t wanna follow the blacks, you wanna follow the queen, you know why, because she’s red, and that means she is hot! So you gotta find the queen, find the queen. The first to play is free today, so who wants to play? You look interestin’, my man, you wanna step on up? Come on, now, who wants to play? Oh, what about you, sweetie, you’re cute –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>All right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>--come on up! Come on up here and play. Cute girls win money all day. You look lucky, now you look lucky, now follow the queen, ladies and gentlemen, follow the queen, follow the queen. Ain’t no Helen Mirren, but this queen is for you. Which one is it, which one is it, which one is it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>It’s right there. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>Right there?  Beginner’s luck, beginner’s luck, I’ll tell you what, takes a woman to know a woman, takes a lady to find a queen.  Whoa… want to double up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>All right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>All right, we got a chance here, we got a chance here, we got a chance here. All right, here we go, here we go, all you got to do is find your queen. You will not win again, you will not win again. All right, here we go, here we go, where is she, where is she, where is she, where is she, boom! Can you find her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>Right there. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>This one?  She is killing me! She is taking all my rent. Anybody else want to get behind the good luck girl?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Young man</speaker><content>I can do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>You can do it? All right, you’re next on. Just get me a chance to recover and get my money back, or else I’m going to be out here sleepin’ on the streets and not just playing. All right, here we go, you ready? This is the last time, and I’m not messing with you no more, you’re taking all my money, girl, I’m not messing with you no more. I’m giving you one more chance, and this is your last chance, you got to follow the queen, follow the queen, baby, follow the queen, where’s she at, where’s she at, one time, I’ll show you one time, and there she is, boom, boom, boom. Pick a card.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>Uh, I can’t decide.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>You’re mean, just pick a card, make a decision.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>I can’t decide.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>Come on, any card will do, left, right, center… </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>I don’t… I don’t know!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>You want the right –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>I don’t know…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>The left, the center!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-20"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>I don’t know!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-21"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>Will you move out of the way and let somebody else play, then?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-22"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>I can’t… decide! I can’t!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-23"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>You wanna flip a coin for it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-24"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>What’s wrong with me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-25"><speaker>Man</speaker><content>I don’t know. </content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>Scariest thirty seconds of my life. I couldn’t do anything, it’s like I couldn’t move inside my head.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>It’s called abuila, the inability to make a decision or exercise will.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>Is it going to happen again?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>It’s part of a T.I.A., a Transient Ischemic Attack. Blood was cut off to a section of your frontal lobe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>Is that like a stroke or something?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>A little. What drugs have you taken recently?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>No drugs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Toxins are another possibility. You might have been exposed to something at work, for instance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>No real job right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Exposure can build up over time and lie dormant for a while. Where was your last job?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>Pet store.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Exotic pets?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>Tropical fish.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>And before that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>Unemployment. And before that I sold subscriptions on the phone. And before that, unemployment. Before that I worked in Jeans Gone Wild. Before that, unemployment. Before that I walked dogs. Before that…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Loss of free will. I like it. Maybe we can get Thomas Aquinas in for a consult. What caused the T.I.A.?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Arteries are clear, no sign of a clot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Could have dissolved. Most likely came from her heart, we should do a bubble study.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Clots are unlikely in a 28-year-old who’s not on the Pill. It’s probably a vasospasm caused by drugs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I don’t think so. She goes from job to job, maybe there’s some kind of ADD here. Help us pinpoint where the neurological –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>She goes from job to job because she’s a scam artist. She works just long enough to qualify for unemployment, then gets fired and gets high. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-22"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I still don’t think it’s drugs. Did you check for infection?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-23"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Her LP showed nothing, no fever, white blood count is normal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-24"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Could be toxic exposure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-25"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You’re the one always saying it must be drugs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-26"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You’re figuring she’s a minority, she must be snorting –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-27"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You know that’s not what I –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-28"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>She seems like a nice girl.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-29"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Come on, cut her some slack, her baby died of SIDS.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-30"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>This isn’t some romantic story of a nice girl scarred by tragedy. She’s a drug-using scam artist scarred by tragedy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-31"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>On the other hand, the tox screen just came back. She’s clean.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-32"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You’re wasting my time – he’s wasting my… [All three finally notice that House isn’t paying any attention to them, and is in fact walking toward Wilson’s office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-33"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Second ex-Mrs. Wilson wanting money?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-34"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I am no longer paying alimony; she wanted her independence, so she got her realtor’s license.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-35"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Market’s doing badly, she wants money.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-36"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Market’s doing badly, she’s moving into a condo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-37"><speaker>House</speaker><content>She wants –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-38"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>She wants me to take Hector.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-39"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Pool boy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-40"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Dog.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-41"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No longer interested.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-42"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>We got him on our honeymoon, so I’m like… other parent. But I can’t take him! My hotel doesn’t allow dogs, besides… I’m always here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-43"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I asked Cuddy to a play Thursday. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-44"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Oh, you… okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-45"><speaker>House</speaker><content>She said she was busy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-46"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>And you didn’t believe her, so you bribed a janitor, broke into her computer, checked her appointments –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-47"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I asked her as a test.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-48"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>What would you have learned if she’d said yes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-49"><speaker>House</speaker><content>A lot about bondage. She’s busy for me, but not for you. She’s not interested in the play qua play, she’s interested in you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-50"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>No. I’m not getting sucked into the vortex of your insanity again. Don’t pass me notes in class, don’t tell me to ask her to the prom –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-51"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You cannot see her socially. You’re leading her on!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-52"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I’ll consider that after I take her to the Hockney exhibit. On Thursday. See, she is busy. It’s not a date.  She enjoyed the play. I enjoyed her enjoying the play. The woman works hard, it’s nice to see her relax.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-53"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So all this enjoying is an act of charity?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-54"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I’m keeping the receipts for tax purposes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-55"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What’s life without the ability to make stupid choices? She needs her free will. Find out why her brain froze before she can’t decide to make her next breath. Find the toxin, run your bubble study. You won’t find anything, but I’ll get the office to myself. There’s a lot of porn piling up on the internet. It doesn’t download itself!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Hello, Mr. Foreman!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Good. You’re lucky you caught us, there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I’ll meet you outside.  Hey, Dad. Gotta go, but… why are you here? Everything okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You didn’t bring Mom with you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I know, we talked about it on the phone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You didn’t have to come.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I talk to her on the phone. She only knows who I am sometimes.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>So what’s up with your dad? Didn’t know he was going to be in town?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Building this old, there could be toxic exposure anywhere: asbestos, mold, the coloring agents in the old wallpaper…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Or it could be drugs. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I thought we ruled out…. Clean tox screen means drugs didn’t cause the T.I.A.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Drugs can be laced with toxic substances – arsenic, rat poison. The drugs wash out of her system, the toxins stick around.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Exposure can come about any number of ways, there’s no reason to assume drug use.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Absolutely, except for the crack pipe. I’ll test her blood for arsenic and rat poison.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You’d like that, wouldn’t you, when your dad asked you out for dinner. I’ll do the tests, you’re stuck with the family.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You like Hockney?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>You heard about that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Hot stuff, were the Venezuelan pictures.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>That’s a trick question.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yes, but you have no idea how it’s a trick.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>I like art. I’m open to new things. What’s the problem?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You’re going to a gallery to see Venezuelan pictures that don’t exist, but you won’t go to a play with me. Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>House, why is my social life suddenly red-hot? One minute I’m mushing along with the huskies as usual, and all of a sudden it’s global warming. You think you saw someone pick up a toy from the sandbox and suddenly you want it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Is that why you said no?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Maybe I just want a friend and Wilson is a safe choice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I’m not safe? Cool. James Wilson is never a safe choice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Going to a gallery, we’re not getting married.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Sure, you say that now. He always marries them in the end!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You can show it to me later.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Sure, I’m okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Yeah. Everything is great, Mom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>That’s why you brought the picture?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>That isn’t mine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>It was in your closet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>It belongs to this guy who used to live with me. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You might want to let him know he’s got arsenic poisoning. We should get a sample of his hair so we can see the extent –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>But I don’t do… I don’t do drugs… </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Get a crash cart in here! Respiratory arrest!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>Are you sure it isn’t from the arsenic? Dr. Foreman said I was poisoned.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Your hair showed only a trace amount, not enough to damage your lungs like this. We need you to stay still now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>6 mm cuts, started at the apexes. Also, I just wanted to let you know, should you change your mind, I’ll be available.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Aren’t you getting tired of hearing me say it? I have no intention of going out with you, having sex with you, doing anything with you, except work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You don’t have to make a big deal about it, I just thought I’d let you know. I decided Tuesdays would be a good day to do that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>You did not suddenly fall in love with me. You were looking for something, and I happened to be st –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Cameron, it’s fine. No need to go on about it. Advancing through the lung bases.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>We need to put this behind us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Understood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>But you keep bringing it up!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You’re the one who’s still talking. Look, I’m not demanding anything from you, I’m not following you home, I’ve got no expectations. A gentle, polite reminder once a week is hardly stalking. There’s a mass just outside the lingual.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Biopsy shows there are white blood cells in the walls of the blood vessels.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>They’re not supposed to get past the bouncers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>It’s got to be autoimmune, something lymposidic. White blood cells are attacking her own body.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The only question is what kind of autoimmune.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Doesn’t matter what kind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It always matters what kind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Treatment is always steroids.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Treatment is always boring! Diagnosis is –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Okay. It’s affecting the larger blood vessels, so it’s gotta be giant cell arteritis. I’ll start her on steroids. It’s affecting her smaller blood vessels, it’s gotta be lupus vasculitis. I’ll start her on steroids. It’s affecting –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, got it. Start her on steroids.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Good idea. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Told you. That was boring. I gotta go out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Wilson’s got a date.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Bonnie</speaker><content>It’s got 15 foot ceilings, an open floor plan…. You know, I can’t believe you called me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Hey, I need a condo. Didn’t you and Wilson have your first date around here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Bonnie</speaker><content>Wow, you remember where our first date was? I didn’t think you were paying attention.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Really? He’s my best friend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Bonnie</speaker><content>Our first date was in Boston.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh. Not quite as close to here as I remembered.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Bonnie</speaker><content>But we’re not here to talk about him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Absolutely not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Bonnie</speaker><content>Wait ‘till you see the kitchen. All granite countertops…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Since I wasn’t paying attention back then, what was it like dating him?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>So this is Hockney?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>No. I don’t know what happened.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>I’m sure you don’t. I never knew your tastes were so ecletic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Oh, the Hockney exhibit finished on April 20th, I thought it was May 20th. Okay, my bad. This is not somewhere I’d bring someone on a date. Not that this is a date, obviously. I was just thinking… he’s doing landscapes on multiple canvases now, and they’re kind of peaceful, and you’re always busy, and…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Wow. I don’t think I’ve ever seen you embarrassed before.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Bonnie</speaker><content>Oh, it was never a date. I was coming off a bad relationship and he said we could go out as friends, you know, go see plays, go to a museum. I didn’t think you liked Trenton.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Love it. So he’d say it’s not a date, but then he’d jump you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Bonnie</speaker><content>Oh no, he meant it. James Wilson, carefully calibrating his level of protectiveness for your individual needs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Did you just compare Wilson to a tampon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Bonnie</speaker><content> No. It was very endearing. He really just wanted to be a friend, so I jumped him. The bedroom’s through here.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>That’s such a bad idea. There’s no way that won’t cause damage to the large intestine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Are you keeping us here to torture me?  Is that a bicycle pump?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>That’s what I’m saying!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>Bonnie</speaker><content>It’s like walking into a sticky trap. Once you’re the focus of all that attention, it’s addictive. This unit’s kitchen’s got a chef’s oven.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I cook a lot. Go on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>Bonnie</speaker><content>It’s the emotional stuff that really sucks you in. He’s just so knight-in-shining armor, you know? Always there to support you, until he’s not, but by then you’re hooked. Hey, do you think you could talk to him about taking the dog? He’s the only one that Hector really gets along with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Hey hey, we’re here to talk real estate, not Wilson. So you’re saying if you actually had sex before you connected emotionally, you’d have gotten over it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>Bonnie</speaker><content>Oh yeah, it seems weird, doesn’t it? Because sex with James is fantastic. Nobody works harder to give a woman what she wants. It’s got six burners. The chef’s oven.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Right.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>How’re you feeling?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>That wasn’t my crack pipe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You told me. Are you tired?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>I just took a hit off of it a couple of times. What’s wrong with having a little fun?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Your personal life is none of my business.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>You don’t like me, though, do you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>That’s your imagination. I’ve seen every account of drug abuse… no offense, but you don’t even stand out of the pack.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>I’m betting you got money the same place you got attitude. You know, people who quit drinking and people who lose weight, they think they’re better than the people who couldn’t, and because you got out of the projects, you think that anybody who didn’t is weak and stupid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I’m not judging you, now take a breath.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>The only difference between me and you is that I made some bad decisions, and you made some good ones.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-11"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You make bad decisions every day of your life. Stop doing drugs, stop having fun, go back to school and get your G.E.D.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-12"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>Yeah, where’s the money coming from? The system’s not set up for people like me. What are you staring at?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-13"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Your eyes. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-14"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>There’s yellow in the sclera. Her liver’s failing. Without a transplant she’ll be dead in the next 48 hours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-15"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We should increase her immunosuppressants and treat her more specifically – .</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-16"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Give her more of what’s not working. This is not an autoimmune disease.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-17"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Her white blood cells are attacking her body. That’s autoimmune.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-18"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>First brain, then lungs, now liver. All getting worse and all in two days. It’s moving too fast! It’s got to be cancer – lymphomatoid granulomatosis. It’s rare even by our standards, but it fits her symptoms. Explains why the steroids aren’t working, the poor fingernail growth –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-19"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>A lot of people have bad fingernails!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-20"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>A lot of people don’t have three organ systems shutting down! Her blood vessels are taking this thing everywhere. She needs total body radiation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-21"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>We can’t do anything until we can confirm –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-22"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Running those immunochemstries can take a week, she’ll be dead by the time we –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-23"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>That doesn’t make radiation any safer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-24"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Okay. Suppose Chase and Cameron are right. Suppose it’s an autoimmune disease. What’s the biggest danger of total body radiation? It suppresses the immune system, which is what we’re trying to do with the steroids anyway!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-25"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I don’t usually put out on the first date, but I gotta say, that is a rad move. Get her consent. Start the radiation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-26"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>The patient is not too thrilled with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-27"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I’ll get her consent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-28"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Foreman’s got a personality issue, so you’re going to step in?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-29"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Patient doesn’t like Foreman. I’m interested.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-30"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Fatigue, hair loss, possibility of damage to the lungs, infertility. All possible side effects of radiation. Why don’t you like Dr. Foreman?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-31"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>He thinks he’s better than he is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-32"><speaker>House</speaker><content>How good is he?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-33"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>I don’t know. Can we get back to what’s wrong with me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-34"><speaker>House</speaker><content>There’s a small possibility of leukemia some time in the future. Hardly worth mentioning. You can’t say he’s better than he is if you don’t know how good he is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-35"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>No one’s as good as he thinks he is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-36"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I am. You might also get cataracts. Sign here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-37"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>I don’t know. You’re telling me how dangerous this is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-38"><speaker>House</speaker><content>We’re saving your life. We’re that good. Sign there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-39"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>I can’t decide.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-40"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Would you rather a pencil or a pen? Who’s the better James Bond, Sean Connery or Daniel Craig? Now, you see, that’s not even a decision.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-41"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>It’s happening again. I can’t… I can’t…  Up her blood thinners, get her down to radiology. The attack will be over in 20 minutes. And then she’ll want to sign this.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Bonnie called last night to talk about the dog. Your name came up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Good lord, how do you still have teeth?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>She’s the worst realtor in New Jersey. What is this, escalation? I go out with Cuddy, you hook up with my ex? I don’t even know what that’s designed to do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You’re an addict. I’m saving you from yourself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>By condo shopping, thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If I can figure out where you keep going wrong, then I can nip this Cuddy thing in the bud before she becomes the fourth ex-Mrs. Wilson.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Yes, I was worried there was no way to stop that train.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You have to have sex with Cuddy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Wait… to stop the train?  Bonnie said  I’m bad in bed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Huh?!  Yeah. She also said if she slept with you before she liked you, then it would have been easier to handle when you turned into the sorry bastard that left her alone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-11"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I told her you were wasting her time, by the way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You think that’s going to stop her? The woman’s the worst realtor in New Jersey.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>How do you feel?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>Weak, sleeping all the time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>That’s normal after radiation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Deep breath.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>A little queasy, too. When I feel sick to my stomach I always want vanilla ice cream, it’s soothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>It’s best to stick with liquids for now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Shhh. I’m getting a murmur.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>Oh, oh my arm! It’s hurting me! Take it off! Take it off! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Pain isn’t the issue. Just the pressure of the BP cuff was enough to start her screaming.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-10"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>That’s not cancer. It sounds like…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It sounds like she’s septic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-12"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>A lot of things can cause pain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>How much?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-14"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Too much.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-15"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>It’s not cancer, it’s not autoimmune. It’s an infection and we fried her immune system.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-16"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>But she had no fever. Her LP was clear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Do an echo to confirm it’s in her heart, and then I’ll tell our patient that we just killed her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-18"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I’ll tell her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-19"><speaker>Bonnie</speaker><content>Oh, great. You haven’t been returning my phone calls.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-20"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I’m busy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-21"><speaker>Bonnie</speaker><content>Well, um, but if you have half an hour this afternoon, I just found this unit, it hasn’t been on the market yet –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-22"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I’m off the market for condos.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-23"><speaker>Bonnie</speaker><content>James was right. I never had the teeniest chance of selling you anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-24"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Of course he was right. He doesn’t stop giving good advice just because you’re divorced. He’s compulsive about remaining on good terms with his exes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-25"><speaker>Bonnie</speaker><content>Do you want to know why I named that dog Hector?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-26"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No. Let’s keep it a mystery.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-27"><speaker>Bonnie</speaker><content>Because even when he was a puppy, he was the worst-tempered dog we’d ever seen he. He was supposed to be house-trained, but he’d pee on the carpet every morning. When we had people over, he would nip at their ankles. “Hector does go rug” is an anagram for “Doctor Greg House” – that’s how early in the marriage I resented you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-28"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Wow. Did I ever waste money on that place setting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-29"><speaker>Bonnie</speaker><content>James at least had the decency to feel guilty when he hurt me!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-30"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Whereas I never hurt you! I never even married you, cleverly hoping to avoid moments like this one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-31"><speaker>Bonnie</speaker><content>You always needed him, and he was always there for you!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-32"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You keep yelling, and I’ll think you owe me sex.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-33"><speaker>Bonnie</speaker><content>You knew he had a wife waiting at home, you didn’t care. I’m not saying you broke up the marriage, but you didn’t help.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-34"><speaker>House</speaker><content>First, “Hector does go rug” is a lame anagram. You want a better one for “Gregory House”: “Huge ego, sorry”. Second, find a new career. You’re never going to sell to anybody if you let them control the agenda. And third, I don’t owe you anything. I’m not Wilson, I’m not going to buy a condo just to make you feel better.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Yeah. Tell me how to do this. House says people thank you after –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>It’s not typical.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I already killed this woman. All I can do now is not make any more mistakes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>First of all, stop thinking you can minimize the hurt. A lot of people are afraid of the word ‘dying’ – if you pussyfoot around it, she’s not going to read your mind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>No, it’s not. When you look in her face, you’re going to feel the instinct to temporize. Crush it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Then wait. Give her time to process the news. Let her know you’ll be with her through all of it. Wait ‘till she’s done thinking, until you think it’s appropriate, then maybe you can touch her, put your hand on her arm like this, let her know that she’s still connected to another human being.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-10"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You’ve got this down to a science.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-11"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You’re freaking out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-12"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I told you –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-13"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Give her what she needs. What she doesn’t need is a doctor who’s not there with her because he made the wrong call. You are freaking out. You should be freaking out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-14"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I won’t let her see it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-15"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Let her see it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>Hey. How come no mask?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>We think… we think you have an infection.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>Didn’t the radiation work?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>It did what it was supposed to do. You’re dying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>What, what do you mean, like some day things are bad, and I’m gonna…  How much time? How much time?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>We can’t know exactly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>A year? Less than a year?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Less than 24 hours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>I don’t understand. Why are you sayin’ this to me, you tryin’ to scare me? Why would you do that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I’m sorry. It’s true.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-11"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>How bad is this cancer? Yesterday you thought I had a chance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-12"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You don’t have cancer. You came in with an infection. We didn’t catch it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-13"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>What kind of infection?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-14"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>It doesn’t matter. The radiation was the worst thing we could have done. We destroyed the part of your body that was fighting it off. It spread to your heart –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-15"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>Then give me drugs! They have drugs for infections.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-16"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Antibiotics work with the immune system, but your immune system is non-existent because of the radiation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-17"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>If it’s my heart, you can get me a new heart. People have heart transplants all the time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-18"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>It wouldn’t help. The infection’s everywhere. There’s nothing we can do. I’m so sorry. We’ve called your grandparents.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-19"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>Get the hell away from me! Get out! Get out! </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I think it’s broken.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Nothing like a melodramatic gesture to solve everything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>We were wrong, too. Steroids wouldn’t have helped her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I didn’t help her, I pulled the trigger.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>There’s nothing left for you to do. One of us could go home with you –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Are you trying to make me feel better?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I killed a woman, don’t you think it’s appropriate I feel like crap for at least a little while?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-9"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>It won’t help you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-10"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Where is he?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-11"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>He went to the ICU.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>What are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Prepping for an aspiration. We still don’t know what infection –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>It’s not going to help her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It’s not going to hurt her. Well, it is going to hurt her, but –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>This will just take a few minutes. Grab a piece of an abscess, some pus –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You really don’t care.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You really don’t care why she’s going to be dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>She’s going to be dead –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>WHAT? What did we screw up, what did we miss? I need to know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You’ll have to wait. We’re moving her back to her room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-12"><speaker>Nurse</speaker><content>Patients who’ve had total body radiation have to stay in ICU.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-13"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>ICU isn’t gonna help her. Let’s give her some privacy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-14"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>What do you want? Wanna see if I’m dying on schedule? Or do you want me to tell you it’s all right, I’m okay with it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-15"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I’d like your forgiveness, but I don’t expect it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-16"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>Good, ‘cause this isn’t like you ran your cart into mine at the supermarket.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-17"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>No. Your grandparents haven’t arrived yet. If they don’t make it on time, is there anything you’d like me to tell them?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-18"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>Never really knew them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-19"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You got any friends you’d like me to call?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-20"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>It’s the middle of the night. They’re not the kind of friends you call to ask you move, let alone watch you die. I never did much. No kid to leave behind. When I leave, the world’s not gonna be any different. Kind of a relief for you, huh? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-21"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You were right about me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-22"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>Yeah, which time?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-23"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I, uh, I had a problem with you. But you were wrong, too. I’ve made some bad decisions. Stole cars, robbed houses.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-24"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>Killed a woman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-25"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>But then I got another chance. Left home, went to college, entered a whole ‘nother world. And yet some part of me I can’t get rid of thinks, “If I’m not the smartest, if I’m not the first, everywhere I go, they’ll figure out I’m not supposed to be here.” They’ll send me back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-26"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>You know that’s not going to happen. You’re out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-27"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I’ll never be out of there. When I came home, that last Christmas I was in college, it was like… the rooms felt so small. It was so suffocating. But when I was standing on the stoop saying goodbye, my mom put her arms around me. That was the last time I ever felt at home. I only put distance between you and me because I know there isn’t any.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-28"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>You were right about me, too. That stuff about the system being against people like me, I know it’s crap. I mean, it’s true, but it’s also crap. I just wasn’t ready to try again. But I always thought I was young, I had time.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>Lupe</speaker><content>Aren’t you ever gonna leave?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Time of death, 3:35. Do whatever you want.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You want to go get drunk?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>No thanks. I’ve got paperwork.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Listen, I don’t… I don’t know what I believe, but sometimes I need to think there’s something out there paying attention. So when I can’t talk to anybody, I talk to God, and pretend somebody’s listening. We were all wrong, Foreman. Even House was wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I got your consent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Her bra hook.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>She scratched herself with her bra hook. That’s how the infection got in. Staph aureus.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>She died from a simple Staph infection?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That and some bad decisions.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I’ll be outside.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Go home, have a few drinks, go to sleep, get up tomorrow, and do it tomorrow, only better. If you need absolution, go to a priest or give alms to the poor, whatever ritual comforts you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I killed her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, me too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>This wasn’t, “oh, I should have thought of that idea sooner”. This wasn’t messing up a dosage. We see a disease rushing down on someone like a train, we can’t always get them out of the way. But this wasn’t that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No. And you’ll do it again. To a lot of doctors, this would be a once-in-a-lifetime kind of mistake. But we’re not a lot of doctors. We’ll save a lot more patients than the guy down the street, but a few of the ones he’d save by doing what everyone else does we will lose.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>So you’re giving me numbers?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Because they don’t lie. I can’t forgive you, Foreman, because there’s nothing to forgive. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>What’d you tell him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That guilt is irrelevant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You wanna get something to eat? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Can’t. I’ve got a dog waiting at home.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I did something bad, Mom. I hurt somebody.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>It was.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Do you know who I am, Mom? It’s Eric. </content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>