<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>
<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>Big Eye this is Cobra zero-six, just entered Indian country, approaching wave .4, request confirmation to engage target on first approach.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>BIG EYE</speaker><content>Roger Cobra zero-six, Big Eye waiting for confirmation as well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>If you wait any longer Big Eye, we're not going to have a choice in the matter, I can't exactly do a U-turn here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>BIG EYE</speaker><content>Roger that, Cobra, hold for confirmation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>MAN</speaker><content>Captain Cooper, are you okay? What happened? You weren't answering.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>GRETA </speaker><content>Because the damn com cord got disconnected! You spend a billion dollars on the avionics and don't bother to check the com connection?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>MAN</speaker><content>No, I checked that twice before you got in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>GRETA </speaker><content>And the next time you ask us to test a prototype, it'd be nice if your direction gyro didn't spin like a top when I'm supposed to be 500 feet off the floor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>MAN</speaker><content>I'm sorry. I'll go review the simulation, see if I can figure out what went wrong. </content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Who is this man? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>C'mon, take a shot. I'm not going to fire you every time you get a wrong answer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>23</speaker><content>Neville Chamberlain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You're fired.  Does this man look like he's ceding Czechoslovakia to a fascist dictatorship?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>26 </speaker><content>It's Buddy Ebsen, the actor, he's dead. Why are we...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>HOUSE </speaker><content>Buddy Ebsen was the original tin man in the Wizard of Oz, for a day. He was diagnosed allergic to the aluminium dust in the make-up. His lungs failed, he nearly died, question is, why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>11 </speaker><content>Didn't you just say he was allergic?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>HOUSE </speaker><content>You may not have legs, but you've got ears, I suggest you use them. I said he was diagnosed allergic.  Since we are currently short exactly one interesting patient, we are going to figure out what really happened to Buddy Ebsen in 1938. Now on one hand he's not getting deader, on the other hand your jobs hang in the balance. So... </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>House? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I want seven alternate diagnoses when I get back. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>Did you forget how to count to three?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I've got a budget for three, doesn't mean I can only hire three.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>Actually that's exactly what it means.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I cut the permanent salaries by 10 percent, over 3 years that'll more than make up for the breakage on the 27 that I'm going to weed out over the next few weeks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>There's forty people in there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Row D, you're fired.  I didn't actually count all the resumes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>This is stupid, you can't manage that many people, you're just going to keep weeding them out arbitrarily.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Sure.  and having them sitting in my office schmoozing about their favourite Algerian surfing movies, that's a much better system. Wait a sec.  Were you in Row D?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>19</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>My apologies, my boss says I'm being arbitrary and stupid.  Row D is not fired, Row C is fired.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>19</speaker><content>Great, thank you. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-22"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>See? That was not arbitrary.  Well, I'd love to chat but I've been paged.  That's interesting, apparently paged myself. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>If you have a resumé there I'm not interested, but I wouldn't mind hearing how you got my pager number.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>It's not a resumé.  50,000 dollars.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Does One-eyed Nicky want me to run that to Jimmy the Nose?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>It's for my medical bills.  I need you to find out what's wrong with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> Insurance is usually cheaper than that. Cash means there's something to hide.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>I'm a captain in the Air Force about to start a new assignment. NASA's astronaut training program.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I discovered salt and created FM radio.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>Something is wrong. With my eyes, my ears.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Well if it's fixable the Air Force will do it for free. If not, doesn't matter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>There are 100 applicants ready to take my place who don't need to be fixed. I need to do this off the books. I did the research, you're the best, you break rules, and you don't care about anyone except yourself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Well let’s say that's true. You get a new job, the hospital gets a nice wad of cash, what do I get?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>I crashed a flight simulator, because I started to hear, with my eyes.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>11</speaker><content>The aluminium could have been tainted...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> Don't care. New patient.  30 year old female, with synaesthesia. New rules.  You generate a lab report – You shred it. X-ray - You melt it. No notes, no records, nothing. As far as you're concerned the patient is Osama Bin Laden and everyone not in this room is Delta Force. Any questions?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>11</speaker><content>We're protecting Osama Bin Laden?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>It's a metaphor. Get used to it. Any more questions?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>11</speaker><content>And you're not even going to tell us her name?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You think her name might be connected to what's wrong with her?  Here's Osama!  Now you all have numbers so we're going to do this, alphabetically. 8, 15 and 5. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>39 </speaker><content>Is the synaesthesia new?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>39</speaker><content>Any history of similar symptoms or psychiatric...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>No, nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>39</speaker><content>Are you on any prescription meds or use any other drugs?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>39</speaker><content>Should we trust her answers?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>What, you think I'd pull you off Buddy Ebsen just for a junkie?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>24 </speaker><content>Can we trust your answers?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You have got to trust someone, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>24</speaker><content>No.  Has anyone close to you been sick lately? A family member, a co worker?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>No, not that I'm aware of.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Two down, Kitty Carlisle?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-20"><speaker>13 </speaker><content>You spend much time above 20,000 feet?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-21"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Why would you ask that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-22"><speaker>13</speaker><content>People who fly are immobile for long periods. Could be a leg clot that embolised to the brain through a PFO.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-23"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>That's an unusual choice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-24"><speaker>13</speaker><content>Well like you said, you wouldn't interrupt Buddy with anything that wasn't.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-25"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>The patient is a frequent flyer. 13, 32, 39, get Osama an EEG, MRI and an angiogram.  How many of you think that Oswald acted alone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-26"><speaker>6 </speaker><content>If by alone you mean that he was unaware that the CIA...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-27"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Oh shut up. Split yourselves into 2 groups, test her blood, test her stool.  Who likes the designated hitter?  You're wrong, you're lucky you're not fired. 2 more groups, LP and cultures.  Who doesn't know what a designated hitter is?  Okay, here is her address, I want you to break in, find out what she's hiding. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-28"><speaker>2 </speaker><content>Why don't we just ask the patient for the key?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-29"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Well, if we could find out what she's hiding just by asking we'd have to redefine hiding. You want to live in this country, learn the language. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-30"><speaker>11</speaker><content>What do you want the rest of us to do? </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>11</speaker><content>Thirty people for three openings and "I want you to wash my car." This is not why I busted my ass in med school!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>18 </speaker><content>So we spend a half an hour cleaning a car, big deal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>11</speaker><content>It's demeaning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>18</speaker><content>Work is demeaning? You're too good for this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>24</speaker><content>Now don't give me that honest day’s labour crap. We all went to med school so we wouldn't have to do an honest day's labour.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>18</speaker><content>What about an honest hour's labour? In exchange we get a shot at learning from one of the best diagnosticians in the world.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>24</speaker><content>No, we don't. If we did we'd be one of the ones drawing blood or checking for toxins. We're done. He's just not going to cut us loose until we've dusted his shelves and starched his shirt.  I'm out of here. Who's with me? </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>2</speaker><content>Are we sure he wasn't joking? Maybe this is just a test.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>10</speaker><content>Everything's a joke and everything's a test and he wants us to do it. C'mon, get up here. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>26</speaker><content>Well, I could try but I pulled a muscle in 1987.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>2</speaker><content>I didn't waste two years repeating medical school to be arrested and deported.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>10</speaker><content>Why did they make you repeat? Not enough gym credits?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>2</speaker><content>According to the state of New Jersey, medical schools in my country suffer from not being from this country.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>26</speaker><content>You know if you get it open you're going to have to come down and let me in?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>10</speaker><content>Or, you could just wait out here. This is a competition. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>18</speaker><content>You change your mind?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>24</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>18</speaker><content>Then why are you here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>24</speaker><content>Never intended to quit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>18</speaker><content>Then why did you...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>24</speaker><content>Intended to get everyone else to quit.  Get off the car.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>18</speaker><content>I need to clean it. WE need to clean it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>24</speaker><content>I stole his keys. We'll take it to a car wash.  He's got people breaking into a woman's apartment, obviously respecting personal property isn't one of the rules. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>26</speaker><content>I told the super I was worried about my niece, she hasn't been answering the telephone. Nice guy. Two daughters in Mount Holyoke. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>39</speaker><content>No evidence of clots and other than elevated red blood cell count, ah, the ah, blood work was unremarkable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Got a problem with the naked female form?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>32</speaker><content>Not at all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>13</speaker><content>Maybe she's just not used to seeing it spooning with the naked dolphin form.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>That's not a dolphin, it's a porpoise. There is a difference you know.  Salary for one thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>13</speaker><content>You want us to give you a minute?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>13</speaker><content>A high red blood cell count likely means...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>HOUSE </speaker><content>Carbon monoxide poisoning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>39</speaker><content>There are a lot of different explanations for elevated red blood cells.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>HOUSE </speaker><content>Yeah well which one fits best with the damaged flue that your competitors found in the gas fireplace in Osama's cave.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>24</speaker><content>Car's clean.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Did you just see a blond guy with a pretentious accent?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>24</speaker><content>Can't see an accent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Good point. Can I have my car keys back?  Give me the car keys, put the patient in a hyperbaric chamber and no more prime numbers for you.  Thank you. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>6</speaker><content>The high pressure and oxygen will flush the carbon monoxide from your system. This much oxygen for too long can have some toxic effects so we'll do this in cycles. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>18 </speaker><content>Can I talk to you for a second?  You're working that thing all the time, is everything all right?  We're supposed to be watching her heart rate and blood pressure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>24</speaker><content>Yeah, I was until you pulled me over here. I'm sending out a consult on another patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>18</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>24</speaker><content>What? I'm not quitting my old job until I'm sure I've got a new one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>18</speaker><content>I didn't say anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>24</speaker><content>You had a look.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>18</speaker><content>Yeah, I did. Sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>6</speaker><content>Hey I think she's having a heart attack.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>No I just feel a little funny. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>24</speaker><content>Tachy-arrhythmia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>18</speaker><content>Call a code.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>24</speaker><content>Nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>18</speaker><content>V-fib. Well where the hell's...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>6</speaker><content>Clear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>18</speaker><content>Are you crazy? You can't use those we're in a hyperbaric...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>6</speaker><content>Clear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>18</speaker><content>She's on fire!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-19"><speaker>6 </speaker><content>Her heart's beating.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-20"><speaker>18</speaker><content>And we are so fired.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>6</speaker><content>We've started her on nitro and blood thinners. Electrolytes and post-arrest EKG were normal, the attack was not caused by the procedure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>So what does cause synaesthesia, high red blood cell count and heart attack?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>24</speaker><content>Aren't we going to discuss what caused the sudden appearance of burnt flesh? He  brought charged paddles into an oxygenated room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>And you didn't stop him. Means either you thought it was a chance worth taking, making you a hypocrite, or you thought he'd fail, making you a cut throat little pixie. What causes...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>15A</speaker><content>Takayasu’s syndrome.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>15B</speaker><content>Not without a rash and a fever. It's got to be Whipple's.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>15A</speaker><content>No way, you ever see Whipple's without abdominal pain?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Stop it! This argument is distracting every male and lesbian here. You're both right, in the sense that you've convinced me that you're both wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>26</speaker><content>What about cardiomyopathy? Structural abnormality causes the heart attack and throws clots to the brain, leading to synaesthesia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>How old are you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>26</speaker><content>I'm 21. Unless it's relevant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Okay, Scooter. Do a trans-esophageal echo, and since the positive divisors of 26 are 2 and 13 have them assist. The rest of you, go to the cafeteria and document 10 things that could cause infection. Each. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>I wouldn't. Someone named 17 thinks there could be Listeria in the cream cheese.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>17's a stupid number.  What's Chase doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>You saw Chase?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Last night, outside my office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>That's interesting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>It's more curious than actually...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Chase took a job at the Mayo Clinic in Arizona. A week ago. Interesting... It wasn't Foreman or Cameron you saw, but Chase, the one you fired.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Not interesting. Someone who looked like someone I used to know walked by my office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>It's always interesting when repressed guilt starts un-repressing itself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>The only thing I feel guilty for is this. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>26</speaker><content>We're going to feed this endoscope down your esophagus, try to find where your heart might be damaged.  It's going to feel uncomfortable but just keep swallowing, I promise you'll be fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>13</speaker><content>She's ready.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>26</speaker><content> Go ahead, take a whack.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>2</speaker><content> Right. So if we don't find anything House blames me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>26</speaker><content>Or you find something, get a gold star.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>13</speaker><content>Why don't you want to do it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>26</speaker><content>House isn't going to be impressed by a grey hair doing his 10,000th echo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>13</speaker><content>So you're just being altruistic? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>26</speaker><content>That makes you suspicious. Doctor?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>13</speaker><content>Call me 13. I'm not getting invested. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>2</speaker><content>Her heart's structurally sound. No clots, no valvular defects, no wall motion abnormalities.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Got that from structurally sound.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>15A</speaker><content>What did she say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>6</speaker><content>Structurally sound.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I assume you're not all walking with me to tell me that you found nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>2 </speaker><content>It showed a short burst in the atrium... </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Okay, who's next?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>13 </speaker><content>Showed a short burst of atrial flutter, I ran a rhythm strip twice and got the same results.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Stop.  Okay. Here's how we diagnose in transit. I lead, you draft, I move, you move, I stop, you stop. Got it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>13</speaker><content>Flutter could mean hormone overproduction, we should...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Wait a sec, why did you do the test? I gave it to Scooter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-12"><speaker>26</speaker><content>We didn't think it mattered.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-13"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>It doesn't. It matters that you let her. Okay. 10, 24, 39 run a TRH stimulation test for hyperthyroidism. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-14"><speaker>2</speaker><content>That could cause another heart attack.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-15"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Proving her first attack was caused by her thyroid.  Which is kind of the point, right?  Uh ah ah ah ah!  I ride alone. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>39</speaker><content>The hormone stimulates your thyroid, don't worry if you get flushed or you start to sweat, it means the thyroid's working.  And if you want I can remove that mole.  I'm a plastic surgeon, you're allowed a little vanity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>I'm fine with the way I look.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>39</speaker><content>Good for you.  Although I do find it a bit odd that someone so self-assured doesn't want her doctors to find out what's wrong with her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>What are you talking about, why else am I here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>39</speaker><content>You're jerking us around. You're handcuffing us with all these restrictions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>I'm feeling warm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>10</speaker><content>Her pulse is 120, stop pushing. If House thought this would handicap us he wouldn't have taken the case.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>39</speaker><content>Or maybe that's why he took the case, he wants to see if we can get it out of her on our own.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>24</speaker><content>What did you find in her home?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>You were in my home?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-11"><speaker>10</speaker><content>Nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-12"><speaker>24</speaker><content>Travel pictures, year book, her name on an employment slip?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-13"><speaker>10</speaker><content>We weren't checking for that stuff, okay?  Obviously House didn't want us to. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-14"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content> You're going to... You're going to out me, aren't you? You're going to ruin everything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-15"><speaker>39</speaker><content>Nobody's trying to do anything. Just relax.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-16"><speaker>24</speaker><content>This is not a normal response to the test. Pulse and BP are too high.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-17"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content> Get away from me.  Get away from me. Don't touch me. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Paging me during Judge Judy, not the best way to win my affections.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>10</speaker><content>She had another episode of synaesthesia, it set off a psychotic attack and now she ran in there  and must've jammed something in the handles.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>So you called me, the guy with one good leg and zero leverage. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>39</speaker><content>We break that door down, security shows up, and her name goes in a file. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Well luckily, violence is not the last resort. Extortion is.  So go ahead, extort her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>10</speaker><content> If you don't open this door, we're going to break it down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Clever. An appeal to her deep concern for hospital property. Let's see how that works. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>10</speaker><content>If you don't open this door, you're going to die.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>GRETA </speaker><content>Go away! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You seem to be getting to her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-11"><speaker>39</speaker><content>She doesn't care if she dies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You think she wants to die?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-13"><speaker>39</speaker><content>No, but I think she only wants to live under certain circumstances.  Open up or I blab your secret to everyone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-14"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>You don't know anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-15"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I do. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-16"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>No!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-17"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Anybody think that a sedative might...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-18"><speaker>24</speaker><content>I'm trying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-19"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Okay. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-20"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content> Who's that?   Who is she?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-21"><speaker>39 </speaker><content>Osama Bin Laden.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>Who is she?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>18</speaker><content>Is she okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>She's stable. Who is she?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>26</speaker><content>What did House tell you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>That she is on the run from an international crime syndicate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>26</speaker><content>That's what he told us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>House may be your boss, but I'm House's boss. You want to work here, I better be okay with it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>2</speaker><content>Honestly, he didn't tell us anything about who she was, or what she...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>10</speaker><content>Her name's Greta Cooper. Wants to be an astronaut. Doesn't want NASA to know her brain's getting her ears confused with her eyes. I went through her mail. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>You're a virus, House, now instead of one liability I've got 20.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Apparently only 19. Which number was it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>From now on everything you do gets charted. With pen, on paper, in a binder that says "Princeton Plainsboro Teaching Hospital" on the cover.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>HOUSE </speaker><content>Mom!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>If you want to run something through the labs, I get a copy. If you do scans, I get a copy. If you THINK about doing scans, I get a copy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You know my current thoughts, right? I don't have to put those on paper. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Three issues. One. Number 10, you're fired.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>10</speaker><content>She told you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Well, it had to be someone who went to her home. Number 26 is half asleep, missed his afternoon nap. Obviously he doesn't feel guilt. Number 2 is here on a visa, she can't jeopardise...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>10</speaker><content>You can't know!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>And that chick's  been pointing at you since I walked in.  Issue two. What causes synaesthesia, high RBC, tachy-arrhythmia, and panic attacks? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>37</speaker><content>Slight glucose elevation. That says thyroid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>39</speaker><content>Baseline thyrotropin's 1.1.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>24</speaker><content>It's 1.3.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>39</speaker><content>Whatever. Her thyroid's working.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>24</speaker><content>What about her liver?  Original A.L.T. levels weren't abnormal but were near the edge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-11"><speaker>6</speaker><content>She has patient data on her PDA.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-12"><speaker>24</speaker><content>I do not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-13"><speaker>6</speaker><content>I saw the lab values, you said we couldn't write anything down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I also said I wanted answers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-15"><speaker>24</speaker><content>Liver cancer's the most likely. Paraneoplastic syndrome. We need to do an MRI.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-16"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Which brings us to issue three.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-17"><speaker>6</speaker><content>You're saying we can write stuff down?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-18"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>To you, I'm saying you're fired. To everyone else, I'm...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-19"><speaker>6</speaker><content>But you said specifically...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-20"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I hate tattle tales.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-21"><speaker>6</speaker><content>She tattled on 10.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-22"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Now you tattled twice. Issue three.  C'mon, let’s go.  Issue three, how do we do tests when we can't do tests?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-23"><speaker>2</speaker><content>Dr. Cuddy didn't say we can't do tests, she said that we have to chart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-24"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>If we chart, then we won't get consent. So we can't.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-25"><speaker>2</speaker><content>The patient's life may depend on her consenting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-26"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Her dreams depend on her not consenting. So, how do we do tests when we can't do tests?  You've got an hour. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>How do you scan a liver without scanning a liver? And what's Cameron doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Interesting. So you're seeing Cameron now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>No. Not interesting because not seeing. Saw. My patient won't consent to MRIs or ultrasounds, and you've dealt with more liver cancer than anyone else here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>So you want me to share the secret scanning techniques I learned in Nepal? Unfortunately, the monks made me swear a blood oath. Where was she?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>In the lobby. I guess we could palpate the area around the liver.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Which won't work unless the tumour's enormous, which you KNOW, which means you're here because these visions are freaking you out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>She had blonde hair, why would I hallucinate that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Yes. Yes, why are you merging Cameron and Chase? We should find out before the next time you see her when she'll be black.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Mm-hmm, because, of course it's scientifically impossible for a person to go back and visit somewhere they worked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-10"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>No. But since she's not a dead cat, it is scientifically impossible for her to be in two places at once.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Physics joke. Don't hear enough of those.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-12"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>She just called me from Arizona.  Notice the area code – 480. They put an offer on a place in Scottsdale.  Do you want to talk or should I? I guess we could both talk. Although they're engaged and if you're staying in touch, you might want to buy them...  Maybe it's not repressed guilt, Maybe it's just panic. Right now you've got enough fellows to build a rail road. But you're going to have to narrow that room full of numbers down to three people.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-13"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Any chance you could turn this creative brilliance towards my patient's liver? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-14"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>I think you're going to choose people for reasons that have nothing to do with their skills. I think you're going to choose people just because you can't stand them. Because if you like them, well, that's just, stressful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-15"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Stress... I like it. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>We need to stress the patient's liver.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>15B</speaker><content>You mean make her sick?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I mean make her sick in a specific way. If her liver's given to malfunctioning, we make it malfunction.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>15B</speaker><content>Are we on the other side of wrong here? Don't we have an ethics board that we should consult or... </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I fired you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>24</speaker><content>He fired you. You're number 6.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I approve of your shamelessness. You're still fired.  So how do we stress her liver?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>15B</speaker><content>Lying and paperwork I get, shutting down organs I think...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>13</speaker><content>We could give her intravenous Vitamin D and stick her in a tanning booth. If she goes into a coma, we know it's a metabolic problem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Nice. But Vitamin D's metabolised by the liver and kidneys. It wouldn't tell us which one's screwed up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I like you, number 9. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>18</speaker><content>You wanted to see me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You a Mormon? You're wearing a ring from Brigham Young. Or did your folks just do the lawns?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>18</speaker><content>The church has a very progressive attitude toward racial equality.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Don't care. Actually I'm thanking God. You're the only non-drinker we've got. We need a control group to establish whether the liver's deterioration is within normal range. Got a big drinker, medium drinker, now I got a no-drinker.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>18</speaker><content>Just do an MRI.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> You really think the guy who created heaven and earth cares what you put in your digestive tract?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>18</speaker><content>Her dream shouldn't outrank my religious belief.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Why not? Her dream might come true.  All life is sacred, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>18</speaker><content> We're not saving her life, we're doing a diagnostic test. Not even a real diagnostic test.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Well that fake test, might really save her life. Would you pull an ass out of a pit on the Sabbath?  Would you or would you not pull an ass out of a pit on the Sabbath?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-11"><speaker>18</speaker><content>Fine. I'll do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Good. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>Why'd you have to pick tequila? I assume a single malt would have worked just as well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>13</speaker><content>Wasn't our choice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Okay.  Two minutes and we go round number 5.  So tell me about the magic underwear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>18</speaker><content> Is that why you're here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I'm the big drinker, doing my part for science. The interesting question is why your religious beliefs are suddenly less important than her dreams.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>18</speaker><content>You're reversing your argument?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I know what I believe. I'm just not quite sure what you believe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>18</speaker><content>Well, LDS doesn't try to dictate every detail of our lives. When a situation isn't clear, we're encouraged to make our own decisions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>But your judgment was to say no. You used my judgment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>18</speaker><content>You made a good argument.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Rational arguments don't usually work on religious people. Otherwise there would be no religious people.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-12"><speaker>18</speaker><content>You're an atheist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-13"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Only on Christmas and Easter. The rest of the time, it doesn't really matter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-14"><speaker>18</speaker><content> Where's the fun in that? A finite, un-mysterious universe...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-15"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>It's not about fun! It's about the truth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-16"><speaker>18</speaker><content>The truth is, we're having this debate because you want to figure something out about me.  What do you got so far? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-17"><speaker>13</speaker><content>Greta. Greta!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-18"><speaker>18</speaker><content>She can't breathe. We need to intubate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-19"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content> No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-20"><speaker>18</speaker><content>At least oxygen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-21"><speaker>GRETA </speaker><content>NASA will need to know why.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>I checked the tests you ordered.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Did you just see Foreman?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>You measured the density of her teeth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> It's a shortcut test for hypercalcaemia. You had to have just passed him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>So you suspected hypercalcaemia from her complete lack of broken bones. Is that why you also ran three tox screens?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> Patient might've been sneaking uppers. He was in a white coat, did you hire him back?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>Foreman is running the diagnostic department at New York Mercy.  Have you been drinking?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>18</speaker><content>She was having trouble breathing. Refused oxygen and intubation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>So you put her on a treadmill.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>13</speaker><content>Records will show that we gave her oxygen as a part of a routine cardio stress test. She gets to breathe, your boss gets her paperwork.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Whose idea was that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>13</speaker><content>It was a joint decision.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>It never is. So how old were you when your brother left home?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>13</speaker><content>Why do you think that I...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Why aren't you answering? Did your mother initiate the divorce? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>13</speaker><content>We should probably focus on what's wrong with her lungs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Are you a Wiccan?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-11"><speaker>18</speaker><content>She really can't breathe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> Okay, hold still. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-13"><speaker>18</speaker><content>What are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Auscultatory percussion. If you have a good ear, you can...   You didn't have a lot of friends because you chose...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-15"><speaker>13</speaker><content>You can hear while you're talking?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-16"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> You can detect not only structural details, but small, deep masses.  Game's over. You either have lung cancer or tuberous sclerosis. We need to cut you open and biopsy... </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-17"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content> That'll... Leave a scar... NASA doctors will see, they'll, they'll know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-18"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I never opened for Springsteen or slept with Barbara Feldon. You can live for years without dreams. Without lungs...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-19"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>Find a way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-20"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Okay. As long you keep saying it strongly, you won't die. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-21"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>Find... A way.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>How do we force a patient into surgery? Texas bag scam? Saratoga wire? Paris exposition trip?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>18</speaker><content>The problem's not the surgery, it's the scars. And we have a plastic surgeon here who can hide them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>39</speaker><content>Not that well. NASA's going to check every cranny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>2</speaker><content>She'll sue.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>24</speaker><content>For what? Making it harder for her to lie to the government?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>39</speaker><content>Uh, we don't need to hide them. We give her elective cosmetic surgery. The incisions will give us access to her lungs and she's got an innocent explanation for the scars.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>2</speaker><content>You mean like liposuction?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-8"><speaker>39</speaker><content>No, no. Those incisions are too far from the lungs. We-we don't subtract, we add.  Turn her B's into C's.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> It's a myth that fake hooters blow up at high altitude, she'll be fine. Just think of it as one giant rack for mankind.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>I fought for years to be taken seriously.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>39</speaker><content>Trust me, you'll be taken more seriously. Just sign the form. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>This'll make me a joke, there's got to be another way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>39</speaker><content>I've known a few people who had dreams. One thing they all had in common was, they got laughed at, and they didn't care. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>You bumped a splenectomy for a boob job?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Would you condemn this woman to a life where people look at her face when they talk to her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>You don't explain this, I'll cancel the surgery.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Can I explain why you're here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>Think I just told you why I...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I scheduled a diagnostic patient for a boob job, which is ridiculous. So obviously you had to confront me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>With you so far.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>But I'm going to give you a reason.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-9"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>Not a good one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>No. Not even close to a good one. But here's the drag from your point of view. My explanation will make sense. Not to the board, not to a judge, but to you. So you'll let me do it. Then you're going to have to sit next to me at the administrative hearing. Don't you have better things to do?  It's in the best interests of the patient. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>39</speaker><content>Trochar's in. You're good to go. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> Deflate the lung.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>2</speaker><content>There, a cyst.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>39</speaker><content>Cysts, I count three of them. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Probably the same if not more on the left lung. Okay, so what's been working overtime to kill Miss Bin Laden?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>2</speaker><content>We know her name now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Yeah, but I forgot it. Say the magic word and get immunity from the next challenge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>13</speaker><content>Alveolar hydatid disease. Hits all the organs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>She would've had multiple seizures by now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-10"><speaker>39</speaker><content>Pulmonary Langerhans.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Wouldn't explain the red blood cells. C'mon. Cysts, synaesthesia, heart attack. You guys have gotten...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-12"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Von Hippel-Lindau syndrome.  Raises red blood cell count, causes masses on the organs. One of the masses is a pheochromocytoma. It'd cause neurologic episodes and a heart attack.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-13"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> Do you see a blond guy who still has peach fuzz standing up there?   This is a closed procedure, gallery's off limits.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-14"><speaker>CHASE</speaker><content>Not to the surgical staff.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-15"><speaker>39</speaker><content>You going to hire that guy instead of us. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-16"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Not a chance. I love you guys. Dig out the cysts, histology to confirm Von Hippel-Lindau. Don't forget her chesticles. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Calling Arizona, that was a very nice touch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>You do have residual...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Not only do I not have residual feelings, I didn't even have primary feelings.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>You freaked...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You lied!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Because you knew it meant...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>It meant nothing! I saw him because he was there.  Did Cameron follow her beshert to the surgery department?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-8"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>I think Chase followed her. She's been a senior attending in the E.R. the last three weeks. A blonde senior attending, to be accurate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Foreman. Is he back in neurology?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-10"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>He's at New York Mercy, he's been there a month.  Did you SEE Foreman?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>No. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>So, I'm cured.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>24</speaker><content>Greta, you need to come clean to NASA.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>You said you got all the cysts.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>24</speaker><content>They could re-emerge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>I'll go to radiology clinics. I'll get regular screenings.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-6"><speaker>24</speaker><content>If something happened while you're up there, you'd be playing Russian roulette with... </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Relax. She doesn't have to tell and neither do you. Turns out that NASA doctors even know where the hyphen in Von Hippel-Lindau goes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-8"><speaker>GRETA</speaker><content>You called them?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I'm not an idiot. Those shuttles fly over New Jersey. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>So here we are. The big moment. Which of you gets to live to be abused another day. And which of you goes home and rationalises being fired as character building?  Following numbers, thanks for playing. 21, 19, 8, 34, 17, 29, 5, 36, 2... Rest of you, 8:00 A.M. Sharp. I'll be in sometime between 10:00 and 3:00.  But 26, stick around awhile. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>2</speaker><content>I did nothing wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Lots of people did nothing wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>2</speaker><content>Other people screwed up. I never even...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Other people took chances. 26. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>26</speaker><content>Buddy Ebsen actually was allergic to...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Yeah, I know. How old are you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-3"><speaker>26</speaker><content>21.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You don't think it's relevant?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-5"><speaker>26</speaker><content>I'll likely have less time to use the skills you teach us, but I don't think that's significant to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>How about the fact that you never went to medical school? Which is why you let the unlucky number do the trans echo. At least you're ethically unethical.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-7"><speaker>26</speaker><content>Thirty years I worked in the Columbia med school admissions office. Audited all the classes. Most of them more than once. I just never got a diploma.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You had to know I'd find out sooner or later.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-9"><speaker>26</speaker><content>I know you break rules. I thought maybe you'd break one for me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I can't hire you as a doctor. But you can still tell me what you think. You can also fetch me coffee, pick up my dry-cleaning, until I can decide whether or not to keep you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-11"><speaker>26</speaker><content>So I'm playing this whole game to be like... Your secretary?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Assistant sounds marginally less demeaning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-13"><speaker>26</speaker><content>It's not my dream job.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Actually it is. It's just not your dream title. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content> Three weeks. For someone who never misses something small, you missed something big.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You're an idiot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>The hair, where I'm working, or both?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>The hair makes you look like a hooker. I like it. Pulling pieces of windshield out of car accident victims and reattaching fingertips sliced off cutting bagels. At least Chase's move is only one step down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-5"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>I can do good here. Get it out of my system. Why'd you rat your patient out to NASA?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I don't know who's been gossiping about ethics instead of sex, but I hope they've already been fired. Which number was it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-7"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Greta.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Number!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-9"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>No number. The patient. How do you think she got your pager number? She came into the E.R. didn't want to talk...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I didn't rat her out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-11"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>You--lied?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Suppose I should tell her that before she keys my car.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-13"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Why lie?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Had to stop some leaky faucets.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-15"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>What did it matter?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-16"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>It was no one's business.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-17"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-18"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>She's going to be the safest astronaut up there. Certainly more vigilant than the guy next to her who's got no clue about the aneurysm in his head ready to pop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-19"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Right. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-20"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You got a better reason?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-21"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>You couldn't kill her dream. </content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>