<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>
<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>SEAN</speaker><content>Doc, help, doc!  It stopped bleeding. It stopped bleeding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>That's because your blood's freezing as it's hitting the air.  Here, apply pressure on it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>SEAN</speaker><content>I think my leg is frozen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>That's the least of your problems.  The blade severed your femoral artery. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>SEAN</speaker><content>Am I gonna lose my leg?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Frostbite's not too bad but I gotta fix your artery now. This is gonna hurt. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>SEAN</speaker><content>You're gonna put that in me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Glue's the best way to repair your artery at this temperature.  It looks okay.  Here, tear off some pieces. I have to check your foot.  Blood flow looks good. Your leg should be okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>SEAN</speaker><content>I thought I was done.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Yeah, like I'd let anything happen to you. You're the only one who can fix the generators. One... two... three. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>SEAN</speaker><content>Cate, Cate, are you okay? Are you okay? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>I... I... I need help.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>SEAN</speaker><content>Who am I supposed to get?</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>Why do I even give you an office? New case. Psych department asked for you personally.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Patient's a crazy person?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>You're a crazy person. Patient's a psychiatrist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> There's something wrong with coma guy's cable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>He seems fine with it. Your patient is an adjunct faculty member here but currently...  The budget committee voted to charge for cable in the patient rooms.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Slippery slope. Today we withhold porn, tomorrow it's clean bandages.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>Talk to Carlson in Derm, he runs the budget committee... After you look at this. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>After you talk to Carlson, maybe I'll...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>The patient is trapped at the South Pole. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>13</speaker><content>Any possibility of evacuating her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Well that wouldn't be any fun. And for the next two months, winds make it impossible to fly anything in or out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>13</speaker><content>Could be appendicitis or a gallstone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>KUTNER</speaker><content>Or a kidney stone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>That wouldn't be any fun. If it's appendicitis down there, her appendix ruptures, she dies, there's nothing we can do. If it's stones, she takes pain meds, the stone passes, there's nothing we need to do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>KUTNER</speaker><content>Could be a struvite kidney stone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Most kidney stones are calcium and benign. Why would you suspect a struvite stone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>KUTNER</speaker><content>Cause he said kidney stones were boring.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>TAUB</speaker><content>It's possible. She's on birth control. Lots of sex could lead to urinary tract infection, which could lead to an infection-laced struvite kidney stone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Excessive Antarctic drilling. Bad for the environment and the ladies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>13</speaker><content>If it's a struvite stone she needs to break it up quickly before the infection shuts down her kidneys.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>This is where it gets fun.  These are the supplies and medications she has available.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>TAUB</speaker><content> Nothing here that could break up a kidney stone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>KUTNER</speaker><content>What else do they have down there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I just said...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>KUTNER</speaker><content>I don't mean medical stuff, other stuff. Some geological equipment breaks ice and rock the same way we break kidney stones.  Discovery channel. I like watching them blow stuff up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Who doesn't? That reminds me. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Coma guy needs cable. Women's billiards is the only thing that's keeping him alive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>I'm sure Carlson will be moved by HIS plight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Carlson won't listen to me since I hit on his wife.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content> You knew? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>God no. I thought I was hitting on his daughter.  Look, you're on the committee. He'll listen to you.  I'm an avid reader of committees with hotties message boards.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content> Amoxicillin, 500 milligrams IV. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> Studies conducted in major hospitals indicate that happy patients recover faster. Studies conducted in my apartment show that TV makes people happy. Premium channels have a particularly striking effect.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Charging patients for cable is bringing in 13 grand a month.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Until this injustice is righted, I am going to waste 13 grand a day.  It's 2 dollars 49 cents down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content> Get an EKG and a cardiac enzyme. If those check out, discharge him and tell him to get a snow blower.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> How much is 13 grand divided by 4 cents?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content> I am not giving you cable. You're going to have to somehow survive with the broadcast networks alone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I'll be fine on Tuesdays. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>KUTNER</speaker><content>If sound waves from the flaw detector break the egg it should safely dissolve your kidney stone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>This isn't going to work. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>KUTNER</speaker><content>There's no reason it shouldn't. Sound waves are sound waves. Stones are stones.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Some are bigger than others. Some are inside me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>How's it going, team MacGyver?  Oh, great. I can't get cable, but I can get the South Pole on hi-def.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>KUTNER</speaker><content>We're almost ready to start the test.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Test? Did Ford test the Edsel? Did Coke test New Coke? Did Shakespeare test his final play, Snow Dogs?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>I'm guessing you're Dr House? I was wondering when you might drop by.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Can she see me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Oh yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Think Jagger shows up for the sound check?  Okay. Roadies, off the stage. Go help Cameron in the ER.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>TAUB</speaker><content>Why? No way you're just doing her a favour.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>ER is standing room only. Which means Cameron's bound to make a mistake. Find it so I can blackmail her. As far as you know, this is way more than just some silly battle over cable. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Ready. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You, you might want to just, dial it down a smidge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>I am not doing this.  Your kidney stone theory hinges on me having sex, but I...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Let me guess. You're as pure as the driven snow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-18"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Only if the snow likes to be on top. But I am here doing psychological research, generally not a good idea to swap fluids with your subjects.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-19"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Struvite stones are possible in people who don't have sex. They're certainly possible in people who claim not to have...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-20"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>I've had no UTIs. No pain on urination.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-21"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You do realise that only one of us is a real doctor?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-22"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>You do realise that only one of us has any control over my actions?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-23"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Dr. Milton, are you able to run a chem 7?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-24"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-25"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>That'll tell us if her kidney function's declining. If it is, he's right. Struvite stone's most likely explanation. If not, she's right.  Sorry, I know how you like to avoid avoiding confrontation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-26"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>While we're waiting for that test to prove me right, start IV cefuroxime. Keep the infection in the stone from wiping out your kidneys.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-27"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>I'll send the chem 7 results when I'm done. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-28"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>She's a great psychiatrist. One session, I've got shrinkage.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>13</speaker><content>House wants us to spy on you, report back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>And you're telling me this because...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>KUTNER</speaker><content>We don't want to do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>I don't see a problem so far.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>TAUB</speaker><content>If our choice is between pissing House off or pissing you off, that's not much of a choice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>So unless I give House cable, you're going to make my life miserable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>13</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>And you're telling me this so you won't feel as guilty when you do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>TAUB</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Accommodating House's every whim is not my job anymore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>TAUB</speaker><content>But it is ours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>KUTNER</speaker><content>House will get what he wants. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>TAUB</speaker><content>Maybe we should just pay for it ourselves and tell him she folded. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content> No. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Your chem 7 results show that your kidney function is declining. Sounds like a kidney stone to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>The decreased function could be from dehydration caused by vomiting due to a gallstone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You agreed that the chem 7 would decide if it was a struvite stone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>I agreed to do the test. The results are up for interpretation. I'll redo the test in an hour when I'm re-hydrated. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Have you noticed any improvement since starting the cefuroxime?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Not really. The pain's about the same.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>While you're waiting, we should run another test with the geology equipment...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You're not taking the cefuroxime. She's right handed. Means she would've put the IV in her left arm. Catheter in the arm makes it hard to bend the elbow the way people do when they drink!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>We have a limited supply of medication and I'm not about to waste it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Last I checked, you had a limited supply of doctors.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Right before I got sick, one of my crew members severed his femoral artery. He needs the cefuroxime. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Right, he called dibs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>His need is definitive. Mine is speculative.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You're breathing fast.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>It's because I'm pissed off!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Lift up your chin. Show me your windpipe. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Ah! My chest hurts.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>It's deviating to the left.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Means her right lung is collapsing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-20"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Cate Is anyone there with you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-21"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Sean went to the mess.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-22"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>You need to call someone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-23"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>There's no time. Get a syringe and a needle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-24"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Why am I doing…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-25"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Shut up and look. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-26"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>She could pass out. She needs...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-27"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>She needs to re-inflate that lung.  Okay, now pull out that plunger. I want you to stab yourself in your right side between the second and third rib in the midclavicular line.  By the time we get someone else there, you'll have suffocated. Just do it.  See all the good stuff that happens when you listen to me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-28"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Means it's not a kidney stone.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Right side pain, vomiting, and now a lung that gets traumatised without any trauma. Sounds odd, probably is odd.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>We should discuss this, then call her back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>No it's fine. I made sure we got the South Pole long distance plan. Your latest kidney function test shows...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>I know what it shows, I ran it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>The more you interrupt, the longer my grandstanding is going to take.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Since when do you let patients participate in differentials?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Since the patient and her doctor happen to be the same person. Your kidney function is still declining, means you have a kidney problem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>But not one that needed antibiotics. Makes us equally wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>No, makes us both wrong. Not equally. You were at least six wronger.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>They run a PPD before you shipped out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>On me and everybody else here, it's not TB.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Excuse us a second.  Cancer explains the symptoms. A tumour in her lung or kidney that threw a clot to the other organ.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>And you're worried the tumour might overhear, realise we're on to it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Cancer's a hard diagnosis for patients even when they're not in the South Pole. We should figure this out, maybe bring Wilson in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Obviously you two think I'm in bad shape.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Only if you count the tumour.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>House!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Probably in your abdomen. But you don't have any advanced imaging equipment. You also don't have a surgeon to biopsy it, any stains to use on the slide, or an oncologist to analyse it.  We're too far away to hold her hand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>I have cancer?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-20"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Possibly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-21"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Since the only imaging equipment you have is X-ray, let's start there. X-ray your entire body.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-22"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>I'll upload the images when I'm done. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-23"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Good for you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>She's annoying. Refused to take the antibiotics because other people might need them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>She said she cares about other people? What a poser. KUB is clean. You don't like her because she's a psychiatrist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I'm a complicated man. I loathe her for many reasons.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Never before has a profession been so decried by someone who needed it so badly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You talk a lot of smack about tranny hookers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Enlarged mediastinal node.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Lymphoma.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Probably, but we can't confirm it without a biopsy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You can't analyse a biopsy without a stain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>We can't biopsy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Cause they don't have stains down there. We need a substitute.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>She can't biopsy that node without a surgical team and an OR.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Anything with a strong colour could work as a stain. Printer ink, food colouring, coffee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>No thanks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Find a node closer to the surface, one she can biopsy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>That makes sense.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>That makes sense?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>I said it first.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-19"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>In a shockingly calm manner, after I'd just been jerking you around for 30 seconds without you complaining or analysing said jerking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-20"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>I was being mature.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-21"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>In a lavender shirt. You for some reason are happy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-22"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>How dare you? The X-rays don't show any other abnormal nodes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-23"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Abnormal nodes can be felt before they can be seen on an X-ray. You're wearing that shirt for someone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-24"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>The health department. They frown on topless oncology. You're going to do a physical?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-25"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Have to. You and Foreman are going to be here looking for a stain. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>I can do the physical. There's no reason you need to watch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I can think of at least three reasons. One of them's medical.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Where are you? Not in your office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You're not in the hospital. No reason for me to be.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>I am not undressing for you in your apartment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You're not in my apartment. You're three quarters of a world away. I promise not to get fresh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>I'm not taking off my clothes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>One of us has to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content> Show me your place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>It's got walls, a floor, and in some places, a roof.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>I am not exposing myself without some reciprocity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>It's my apartment, it's not my soul.  Living room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Slow down.  Lots of books. I'm betting all medical.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> Only if you count Jenna Jameson's autobiography as a gynaecological text.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Fiction is a waste of time unless you can laugh at it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I love to laugh. Moving on. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-17"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Back up.  How bad is the insomnia? Let me quantify that. Do you drink two or three scotches before passing out in front of the TV?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-18"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You are so far off. It's bourbon. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-19"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>No photos anywhere. Family and friends aren't important?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-20"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Well, you're sick. You have 20 people down the hall and you've had exactly one visitor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-21"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>I don't want to panic anyone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-22"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You don't like people. You hide on that ice cube so…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-23"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Stop projecting. You're anti-social, so you assume I'm anti-social.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-24"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> How about if I just get naked and you shut up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-25"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>If I thought I could get you naked, I would've led with that. You'd rather show me your soul than your leg.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-26"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Great. You’ve got me all figured out. You going to try and fix me now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-27"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>I never said you needed fixing.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>He's letting her take part in the differentials.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Of course he is. He likes her. Big shock, spaghetti sauce doesn't work as a lymph tissue stain. I'll try... the coffee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>He's annoyed by her, doesn't respect her as a doctor, constantly insults her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>That's House's version of courtship.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Oh, god. He's been wooing me for years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>She's the perfect woman for him. Willing to literally go to the end of the earth for her career, making her unavailable for a real relationship. And she's afflicted with a mysterious illness.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Soya sauce is a no-go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>We're going to be here all night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>How long does it take you to get naked?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>It's the South Pole. I wear a lot of layers. Okay. Ready. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I saw socks. That's not naked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Have I mentioned it's freezing here? When they discover lymph nodes in feet, I will take off my socks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Use your right hand to palpate the nodes. Any node you can feel is one we can biopsy. Let's start with your breasts, move down to the ass, then...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>I was thinking... go from the neck and work my way down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Well, you could. But I'd never forgive myself if we found something before we got to your breasts.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-16"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>I'm starting with the anterior cervical nodes. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-17"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Turn your head. Locate the SCM muscle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-18"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>I know how to find my lymph nodes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-19"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>They teach you that before or after the class on fondling your inner child? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-20"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>No swelling, no tenderness, and I can hear that, House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-21"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Just thought it might help you relax. Anything in the axillary nodes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-22"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>All clear. Both sides.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-23"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Slide your hand to your sternum, probe for nodes. Moving slowly downward. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-24"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Down to what, House?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-25"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Sorry, can't hear you on account of your heavy breathing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-26"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>I'm supposed to be on oxygen, you tool.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-27"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> Hold it.  Your fingers didn't go quite as deep. Feel that node again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-28"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>It…it's swollen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-29"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Looks like you're doing a biopsy.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>It's pretty numb.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Okay, take a deep breath... and insert the needle into the node.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Come on, Cate. Let's get this over with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>You used her name.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Just trying to move things along, Bob. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content> Okay, I'm in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>You need to pull back on the syringe.  You need to pull harder. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Are you okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>It's a valid medical question.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>I have never heard you ask a patient that question. You've never asked me that question, and you've seen me fall down a flight of stairs drunk. You've slept with her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>She's 9,000 miles away.  And while a certain part of me unfurled…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>No, you… Somehow you've been intimate with her. Why are you following me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Thought you were following me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>No, you are definitely following me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Where are you going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Out to lunch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You never go out to lunch. Means there's a reason you're going out to lunch. I assume that reason is a human being.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Or a sandwich.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Sandwiches can come here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-13"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>So can human beings.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Yet she's not, which I find interesting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-15"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>I'm leaving now. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-16"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Small world. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-17"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Are you going to follow me into my car?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-18"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>It's got two doors.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-19"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Okay, look. The reason I haven't told you is… </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-20"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Call off your dogs, House. Your little helpers are interrogating my patients, swiping my charts, intercepting prescriptions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-21"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Why would you think that I'm…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-22"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Because I'm not a moron. You had to be pulling the strings here. You think that because they make me miserable I'm going to give you cable?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-23"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Let's assume that's true. And it certainly sounds like it might be. What are you going to do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-24"><speaker>CAMERON</speaker><content>Nothing. I resigned from the budget committee.  I only joined the committee to help the hospital. You made me a liability. I now have zero influence over the hospital's cable policy. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Well done.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>TAUB</speaker><content>It didn't work. There's nothing more that we can do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Put these up. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>KUTNER</speaker><content> Free Rottweiler puppies. Please call after 11:00 pm and before 5:00 am.  Is this Cameron's home number?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> I love a new puppy. My last one was delicious, very tender.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>TAUB</speaker><content>There's no point in torturing her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>If she can resign, she can un-resign. Go to def-con one. Forget waiting for a mistake, make her make one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>13</speaker><content>You want us to sabotage another doctor, possibly harm a patient, all so you can have cable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Harm suggests permanent damage. Get her to screw up, then fix it. Oh, and this time, don't tell her what you're going to do before you do it. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>So, how long do I let the lymph node marinate in the red wine?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>It should be ready now.  Try increasing the magnification on the camera. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>You know, I e-mailed a couple colleagues at the hospital about you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>You're checking up on me, not House?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Yeah, well House is straightforward, brilliant, and an ass.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Two out of three good qualities, clear majority.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Whereas you, on the other hand, have a perfect score. You are responsible, nice, human, and yet you're House's best friend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Hold there.  Makes you think he's secretly nicer than he seems?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Makes me think that you're secretly a lot less nice than you seem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-10"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Do you always insult your doctors?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-11"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>It's not an insult. Indiscriminate niceness is overrated.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-12"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content> No wonder he likes you. Based on this slide, you do not have cancer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-13"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content> Oh thank god.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-14"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>I do see some inflammation which could mean…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-15"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content> Ah!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-16"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Cate? You all right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-17"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>My left side, it hurts... It's the same pain that I had on the right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-18"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Your other kidney.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-19"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>No, I hope it's something, It's maybe  Oh, no! I'm screwed.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Bad news is you're 0 for 2 in the kidney department.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Is there good news? You're back at home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Of course. There's cable. And the freedom to work pant-free.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>That is good news.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Wilson found signs of inflammation in your biopsy. That plus the two failing kidneys points to autoimmune disease. Probably SLE or vasculitis. Treatment for both is prednisone. Start with 100 milligrams...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Autoimmune is just your latest theory. Like cancer before that, and a kidney stone before.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Take the prednisone, you'll get better, that'll be your confirmation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>You practice medicine like it's a fire sale. You've wasted antibiotics, X-rays.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>That was not a waste. We ruled out…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-10"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>We have a crew member here who has asthma. If he has an episode after I've used up the prednisone, he'll die.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>There a good chance he's going to die anyway, since there won't be a doctor there to help him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-12"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Show me proof that it's autoimmune and then I'll take the prednisone. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>We should send her outside.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Right, just tell her to head north until she runs into a hospital.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Autoimmune diseases are basically inflammation running wild. Extreme cold has been used as treatment, like putting ice on a sprained ankle. She starts to feel better outside, we know it's autoimmune.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content> Is that my wallet?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Yeah, you can have it back. I've already been through it. I like your ice on a sprain metaphor. Makes it seem like we're not killing her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>She'd only need to be outside five minutes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Without her mittens. Mom told me that was a bad idea. Especially that winter it was 70 below and I had dual kidney failure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>This is a good idea. It's perfect for you. Experimental, risky. Wilson's right. You care about…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-9"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>You didn't touch the cash, but you took the receipts?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> $190 restaurant tab. That's dessert, probably booze. Means you lingered. Means it's at least the third date. Means… </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-11"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Where are you going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>To talk to the people I pay to come up with medical ideas.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-13"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>There are no ideas. The test for autoimmune is ANA. Unless penguins poop immuno-analysers, she's not…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Before A.N.A. testing, people had autoimmune diseases. How did they know?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-15"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>C3.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-16"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Before that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-17"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>LE Prep. But she doesn't have any controlled pore glass beads.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-18"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>You don't need them. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>When you shake the test tube, the paperclip will damage some of your blood cells. If you have an autoimmune disease, your immune system will gorge itself on the damaged cells. They'll get big and fat so you can see them under a microscope.  How you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>No change. So how long should I give the cells to fatten up before I check them?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Couple hours. Or you could stop being a hypocrite and take the prednisone now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Not bending to your will makes me a hypocrite?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>If your psych patients demanded lab results, you'd never make a diagnosis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>So I'm wrong. You sleep like a baby, your life is unfolding as you dreamed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Everyone is miserable. You don't change that because people don't change.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>You want to believe that because then you're freed from any responsibility for your misery.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Oh shut up. I get enough of this from Wilson.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>And yet you keep hanging out with him. And from what I hear, you have spent more time with me than with any other patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Sorry about that. Call me when you get the results. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>How's your patient?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>She has an autoimmune disease. Tell the psych department she's in denial.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>I had to fire Cameron.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>What? What happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>65-year-old man came into the ER with a hip fracture. Cameron gave him Demerol. The guy was on an MAOI, put him into a hypertensive crisis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Is he going to live?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>Taub caught the error in time. If she'd just admitted the mistake, maybe I could've just suspended her. But... she's packing up, if you want to say good-bye.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>We should be hearing from the South Pole in a few minutes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-9"><speaker>CUDDY</speaker><content>That's it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Well there's nothing to be done. She screwed up. She's got no one to blame but herself. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-11"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>I got to go talk to Cameron.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Cuddy wouldn't can her for one screw-up and if she did, she wouldn't come to me. And if she did, she wouldn't open with, "how's your patient." And if she did...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-13"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Why would she lie?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Timeless question. In this case, she conspired with your coworkers to teach me that some things are more important than cable. And I'm gonna have to teach them that they're wrong. Come on, South Pole really should be calling. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>LE Prep test was negative. It's not autoimmune.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You're basing that on a test done with a paperclip. Just take the prednisone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Either find another diagnosis or find another test.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>There is one way. You can take this experimental drug called... pred-ni-sone! Your Kidneys start working...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>There is another test.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> I, I think Foreman may have just broken up there. What he actually said was there is no other test.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>If you have an autoimmune disease, exposure to the cold should decrease your kidney pain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>If I go outside, we'll have our answer?   And you knew about this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I rejected it because if you're frozen solid, it's hard to get the needles into your arms.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content> How long do I need to stay out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>At least five minutes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Eight minutes outside would kill a healthy person. And healthy people don't suck on oxygen masks. Healthy people can pee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-13"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>I'll go get Sean, have him come with me. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Just take the prednisone!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-15"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Once I come inside. If it's autoimmune. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-16"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Are you all right? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-17"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Oh I'm sure she's just fine. Cate?  Do you know if there's anyone down there who has a cell phone.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Took the station mechanic 20 minutes to respond. She'd already slipped into a coma. Started her on prednisone, but no improvement.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Means it's not autoimmune. Good thing she's in a coma, or we'd have to listen to her gloat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>And where are we going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>To find the useful members of my team.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>You're letting them off the hook?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Happy? Because of you, I'm not going to be able to watch law and order in Korean.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Why am I here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Because I want to ask you about your girlfriend. I must know who she is or you'd have told me her name.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>She doesn't have a name. It's some sort of birth defect.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>There's only about 12 people we both know. I can't remember five of their names, so we're down to... Cuddy… Your ex-wives...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-11"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Your mama.  You need to run a kidney function test.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Yes, if only she wasn't in a coma, we could get her to run a test to find out why she's in a coma. The results would likely be paradoxical. Can't be Cuddy, 'cause you're straight. Can't be…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-13"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>We could talk the mechanic through the test.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Too complicated... Unless he's thirsty.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>SEAN</speaker><content>Drink her urine?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>If it has a strong, concentrated taste, it means the problem's in her kidneys. Watery taste means it's her brain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>SEAN</speaker><content>And then you can fix it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Let's say yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>SEAN</speaker><content>How do I get the urine out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Take a straight catheter and insert it...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>These are your only questions? Not, is it safe? Or, is there another way? Or, are you out of your minds?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>SEAN</speaker><content>You wouldn't ask me if…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Wait a second. You're in love with her. That explains why you're so eager to get her naked, then have a drink. Cause most guys like to go the other way around.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>SEAN</speaker><content>Why do you care how I feel about her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Because now, I know that I can get you to do anything to save her. Tell him how to tap the keg. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You got Cameron fired.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>TAUB</speaker><content>Cuddy wasn't supposed to find out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>No kidding! Get me cable. How tough can that be? Cost a woman her job. There's only one thing you can say to keep me from firing you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>13</speaker><content>Cameron wasn't fired.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>TAUB</speaker><content>You know?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>KUTNER</speaker><content>We're still fired?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>That should be a hint as to what you're supposed to say.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>TAUB</speaker><content>We're sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-11"><speaker>KUTNER</speaker><content>I love you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-13"><speaker>13</speaker><content>This is a game? First we have to screw with our co-worker and now we have to try to figure out what you want us to say? This is insane. I'm not playing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Right. You should've said this two days ago. Do not play games with me. Number one, you're going to lose, you're just not ready. Number two, the game was to force you to stop playing games. I need you to stand up to me. Challenge me. I need you to stop worrying about getting fired. Go pay for my cable. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-15"><speaker>KUTNER</speaker><content>No!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-16"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I didn't mean on this. Seriously, I need cable.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Milk, milk, lemonade?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>SEAN</speaker><content>This tastes kind of watery.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>That's bad news.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Either increased intracranial pressure or something's wrong with her hypothalamus.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>SEAN</speaker><content>How do you figure out which one it is?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>We don't do anything. You're going to drill a hole in her skull. If she regains consciousness, it's increased intracranial pressure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>SEAN</speaker><content>And if it's the other thing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>She'll die. But if it's the hypothalamus, she's dead anyway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>SEAN</speaker><content>If the problem is the pressure in her brain, and I fix it, is she going to be all better?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Nope, but it'll give us more time to figure out what's wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-11"><speaker>SEAN</speaker><content> I have to get someone else. I can't do this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You love her, right? You'd do anything to save her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-13"><speaker>SEAN</speaker><content>Not this. I can't do this. If, if she dies because of something that I did, then I…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Listen, listen. I am not going to let you hurt her. Okay? Now please... This is her only chance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-15"><speaker>SEAN</speaker><content>Okay. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-16"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Well, that was easy.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>SEAN</speaker><content>Okay, her head is stabilised and the drill bit is sterile.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Place the drill bit against the upper left part of her forehead. About an inch above the temple. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>SEAN</speaker><content>It's not going anywhere.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Bone's harder than wood, lean into it. The skull's only a quarter-inch thick. Once you're midway through, drill in shorter bursts. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>If it comes out the other side, you've gone too far.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>SEAN</speaker><content> Okay, now what? Now what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Let the fluid drain. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-8"><speaker>SEAN</speaker><content>She's waking up. She's waking up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-9"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Sean? What's going on?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>South Pole doc is out of her coma, and now we have a new symptom. Increased intracranial pressure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>KUTNER</speaker><content>Why are we out here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>That's the patient room. ICP plus kidney problems plus lung collapse equals?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>TAUB</speaker><content>The most likely suspect is a tumour throwing off clots.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>We ruled out cancer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>But not clots. What causes blood clots?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>13</speaker><content>Bacterial endocarditis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Not without a fever.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>TAUB</speaker><content>Deep vein thrombosis plus an existing PFO.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>PFO would've been discovered in her pre-South Pole physical exam.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-11"><speaker>KUTNER</speaker><content>What if the clots aren't clots? Atherosclerosis. Fatty plaque builds up on the arterial walls, pieces break off, block blood flow. Explains everything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>She has zero risk factors. Forget fat, think clots.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-13"><speaker>KUTNER</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You're standing up to me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-15"><speaker>KUTNER</speaker><content>Maybe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-16"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Just to clarify. You should do that when you're right. Sorry for the confusion. How could a clot…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-17"><speaker>KUTNER</speaker><content>Could be a different kind of fat, fat emboli.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-18"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>That's a perfect fit... Except it's completely impossible! Fat emboli requires an unrepaired bone break. Between the x-ray and the exam, I've seen her entire…  See, that's what I'm talking about. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Take off her socks. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>I could, I could do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>SEAN</speaker><content>No, I got it. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Your toe is broken.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Oh, my god.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Bits of bone marrow have been leaking into your blood stream. Those fat emboli have caused blockages in your kidney, lungs, and brain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>It doesn't even hurt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Cold numbs everything. Does a particularly great job on the extremities.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-9"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>You'll need to close the break to stop the marrow from leaking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>This one you will feel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-11"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content> Will you do it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>He drilled a hole in your skull after drinking your pee. I think he's up for this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-13"><speaker>FOREMAN</speaker><content>Grab the tip of her toe with your right hand. Hold the break with the other.  On the count of three, pull hard. One... two... three. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Now splint your toe. You'll be fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-15"><speaker>CATE</speaker><content>Thank you, House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-16"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Don't thank me. He's the one who saved your life.  He likes her. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content> A bottle of the Bordeaux and some sparkling water.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Well, you didn't pick her up. Which means she's coming from work too. Which means you're comfortable enough to meet her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Damn. Thought I lost you when I walked backwards through my own footprints in the snow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>I think I've got it narrowed down to three possibilities.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Better leave, if you see her, it'll be cheating.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>It's not one of your ex-wives.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Because they hate me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>They don't. They should, but they don't. I called them. Someone new, but someone I know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-9"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Did you ever consider being happy for me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-10"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Briefly. You ordering the wine before she got here…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-11"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>Girls are good, House. And you know it. You solved your case because you cared about that girl.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-12"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>You're demonstrating the illusion of manly confidence. Which means you haven't closed the deal yet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-13"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>I closed the deal. I just like her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-14"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Still?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-15"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>You knew your patient hated having cold feet because you did a physical exam, because you liked her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-16"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>Your theory is I cared, therefore I let her keep her socks on? If that's what love is, then I don't want to have anything to do with it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-17"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>It starts with warm feet but leads to other things. Your mom and I will explain when you're older.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-18"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content>If I'd made her take them off like I should've, I would've seen the toe and would've solved the case days ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-19"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>But you don't care about her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-20"><speaker>AMBER</speaker><content>Of course not. House doesn't care about anyone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-21"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content> Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-22"><speaker>AMBER</speaker><content>Sorry I'm late.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-23"><speaker>HOUSE</speaker><content> Cut throat bitch?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-24"><speaker>WILSON</speaker><content>I call her Amber. Was she on your list?</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>