<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>
<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Charlotte</speaker><content>Bye</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>I… I want to be alone… with my wife.  I’m a selfish S.O.B. I… I never got you to Rio. There was always… one more problem at the stores. You deserved better than that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Charlotte</speaker><content>I love you. I always have.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>I’m ready.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Charlotte</speaker><content>It’s okay.  I know…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>Somebody…  Help her. Help her!</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>54-year-old woman with acute respiratory failure. No anaphylaxis, lung issues or tracheal lesions. Tox screen was clean for coke and amphetamines.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I will give you 30 reasons, one for each pound that cause the apnea which enflamed the epiglottis. Why is our rainbow coalition missing brown and bi?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Thirteen’s with a patient, and Kutner’s dog’s sick. He should be in by lunch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>No apnea because no sleeping problems when she’s sleeping. She spent the last six months caring for her husband who’s dying of heart failure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Reason 31 — whatever whacked the husband’s heart is also whacking her airway and… Oh, good. I thought maybe Kutner was home nursing the rib you broke when you elbowed your way in for credit on the last patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I contributed. And the patient’s illness wasn’t caused by her husband unless lung cancer’s contagious.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Interesting. Not about the patient. That was kinda dull. I thought maybe you were lying to cover for Kutner which sounds noble. Except you’re doing it out of guilt instead of love.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>She visited her sister in Hawaii about six months ago, just before her husband got sick.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Could have picked up melioidosis from one of the islands.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Would have jumped to the husband and finished off him and his lame immune system.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>No tumors, no drugs, no bacteria. Leaves viral — varicella zoster.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Start her on IV fluids and acyclovir.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Can’t. She’s demanding to be released so she can get home to her husband.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>How sweet. They can die together instead of separately, 40 years apart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>She claims he got stronger as soon as she stopped breathing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>The mind can heal the body. Seeing his wife in distress might have actually slowed down his death.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Or he could have just had an adrenaline surge when he saw his chance to hit the singles market. Send her home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>We don’t need to. I had an idea… All by myself.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Charlotte</speaker><content>Eddie?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Found him loitering in the lobby.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Charlotte</speaker><content>You’re still with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>Where the hell else am I gonna go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>And now, with your permission, we’d like to try to make you better.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Mother</speaker><content>The pageant starts in an hour. You have to do something. There’s something wrong inside her head. It’s like she has no idea what’s going on around her. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I thought she was just flirting with me.  I can fix it, but it’s gonna cost you… $3.75. I’m not just gonna give you my coffee.  Think of it as Costa Rican sober juice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Mother</speaker><content>She’s drunk?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That little minty scent hiding beneath the rose petal perfume and the cherry blossom moisturizer and the morning dew hair spray. You sneak into mommy’s bathroom and gulp some of her mouthwash?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Daughter</speaker><content> Gotta be perfect.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You spit it out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Daughter</speaker><content>Mommy doesn’t.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Treatment worked. Charlotte’s breathing’s back to normal. She’s being discharged.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>She can resume her vigil over her husband who started fading again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Win some, lose some. And strictly speaking, since he’s not my patient, win some. Look at the time. It’s half past “Taub was lying about Kutner.”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>He probably went to a comic book fest, spent the night at some Wonder Woman’s lair. I’m sure he’ll —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Find out what or who he’s doing. Either way, Cuddy’s gonna want me to write it under “reason for termination.”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>That Kutner?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Charlotte.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Nurse</speaker><content>O2 sat and S-T are normal. It’s not her airway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> You’re okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>Yeah. Don’t worry about me. She’s in pain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Pulse is rapid and regular. No fluid in her lungs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>What’s happening?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I don’t know.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Kutner. It’s Foreman and Thirteen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Where are you going? House didn’t ask us to find out where he wasn’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>If you wanna climb a fifth floor fire escape…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content> This might be faster.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Kutner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Man/boy heaven. Surprised he ever leaves.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content> There’s nothing on his calendar. His pager’s still here.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Oh, God.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I need an ambulance at 410 Willis. Apartment 5-C. 28-year-old male. Single gun shot wound to the right temple.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>No pulse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Alert Princeton Plainsboro. Have a trauma unit ready. His pupil’s dilated. His head’s swollen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Still no pulse! Come on, Kutner!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Let me try.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>He’s cold. Eric!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He didn’t say anything? To any of you? Family problems? Bad relationship? Financial pressures?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>His parents were shot right in front of him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Parents are ancient history.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Not to someone who actually cares.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He didn’t slit his wrists and… peacefully drift away. He shot himself. He didn’t leave a note. That means panic. Which could have been preempted if the idiots who worked alongside him for 80 hours a week had seen this coming.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>You’re blaming us?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Just trying to figure it out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>We would have helped him if he had reached out to us. He didn’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>We should have picked up on something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>This isn’t our fault! Something like 25% of suicidal people show no outward signs of depression.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No. 25% of suicidal people have friends who didn’t notice anything and don’t want to feel guilty.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Killing himself also kills all other options. Makes Kutner an idiot. So pity, yes. But guilt, no.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>That’s what you wanna tell yourself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>We still have a patient. Actually, two. One worsening, one who should be worsening.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You can’t be in denial about Kutner and the husband.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>It’s possible Eddie’s body is willing itself to live.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, call the tabloids. Tell them you just witnessed the miracle of slightly increased kidney function.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Maybe we should pass this file over to another doctor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And the next one too? The one after that? How many files till it’s okay that Kutner’s dead?  Cardiac enzymes means she didn’t have a heart attack. No vision problems means no mitochondrial disease.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-20"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Could be a metabolic disorder, acidosis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-21"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Blood pH was normal. Polyserositis would inflame the membranes near her epiglottis and the heart’s pericardium, causing the chest pain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-22"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>I’m sorry. I’ve hired a grief counselor whom I’m sure none of you will see and I’m offering time off, which I’m sure none of you will take. But just know it’s available. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-23"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Polyserositis fits. Start her on indomethacin. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-24"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>If you’d rather not deal with this case…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-25"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I’m fine. Despite what Wilson will say.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-26"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>He hasn’t come to you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-27"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Pretty sure he has mah-jongg Tuesday mornings. I assume he thinks I will work through this better if I don’t have to keep flicking his wings off my shoulder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-28"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>You didn’t even have an inkling?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-29"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I know his fantasy football team cratered. Figured he’d gotten over it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-30"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Well… Sorry for your loss.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-31"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Thanks. But it’s not my loss.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-32"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Then I’m sorry you don’t think it is. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-33"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Patient’s membranes aren’t gonna heal themselves.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-34"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Taub went to run the treatment. We’d like to go see Kutner’s parents.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-35"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I’ll join you. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Polyserositis damages the protective covering of the tissue around the organs. The indomethacin is simply an anti-inflammatory but it should fix it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Charlotte</speaker><content>Just make the pain stop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>Charlotte… Close you eyes. Now… pretend you finally made it down to Rio. You’re on the balcony of a… some fancy hotel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Charlotte</speaker><content>You never talk like this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>Yeah, just shut up and let me do this.  And you’re on that balcony, and you’re watching the Mardi Gras.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Charlotte</speaker><content>It’s called Carnival. And I don’t wanna go without you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>I want you to. And I want it to be everything you’ve ever dreamed of.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Sorry to interrupt… but I’d like to run one more test… on you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Julia Kutner</speaker><content>This is the first day we got him. He was six. Sweetest little boy you ever met.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Must have been scary, going through a trauma and then being handed off to a new family.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Julia Kutner</speaker><content>We kept telling him to call us Richard and Julia. But it was always Mr. and Mrs. Kutner. And on his ninth birthday, we gave him a chemistry set. Lawrence always loved blowing things up. And he said, “Thanks, Mom. Thanks, Dad.” That’s who we were from then on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>He was pretty special. We were lucky to have him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Julia Kutner</speaker><content>You spent the most time with him. He spoke so highly of all of you. Do you have any idea?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Wish we did. We all —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It was his name. He was conflicted, didn’t know where he fit in, being ripped out of his world and stuck into yours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Julia Kutner</speaker><content>We encouraged him to hold onto his heritage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It’s hard to still be Lawrence Choudhary when everyone sees you as Lawrence Kutner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Julia Kutner</speaker><content>It was his idea to take our name.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Then you should have said no.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>All his Anglo name gave him was the illusion that he was someone he wasn’t. You were being emotional, not rational. You didn’t understand him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>Richard Kutner</speaker><content>We loved that boy, you son of a bitch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You wanted to make him happy by shutting out his pain. When he looked happy, you assumed the pain had gone. It just got buried deeper, leaving him tormented about who he was until finally he put a bullet —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-16"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>House! Go back to the hospital.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I’m sorry about your son.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Indomethacin had no effect. She’s still in pain. Rules out polyserositis. I ran a hormone panel on Eddie. His prolactin’s above normal. Means he’s actually improving. Body chemistry changes for all sorts of reasons — stress, fear… Why not love? But maybe he’s going into some sort of remission/</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You haven’t asked if I learned anything relevant from the Kutners.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>If you had, I’m sure you would have mentioned it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Or you’re afraid there is something relevant. Which would mean you could have saved him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I don’t buy that suicide is always a cry for help. Sometimes you just don’t want help.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Good thing you got some. Or you’d have tried again and gotten it right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>She doesn’t have Wegener’s. Kidney function’s normal. It’s not byssinosis. It’s not mitral valve stenosis. Nothing fits.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If it doesn’t fit any diagnosis, it just leaves one diagnosis.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I’m Dr. House. You have hypertrophic cardiomyopathy. His heart is too weak. Yours is too strong. Good news is it’s fixable. We induce a massive heart attack and kill off the extra muscle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Charlotte</speaker><content>You wanna give me a heart attack?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It’s only dangerous if your heart is normal size. But since all the —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>Are you serious?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No. This is actually very annoying and I’m getting really bored of lying to patients to scare them into telling me the truth.  She’s faking. And yes, if she keeps faking I’m going to eventually do something that will kill her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>How could she be… The windpipe thing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That was real. Treatment made her better. But good for her was bad for you which was bad for her. So she made herself bad. It’s all so simple. She figured the sicker she was, the longer you’d hang on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>Charlotte?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>Charlotte</speaker><content>We haven’t been this close for years. I wanted to hang on to that. Ow!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh, please. People hate reruns.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>Charlotte</speaker><content>It’s my leg. I swear this is real!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What, you pinky swear or you just plain swear? Because —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-13"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>How can she fake that? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>She can’t.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So, what can shred an epiglottis and make muscle disappear?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Mr. and Mrs. Kutner. They caused Kutner’s death. Why not Charlotte’s?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Mourning period’s over. Foreman’s sense of irony is back. I was wrong about the ethnic reason. Step one — change your name back. Step two — if step one fails — move to Bangalore. Step fourteen, if step thirteen doesn’t work, kill yourself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>So what now? You gonna insult your way through his Rolodex till you find someone with an answer?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I’ve been polite to the friends I’ve called. All of whom were useless.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>They weren’t useless. They just didn’t know anything more than we did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Tomato, tomah-to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>MS. Weakens myelin sheath, compromises nerve conduction. I’m talking about Charlotte, the one who’s still alive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content> You two, stick her in an MRI. Confirm MS.  And you, run the echo on Eddie that you’re planning to do behind my back to see if his heart’s improving.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Did you let me hire a pervert?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Kutner’s police background check from when he started. He was charged with indecent exposure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Kutner streaked at the Penn-Dartmouth football game. Precisely the kind of thing you’d expect him to do. It’s okay. You should be upset. He thought like you, pushed boundaries like you —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If he thought like me, he would know that living in misery sucks marginally less than dying in it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Just a few more minutes then we’ll get you back to Eddie. What’s it like — 30 years with the same man?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>Charlotte</speaker><content>Great for me. Good for him, I hope.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>You don’t think he loves you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>Charlotte</speaker><content>I think he always loved me in his way, just not in a “spend time with me or show emotion or any affection for me” sort of way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Why did you stay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>Charlotte</speaker><content>I didn’t need him to feel about me the way I did about him. Love… doesn’t… </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Charlotte?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>I’ve heard stories of cancer patients going into spontaneous remission. You think this might be that sort of thing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>It’s unlikely, but you never know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>If I just had a little more time… be with Charlotte, try and do better by her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Yeah, maybe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>You don’t think I mean it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I think you mean it now. I think it’s much easier to mean it than to do anything about it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>Ha.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Chamber walls are barely moving. I’m sorry.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>He needs a friend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I can’t deal with this and House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>You need a friend too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You couldn’t give a crap what I need. You just want someone to take care of him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content> He told Kutner’s parents it was their fault.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Ruptured spleen means it’s not MS.  What are you doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> Waiting for you to fix her spleen so we can biopsy it for rheumatoid arthritis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I’ll do it. Go home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>She’s not your patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>And Kutner wasn’t my friend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Kutner wanted to die. Charlotte doesn’t. So in a contest for my concern and interest, she wins.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Okay, either you’re a cold-hearted bastard or you’re too miserable to face it. Go home and cry. It’s not rheumatoid arthritis. Her liver’s scarred. Whatever she’s got, it’s spreading.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>For the record, I’m uncomfortable violating a dead colleague’s dignity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It’s only violating it if you find something. Good to see you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>What are we looking for?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He was hiding. Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Shame? Fear? Are you okay? It’s okay not to be okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content> “Colonial Warrior Blaster. Number One One.” He spent months tracking this down. He had passions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>He was obviously in pain. Does it really matter why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He hung the bad with the good.  His loss beside a reminder of what he’d gained. Means he was open about the pain. Should mean that if it got worse, he had no reason to hide it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Here’s how we’re going to handle this, House. We’re going to leave here and go to the closest bar and drink and tell stories about the time Kutner almost blew up an OR. And pass out in our own sick. Sound like a plan?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What am I missing?  You’ve got that look. You figured this out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You’re not here because you care about Kutner. You’re here because it’s a mystery. You’re here for the puzzle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What if I didn’t miss anything ‘cause there’s nothing to miss? He didn’t kill himself. He was murdered.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Epiglottis, spleen and now her liver which is operating at 20% and deteriorating fast.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Autoimmne hepatitis? Did you page Foreman?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Took up Cuddy’s offer of time off. Normal thyroid means no hepatitis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Could be amyloidosis. Amyloid buildup hits the organs, tissue —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Her muscles wouldn’t have atrophied. You run the echo on the husband?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Heart’s still failing. The improvement was only temporary.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I prefer the less subtle answer: You were right, House. So… Less time proving why hubby isn’t dead, more time proving why Kutner is.  Motives for murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>House… it was a suicide. The police have already investigated.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>They investigated what they saw, not what they didn’t saw. Talk to friends, classmates, pizza delivery guy. And draft Foreman. He can make calls through his tears.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Is that “No, I’m not calling my boyfriend, who apparently called my boss instead of me to say he wasn’t coming in?” ‘Cause it’s really not fair to have that much subtext in one syllable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-12"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>We all want to know why Kutner did it but we’re not gonna waste time chasing ghosts.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You’re not remotely curious?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-14"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Only why a man who embraces the rational is suddenly pursuing the irrational.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>She could have alpha-1 anti-trypsin deficiency. Run her AAT proteins.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>It’s too soon after your surgery.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>Charlotte</speaker><content>You can ask that someone get your organs when you die, right? Even if the donor bank turned them down?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Individual donors can bypass the registry, but there are a lot of other factors… Blood type —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>Charlotte</speaker><content>I’ve given him blood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>It’s not just —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>Charlotte</speaker><content>Please. If I go before him, I want you to give him my heart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>This isn’t over yet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>Charlotte</speaker><content>For me. But it is for him, isn’t it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Remy Hadley. I also answer to Thirteen. I sometimes sleep with you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I know I should have called. I just need some time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Alone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I’ve worked through a lot of bad stuff in my life. Always done it solo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content> So I should go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I’m sorry.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>IT’s been trying to close out Kutner’s email account. Apparently someone’s still logged onto it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It wasn’t hard to figure out that his password was Kutner. He did what they tell you not to do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>He wasn’t murdered.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>But his parents were. And the guy who killed them is coming up for parole.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>He’s coming up for parole. He’s not out on parole.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Kutner testified at every one of his hearings. The guy wouldn’t be the first to see the clock ticking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>He was killed by his own gun.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Which he bought years ago, obviously for self-defense.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>In the temple. Cops found residue.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Right. The murderer would never try to make it look like suicide. That would be unethical.  You haven’t asked about my patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-11"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>You’re waiting on an AAT protein results.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Means you checked up to see that I’m still on it. You wanna transfer the case but you won’t because you think it’s the only thing that’s holding me together. Relax. Either I’m right or I’m wrong. We’ll know soon enough.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-13"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Find what’s killing your patient. And then I’ll find you another patient.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>What happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Nurses found her like this. She broke into the cart and injected whatever she could grab. Dumb way to look worse for Eddie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>She wasn’t trying to look worse. She was trying to kill herself. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> She’s stable. But whatever was left of her liver is definitely shot now. And there’s no change in Eddie.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So, thanks to her idiotic move, she’s dead in 24 hours if she doesn’t get a new liver.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>It was selfless. She loves him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>How does that disagree with what I just said?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Test was negative for AAT deficiency. Myelofibrosis fits but testing takes at least 48 hours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>We should try a partial donation from a live donor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Damage is too severe. She needs a whole new liver.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>No diagnosis, no liver. No liver, no living.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What do you know. It is myelofibrosis.  Says so right here. Who wants to tell Cuddy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-9"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>How many times have you lied to the transplant committee?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Just twice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-11"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>How many times has it worked?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I don’t quite see how that’s relevant.  Cheese it. It’s the coppers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-13"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content> We’re not just going to leave them to die while you fixate on Kutner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Technically, he’s not our patient. So I’m really only leaving her to die.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-15"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>We’ve already explored the usual options. Shouldn’t we at least explore unusual ones?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Absolutely.  Don’t worry. This is why God gave me two ears.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-17"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Kutner would say we should just come clean with Cuddy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Wow. If only he were here to say that. I’m sure Cuddy would be bound to fall for the old, “Hey, the dead guy won’t mind if we’re wasting —”</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Need an incurable romantic to talk to an incurable romantic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Kutner wasn’t murdered.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You deduced that by removing your sunglasses to the strains of a Who song?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Suicide means you could have helped him. Murder lets you off the hook.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Needs a liver. Has a liver.  He can make a partial donation. The faster he agrees, the faster she gets to not die.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Partial won’t be enough. She needs a whole liver and he’d never survive the procedure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Nice symmetry, huh?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content> He dies on the table and you give her his whole liver.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If he’s gonna do this, he’s gonna do this for love. I though he should talk to someone who spoke the language.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>You want me to die on the table.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>We don’t want you to. Your wife needs you to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>My heart?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Is still dying. You have a couple of days at most. But this could buy us enough time to save her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>When can I say good-bye?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>You can’t. If she knew what we were planning, would she be okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-7"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>She’ll resent me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-8"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>She’ll be alive. Nothing else matters.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>You can’t do the transplant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Only if he said no. But your urgent hovering means he said yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>His fingers have nodules. I think his doctors misdiagnosed him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Or you sprinkled too much wishful thinking in your tea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Obese man with lung cancer — Two easy explanations for his heart failure. Nodules can mean something else. Something curable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Go back to the ER. My thanks to you and your cold feet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-7"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>What’s going on? I’m giving you a shot at a cool result. Better yet, a chance to prove other doctors idiotic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Except you’re wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-9"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>You figure that out by taking off your sunglasses to the strains of a Who song?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The guy who killed Kutner’s parents died of an aneurism two months ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-11"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Kutner hid from everyone. You didn’t get a chance to save him. No one did. Run the tests. Find out if you have a chance to save Eddie.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Bad news. Love can’t save you. On the other hand, mold can.  Your heart failure was caused by a fungal infection called cardiac blastomycosis. It started as nodules in your lungs which every doc, except one, mistook for cancer. It’s very rare, very curable. I’m starting you on itraconazole.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>But how come I was getting better without the medicine?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Your emotional state bumped your catecholamines which helped raise your prolactin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>My emotional state?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Three months of treatment, you’ll be back to your buff, chiseled self.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>I don’t want the treatment. Do the transplant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>But you’d be trading the certainty that you’ll live for the uncertainty that she’ll live.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-8"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>I was ready to die anyway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Now you get to be nicer to your next wife.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-10"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>If you won’t do it, release me. And when I get hit by a car and show up in your morgue, you can give her my liver then.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>You’re basically asking us to commit murder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I was yesterday too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-3"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>There’s a difference when he has 20 years to live instead of two days.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Not really. Not legally.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-5"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>That’s your way of convincing us to do this, by saying it’s no more immoral?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The idiot is gonna do this with or without us. This way we can protect the organ.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-7"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>We should be protecting him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So we strap him to the bed, wait till his wife dies?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-9"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>I’m not doing this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I will. We’ve already had one pointless death.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>Charlotte</speaker><content>Eddie, what’s going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>I don’t know. He just came and got me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Your husband has a curable disease, but he wants to die so he can give you his liver. Are you okay with that or would you rather he take the treatment?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-4"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>You son of a bitch!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-5"><speaker>Charlotte</speaker><content>Eddie, don’t!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-6"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>You have to let me do this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Charlotte, can you hear me? </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="34"><utterance uid="34-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>She spiked a fever. LP shows her white cells through the roof. She’s infected everywhere.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I should fire you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Just did what you failed to do, convince Eddie to live and let his wife die.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-4"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Infection means we have a new clue.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And a full two or three hours to figure it out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-6"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Sarcoidosis hits the spleen and the liver.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>She would have lung issues.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Scleroderma inflames the tissue.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No skin or GI problems.  What is she hiding?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You don’t know that —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Either we have all the clues and we’re idiots or we don’t have all the clues.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-12"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Possible exposure, people, places.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Both.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="35"><utterance uid="35-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Bad lie. Did you really think the beaches in Hawaii were just like the beaches in Rio? The disease bearing sand flies are completely different.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-2"><speaker>Eddie</speaker><content>She’s never been to Rio.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Who’d you go with?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-4"><speaker>Charlotte</speaker><content>Why are you doing this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I don’t actually need to know who it was. I just need to know that you went so we can know that you have visceral leishmaniasis. But since Lancelot there was ready to die for you, he might want the answer to both.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-6"><speaker>Charlotte</speaker><content> Last year… It was nobody you know. Rio was supposed to be ours. I got tired of waiting. I’m so sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Start her on antimony and have Cuddy find her a liver.  They were ready to die. But for guilt, not love.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You can’t feel that much guilt without love.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="36"><utterance uid="36-1"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>New York Mercy’s medevacing the liver. It should be here…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Tell them to turn around. Charlotte’s treatment isn’t taking. We diagnosed it too late.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-3"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Everyone’s heading over to Kutner’s funeral. You’re welcome to ride with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I’m gonna stay with Charlotte.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-5"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>She bought you some time to save Eddie. It’ll give her death some meaning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>No. It won’t. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="37"><utterance uid="37-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I was wrong about you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, you weren’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You’re in pain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And you’re romanticizing. Again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You worked with him every day for two years and you never saw this coming.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No one saw it coming.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>But you see everything coming. This has never been about what you missed. This is about why you missed it. You’re terrified that you’re losing your gift, losing… who you are. And I’m terrified of what you’d do then.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Unless you feel there’s more to do here to cure me, don’t you have a funeral to go to?</content></utterance>
</scene>

</script>