<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>
<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Originally aired</speaker><content>April 13, 2009</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Man in Crowd</speaker><content>You made your point. Now how about letting us do our jobs?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content>Our point will be made when your company stops tearing down this mountain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Second Man</speaker><content>Then who’s gonna feed our kids? You?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content>If you really cared about your kids, you’d want them to have air to breathe when they grow up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Second Man</speaker><content>What’d you say, you son of a bitch?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Susan</speaker><content>You guys aren’t the problem. You’re being hurt more than anyone. You breathe in that coal dust.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content>Coal is the dirtiest energy on earth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Policeman</speaker><content>Gonna need some backup.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content>Not enough for you thugs to assault the environment?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Susan</speaker><content>Doug. Please, don’t. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content>Susan? Susan! You okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Policeman 2</speaker><content> She needs to get to a hospital.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content>She’s just dehydrated. We have medics here. Let ‘em give her fluids.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Policeman 2</speaker><content>She has no pulse. Either unhook your arm, or I’m gonna break it off. Either way, this protest is over.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Man in Crowd</speaker><content>The protest is over now! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content> All right. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Susan</speaker><content>What happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>Policeman 2</speaker><content>You passed out. It’s okay. Just dehydrated.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-20"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content>;You know we’ll be back.  We’ll be back!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-21"><speaker>Policeman 2</speaker><content>Hey, stop screwing around.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-22"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content>I’m not… screwing around. I just can’t…  I can’t stand up.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I need to push back our getaway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>No you don’t. Found you a board. Perfect size to learn on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I’m just postponing. O’Neill from Philly General wants me to get a patient in to see House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>So?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I meant so, that’s five seconds to hand House the file, 30 for him to question your real motives, a minute for witty comments comparing the length of your legs to Thirteen’s… Plenty of time left over for the shore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I need to make sure he doesn’t toss the file in the trash as soon as I’m out of sight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Babe, can’t you repay the favor on another case? After last week, I could really use a break from this place. We both could.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Once I’m sure he’s really on the case, then we’re out of here. And these legs and every other part of me will be all yours. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>He’s seen three different specialists.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Interesting. Almost as interesting as you trying to step into Kutner’s shoes just days after he stepped out of them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I am not shoe shopping. I’m just trying to repay a favor to his referring doctor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>What’s the mystery? The nutcase spends all his free time wreaking havoc at toxic waste dumps.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Tox screen’s negative. No neurological, muscular or cardiovascular abnormalities.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>The guy cares about the environment. That makes him a nutcase?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>He’s a single guy in his 20s. He cares about getting his hybrid waxed by girls who care about the environment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>See? Not a nutcase. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>He’s probably just faking so he can sue the cops and get a six-figure settlement.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>If he was trying to fake an illness, why would he consent to be seen by the best diagnostician in the country?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Now who’s trying to get her hybrid waxed? We need to do a vestibular caloric test. See if the balance problem starts above or below the neck.  And when I say “we,” I mean “you.” You’re the one with the favor to repay, not them.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I’m going to be injecting ice water in your ear canal. If the resulting eye movements are at all erratic, then the balance problem is in your inner ear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content> Those in every room?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I think so.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content>Can you get rid of them? Preferably from every room. They use over 30 pesticides to grow commercial flowers. You’d think the medical industry would be a lot more —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Concerned with medicine? Let’s fix your body. Then you can go back to fixing the earth. This is gonna get a little uncomfortable. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content>I just spent 14 hours chained to a tire.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Most doctors would recommend —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content>Our planet’s headed for destruction. Coastlines under water. A million species extinct. Whoa.  Feels like I’m tumbling head over heels.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>That’s normal. Sometimes this test causes vertigo  and nausea.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Cameron just brought me a case.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Cameron is happy in the ER. There’s no way she wants her nose back on your grindstone.  Egg white omelet, no bacon, whole wheat toast.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I say it’s not my grindstone she’s after. And not her nose she wants on it. She and Chase are practically living together. What did you just order?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>An omelet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Since when do you pass on the swine? And wheat toast? Might as well eat a sheet of sandpaper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Yes. But I don’t like eating the same thing two days in a row.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Your bro’s nurse not lovin’ the love handles?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I’m just not in the mood for bacon. And you’re obviously trying to avoid talking about Kutner. Which is odd, because you spent a whole week obsessing about why —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He’s no longer on my team. I’m sorry he’s no longer on my team. Nothing else to talk about.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You’re wearing the watch he gave you for Secret Santa.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Five functions, including a stopwatch to time how long it takes you to ask me if I’m okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You gonna order?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Not hungry. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>It’s just weird. She’s brought cases before but he’s never made her run the tests.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Maybe he’s looking for someone to mother him after what happened.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>The only kind of mothering House wants involves a bullwhip, leather diapers and a credit card.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Mommy’s home. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Test made the patient lose his lunch. But his calorics are normal. His inner ear is fine and he still can’t balance himself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>How many normal test results do we need to know the patient’s a granola-filled phony?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>He’s not lying about his symptoms.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>And you know this because —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>She changed her shoes. If he was faking, he’d have vomited on the other side of the bed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Sparring with the police and chaining yourself up for days can cause stress. Stress screws with the heart and arteries. Carotid atherosclerosis could cause a loss of balance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Wouldn’t show up on a CT or MRI.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Could also be our only warning before a massive stroke.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Do a Holter and a carotid Doppler. See if his heart skips for more than the spotted owl.  Although I didn’t say “we.” If I had… {Cameron leaves instead.]</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content>Sorry if this is screwing up the test. Been hiccupping a lot lately but…  not as bad as this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>How much is “a lot” and how long is “lately”?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content>It’s been on and off for about a week. Maybe a few hours a day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Did you tell the doctors in Philly about it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content>They didn’t seem to think it was any big deal.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Hey, so we’re still leaving tomorrow, aren’t we?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I’m not sure. The referring doctors didn’t realize that his hiccups were —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Hiccups?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>With this duration and intensity, most likely pathological, and it could mean it’s serious.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Are you avoiding me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>So I shouldn’t be at all concerned that you’re treating another doctor’s patient for hiccups instead of going on a vacation I spent a week planning. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>There is a reason I need to stay with this case a while longer, but I can’t tell you what it is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>So you admit you lied to me. And now you’re asking me to trust you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content> Okay.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>No sight of heart or arterial problems but he’s been hiccupping on and off for over a week.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Nice. I’m hooked. You can get back to your shift at the ER. Except, as far as the ER is concerned, you’re on vacation, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I postponed a trip because I’m concerned about the patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Explains why you ditched Chase and came to differentials, not why you ran the tests.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>You told me to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, I’m not your boss, as you usually take great pleasure in pointing out. Hey, you don’t still have the hots for me, do you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I care about the patient and I care about the people who work on your team. They’ve been through a lot lately. I just thought I —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Was Florence Nightingale. Yeah. You’re gonna nurse us back to spiritual and mental oneness. That would make sense if we were having this conversation a week ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Think what you want — that I’m here to get a job, that I’m here to wrap you in swaddling clothes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The problem is, I think neither. Because neither makes sense. The only thing that does… doesn’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Pathological hiccups plus inability to balance. Go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What she said.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Brain would connect the two.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It could, if Cameron hadn’t already CT’d his head. Empty as her boyfriend’s calendar.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>What does this have to do with Chase?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Not sure yet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-18"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Patient is on a Jihad against commercial flowers. He’s picketed several nurseries. Organophosphate poisoning can cause both hiccups and —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-19"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>No GI problems. No hyper-salivation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-20"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>It’s possible it’s not connected to a protest. MS wouldn’t show on the CT and his name’s Swenson. Scandinavians have an increased susceptibility to MS.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Better theory than he’s faking it. The clogs have it. Do a lumbar puncture to confirm MS.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-22"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>I guess we’ll just continue to twiddle our thumbs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-23"><speaker>House</speaker><content>God, I hope that’s a euphemism.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-24"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>How am I supposed to do a lumbar puncture on a patient with intractable hiccups?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-25"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I’m trying to figure out what that could be a euphemism for.  You’ll find a way. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>You’re not worried House is gonna be pissed you’re helping me do the test?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>He said find a way. And you did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>How do you think House is doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>That why you’re here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>No it isn’t. Even if House was messed up by Kutner’s suicide, it wouldn’t matter. He already thinks life is nasty, brutish and long. And misery helps his diagnostic skills. All of which you know so… Why are you here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Which answer would you believe?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>If you want Kutner’s place, it’s fine with me. I could use someone else with the stones to stand up to House. But you’ve gotta know it’s gonna blow up your relationship with Chase.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>All I did was postpone a three-day trip.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>With Chase. To be with House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Ordering IV chlorpromazine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>This could still be neurological. You could cloud his mental status.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>You wanna get the needle in his spine or you wanna talk?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You and House been talking about filling Kutner’s slot?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Yeah. We went straight from the funeral to Human Resources. You interested in getting back on the team?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I’m interested in knowing if Cameron’s interested. She’s been running all the tests for House’s case.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Well, she hasn’t said anything to me. But I guess, uh, the referring doctor might have asked her to keep an eye on him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Do you think Cameron’s in love with House?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>That is a ridiculous question. She’s in love with you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Are you in love with House?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>That… is an even more ridiculous question.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Two questions. Zero answers. Think I can extrapolate from there. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Franni</speaker><content>Dr. House?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Sorry, I’m just the Zone delivery guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Franni</speaker><content>I’m, uh, Doug Swenson’s wife.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>His history said the environmental kamikaze was single.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>Franni</speaker><content>He, um, he probably didn’t want me to worry. He told me he was in jail with some of the other protesters.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah. No worries there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>Franni</speaker><content>He’s in jail a lot. Not so often in the hospital. I searched his e-mail and I found the referral to you yesterday.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You must really love your husband and travel by rickshaw. It only took you 18 hours to get here.  Who eats kale? It’s so bland it doesn’t even taste like kale.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>Franni</speaker><content>Uh, I had to find somebody to take care of our four-year-old son. Doug’s all right, isn’t he?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I have no idea. I know he’s an idiot. And now I’ve learned that he’s a liar. So we’re making a —  Who told you I was in here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>Franni</speaker><content>The doctor in the office next to yours said that you might be here.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I got it figured out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>That mean we don’t need to do the LP.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content> I was talking to her. You’re not even supposed to be here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>You want us to stop or not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What? Oh, I don’t care what you do with him. You’re not doing a favor for a doctor in Philly. You’re doing a favor for an oncologist in North Jersey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I’m spying on you for Wilson?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Spying, preemptive grief counseling.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Wilson sees you ten times more than I do. He’s a better liar and he wouldn’t have to cancel a vacation to do it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Good points. Also doesn’t explain the diet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>Franni</speaker><content>What does any of this have to do with my husband?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Nothing. Meet Mrs. Environmental Nutbag. Or did you keep your maiden name?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-12"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>He’s married?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yep. Got a kid too. Double threat. Eco-freak and deadbeat dad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-14"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-15"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Sorry… Parentally challenged.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-16"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>No, his neck.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-17"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>It’s torticollis. Reaction to the chlorpromazine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It’s not just a spasm. It’s swollen.  Crunchy.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>It’s definitely not MS. Crunching sounds were caused by an air leak between his lungs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Leak in his mediastinum could have been caused by prolonged hiccups.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>More likely, it was the neck spasm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Most likely, it was there all along. We just didn’t notice it till the other symptoms made it worse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So, what causes loss of balance, pathological hiccups, and a hole in his Gloria Steinem?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>He was protesting a lumber mill last fall. Sarcoid’s been linked to pine forests.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No. His A.C.E. levels were normal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Progressive systemic sclerosis. Guy practically lives in industrial waste sites. If a solvent got absorbed through his lungs, caused an autoimmune firestorm…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Start him on IV methyl-prednisolone for systemic sclerosis. Do a full work-up to confirm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-10"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>By myself?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Without yourself.  Grab a bat.  Grab some pine. Time to bring in the first string.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-12"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You obviously want to be here. I can’t figure out why. I wanna see where you go when you can’t be here. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>You know what vacation means, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>You’re here because of House, Chase or overtime issues.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Well, if it’s all right with you, I’d rather communicate with Chase by communicating with Chase.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Are you in love with House?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>You… are not concerned about me. You’re marking your territory.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>You shouldn’t be involved with House. Neither should I. Neither should anyone. You and Chase are good together. Just don’t screw it up.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>Franni</speaker><content>When are you gonna stop this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content>How can you ask me to stop?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>Franni</speaker><content>You’re in a hospital. You have a son.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>The steroids ought to get him breathing normally again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>But autoimmune diseases are serious. It might not be a bad idea to take some time at home. Rest up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content>I can’t just quit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>Franni</speaker><content> Do you hate us that much?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content>I love you. And I love our son. But why should he matter more than everyone else’s?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-9"><speaker>Franni</speaker><content>He does.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-10"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content>Why? Because he’s biologically connected to me? There’s no rational reason.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-11"><speaker>Franni</speaker><content>He’s our son!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-12"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content>And he’s gonna need to drink clean water. And breathe clean air. I’m doing this for him too.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Come on in, House.  Because who else is it going to be at 10:30 at night? And, no thanks, I already ate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Didn’t ask you to dinner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>But you were going to. And, when I explained that I’d eaten hours ago, you were going to move on to your real entrée, rifling through my kitchen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Hmmm. Inviting me to search your kitchen. Means that you know that I’d find nothing. Or that you know I’d find something so you’re hoping that I’m going to assume the former and I won’t bother to look. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Or it means it’s late, I’m tired, I know you’re here to advance some paranoid theory based on a single egg white omelet, and I’d like to get it over with so we can both go to sleep.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Your single omelet theory conveniently overlooks the grassy knoll you had for lunch today. Vegetable and grain gag-athon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>The Warren Commission found no evidence of a second lunch. Possibly because it was stolen from the doctor’s lounge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You’re not getting any fatter. Your medical records were clean.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You checked my — ?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You’re alone tonight, so it’s Kutner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-11"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>How could Kutner have any conceivable —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Your patients live, your patients die. You float above it all like a medical colossus. But a fellow doctor dies…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-13"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>That’s brilliant. Kutner was a wake-up call that if I didn’t eat healthier, I might kill myself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Mortality is mortality.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-15"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>And… Ice cream is ice cream.  Full fat content. Quadruple fat content. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Stuff you haven’t eaten just proves you haven’t eaten it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-17"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You were hoping for evidence of stuff I have eaten? First door on the right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-18"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content> Excruciating pain in his left leg! Acute onset about ten minutes ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-19"><speaker>Franni</speaker><content>What are you doing to him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-20"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I assume they were checking for vascular pulsations. Either it’s negative or he’s a big wuss.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-21"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>It’s not a tumor or an aneurism.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-22"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Metabolic bone disease?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-23"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Bone density’s normal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-24"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>But the bone covering might not be! If it’s osteomyelitis, an infection eating away at his periosteum —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-25"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That explains the pain. Odds are it’s a subclinical infection that we made worse with the steroids we gave him. Start him on IV antibiotics. X-ray his legs to confirm osteomyelitis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-26"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Cameron’s already done a full set of lower-body x-rays.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-27"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The infection obviously flared. Do ‘em again. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-28"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Even if I had changed my diet, what possible reason could I have for hiding it from you?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Ankle, tibia, fibula all look normal. No inflammation, no signs of osteo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Hang in there. We’re almost done.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>You and your wife… You talk about stuff?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Sex.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>No. Anything else?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Money.  I’m gonna go way out on a limb here. Foreman not a Chatty Cathy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Normally, it doesn’t matter. But last week it did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>If you wanna date men, good chance talking won’t be —  His femur’s fractured.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-9"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>That’s impossible. It’s the hardest bone in the body.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>And he broke it lying in bed.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>How can you have a broken femur without so much as a bruise?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Whatever broke it had to do it from within.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Osteogenesis imperfecta?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Brittle bones wouldn’t cause hiccups. Plus, we’d have seen abnormal coloring in the sclerae.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Which leaves cancer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Since when does bone cancer cause hiccups? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Which means it’s not bone cancer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Or it’s not cancer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>House is right. It’d be hard to find a guy outside Chernobyl who’d been exposed to more carcinogens. Pesticide plants, nuclear waste sites.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Tell Chase to repair the break. You two prep him for chemo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You want to blast him with chemo for a cancer we don’t even know he has?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Nope. I wanna blast him for with chemo for a cancer that explains the symptoms.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Intramedullary nail.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Hold on. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>That your House imitation? Some late-breaking epiphany</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I just want you to get a bone biopsy before you insert the pin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>For a broken leg?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>House is prepping him for chemo. Thought it might be worth checking for cancer before pumping him full of poison.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Does Cameron agree with House?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Cameron isn’t on the case anymore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Huh.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Still enjoying your day off, I see.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Why are you prepping him for chemo?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The more interesting question is why do you care?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>You’re not even sure that it’s —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What I mean is, why do you care from here? You can monitor the patient from home. What’s the difference between here and home?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content> You’re not at my home.  This has nothing to do with —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Any other differences? Hmm… there’s less medical equipment, more training bras, and more Vegemite sandwiches. Actually, technically, right now, Chase is here. But that’s because I called him, and you didn’t know that. And it’s irrelevant to my point. Which is… You and Chase are over.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>You are wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You decided that his single drawer of clothes is one drawer too many. But you don’t have the guts to tell him. So… You’re emotionally walking away instead of actually walking away. Which is stupid ‘cause only one of those is good for your heart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content> He’s gonna ask me to marry him. I was looking for some thick socks. Found the ring.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And you want to say no. So I circle right back to his single drawer of clothes —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-12"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I don’t want to say anything. I don’t want him to ask. Not now. Kutner… We’re all a little freaked out. We go home, we just wanna hug someone. We just wanna know everything’s gonna be okay. I don’t want him to propose just ‘cause he’s scared.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>Husband</speaker><content>She’s got a headache, fever. She’s completely exhausted. Tell him about your chest, honey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>Wife</speaker><content>Um —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>Husband</speaker><content>Her breasts are really tender.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You guys have a hot tub?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>Husband</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>She must go to the gym a lot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>Husband</speaker><content>Not in years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Then maybe when you travel on business you zip on down to that complimentary hotel spa.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>Wife</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Sorry, did you just say yes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-11"><speaker>Husband</speaker><content>What the hell’s wrong with her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-12"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Got a minute?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-13"><speaker>Husband</speaker><content>He doesn’t. What’s wrong with her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Sorry. I’m sure she’s got a medical crisis. And I need more time to figure out some leading questions for your wife.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-15"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>What’s going on with Cameron?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>She doesn’t want back on my team and she doesn’t want to jump me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-17"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Okay. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Wha, wha, wha, what? You ask a question. I rule out two possibilities and you’re satisfied? That means you don’t want an answer. You just wanted to know there wasn’t a particular answer. Either you were worried that she wanted back on my team, or you were worried that she wanted back on me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-19"><speaker>Husband</speaker><content>This isn’t a medical crisis, is it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-20"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Could be. A lot of STDs hang in the balance.  I give up. Vinegar compresses four times a day. Any chance I could just leave it at that?  No. Pseudomonas folliculitis. It’s a skin infection from crowded and contaminated hot tubs, which you obviously use, but not with your husband.  Tried to help a sister out.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>The nuclei were all normal. Bone cells were well differentiated. No dysplasia means no cancer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>Franni</speaker><content>That’s good, isn’t it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>We hope so, although it also means we still have no idea what caused the break. How does it feel?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content>It hurts.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>Franni</speaker><content>Is it supposed to look like that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>No. But it’s probably just residual bleeding from the surgery. We should be able to…  I need two units of FFP, right away!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>Franni</speaker><content>Oh my God! What’s happening?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>He’s bleeding out.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Means it’s gotta be cancer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>It’s gotta be, except it’s not. The biopsy was negative.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Biopsies can be wrong. Symptoms can’t.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>All signs point to cancer but you can't blast a cancer you can’t find.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Sure you can. Prep him for total body irradiation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You do realize that’s insane.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Not unless you think the cancer’s cleverly hiding outside his body.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-8"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Steroids already weakened his immune system. That much radiation’ll kill him before it kills the cancer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>And if he doesn’t have cancer, we could cause one or destroy his immune system altogether. The guy could die from an infected toenail.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content> You’d rather do nothing, just let him die on his own?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-11"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I’d rather make his cancer worse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-12"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>That’s like pouring gasoline on a fire. At least total body irradiation’s an actual treatment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content> His idea is better. Pour away.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I lost my mojo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Have you retraced your steps? Does your cleaning lady check your pockets before —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I was clueless about Kutner. I was wrong about Cameron. Taub just came up with an idea that I should have seen long before he did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>No one saw anything coming with Kutner. You hardly ever see Cameron anymore. And you hired Taub to come up with ideas that you wouldn’t have come up with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And I have no idea why you’re eating carrots.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I’m losing my mind. All you got to say is “good”?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>House, a guy you worked with for two years, who you mentored and, yes, possibly even cared about, just blew his brains out. You can’t find the reason, can’t find meaning in it because sometimes there isn’t any. Sometimes… this is all there is. You should be losing it. You’d be crazy not to be off your game. But your mojo is right where you left it. Just… keep playing with it. I gotta go. Help yourself. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I know this is a tough process. At the first sign of any tumors or masses, we can —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>Franni</speaker><content>Start saying prayers?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>It’s gonna be okay. Once we can —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>Franni</speaker><content>No. It’s not gonna be okay. You’re growing his cancer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content> This isn’t the doctors’ fault. I’ve exposed myself to a lot of bad stuff. I knew the risks. I want my life to mean something. If that means I’m destined to… </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>He’s in V-tach and no pulse. Grab the paddles!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>Franni</speaker><content>Oh, God!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Charging. Clear! Charging. Clear!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I’ve been looking for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>And… I’ve been thinking about you. Just hadn’t reached the looking stage yet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Which is the problem. You asked for a day. I gave you two. You told me you had a secret you couldn’t share. I respected that. Now I don’t know what’s worse — blowing off our vacation to hang around House or continuing to blow it off when he won’t hang around you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>If you think I’m the least bit interested in House —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I don’t know what I’m supposed to think.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I know this looks bad. And —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I don’t care how it looks. I care what it is. And you’re not telling me what it is. I’m trying to trust you, but…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I just… I need a little more time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-10"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>This… has nothing to do with House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-11"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Yeah, well it has nothing to do with me, either. Not anymore.  Let me know when I can come pick up my things.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> Nothing on the echo. We drew a troponin level. No signs of myocardial ischemia. All the tests were normal.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Loss of balance. Pathological hiccups. Air leak between the lungs. Broken femur. Now tachycardia. Go!  Come on, give me something. Give me a bad idea. Maybe I can turn it into a good one.  Fine. Open him up and put in a defibrillator.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>That’s permanent and risky. We don’t even know what, if anything, is wrong with his heart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Redo all the tests. In the meantime, open him up, put in a defibrillator so he can live long enough for you to finish the tests. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Balance, organs, nerves, lungs, bones, heart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> Things you use to make bratwurst.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content> There’s no sign of infection. It’s not a metabolic or autoimmune disease. It’s definitely not cancer. I think.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Definitely not cancer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Aren’t you going to pick?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I’m thinking. Is there a ticking clock?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You already put your money in. You never do that until you decide.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>That’s very observant of you. Too bad you distracted me. Now I’m… thinking I might change my mind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>There’s nothing healthy in that machine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>No, there’s not. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Gummi bears. You hate gummi bears.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-12"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>People can change.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No. And more importantly, I hate them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-14"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> Oh, fine. Then I won’t offer you any.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You manipulative bitch.  You’re not suddenly eating healthy because you want to. You’re eating healthy because you know I don’t want to. I’ve been mooching food for ten years.  Now, either it suddenly started bothering you this week or you’re —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-16"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Screwing with you. It needed to be done. After Amber died, I withdrew, tried to change everything, hoping I’d sort it out. Find some deeper truth. It was a mistake. I should have gone back to normal, to here and now, because that’s all we can every really count on. Things need to get back to normal in your life. And… what could be more normal than me screwing with you and you figuring it out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content> You manipulative bitch.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>We need to put in a cardioverter-defibrillator. It’ll keep your heart beating while we keep looking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content>What does that mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>It means, even if we figure this out, you’ll have to stop protesting anywhere not near a hospital.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Hi! Got a few questions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Uh, we’re about to start doing —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>A hopefully pointless medical procedure. Your life and my mojo hang in the balance. Pesticides are evil, which means that commercial flowers are doused in evil. But plant life is nature’s answer to evil. So you have a garden.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-7"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content>No, we live in an apartment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>A window box, then.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-9"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Potted plants?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-11"><speaker>Franni</speaker><content>Nothing. The commercial growers —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, yeah. They’re evil. Yeah, got it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-13"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>House, I really don’t think we have time for this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Your marriage sucks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-15"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>All marriages suck.  Your marriage sucks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-17"><speaker>Franni</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-18"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content>I love her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He loves a tree in Oregon more than he loves you. But he can’t have sex with it. Unless it’s that slutty oak outside Portland.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-20"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You wanna get to your point?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content>She’s had enough. She’s gonna leave. Or maybe she’s jut not putting out. Whatever. You gotta make it right, right away. You gotta compromise that precious flower principle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-22"><speaker>Franni</speaker><content>Never.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-23"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content> Once.  Three weeks ago. Our anniversary. I missed the dinner to be at that rally. You planned it for months. You were mad. Really mad. I bought you flowers. I brought them home. You were gone. So was your suitcase. I tossed them and bought you the earrings.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-24"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Roses?  Yes. You have sporotrichosis. It’s an infection from the thorn of the rose which, by any other name, is still a cheap marital aid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-25"><speaker>Doug</speaker><content>The flowers are what gave me —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-26"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Lesion on your eighth cranial nerve knocks out your balance. Another on your phrenic nerve gives you serial hiccups. We then spread it to your bones and heart with steroids and insulin-like growth factor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-27"><speaker>Franni</speaker><content>Please tell us that this is good news.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-28"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It’s good news for him. It’s good news for future generations. It’s crappy news for you. He’s gonna be fine. And he’ll never doubt himself again.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>There you go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Damn. I was hoping I would interrupt something.  Your favor’s repaid. Patient’s cured. He’s already packing for another Earth Day extravaganza next week.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>He almost died. He can’t take a few days at home with his family?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>People only change after trauma if they wanted to change before the trauma. Or if they’ve watched too many afterschool specials.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-5"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>You talking about Chase?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I’m talking about you. You lost husband number one. No surprise that the death of a colleague would make you question another long-term lease.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-7"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>You teaching commitment classes? ‘Cause I thought you were too busy with your lecture on —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-8"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I told you I never wanted to dump Chase.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Absolutely. You want him to dump you. It’s totally different. Much less guilt. Either way, you’re out of reasons to avoid him. Kutner was a pretty dumb one to begin with. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="34"><utterance uid="34-1"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I should never have postponed our vacation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content> I should never have planned it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-3"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content> I found the ring in your sock.  I didn’t want you to propose out of some sort of knee-jerk reaction to what happened to Kutner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Well, I guess you don’t have to worry about that anymore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-5"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I’m not. I… I don’t care how it happens. I just want it to happen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Are… Are you proposing to me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-7"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I’m... proposing that… you propose to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>After I broke up with you. After you ruined my planned proposal, you expect me to —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-9"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I’m not expecting.  Hoping.</content></utterance>
</scene>



<scene id="35"><utterance uid="35-1"><speaker>Amber</speaker><content> Solved another case. Busted Wilson.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>