<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>
<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Nicole</speaker><content>Do you see them anywhere?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Fang Dong Wen</speaker><content>Why don't we go back to their house, wait for them there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Nicole</speaker><content>Yeah, 'cause they'll probably answer the door the sixteenth time I knock.  There they are. Hi. I'm sorry I followed you here. I just really wish you could give me a few minutes of your time.  I know you never agreed to make it an open adoption, but I just figured maybe you never had a choice. I mean, it's China, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Nicole</speaker><content>W — what did he say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Fang Dong Wen</speaker><content>He wants you to leave them alone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Nicole</speaker><content>Please.  I just want ten minutes. Learn what you're like, tell you about my life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Fang Dong Wen</speaker><content>He said they have no daughter. I am sorry you wasted a trip.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Nicole</speaker><content>I know that's them.  How does that work? How do I pray?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Fang Dong Wen</speaker><content>You make a wish and lift the Buddha.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Nicole</speaker><content>I wish they could understand how badly I need this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Fang Dong Wen</speaker><content>Now make the wish again. If you cannot lift the Buddha this time, your wish will be granted.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Fang Dong Wen</speaker><content>Are you okay?</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I picked Cameron’s pocket down in ER. I came up with a doozy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>Your mother called — twice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>She's still healthy. This 25-year-old woman, on the other hand…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>Her messages sounded kind of urgent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, that's the way women sound when their spouse of 50 years dies. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Your dad died? Are you —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yep. Fine! Our patient, who's been known to take a few drinks on non-occasions, vomits blood and collapses on a trip to China. Chinese surgeons cut out a foot of bowel, but the pain is worse now than it was before.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>House, call your mom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What are you, my mom?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>We can continue this differential in five minutes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Are those bags under your eyes? You were up all night. You told her, didn't you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I don't know what your daddy issues are, but don't deflect them on me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Told his wife he's been getting some strange. She kicked his adulterous tuchus to the curb.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>Seriously, you told her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Yes, I told her. But no, she did not kick me to the curb. We stayed up late talking. We're going to continue talking. Much like House should be doing with his mother right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Anybody read Chinese? Otherwise, we have no idea what these doctors did to her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Kutner, you're sort of Asian, right? Get it translated.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>What about Meckel's diverticulum? If the surgeons didn't remove the diverticulum, it can cause pain, bleeding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Too high up for a colonoscopy. CT could miss it. Ultrasound's fastest. And since I'm fastest with the ultrasound…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>House, let me do the ultrasound. You need to deal with your dad and stop —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm not deflecting because I'm avoiding something deep. I'm deflecting because I'm avoiding something shallow. Seriously, I'm fine. I didn't even like the man.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No Meckel’s.  Were you there for the rice or the reeducation camps?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Nicole</speaker><content>I was there to track down my biological parents.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Like a salmon returning to the stream where it was born. Did you become whole again, or did you get eaten by bears?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Nicole</speaker><content>They denied my existence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Four parents, and not one of them taught you to cover your mouth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Janice</speaker><content>Oh, my God! It looks like they cut you in half.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>Doctor, we're her parents.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm just a technician. Her doctors will be by later. You can schmooze then.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>Can you let them know that we, uh, we went by her apartment and collected all her medication.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm a technician and a doctor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Nicole</speaker><content>You went through my apartment?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Janice</speaker><content>We found alcohol. We thought you'd quit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content> Did her drinking cause this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>Can you tell her it did?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Licorice root.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Uh, no, thanks. I'm good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I threw it to you for a reason. That's what the Chinese doctors gave her. It contains glycyrrhizin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content> They were treating her for…  SARS?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Not very effectively. But SARS explains the cough, causes hypoperfusion, which explains the ischemic bowel. It's perfect.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Lung involvement isn't very severe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Okay, well, so call it "ARS." Start her on ribavirin and interferon.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Sorry about your father.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm not. Are we done emoting now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>If there's anything I can do, just —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You know, you're right. I don't think I can sleep alone tonight.  And you can tell me that that is liquid Vicodin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>We're giving IG shots to everyone who came in contact with your patient. Shockingly, none of the nurses volunteered to administer yours.  It goes better in a large muscle. Drop your pants.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content> You know, I usually pay tens of dollars to hear that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content> The funeral's tomorrow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>My mom called you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>There is a 3:40 flight out of Newark. If you leave now, you can be in Lexington tonight. Your mother wants you to deliver a eulogy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>"Eulogy," from the Greek for "good word." Now, if she asked me to deliver a bastardogy, I'd be happy to —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Then be a grown-up. Call your mother back and tell her that you're sick with grief, but you're too busy to be there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>She knows when I'm lying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Then start writing.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Nicole</speaker><content>They yanked my brother and sister out of college. Can you please tell them I'm not dying?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>You have SARS. I'm wearing a mask. It's a big deal. Cut 'em some slack.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Nicole</speaker><content>But I am gonna be okay, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>That's what all this stuff is for. We're gonna need the names and numbers of everyone you came in contact with here and in China. Flight numbers, dates…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Nicole</speaker><content>That doctor that I coughed all over… Is he gonna be all right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>So far he's fine.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Nicole</speaker><content>Oh, oooh. It's back. This is where the pain all started.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content> She's tachycardic. Get a crash cart in here!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Janice</speaker><content> What's going on? I need to know what's going on. That's my daughter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>Her liver's failing. It's not SARS.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I am not doing this because I care.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Cuddy drugged me. She… My mom didn't call Cuddy. She called you. I knew you couldn't stay away. I knew you loved me too much.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'm doing this for your mom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm not doing this at all. If there were something to be done, I would have done it in the year he spent dying.  You took my Vicodin? I'm in pain.  One? So the Vicodin is my leash. One'll take the edge off, but it won't give me enough relief for an escape back to Plainsboro. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Where's my phone?  It's the team. It's their ring tone.  Forget it. The patient's blood is on your hands.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>House? You there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm being held against my will. Call the police!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Nicole had a clot in the hepatic vein. Chase sucked it out, saved her liver.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>No signs of a tumor or venous malformations. Nothing that could cause —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>She's an addict.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>Drugs and alcohol wouldn't —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>She's a smoker. Combine smoking with any one of a dozen genetic disorders, and she's a clotting machine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Multiple blood clots would tie together bowel ischemia, lungs, and the liver.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>We need to pinpoint which defect she has so we can start her on the right anticoagulant. Draw her blood. Let's find out which genetic gift her genetic parents gave her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Thanks for calling.  My ring tone for you is "Dancing Queen," by Abba.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>Nicole?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I need to pee. Pull over at the next stop.  I'll just pee on the floor.  You bought used floor mats? That is brilliant. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>There's a rest stop in five miles.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Cane.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>The restroom's right there. You can make it on your own.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I suppose I could talk about the summer he decided he wasn't speaking to me. Two months, not one word. Anything he wanted to say, he typed up and slipped under my bedroom door.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You don't want to say anything, don't say anything, but go. Tell your mom you're sad for her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Just by being there, I’d be lying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>She wants to think, for a moment, that she had a happy family. So give her a gift — lie!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Give me my cane, I'll go to the damn funeral.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I said I'd go to the funeral. I didn't say when.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>We have these two categories: Inside and outside. Patients stay inside. Then, when they're better, we let them go outside.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Nicole</speaker><content>Thanks. But they don't let you smoke inside. So why don't you go back there and give me five minutes outside?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>Make a fist.  Such a beautiful day, we thought we'd do all our doctoring outside.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>Nicole</speaker><content>People stare at me any time I'm out with my family. It's like a puzzle. "Which one of these things doesn't belong?"</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>Belonging's overrated. I was adopted by a white family when I was nine. I like being different. The view's better from the outside looking in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>Nicole</speaker><content>Must be easier to be different when you're a success.  Is that a problem?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>This is why we prefer inside.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You actually keep a flashlight that doesn't need batteries in the trunk? Next to the jacket, emergency water, nail clippers, tooth brush, space blanket —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>When things go wrong, I like to be ready. Will you… please hold the flashlight for a minute?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You know, those aren't just my car keys. My house keys are on there too. Amber gave me that key chain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, she didn’t. Not unless your pet name for her was "Volvo."  A man who would lie about a gift from a dead girlfriend…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Is probably responding to a childish, pointless act of petulance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The struggle to resist one's captors is never pointless. Vive la résistance!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Well, I hate to break it to you, Che, but simple delay won't work. Your mother will hold the funeral till we get there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content> My father was a punctual man, beholden to time. Two minutes late for dinner, you didn't eat. My mother would never disrespect him by starting the funeral late.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Yeah, yeah, you clearly have no issues to work through.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Come on, forget the keys. Call a locksmith. We'll go inside and play "guess that smell" with the truckers while we're waiting. Join me on the dark side.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-11"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> The dark side's done, House. I'm delivering you to your mother, and that's it. I’ve moved on. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>What do you think House would send, the "gentle comfort" arrangement or the "warm thoughts" bouquet? I mean, if he wasn't an ass.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Send one of those giant cookies shaped like a coffin.  His mom would believe it was from him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I didn't tell you so you could send anything. Just wanted you to know the extent to which the man is disconnected from the human race.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content> Took a six-pack of FFP to stop the oozing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>She's bleeding and clotting?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>Plus schistocytes on her smear means it's DIC, which means she's got cancer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>She's young. It could be leukemia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>Normal WBC makes that less likely.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>The belly pain points toward a GI tumor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-10"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>House already did an ultrasound.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-11"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>He wasn't looking for a tumor. Go run a CT.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-12"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I don't buy it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-13"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>CT can find small intestinal cancers that an ultrasound —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-14"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I don't buy House. When my father died, I wound up killing a patient. And I hated the man. Whatever House says or doesn't say, I'm sure the guy's a mess.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>So he was a bastard. He was still your father. You're biologically programmed to have feelings for him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, I'm not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Feelings aren't rational. I know you have trouble with anything that can't be quantified and counted.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He's not my biological father.  I figured it out when I was 12.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Of course. You were a brilliant, socially isolated 12-year-old, and you create a parallel universe in which your life doesn't suck.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I look at the facts. First of all, he was deployed on training exercises off Okinawa during the time I had to be conceived.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>And since you're 150 years old, air travel was impossible.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>His second toe is longer than his big toe. Mine isn't.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>This is sad. You don't believe your mother screwed around —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I have a distinctive red birthmark on my scalp that matches a certain friend of the family.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-11"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>If you believed this story, you wouldn't be telling me about his birthmarks. You'd be telling me about the genetic testing you had done.  And since you haven't mentioned it, obviously, you didn't do it. Because you don't want to — House, what are you doing?  Get your — get off the — there's a cop!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Uh-oh.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>Nicole, lie still. This'll only take a few seconds.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>One millimeter cut through upper abdomen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>She was adopted when the parents thought they couldn't have kids. Then they had three more. She took the message as "thanks for playing, but we have our real children now."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>And the real children probably think they're accidents while she was hand-picked. Everybody's got problems with their parents.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>She's an addict. Something went wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>And it has to be the parents? Magnifying pancreas.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>I'm not saying the parents screwed up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You're saying you like her. So you don't want her faults to be her fault. But they're someone's fault, and the only other people you know are —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-9"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>I think we may need to call House again.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You lost track of your speed? I think that was Hitler’s excuse. Lost track of the Jews. No one held him responsible.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'm not playing, House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You were protecting me. Anybody in their right mind would have ratted me out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'm just trying to speed things along. You are going to this funeral.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Make it fast. I don't want to miss the anal cavity search.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Looks like a mass in the pancreas.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Not to me. This is radio. And I want a full play-by-play.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>It's fluid-filled.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>Costello</speaker><content> Would you get out of the car, please, sir?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Officer, if you want to give me a ticket, I totally understand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-11"><speaker>Costello</speaker><content>Just get out of the car, sir.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Cyst?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-13"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Large cyst. Something going on there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Wilson's getting arrested. How large? SUV sized, or mid-range sedan?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-15"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Seriously? What'd you do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm obviously joking. If Wilson was getting handcuffed on the hood of his car, would I be carrying on a differential?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-17"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Diameter is at least eight centimeters.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Is it in the tail or in the head?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-19"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>The head.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-20"><speaker>Costello</speaker><content> You too, sir. Out of the car.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content> We've got a construction site. A steamroller is plowing —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-22"><speaker>Costello</speaker><content> Out now.  No cane.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-23"><speaker>Costello</speaker><content>James Evan Wilson, there's a warrant for your arrest in Louisiana.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>What are the traits of a steamroller? Powerful. Maybe pancreatic cancer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Great idea, except the only symptom it matches up with is being steamrollerish.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>You don't think House is onto something?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I think he thought he had an idea. I also think his metaphors are tough enough to decipher after he's said them. We need to be focusing on the medicine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>No answer. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>There's not gonna be an answer. They've been arrested.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>He was joking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>He reacted to the size and location. That's what we should be focusing on. Not playing Mad Libs while our patient's exploding noun destroys her life-sustaining noun.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-9"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I'll try to get Wilson on the line.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-10"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>What if it's not how a steamroller works, but what it does? Clears things.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-11"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>This is a waste of time. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I need that phone call. I'm a doctor, and when someone tries to call you three times, it's code for "pick up the damn phone before someone dies."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>Costello</speaker><content>I'm sure there's other smart doctors.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You'd be surprised.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> You told me you'd taken care of this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>First words you ever said to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I took care of it. You must've screwed up somehow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> Sir? Not to hurry you, but we need to be at a funeral in —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>Costello</speaker><content>Nobody is going anywhere or taking any phone calls till I hear back from Louisiana.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>It's a really old warrant. Isn't there a statute of limitations on this kind of thing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's suspended when you flee the state.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-12"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I didn't flee the state. I left the state. Because I don't live in the state. And the charges were just so minor…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-13"><speaker>Costello</speaker><content>"Vandalism, destruction of property, assault."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-14"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>There is a simple explanation. There was a medical convention in New Orleans…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-15"><speaker>Costello</speaker><content> You don't need to explain to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-16"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I was fresh out of med school. I didn't know anybody at the convention.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You heard the man, Wilson. You don't have to explain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-18"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> I am not gonna sit here wasting time just so you can avoid your father's funeral! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He's my father. I have the right to avoid his funeral.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-20"><speaker>Costello</speaker><content>Not if your mother's alive, you don't.  Okay… explain.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Did House react to the eight centimeters?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>He whistled. It's huge. Anyone would think so.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>House doesn't whistle because he's impressed. It means he wasn't expecting it. It means he changed his mind at that point.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>A single super-sized cyst ruled out a diffuse process like scleroderma or lupus.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Rule out diffuse process, you're stuck with single process affecting just the pancreas.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Gallstones or pancreatic divisum.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Whatever he asked next would have narrowed that down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>He asked about location.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Heads it's gallstones, tails it's divisum.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>It's at the head. She's got gallstones.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-11"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>The steamroller means potholes —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-12"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Relax. We got it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-13"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>You figured out she's got gallstones?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I was at the hotel bar trying to unwind, have a drink. There was this guy who kept playing Billy Joel’s "Leave a Tender Moment Alone" on the jukebox.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>Costello</speaker><content>"Leave a Tender Moment" is a good song.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's a great song. He was out of line.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>Costello</speaker><content>Not as good as "Scenes from an Italian restaurant" or</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>So I — I asked the man to stop, politely.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, you yelled politely.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I was polite the first couple of times, but courtesy made no impression on this ass. So I threw a bottle into the mirror, which successfully conveyed my message.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And smashed a ten-foot antique mirror. And set an example to two other patrons who threw shot glasses.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I had nothing to do with that fight. The assault charge was totally bogus. And I paid for the mirror.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>Costello</speaker><content>I think I have the picture. I assume you're the guy who was playing the song.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, I was the guy who bailed him out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-12"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>That's how we met. I was in jail.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-13"><speaker>Costello</speaker><content>This guy was a total stranger to you, and you bailed him out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It was a boring convention. Had to have somebody to drink with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-15"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>And there's the foundation of our entire friendship. If you hadn't been bored one weekend, it wouldn't even exist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Hey, there were 3,000 people at that convention. You were the one I thought wasn't boring. That says something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-17"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>It also says something that you lied to me about getting the charges dropped!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I got a lawyer. He cut a deal. You didn't call the guy? You have to show up at the arraignment. Everybody knows that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-19"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Everybody with your misdemeanor experience.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-20"><speaker>Costello</speaker><content> You can go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What? He — he's a fugitive from justice. That whole story was lies. He stabbed a man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-22"><speaker>Costello</speaker><content> Louisiana doesn't want to pay to get you back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-23"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Forget Louisiana. He was driving recklessly through your comatose village. Do they put lead in the jelly doughnuts here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-24"><speaker>Costello</speaker><content>Stop acting like such an ingrate and go pay your respects to your father.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>The CT confirmed gallstones. Normally not dangerous. Almost everyone has them. But sometimes…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>Nicole</speaker><content>They kill you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Yup. Unless I take 'em out. We do it laparoscopically.  Um… how long has her urine been brown? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Kidneys were fine this afternoon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>They're not now. It's not the gallstones.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, of course it's not gallstones. Who thought it was gallstones?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>You said "steamroller."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I also said "construction site."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Gallstones could cause a pancreatic cyst.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Will you just turn around. The thing is two hours over already, and that's the third time we passed that colonial with the cross burning out front.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'm not lost.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm not talking about what caused the cyst. I'm talking about what the cyst caused. Everything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Cysts are symptoms, not diagnoses.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Unless it's a multiple cyst, with connections to other organs… like a steamroller.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>That's a long road down to the kidneys.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-11"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>How do we prove it? Won't be visible in a scan. Chase isn't gonna go groping around when she's got kidney failure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-12"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Bubbles.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Is that your new stripper name?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-14"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Yes. And also, we inject bubbles into the cyst and follow where they drift. If they end up in the other organs, we know you're right, cut it out, she's fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Bubbles is right. Go echo. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-16"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'm not lost.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Nicole, you gotta stay still.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>Nicole</speaker><content>I'm — I'm nervous.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>You're not nervous. It's the DTs, isn't it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>Nicole</speaker><content>I haven't had a drink since I got here.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Good heavens, we haven't missed it after all. It's like the end of a Christmas carol.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>Blythe</speaker><content>I'm so glad you're here. Oh, it's a load off of my mind just to see you.  Thank you, James.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Mom, how could you delay the funeral?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>Blythe</speaker><content>Honey, your dad is dead. He's not going to care. Do you know what you're going to say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I don't know. Just let the minister or one of his buddies from the corps…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>Blythe</speaker><content>You're talking. I don't care that you didn't like him. He was your father, and he loved you. The war is over, Greg. Please do this for me.  Stop looking so worried. I know he's gonna make me proud.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'm sure you know him better than I do.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Her liver's been compromised. And the DTS will cause her muscles to continue to twitch, even under sedation. We need to paralyze her to do this procedure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>Nicole</speaker><content>I wanted to stop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>A phenobarbital coma will not only allow us to inject the cyst, it'll treat the DTS. When she wakes up, she won't be in withdrawal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>We've seen her through withdrawal before. We've seen her through everything. We've been supportive. We've been combative. We've picked her up from bars in the middle of the night. We've let her spend the night in jail.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>Nicole</speaker><content>I used to say it'd be okay. That I'd get it together. I don't say that anymore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>Let's make you healthy. Then we'll worry about making you sober.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>Minister and mourners</speaker><content>The lord is my shepherd, I shall not want…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content> I am not talking We were strangers who shared some geography 30 years ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Right, he had no influence on you at all. The father who was compulsive about punctuality.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>His issue. Which I deliberately made not my issue.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Thereby making it your issue. Compulsively showing up four hours late, ignoring discipline, ignoring rules.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Oh, God, he's here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Who's here?  The one you're pretending is your father? Nice pick. He looks like Sean Connery. So back when you were devising this fantasy, did you tell your father: "Dad, I refuse to recognize your existence because I have chosen James Bond as my dad"?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I used different words.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>What? Hearing that your own son hates you so much he's replaced you in his mind? That's gotta suck. How did he take it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I already told you. He didn't speak to me for a summer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-11"><speaker>Blythe</speaker><content> It means more to me than — than I can say to have all of you here today. And now, uh, our son Gregory would like to say a few words.  Greg?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>There's a lot of people here today. Including some from the corps. And I notice that every one of them is either my father's rank or higher. And that doesn't surprise me. Because, if the test of a man is how he treats those he has power over, it was a test my father failed.  This man you're eager to pay homage to, he was incapable of admitting any point of view but his own. He punished failure, and he did not accept anything less than —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He loved doing what he did. He saw his work as some kind of… sacred calling. More important than any personal relationship. Maybe if he'd been a better father, I'd be a better son. But I am what I am because of him, for better or for worse. And I just — I just wish —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-14"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Put it back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, he's not gonna miss it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-16"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'm done enabling. You can't even let them put him in the ground without making it serve your agenda?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You really want to do this in front of everybody? You wanna punish me or them?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>How can I still feel surprise? You would take, even this, a moment of real human grief, and turn it into a farce.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh, cut the crap. You enjoy what I do. I never had to force you. You like coming along for the ride.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Yes, that's why I'm cheering you on now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>This is about you needing to be prepared for the worst. So you become an oncologist. No surprises there. Worst happens all the time. But Amber, she was young and healthy. Her death came out of nowhere.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Don't bring Amber into this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And you weren't ready. That makes you angry. The world sucks, and you didn't have time to brace yourself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>What happened out there is your show!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're scared to death of losing anyone that matters. So you dump the person who matters the most to you!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'm not scared to death. I'm moving forward!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Because no one can take away from you what you no longer have.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-11"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Oh, ho, ho, ho, ho. Your father's death is about you. Amber's death is about you. I can't imagine why someone wouldn't want to be your friend!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Admit it, you're angry and you're scared of losing me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-13"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'm not angry, I'm not scared.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Admit it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-15"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'm not afraid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Admit it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-17"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I've lost people. It happens.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Admit it. Admit it!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-19"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>What are you, five? Stop repeating —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-20"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Admit it. Admit it. Admit it. Admit it. Admit it. Admit it. Admit it. Come on, admit it. Admit it!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Still not boring.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Did you know I was gonna do that? Because I didn't know I was gonna do that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I know you have trouble losing people. In New Orleans, I saw you carrying this express package around the conference. And you wouldn't let it go, but you wouldn't open it. So I peeked at the return address.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Diamond, Fairbairn.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Divorce attorneys. Your first wife had just served you with papers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Did you know that when you bailed me out? Were you… doing something nice for me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What did I say about being boring? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>We owe your mom an apology.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Hello? It's House. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>How'd the bubble test go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>The problem wasn't the cyst. It's advanced dilated cardiomyopathy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>We did a three-dimensional echo. Showed a mass in the left atrium.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>Looks like an atrial myxoma, but the ultrasound images are a little grainy, so it's hard to tell. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>House?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The images aren't grainy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>They sure look grainy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I've seen pictures of you where you look tall. It's iron overload. Creates speckles on the image, makes it look grainy. Also makes her pancreas fail, her blood clot, and her intestine —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-10"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>Atrial myxoma is more likely.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>MRI for a better view. And call me back and tell me you're embarrassed because my eyesight is better 500 miles away. I need a phone number.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm a doctor in New Jersey, treating one of your clients. A young woman looking for her biological parents.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You know, you could just wait for the MRI to have your curiosity satisfied.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What person who is nothing like me are you saying that to?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Did the parents look tan? The disease she has is genetic, which means they should have it too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-5"><speaker>Fang Dong Wen</speaker><content>They don't look more tan than anyone else.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Discolored teeth?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-7"><speaker>Fang Dong Wen</speaker><content>They're farmers — the village doesn't even have a dentist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Right. Thanks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-9"><speaker>Fang Dong Wen</speaker><content>But if it matters, I'm not convinced they were her parents.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Why not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-11"><speaker>Fang Dong Wen</speaker><content>Because they said they have no daughter. The man was adamant, and the woman seemed confused and frightened.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Thank you.  Differential. Say you're a middle-aged Chinese woman…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-13"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Say it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-15"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'm a middle-aged Chinese woman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Girl comes to you, says that she's your long-lost daughter. Why would you be frightened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-17"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'm frightened because she's a threat? Maybe she knows something?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>She hasn't seen you since she was an infant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-19"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Maybe an inheritance issue.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-20"><speaker>House</speaker><content>They're peasants.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-21"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Her very presence is a threat. She — what year was she born?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-22"><speaker>House</speaker><content>'83.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-23"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>She's not supposed to be alive. China introduced the one-child policy in 1979. Say they didn't want a girl. They tried to kill her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-24"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Maybe the baby doesn't die. Maybe the father panics or regrets it. Takes the baby to an orphanage. Maybe he doesn't tell his wife.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-25"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Who freaks out like she's seen a ghost 25 years later when the girl shows up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-26"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Why does attempted murder from 25 years ago suddenly become relevant to her health now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-27"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Maybe they gave her something toxic. It would have to be fat-soluble.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-28"><speaker>House</speaker><content>This is fun, isn't it?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Let me see the MRI.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>We don't have one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>She started vomiting as soon as we started the scan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Then let her vomit through the MRI. That's what nurses are for.  Her parents tried to kill her. I don't know how, but I know it caused her to get sick 25 years later trying to lift a Buddha. Explain. I already had this conversation with Wilson — just go with it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Poison?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Buddha wouldn't make it worse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-7"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Maybe the weight stressed her back, which —</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Makes sense if she's never lifted anything in her life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-9"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>She actually didn't get sick till she tried lifting it that second time. I'm guessing the weight changed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Anybody have Taub’s pager number?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-11"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>What's up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Maybe give him a call. If he tosses that switch on the MRI, she's dead. X-ray her brain.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="34"><utterance uid="34-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Pins. Push them through the soft fontanelle of an infant, you skewer the brain, and the hair hides the entry wounds. It's the perfect crime.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>She's had them in her all these years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-3"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>What changed at the temple?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Same thing that changed in the MRI. Shockingly, not all religious leaders are honest. I'm guessing these particular monks are bilking the faithful by pushing a magnet up Buddha’s butt. There's another one under the table that'll repel or attract, depending on how you shift them. When she picked up that magnet, it moved one of the pins deeper into the sympathetic nervous center of her brain. This sent a signal through the nerves to the blood vessels in her small intestine, which caused the symptoms in China and in the giant magnet we call an MRI. She's lucky. We're all screwed up by our parents. She's got documentation.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="35"><utterance uid="35-1"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>The pins will be removed surgically, and she'll be fine. We'll wake her from the coma after the operation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-2"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>Is there any way you could not tell her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-3"><speaker>Janice</speaker><content>Please. She's fragile. She desperately wanted to know her biological parents. For her to find out that they wanted her dead… I don't know what that'll do to her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-4"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>She may not be as fragile as you think.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-5"><speaker>Janice</speaker><content>We know our daughter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-6"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content> See this pin here? It's been pressing directly on her addiction center. It's not her fault. And it's definitely not your fault. She's not who you think she is.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="36"><utterance uid="36-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I hear your patient's gonna be all right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Is that why you're here? A colleague checking up on a patient?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Something goin' on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm celebrating.  My mom hated him too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Your DNA test showed no match? That's incredible. At the age of 12, you actually figured out your father wasn't your birth father? That's what you wanted, wasn't it? Why should it depress you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It doesn't depress me. Doesn't make any difference at all. That's what depresses me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Well, I guess nobody gets to choose who their parents are. I'm not even sure anymore if we get to choose who our friends are.  I spoke with Cuddy. She hasn't filled my position yet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If you're coming back just because you're attracted to the shine of my neediness…  I'd be okay with that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'm coming back because you're right. That strange, annoying trip we just took was the most fun I've had since Amber died.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You hungry?  Wilson.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-11"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Yeah?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>My dad's dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-13"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Yeah. My sympathies.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>