<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>
<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Rick</speaker><content>This bagel's as hard as a hockey puck.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>Then don't eat it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Rick</speaker><content>Used to be a full breakfast service. They're trying to starve us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>You're worried about the food?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Rick</speaker><content>No, I’m worried about what the food represents. I got seven scenes to shoot today on half of what we used to spend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>We're going through a recession. It is what it is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Rick</speaker><content>But nobody's gonna bail us out. Free content everywhere, DVD sales in the toilet. Now the back office bean counters are vetoing half my ideas.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>So we begin to make it about the performances.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Rick</speaker><content>You okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>A bit of a headache.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Rick</speaker><content>If you need an ibuprofen –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>I need you to put your game face on, all right? Screw the bagels, screw the sets, screw the wardrobe. Do you have any idea how lucky we are?  We get to do something we like, we get to touch people's lives and we get paid for it? Let's make a movie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Topless Actress</speaker><content> Hey, baby.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Rick</speaker><content>Roll camera. And… Action.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>Oh...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Rick</speaker><content>What's wrong?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>Ah... My eyes... They feel like they're exploding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Rick</speaker><content>All right, turn off the damn lights. Get an ambulance. Now!</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We're gonna be late for work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Then we'll be late.  You took a patient's life, you lied about it for weeks, you broke who knows how many laws and oaths to cover it up, but I can live with it. We can get through it together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content> You have no idea what I've been living with, and what it means to hear you say that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>But we need to get away from Princeton-Plainsboro. You can barely walk by the rooms where Dibala was treated.  Why should we live with that hanging over our heads? If there was ever a time to turn the page...</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Three-month-old with fever, incessant drooling, and chronic muscle weakness.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Or... porn actor Hank Hardwick, born Henry Lefkowitz, totally clean workup, collapsed on the job with extreme photophobia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Or... an infant as limp as a rag doll.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah. Let's wait till Chase and Cameron get here. I have a feeling they'll have the good sense to side with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Doesn't matter who they side with, I'm still in charge. We're taking the limp three-month-old.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh, good. You paged the limpness specialist.  This envelope is oddly medical license-shaped.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Congratulations.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>House is back in charge. We get to treat a porn star.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Congratulations.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Perfect timing for us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We're leaving the team and the hospital, effective immediately.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That's kind of sudden. Unless you've been circulating your resumes for a while.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We're just starting to think about new jobs, where we want to live.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Moving too. Interesting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Are you sure about this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content> Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Uh... We'll miss you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>We'll miss all of you too. We'll start clearing out our things.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Run an STD panel and a tox screen. Send a C-reactive protein to look for inflammation and an A.N.A. to screen for autoimmune. The rest of you take a history and do an LP to rule out viral encephalitis.  Oh, it's just you. Here's hoping you're good at multitasking. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>I get tested for STDs regularly, so does everyone I work with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Since I'm guessing you don't take their word for it. All right, I'm gonna need you to lie on your side and put your knees to your chest. Any history of alcohol or substance abuse?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>My wife used to smoke a little pot, but I-I never touched the stuff.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content> You're married.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>Happily, for two years now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>She happy you do porn?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>Very, since she does it too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Hmm. You ever get jealous when your wife's working?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>It's a job. Once you start letting your work life rule your home life, especially if you're in the same line of work, your relationship's gonna be short.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You're gonna feel a little pressure.  Any history of sexual abuse?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>I defy the cliché.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Have you ever suffered depression or psychosis?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>Let me save you some time. There's not a blotch on my medical record. Look... I know most of the people in my field are drug addicts with daddy issues, but I’m a nice, Jewish boy from the ‘burbs. I wasn't driven to this. I chose it. I believe in it. I actually think it's – Oh! My arms are killing me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Looks like tetany. Your muscles are contracting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>Oh!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Need some meperidine in here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content> Oh, God.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Jew with megalophallus, photophobia, and muscle spasm. You tell me which is the most unusual.  Four candidates, three slots on the team. Need to know if you've still got your diagnostic chops.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I leave this office by 6:00 every day, I have my weekends again, I recognize my wife again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, I agree. Does sound pretty dull. No wonder you want to work for me. Tox screen was clean, We ruled out viral encephalitis.  The only obstacle to you coming back is your wife. Which has never been that much of an obstacle to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> Maybe you're right. The only link between eye and muscle is the brain.  Tumor, seizure...</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Taub seems to think the link has to be the brain, but eye and muscle are governed by different parts of the patient's second-favorite organ.  Which means it's...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Thailand was wonderful. Thanks for asking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Of course. Yes. It has to be multifocal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>I have an interview with a community health clinic in two hours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Back-up plan's fine. But Taub's swinging for the fences. I suggest you don't divide your attention.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Good point. I won't divide my attention, then. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Taub thinks it's a brain issue, Thirteen thinks it's multifocal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>And neither of them wants to work here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Don't take their word for it. Taub's problem is his wife, Thirteen's problem is you. Chase and Cameron's problem is the dead African dictator. None of them has a problem with the work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Cerebral vasculitis would explain both the eye and arm findings.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Steroids to treat, brain angiogram to confirm, EMG and nerve biopsy while you're at it. I'll be at lunch.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content> I'd hire all four, but a five-person team seems unwieldy. Who would you turn down?  I'll have whatever he's buying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Two cheeseburgers and two large fries. There are a thousand people in the world who want to be on your staff, but you're going after the four who don't.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>They don't because their lives are irrelevantly and annoyingly complicated, which makes them confused, which makes them make poor decisions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>And your life is simple? You went all the way up to the medical conference to cozy up to Cuddy. Instead she's dating one of two people in the world you think of as a friend. There's no way that's not devastating.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So I had an attraction of sorts.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Yeah, the sort in which your imaginary tryst landed you in a mental hospital.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And I got help. And she got Lucas, who bought me a ginger ale. It's all fine. Which won't be true of my department unless I can figure out which doctor I’m not hiring.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I suppose throwing yourself into your work isn't the worst thing you could do. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content> What is the worst thing I could do?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>House thinks it's cerebral vasculitis. If you could just do the brain angio while I finish up the blood work –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We're out the door.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>He's got me running every test and treatment by myself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Which is why you should be out the door too. This is completely unreasonable, even for House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content> You owe me this.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content> You really believe this is cerebral vasculitis?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Could be.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>House wants to thread a catheter through his brain, which could cause a vasospasm, give steroids, which could spread infection all over the place, because it could be.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Sounds like House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>It could also be a severe vitamin D deficiency. He has a restrictive diet, works long hours indoors, became hypocalcemic, got tetany and photophobia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Are you saying I shouldn't do the angio?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>House ordered it, Foreman wants it, of course we should do it. I'm just saying we're right to leave.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You sure? Because right now I’ll basically do anything you ask me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I'm not interested in guilting you. We're moving on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Right after I take the patient to the phototherapy suite, blast him in ultraviolet light, and IV vitamins for his severe vitamin D deficiency.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>So do you guys actually work together?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>We did at first, but now we like to keep our films produced separate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>So do you, uh, watch her work?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>We're both busy with our own stuff. Think what you want, but we're proud of what we do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Divorcing sex from all emotional content?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Lexa</speaker><content>Emotion is emotional. Sex is mechanical. There doesn't really need to be any overlap.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Certainly not in your world.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>We've helped a lot of couples by taking sex out of some deep, dark dungeon. Do what you want without some big, moral comeuppance. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You think you can escape the consequences, but you can't. You don't get to make your own rules or morals.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Lexa</speaker><content>Well, you're here to treat him, not lecture us about our – Hank. Are you all right?  Are you okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Just a nosebleed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Inside his leg? Petechial hemorrhages.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We were wrong. So was Foreman.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Patient's blood won't clot. We're back to square one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And you're back in my office. So much for playing hard to get.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We're just here to help Foreman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Is that –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He's not without talent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>UV rays made the patient's capillaries more fragile, hastening the onset of D.I.C. Sounds like sepsis –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>But isn't. No sign of shock. No drop in blood pressure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Can we turn that off?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Right, 'cause Cameron thinks pornography is evil.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I don't care what he does. I don't care what you watch. I just think it's annoying that he pretends it's some beautiful life we should all be aspiring to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Left shift points to bacteremia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>No fever. Plus it wouldn't explain his spasmodic muscle contractions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The ball and chain smacked you down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>But widespread petechial rash, nervous system involvement. It's some kind of blood infection. Meningococcemia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Start the patient on heparin for the D.I.C. broad-spectrum antibiotics for the meningococcemia.  Dr. Cameron.  Chase is relaxed, at ease, in lockstep with you again. I guess he finally told you that he iced Idi Amin Junior. Does that mean he can break the other nine commandments too? Taking the Lord's name in vain, sure, but coveting thy neighbor's wife? Is she hot?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-16"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I've forgiven him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Not for murder. Not you. Doesn't matter how evil Dibala was. By every conscience-hugging, Mother Teresa-loving bone in your body, you should be leaving him, not leaving with him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-18"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I thought your position was our leaving is a ruse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>We're not talking about my position, we're talking about yours, which doesn't add up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-20"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Here's what doesn't add up. If you were serious about staffing your team, you would know exactly which three fellows you wanted. You plowed ahead with this case even though you hadn't hired new fellows because you knew Foreman would ask Chase and me to help, giving you more time to blow up our marriage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I don't want that. But we'd be foolish not to plan ahead. A: my firing Chase was the only reason you left two years ago, B: when the full horror of his homicide hits you, your marriage will blow up. And Z... The only obstacle to you working here will be gone. Or maybe I skipped a couple of letters.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Meningococcemia's spread person-to-person. Something you ought to think about next time you show up for work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>It's okay.  Your wife's not here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I'm just telling you what –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>You have to lecture me when she's around, I get it. But I can tell from all the questions you ask that you're more like me than you admit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I'm a guy. I look around every once in a while, but I love my wife. I love the fact that she's the only one that I’m intimate with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>And no part of you wants to just toss this rulebook everyone's forced on you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>No part of you wants a life of actual commitment?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>Is my relationship perfect? No. Am I ever horny when my wife has just had sex for nine hours?  Yes. But we are committed to each other, in every way that matters.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>In other words you're committed, except when you're not committed. Doesn't work so well if you have a conscience.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>Conscience. You mean that thing that kicks in when there's no logical reason to behave the way people want you to?  What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You have a fever. Means the antibiotics aren't working.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Mr.  Takayama.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Yes. I'm really happy with what the last guy did with my eyes. But why would broad-spectrum antibiotics fail to work on meningococcemia?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>If you'll excuse me, I've got a real patient. Mister... Hitler. Really.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Had to do something to amuse myself while your receptionist fought with her boyfriend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Who's next?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>A guy who needs two decades' worth of corn chips Hoovered out of his neck, or a guy who can't stand daylight, and whose blood won't clot. You do the triage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Someone with zero chance of hiring me back.  I told you. I'm content at home and at work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>But you're not content with content. That's why you got sucked into those stock scams, why you cheated on the wife you love.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>At bridge. My wife and I play a lot of bridge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Why you worked on a case last time I was here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-11"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I gave you a theory. Just like I’d help a guy who needs a Heimlich in a restaurant. And then I shut the door behind you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>But you'd knock over three other doctors to give it to him. Metaphorically speaking, you're a Heimlich addict.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-13"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>And you're an addiction addict. Right now your drug of choice is your old team, and like any addict you're trying to solve some other problem and it's not gonna work. If you'll excuse me, I have a –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You have a tight schedule of nose jobs and tummy tucks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-15"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Yes. I do nose jobs. Just like the guy who came here after a car crash, Couldn't even breathe through… his...  Antibiotics wouldn't work if his sinuses were infected and clogged. If there was a pocket of bacteria his blood vessels couldn't reach. You surgically drain his sinuses, the drugs will work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Nice. Tell me that didn't feel good.  See you tomorrow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-17"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> Not coming back.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Looks like quite a trip.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content> It was. House send you to talk to me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Then there's nothing to talk about. I don't want to work for him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You're a great doctor. House is right to want you in the mix.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Are you saying this because you still have feelings for me and you want me to come back?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I'm saying that shouldn't be an issue.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Do you have feelings for me or not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I don't want our work life to have anything to do with our personal life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-10"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>You couldn't keep them separate. And that's why our personal life doesn't exist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-11"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>None of that has to –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-12"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>I can't work with you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-13"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Actually, you can. I was the one who had the problem. I don't anymore. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I owe you an apology. I was wr-rr-r... I was wrr-r-rr...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>What were you wrong about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You spent weeks elaborately concealing the fact that you...  crashed daddy's car. And then you just confessed. Seemed idiotic. Certain to end in disaster. Instead you're riding off into the sunset together. Any theories on why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I assume you've already dismissed the "she loves me" theory?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, it's possible. It would require the presupposition that everything she's done for the last six years has been completely inconsistent with her character, but yeah, it's possible.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>And as we've already established, it's also possible that you're wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Or there's another explanation. Since you don't have one, I’m gonna keep looking for you. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content> Let him drain, then pack it with anesthetics and sterile gauze.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Do you have any idea what's going on with House?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Uh, he's trying to get his old fellows back?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>It's called stalking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>I am way too busy to play officer of the court.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>That's a shame, since you're the one who triggered this.  What do you see in Lucas anyway?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>I don't see that it's any of your business.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Did you think House wouldn't find out? You could've at least told me so I wouldn't have coached him on how to prove his worthiness to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>I know you're upset with me because I didn't choose to date your best friend. But I’m living my life. And for the first time I’m not gonna change that because of how it might affect him… or you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>I feel like crap.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>Lucas</speaker><content>Yeah, look, our relationship is gonna be about House, or it's gonna be about us. I vote for it being about us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Well, House is gonna make it about him for us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>Lucas</speaker><content>This is very insulting. You're apparently shocked by this, which means that you thought that there was some way that we could date, get married, have two kids, a dog, retire to Florida, all without House finding out. Or you thought that we wouldn't date all that long. First means you're delusional. The second means I’m delusional. Technically it could also mean you thought House had matured, but then we're back to your being –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Shut up. You're right. I’m sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>Lucas</speaker><content>I'm also flattered. Yeah, 'cause you acted all cool and everything with Wilson, but you feel comfortable enough with me that you can freak out. That's cool.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>His sinuses are clear. Antibiotics should work this time. Why did you forgive me? I mean, I’m-I’m glad. I’m grateful, but I’m confused. You've been harder on the patient than you've been on me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Well, the difference between you and the patient is that you feel shame. Guilt. That's how I know we're gonna get through this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content> My stomach. Oooooh. It really hurts. Oh...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>His liver’s failing.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>His liver's failing and his abdomen keeps filling with fluid, so –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>It's not meningococcemia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content> No matter how much you finish each other's sentences, don't count on being a diagnostic package deal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Patient's liver's not working. We don't have time for your little team-stakes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Sometimes you're just wr-rr-r-wrong. Something genetic, something in his family history we overlooked?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>History and genetics are spotless. Plus every time he had a bad cough as a kid he went to a doctor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Klatskin tumor, obstructing his bile ducts?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>No jaundice. Wouldn't have ocular effects.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>But if it's inflammation inside the bile channels, sclerosing cholangitis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Could've stopped him from producing clotting proteins, damaged his blood cells, causing small strokes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Enough! Enough! Stop pummeling Thirteen and Taub.  It fits. Prep the patient for an ERCP. See if there's any hope of opening his blocked bile channels. And tell him to start looking for a liver donor.  Dr. Chase. Your turn. So what'd she say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-12"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>She forgave me because I feel guilty.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That works too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-14"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>And now you expect me to ask you what the "too" refers to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Only if you're interested. Only if you have doubts about her answer.  She thinks that you don't have anything to feel guilty about, because you didn't kill anybody. I did. She blames me for Dibala's murder, not you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-16"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You were barely involved in that case. She knows that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>But I created the big, bad, evil climate that allowed it to happen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-18"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You're wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Powerful counter-argument.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-20"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Why are you doing this? Why are you trying to screw things up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You got the tense wrong. Things are already screwed up. Which is why you don't just want to work for me, you need to. Cameron thinks you're my personal sock puppet. If you don't stay, it's gonna be hard to prove you're not. I have to go.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Last week, my cane could only do ten minutes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content> What are you doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Waiting for you to take a nap so I can surge into the lead.  What's the best way to restore the liver in someone with sclerosing cholangitis?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content> Not getting drawn into this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You already are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Because you crashed my workout?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're doing core training. Which improves balance, which staves off the most debilitating symptoms of Huntington's. You've ended your self-destructive streak. Want to do something significant, something that'll last longer than the few years you have left. My team is your first-best choice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>And my first choice is the community health clinic I interviewed with yesterday.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Absolutely, you should do that. Three hours a week. Every doctor should 'cause every doctor can. But you don't want to be every doctor. Plus, on my team, you get to screw with Foreman. Every way but literally.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Why are you doing it this way? You're pretending to assume we're all coming back without actually asking us. Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>See, this is why you'd be miserable wiping noses in a clinic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-12"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content> You can't ask because you can't face the rejection. Why not? What's going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Are you asking me to ask you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-14"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>I'm saying you shouldn't, for your sake as well as mine.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>We don't know how much the sclerosing cholangitis has damaged your liver. It might be in a year, it might be in ten. But the odds are you're gonna need a new one. And you should know, while no transplant committee will say this openly, they'll never grant an organ to someone working in your profession.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>You're saying I have to change jobs? You're medically advising me to change jobs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>Lexa</speaker><content>Hank, if you're too sick –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>She wants me to have some kind of religious conversion. She's practically salivating over it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I'm just being candid about –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>So you don't think I’m scum. Just some committee thinks I’m scum.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>That your lifestyle has risks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>You work around more sick people and germs and blood than I do. I’m not gonna live my life afraid like my parents did. Barely letting me play outside and God forbid that I get a scratch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>Lexa</speaker><content>I'll talk to him. He'll calm down and realize that this is the only –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>No. No, I won't. Why does everyone want to dictate the way I live my life?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>Lexa</speaker><content>Because the way we're living is gonna kill you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Passing the pancreatic duct...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Don't listen to House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You have no idea what he said.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I know that House is manipulative. I know that you're in a vulnerable state right now, and I know that Cameron wants your marriage to work. So do you. So don't listen to House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>House doesn't make my decisions. We're in the common bile duct.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content> What's that mass? Gallstone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Can we magnify times five?  That's not a gallstone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>His liver's completely filled with worms.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You have strongyloides, also known as threadworms. They disseminated all over your body, causing all your symptoms.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>How'd I get a parasite?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Most likely through sexual activity, but we can't be sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>Lexa</speaker><content>And… w-what's the treatment?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Two mebendazole pills.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>Hank</speaker><content>That's it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You'll be fine. Your liver too. Go back to your lives.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You know this is the doctors’ lounge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>Lucas</speaker><content>I know. It seemed like the place to read doctors' notes. You are good at it, by the way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content> Why are you reading my charts?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>Lucas</speaker><content>Because I’m worried about my girlfriend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Your girlfriend... is a male porn star?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>Lucas</speaker><content>Oh, no, I’m dating Lisa Cuddy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Seriously?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-8"><speaker>Lucas</speaker><content>Cool, huh? And if House doesn't have his team, that'll make her miserable, which will make me miserable. Which brings us to the fact that you have elevated noting to an art form.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I see the connection.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-10"><speaker>Lucas</speaker><content>Most doctors write "9:00 a.m." if they scrub in at 9:00 or anything near it. You write 9:03, and you make little notations when procedures are delayed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-11"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You're easily impressed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-12"><speaker>Lucas</speaker><content> Well, yeah. I was, till I saw that you had virtually stopped writing them about four weeks ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-13"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Been busy. Got a backlog.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-14"><speaker>Lucas</speaker><content>Yeah... People with your level of precision don't really just "get" backlogs. No one knows why you're leaving PPTH.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-15"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Because it's personal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-16"><speaker>Lucas</speaker><content>Well, if something happened, I mean, if you're leaving to get away from something that you did, or she did, or both of you did. I mean, emotionally maybe you want to run away, but in my experience, if you're staring at a pit bull in some guy's back yard, you're better off staying right where you are. Face the problem. That way it can't bite you in the ass.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-17"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Thanks for the folksy wisdom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-18"><speaker>Lucas</speaker><content>Hey, you got any, uh, dirt on any of the other three? It'd really help me out.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>Lexa</speaker><content>I thought you said those two pills was all he needed!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Lungs are filling with fluid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Suction him and get him on oxygen.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Patient's lungs are severely compromised. Liver's still failing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Worms could easily have been a coincidence. Almost be surprising if he didn't have 'em.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Which means it could be a hematological problem plus cardiomyopathy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, neck veins are flat, precordial exam was normal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>What if it's lymphoma? Peritoneal carcinomatosis explains the liver failure. Paraneoplastic syndrome explains everything else.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Lymphoma it is. Prep him for chemo. Fax Taub and Thirteen the latest update on the case.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content> Seriously?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>They have as much right to know as anyone on the team.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-9"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>You either like the diagnosis or you don't. If you don't, we need to keep talking. If you do, you need to shut up. What we don't need is this stupid game.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You're mad at House, but you're not mad at me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Do you want me to be mad at you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You blame House. Not me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I am mad at House because he's an ass. And I am mad at you, but I don't want to leave you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>What I did may be the worst thing I ever did. It may be the best. I'm either a murderer or a guy who stopped a mass murderer, but I did it. Me. And even if it destroys me, I’d do it again today.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>You don't mean that. This isn't you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I'm not running away from what I did because you want to pretend I never did it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>If that's how you feel... Okay.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>My strategy's not completely working. All four of them want to work for me, but all four of them have reasons why they don't want to work for me. How do I get them to take one from column A and none from column B?  Right. Right, by not saying anything, you're saying that the answer is inside me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>The answer has nothing to do with the question.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Then it's not technically the answer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Why do you need three of these doctors?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Because I know they're good. Other doctors fall into the "might be good" category.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>It has nothing to do with them being good. You think they're idiots half the time, but they're comfortable. You feel abandoned by Cuddy, so you're reaching out to people you know for comfort.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh, my God, you're right. I don't need doctors at all. I just need a good friend. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Cuddy's right. Maybe, just maybe, if I don't play along, you'll realize you can't solve a deeper problem with a surface solution.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Would've been more profound if you hadn't said anything.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Getting through it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Be a lot easier once you two are away from here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Yeah.  He's peeing blood.  BP's rising.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Heart rate's up to 250. He's going into cardiac arrest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Charging. Clear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>He's bleeding out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>His body's completely giving out. Charging. clear.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>We've got him stabilized, but no red cells, no white cells, practically no platelets either.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Mebendazole can cause adverse effects, but nothing like this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>He's been off 'em since yesterday, anyway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Long passes, wild guesses, anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Hypopituitarism. Could cause multi-organ failure if –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If his thyroid hormone wasn't completely normal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-7"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Renal cell carcinoma.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Renal ultrasound was clean.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I'd say aleukemic leukemia. Marrow's not making enough normal cells –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Ablate the patient's bone marrow. Find him a donor match.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-11"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>You want to nuke the patient's marrow? He had no evidence of being anemic or immune-compromised when he was admitted.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-12"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Perfect white count as well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-13"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Ablation could kill him or leave him defenseless against an infection that could.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, then come up with something better.  He may as well die while we're treating him.  Okay with you if I bring the other candidates into the loop now?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>The risks are, uh, they're really minimal. We'll do a series of painless injections, and –  Excuse me.  The whole thing can be done as an outpatient.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>You're leaving at 11:00 a.m.?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Trust me, the case is almost over.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Foreman told me you're ablating the patient's marrow, on a non-theory that Foreman himself withdrew. You're gonna kill the patient. Is this about me and Lucas?  I want alternatives for the patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So do I.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="34"><utterance uid="34-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I want to be on the team.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You think that's gonna save your marriage?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I don't know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Four candidates, three spots. I got a tough decision ahead of me.</content></utterance>
</scene>


<scene id="35"><utterance uid="35-1"><speaker>Phyllis</speaker><content>I want it to look natural. I mean, much younger, but natural. Can you get rid of the crow's feet altogether? Or is it better to leave a trace of them?  I don't look old enough to have them anyway, do I?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> Absolutely.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-3"><speaker>Phyllis</speaker><content>I do look old enough?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>No. What? I’m sorry. Hang on a second.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="36"><utterance uid="36-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Why are you here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>'Cause I think we're wrong. Which means something's gonna go wrong.  Or right. Takayama here.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="37"><utterance uid="37-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>It's me and Thirteen. Stop the ablation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Because?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-3"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Those threadworms. Why would his body have gone to hell just hours after they were gone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>The worms weren't hurting him. They were helping him. He has extraintestinal Crohn's. He got it from being raised in a too clean, too overprotective of an environment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-5"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>It's the hygiene hypothesis. Why there's so much autoimmune disease in the developed world, and almost none in the developing world.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>The worms were keeping the Crohn's in check, teaching his immune system what it should've learned from eating dirt growing up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-7"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Once you killed them, it started killing him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So his life of filth wasn't the problem. Clean living was. Let's start him on methylprednisolone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-9"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>And some helminths.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Worms. Cool, huh?  Best out of three?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="38"><utterance uid="38-1"><speaker>Porn actress</speaker><content>Have you been a bad boy? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I want to be on the team.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Good news for your wife.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Thanks for the sarcasm. I reorganized my life to spend more time with her, but apparently I don't love her as much as I thought.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Or you love her more. This job gives you the thrill you used to find through philandering. Better to cheat with a beaker and an MRI than one of your platinum-blonde plastic surgery patients. I'll let you know.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="39"><utterance uid="39-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I told House I want to work for him again.  Stay on the team. You were always more into it than I was, more interested in diagnostics. Unless House was right about why you want out.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="40"><utterance uid="40-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Four for four.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I was in love with you. I was an idiot. Tried to be like you, tried to understand you because I thought I could heal you.  You almost killed that patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If almost not saving his life means –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-4"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>You knew the diagnosis a long time ago. You risked another patient's life to bait your old team.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Another one?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-6"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>You did kill Dibala. By playing God and teaching us to do the same.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I taught you to think for yourselves.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-8"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>You don't even think of them as people. They're just lab rats for your little puzzles.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>As you celebrate their humanity, I'd rather solve those little puzzles and save their lives.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-10"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Motives do matter. Lives can't come second.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The patient is alive. That's what matters.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-12"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Not to you. All you care about is that Taub and Thirteen fell for your game. You'll poison them just like you poisoned Chase.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Your husband killed a patient and you're breaking up with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="40-14"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>You ruined him. So he can't even see right from wrong. Can't even see the sanctity of a human life anymore. I loved you.  And I loved Chase. I'm sorry for you both.  For what you've become. Because... there's no way back for either of you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="41"><utterance uid="41-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Any idea where I can get a great, big "Mission Accomplished" banner? Got my sanity back, my license back, and now...</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> You're kidding. All of them?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Three out of four. Which is almost as good as four out of five.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Who was the –</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Cameron.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Wow. I can't believe it. I mean, really. I can't... believe it. You were right, House. Good for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="41-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, it is. She's broken up with Chase, and she's leaving the hospital. Still, three out of four ain't bad.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>