<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>
<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Note 1</speaker><content>House is physically in Nolan’s office for the entire episode and describes other scenes to Nolan. Because of this, cuts between locations are not as clearly defined in the transcript as they usually are. If the same scene shifts from being what House is talking about and back to Nolan’s office, the cuts are more likely to be identified within the usual descriptions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Note 2</speaker><content>In an interview, David Foster said that as House envisions the other locations he sometimes includes an object from Nolan’s office. This happens once in each of the six acts. These have been identified in the transcript for acts 2, 4 and 6. If you find the objects from the other three acts, please leave a comment as to what and where it is. If I see it too, I’ll add it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Okay. "Therafy" me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>You're late.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're fat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>It's unusual.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You know how far the parking lot is? My leg's been hurting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Anything been on your mind lately, any particular stress?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No. Probably just gonna rain. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Mm-hmm. You like the new Monet reproduction in the waiting room — the Water Lilies?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I was late. I wasn't focusing on the decor, but it sounds appropriately bland and calming.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Stress can also make you absentminded.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm not stressed… Beyond the stress induced by you telling me how stressed I am.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Just an ordinary week.  Okay.  Tell me about it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I had a patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>House. Good. I have a case for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Beer?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Amnesia. She was found jogging in the street, disoriented. She almost got hit by a truck.  The MRI showed no abnormalities. No I.D. on her. Just her jogging clothes and her heart rate monitor. We know absolutely nothing about her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>We know she has money.  Blaze Outriggers — 400 bucks a pair. People who have money don't just disappear. Sooner or later, someone's gonna show up looking for her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-20"><speaker>Nurse</speaker><content>She just ate 15 minutes ago. She keeps forgetting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You don't eat because you remember it's time to eat. You eat 'cause you're hungry.  Her metabolism is in high gear. She is an extreme long-distance runner—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-22"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content> Why were you in the ER?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-23"><speaker>House</speaker><content> That's your question?  You're a psychotherapist. You're hearing about a great amnesia case, and all you're asking me is geography.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-24"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content> Just curious.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-25"><speaker>House</speaker><content> I was avoiding Wilson. It's not something you couldn't have seen eight miles away.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Wilson's a processor. I knew there were some things that he'd want to process with me… at length.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Sam's moving in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If it's before Friday, your assistant wins the pool. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I was just wondering what your plans were.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Tonight?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>In life. Sam likes you…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>But she wants me to move out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>No. I want you to move out. I didn't know things with Sam would happen so quickly. I d–I don't want to make a mistake here. I've made a lot of mistakes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>By moving too quickly. Given your usual rate of commitment, I'm surprised you're not already re-divorced.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> I could help you find a place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What's wrong with my old place?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Nothing. I just thought… You might want to find somewhere new, somewhere…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Where I didn't abuse drugs and hallucinate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>You're fine?  Your best friend is tossing you out, and you're fine?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Why wouldn't I be?</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>You're not feeling a little… betrayed and angry? Wilson bought a two-bedroom condo specifically so that you could move in with him. It wasn't that long ago. You don't feel a little… jerked around?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He couldn't foresee Sam coming back into his life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>That's a very rational defense of your friend. And, uh, I'm not buying it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Based on what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Based on the fact that you were late, and you didn't notice the pictures in the outer office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Those aren't symptoms.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>They are to me. And here's another one. You took the case. Hmm? No negotiating, no bargaining. No clinic hours changed hands. Were you looking for something to distract you from the fact that your best friend just threw you out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Case was interesting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>It's not organic. It's not mysterious. Most likely some psychologically traumatic event occurred that made the patient's brain choose to forget everything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Or not.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Here. Loss of differentiation between gray and white matter. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>It's subtle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>But it's in the area that controls memory. Not likely it's a coincidence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Bacterial infection?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content> Do I need to know this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Fine. I'll give you the Cliff Notes version. Chase – MS, Taub – physical trauma. I can tell you why we ruled them out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Or not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Then it's probably a toxin, and we need to find it before it kills her. We should search her house.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Good luck with that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Her heart rate monitor has a serial number. The distributor can match the number to the store that sold it. She's a serious athlete. She might have been there often enough to be remembered.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Brilliant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Did he really say that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Subtextually.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Long shot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Even if the store clerk doesn't know who she is, the store's probably close to where she lives. Just seeing those surroundings might spark a memory.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You want us to take her there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No. I'll take her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Really?  Uh, it's unusual for you to spend time with a patient, isn't it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Patients are boring… As people. This one I'm sure was no exception, but her situation was interesting. Besides, I was still avoiding Wilson. And no better way to avoid than leaving the hospital.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-20"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Maybe. Or were you avoiding going home? There's a reason they tell addicts to stay away from old geography.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I wasn't avoiding going home. I'd already gone home…</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Before I came into work that day. I went straight there from Wilson's.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content> Hey, take it easy! You're gonna kill me! God, why don't people knock?  House, it's you! Where you been? Hold up a second. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content> Alvie? Juan Alvarez — you let him stay at your place?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Not exactly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>I was beginning to wonder if you were ever gonna show up. Su casa, mi casa. Casa!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Why are you here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>When I left Mayfield, I went back to the old neighborhood. You know, you shouldn't leave the bathroom window unlocked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, thanks for the safety lesson. Why are you here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>Like I said, when I went back to the neighborhood, I found out immigration was looking for me. So I decided to visit my old buddy House!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And turn his apartment into a giant prison jumpsuit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>Juan Alvarez is no freeloader. I do my part, earn my keep. The first week I made your dinner, but you never showed up. The second week I organized your stuff.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>My stuff?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>But still, you never showed up. So this week, since I'm a real good painter, I decided to—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Coffee table — where'd you put it? In the bedroom?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>The paint's not cheap, House. It's a custom color. It's a mix of titanium, yellow, and ochre. Ochre — I don't even like that stuff. It's like a fruit. It's got hair on it. But they say it's a vegetable—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You sold my table to pay for paint that I don't want?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content> I had to sell some other things too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Get out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-19"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>No, papa, just give the color a chance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-20"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Look, I'm going to work now. And when I come back, the walls will be a less exciting color, and you will be gone. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>So Wilson threw you out, and you threw Alvie out — just, uh, another week?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Unlike me, Alvie didn't leave. I took my motorcycle to work that day. When I went home to get my car, he was painting the ceiling magenta. So I brought him with me to protect the apartment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>To protect the apartment. Whoa. Deja vu.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Tossing him out or, uh, sending him to the movies or, uh, locking him in the bathroom would also minimize Alvie's destructive force. But you chose his company deliberately. Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Obviously because he's a Wilson substitute. You can barely tell the difference between them, especially when Wilson raps about the hood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>I'm not suggesting Alvie's a substitute, but he would make a great distraction.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>From what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>That's what I'm trying to find out. Go on.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>Maybe the heart rate monitor was a gift. That's why no one recognized her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Shut up, Alvie. Anything familiar… Church, grocery store?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>It's okay, Ms. X. Maybe she's never been to this town before, bought the heart rate monitor on the store's website.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You know that Puerto Ricans are U.S. citizens, right? Instead of working the case, why don't you contemplate the inanity of an American with American immigration issues?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>I had a birth certificate. I lost it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So get a new one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>I tried that, House. But the town hall had burned down when I was a kid, destroyed the records.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>There's only one copy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>They tried to make me fill out a whole bunch of forms before they'd give it to me. I decided it would be quicker and easier to do it myself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>How'd that go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>They figured out it was forged. And now, for some reason, they don't believe anything I say. They actually think I'm lying about being Puerto Rican. Told me I had to go to a special hearing to prove it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Then someone will show up — a spouse, a friend — to tell you who you really are and what you should be feeling. They always do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What did they say at the hearing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>I didn't go. I lied once.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Your mother is Puerto Rican, therefore, you are Puerto Rican. All you got to do is prove your mom's your mom, find some documentation—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>People like that don't listen to people like me. Doughnuts!  Hey, House, let's get doughnuts!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Alvie, the hearing—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>Everyone loves doughnuts — glazed, crullers, elephant ears, even doughnut holes. Much better than the sporting goods store. I bet Mrs. X went there all the time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>We're not here—  And then I realized…  You make a good point.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-20"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>Really? I was making that up.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Durdanna</speaker><content>Dozen glazed, dozen jelly-filled?  You want the usual, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Your old friend, the fried carbohydrate.  She needed the calorically dense food to support the running habit. Do you know her name?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Durdanna</speaker><content>Sandy… Or Shelley. I don't know. The guy she's with called her that once. I just work here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Do you know where they live?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Durdanna</speaker><content>He left a business card in our free doughnut jar. It's up on the wall of winners.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Jay</speaker><content>Sidney.  God, I was so worried about you. What happened? </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Jay</speaker><content>The police said it was too soon to do anything, so I started calling hospitals on my own. Princeton Plainsboro wasn't even on my list. You really think something around here could have made her sick?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Here, work, anywhere she could have been exposed. Why wasn't Princeton Plainsboro on your list?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Jay</speaker><content>Well, I mean, it's a long way to run, even for her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Sidney</speaker><content>What is it I do besides run?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Jay</speaker><content>You're a lawyer — civil rights, class action suits. It's a stressful job. Running's the way you deal with it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Sidney</speaker><content>That doesn't sound like me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Do you have any idea what would sound like you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Sidney</speaker><content> Good point.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content> So what were you thinking during all this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content> That it was a strange position to be in. At that moment, she was more comfortable with me than with her husband. And he was picking up on it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content> What about you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What about me how?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Well, there was a sort of, um, artificial intimacy between you? She had been dependent on you. Uh, did you find that attractive on some level? Disturbing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Those are my two choices? None of the above. She was just a patient. She was interesting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>Sidney</speaker><content>So we're really… married?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>Jay</speaker><content>For four years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-17"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>Ms. X, you lead a lemon fresh life. Found three different cleansers under the sink. Cleaned out the medicine cabinets too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-18"><speaker>Jay</speaker><content>You know, she just won a settlement for some families whose housing development was built on an old methane field.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Toxic exposure to methane could explain this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-20"><speaker>Sidney</speaker><content> I surf?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-21"><speaker>Jay</speaker><content>You stopped before we met. You've been too busy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-22"><speaker>Sidney</speaker><content> And we're married?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-23"><speaker>Jay</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-24"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>All right, it's nothing personal. Bet she didn't think you were her type back when you first met either.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>We'll take her back to the hospital, test her blood and urine and start treatment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Sidney</speaker><content>Oh! I'm all right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Sidney</speaker><content>I don't know. My foot suddenly went numb.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>Her pants are wet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Urinary incontinence.  She's having complex partial seizures. This isn't methane. And you can leave the bucket. We need to get her to—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content> Seizures?  This is the second diagnosis you've come up with that has a personal resonance for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm choosing my diagnoses based on personal issues? You think she fell down the stairs and peed her pants 'cause Wilson dumped her too?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>You're choosing to tell me about this case, so let's look at it. First you were fixated on a harmful toxin from her past, possibly because you're worried about a harmful toxin from your own past.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Chase had the toxin idea. Maybe he's obsessed with my past.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>And–and now you're talking about a seizure disorder?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Which is also not a toxin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>But which is most likely caused by an old injury to the brain. Wh–why do you see your past as such a threat?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Not only am I unthreatened by it, I was trying to get it back.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>There's a ding mark.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Dutch</speaker><content>It's a piece of junk. It was dinged when it came in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Sure, the–the cup marks and the scuffs and the paint and those three chips. This fourth one’s new.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Dutch</speaker><content>I run a pawn shop, not a storage company. Do you want it or not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>That should be it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You said you pawned five books. There's only four.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>That's all there is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Where's “Approach to the Acute Abdomen”?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>Dutch</speaker><content>Sold it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>To?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>Dutch</speaker><content>I can't tell you. It's a law, and should be. Crazy bastards like you try to hunt down their stuff.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>How much for the pile?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>Dutch</speaker><content>$500.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content> You said it was junk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>Dutch</speaker><content>No, no. It's your junk. You want it. $500. Take it or leave it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Why is it so important that you get your stuff back?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Unlike the rest of humanity… Who's okay when their belongings are taken. Everyone wants their stuff. That's why it's their stuff.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Everyone doesn't pay five times what it's worth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I like my stuff. I hate it when Wilson moves it—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Oh…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>This is not about Wilson!  Say it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>I wasn't gonna say anything.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>31, 31! Hike!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>First down!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>One more, you get a touchdown.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>Whoo!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Hike!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>Huh!  House, you can't run for the touchdown.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And… hike!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Because I thought you were a smart guy who didn't need the obvious spelled out to him. Wilson noticed that I didn't come to my office all day. He came to find me, wanted to make sure I'm okay — boring, boring, boring.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Um, but you thought it was important to tell me about Nerf football?  Sorry. Your story. Continue.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>House, House, stop! Stop, stop, stop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>Yeah. It was my mother's. She died when I was four. It's all I have left.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That's very sad, Alvie. Listen, I set up an immigration hearing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>No, House, I'm gonna end up in jail or worse — the Dominican or someplace. Que se yo. Que no.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Um, interesting. You present yourself as, uh, not giving a damn about other people's emotions, but your actions indicate otherwise. You dismiss Alvie's story about his mother, but you cared enough to schedule a hearing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I cared for eight seconds. Then I got distracted.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> We've kept the patient up for 12 hours now. No hint of seizure-like activity. We should shut this down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Try a strobe light, add more stress.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> I think there's plenty of stress in here.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>Sidney</speaker><content>Don't we ever do anything but work?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>Jay</speaker><content>You run.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>Sidney</speaker><content>That's just more work. What about fun? God, how can we be this boring?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> Apparently, without her memory, the patient's personality has returned to what you might call its “natural state.”</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Seems she had a wake-up call while she was at college. Her brother died in a car accident. She decided to make her life mean something. Went to law school. Now that's all gone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>The thing that caused the change is gone… So the change itself is gone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah. I knew the psychological aspects of this case would interest you. Bet you got a theory already. What is it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>It's not relevant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content> What is it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Why do you care about my theory?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I think he just… bores her. She's at an earlier stage of development. She's looking at her grown-up future, and it puts her to sleep.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-12"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>If he just bored her, she'd hide it to be polite. Their problem is synchronicity. Just like you and me, House, they're not on the same page. He talks to her like someone he shares history with. But from her point of view, he's a stranger forcing intimacy on her. Of course she doesn't like him. He's not helping. He can feel he's losing his wife, and it makes him come on stronger.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He almost did lose his wife.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>The breathing problem was caused by fluid overload in the lungs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Diabetes insipidus.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>And the D.I. came from damage to the hypothalamus.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Hypothalamus here, hence the D.I. and incontinence. The amygdala here, hence the global amnesia. And the motor cortex —that's the foot paralysis. What do they all have in common?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It ends with a diagnosis of spongiform encephalitis. I convinced the team to cut out part of this woman's brain. That's not interesting to you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>No. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Not even if it's the amygdala? She'll lose all her long-term memory.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Well, this is where you tell me that being cavalier with someone else's past has nothing to do with avoiding your own past. The case is irrelevant. You just found it, uh… interesting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Aren't therapists supposed to be nurturing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Nowhere… is that in the manual. Look, you–you've been in therapy for a year. You know when I ask you to talk about anything, I mean anything that affects you —what upset you, what made you mad or relieved or joyful. You want me to believe that this case means nothing? Then, um… why should I listen to it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Are you charging me for this time?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content> Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>This is ridiculous.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>What's that? On the back of your arm?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's just a bruise. And I fell.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-12"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>You remember falling?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No. I was drunk… Hence the balance issues. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-14"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Well, it looks like you fell on the tip of someone's boot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I said something that someone objected to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-16"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Well, if you don't remember, then how can you—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's usually the way it is when someone hits me. People who kick when you're down are jerks, but they're generally not irrational jerks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-18"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>You got drunk enough to get into a bar fight and not remember, and you've been insisting that everything's fine? W–why–why go out and get blind drunk? Were you looking for a fight?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I don't know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-20"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content> What have you screwed up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content> What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-22"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>You say that when you've been hit in the past, it's because you provoked it with something that you said, which means you're well aware of the risks. So on some level, you were in that bar looking for someone to hurt you. Logically, people punish themselves for something they did or something they didn't do. So what… did you screw up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-23"><speaker>House</speaker><content> I don't know.  Okay, there may be a problem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-24"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>All right… Let's talk about Wilson.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I told him your book was contaminated with Anthrax spores. Then I gave him $300.  The address of the buyer.  Maybe I was hasty in asking you to move out. Why don't you stay with me and Sam for a little while? There's no need to hurry things.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What prompted this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Look, the whole idea was that after Mayfield, you wouldn't be on your own. I can touch base with you a lot more easily if you're staying with me than—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content> God's sake, Wilson. You really span the chasm from wishy to washy. If you're gonna be an ass, be an ass. Stick with it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Why were you being so hard on the guy, when he was being conciliatory?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Come on. Cuddy played on his guilt. She put him up to this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>How do you know that? How do you know this wasn't entirely his own idea?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Two reasons — first, he wants to create the perfect environment to be with Sam. He's been thinking about asking me to leave for a while. Finally he does it and immediately turns around and changes his mind? No. He talked to somebody.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Maybe it was Sam.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Yeah, that's a possibility.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I want this to be the last serious relationship I ever have. I want this to be the one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>Sam</speaker><content>Me too.  Where's House? It's not as meaningful without him. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Okay, um… Not Sam. Uh, that still doesn't answer why Cuddy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Because they've been talking about me. She called me to check on the patient, which she never does without a reason. I asked why, and she said…</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>She's a barracuda attorney, House. These are the kind of patients we like to keep happy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Right now the patient's lucky if she can spell jurisprudence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Yeah, but when she gets that memory back, which we are trying to make happen, she'll be able to spell lawsuit. I'm just touching base.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Touching base. Wilson used exactly the same phrase. Colluding about me is their favorite pastime.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Okay, you think they talked. How do you think that conversation went?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'm worried about House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Me too. Couldn't you have waited? It's way too early for him to be on his own, back in the old apartment. What makes you think he can handle it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I offered to find him a new place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-9"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content> You have to let him back into your condo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> Sam and I just got him out of the condo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-11"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>You know what House is like. He's self-destructive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-12"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content> Without constant supervision, he's gonna slide back into drugs. If you're not watching him, I've got to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-13"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-14"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>So they don't trust you. They assume you'll fail. Are these their fears or yours?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-15"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Let's turn on the lights, Hmm? In your brain. Maybe they did talk about you, but… How do you know it didn't happen like this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-16"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'm worried about House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-17"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-18"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>It's the first time he'll be on his own since Mayfield.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-19"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Now you're being overprotective. House doesn't need to be wrapped in cotton wool. But you know that, or you wouldn't have asked him to move out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-20"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Okay. I guess this is really about me. It's just… I feel like a jerk. Sure, Sam and I are gonna want to be on our own eventually, but I kind of sprang this on him. The right way would have been to just tell him to take as long as he needed, that there's no hurry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-21"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>So it's not what you did, but how you did it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-22"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>That matters in a friendship. I need to fix this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-23"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Why don't you talk to him about moving back in? Just touch base.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-24"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>We're having a consent issue with the patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-25"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Wait a minute. Taub's not here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-26"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, he is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-27"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>We're having a consent issue with the patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-28"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>What's Taub doing in my imaginary version of a scene with Wilson and Cuddy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-29"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Your version needed to be ended, 'cause it's crap. It's all sweetness and light and… faith that I'm gonna choose the right path. Yeah, that sounds like Wilson.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>I have as much evidence for mine as you do for yours. I know Wilson's your friend. So he could be wondering if he did right by you. And I know he wouldn't have asked you to move out in the first place unless he was convinced you could handle life on your own.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And I know that he and Cuddy have gone behind my back before to strategize about the House problem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>So there's truth in both versions. But you choose to focus on the parts that make you uncomfortable. So…  Why are you and Wilson… friends? Do you think this friendship is the best you can do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Wilson is not a consolation prize.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>There… You're defending him. And a minute ago, he was skulking around in the background like some sort of manipulative Iago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content> He's my friend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>So what do you value in him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content> I can say whatever I want to him, and he'll never leave.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>He's sort of leaving. At least, he won't be around as much… because he's putting Sam first.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>For now. After the divorce, he'll probably ask me to move in again. I take the long view.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-11"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>You say that to Wilson?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Are you kidding? That's the kind of remark that leads people to hit you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-13"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Uh, maybe you've been right from the beginning. Maybe this isn't about Wilson.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You say that now that I finally agree with you? Do you just argue the opposite of whatever I say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-15"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>I don't mean the Wilson thing doesn't, uh, bother you, uh, but it sounds like he's the closest you can come to a safe relationship. You'd have to do something major to screw it up. Um, what–what else have you been involved in this week? What would you want to punish yourself for?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content> I told you, I don't know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-17"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Okay, um, let's approach it from a different angle. Have you gotten any other people angry at you over anything?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, yeah. That's why I called it an ordinary week.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-19"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Okay. Tell me about it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>Jay</speaker><content>You'd be losing a part of your brain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>Sidney</speaker><content>It is my brain. Why is it not my right to consent?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>Jay</speaker><content>I'm sorry, but… I'll take this to court if necessary. All right, Sidney's in no position to make decisions about herself right now. She doesn't even know who she is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>Sidney</speaker><content>I read your consent form, and I understood it. I want the surgery.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>Jay</speaker><content>Why wouldn't she? Of course she's willing to risk losing her memories permanently. She has no idea how important those memories are. Does she even know what risk is? She's never lost anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Without the surgery, she'll lose everything. The prion infection will continue to advance and destroy her whole brain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>Jay</speaker><content>Well, there has to be another way. Please. I'm speaking for my wife, the wife I lived with for four years who isn't here and can't defend herself.  Dr. House, are you listening?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, you can stop arguing, 'cause it doesn't matter anymore. Look at the variability in the heart rate. The S.E. has spread into the brain stem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-9"><speaker>Sidney</speaker><content>W–wherever it is, you–you can still cut it out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>No. We can't cut the brain stem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>This thing's moving too quickly. Surgery's no longer an option, which I guess means you've won. Congratulations.  Put in a pacer and start her on chemo and radiation. It won't cure her, but it'll buy a couple weeks so she can find out who she is before she dies.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>That was pretty rough Do you always break the news to your patients that way? Or were you short-handing it for me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Husband was being an idiot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Well, he was asking for it. But, um, to punish him you have to punish the wife too. Why–why did he make you so angry, Hmm? Because he didn't want to cooperate with you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He'd rather risk his wife's life than their marriage. People's brains stop working when they think they're gonna lose someone they love.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Your leg hurt?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's all right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Okay. Anyone else you pissed off?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>50 bucks for the book.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>Harris</speaker><content>Forget it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You paid $25. That's 100% return.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>Harris</speaker><content>That's what I paid. But it's a rare surgical text, nearly 100 years old — plates in mint condition. That book's worth several thousand dollars.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>$2,000. I'll write you a check.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>Harris</speaker><content>Nice try. Face it — I had the wit to recognize something valuable when I saw it. In the great Darwinian race, I get my just reward. You become road kill.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>Yo, House, you want to stop by the library? 'Cause I got a book to return. Ta-ka-plow! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Anyone see you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>Yeah, prof saw me walking down the driveway. He said the roses need more fertilizer.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>I didn't know there was a section of the brain just for hope.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's very, very tiny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> We used fluoroscopy to guide pacemaker placement in the patient's heart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>Hello. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> Hello.  Rapidly progressive dilated cardiomyopathy. This isn't S.E., and whatever it is, it's not just in her brain. It's attacking her whole body.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>You work for House? I guess we're teammates. Isn't that cool?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> Hello.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-8"><speaker>Durkee</speaker><content>Juan Alvarez?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-9"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>What the hell?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-10"><speaker>Durkee</speaker><content>We're taking you into custody — deportation order.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-11"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>I'm a citizen. You're disrespecting Puerto Rico.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-12"><speaker>Durkee</speaker><content>If you're a citizen, why'd you miss your hearing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-13"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>You called them?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-14"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>What's going on?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>We're trying to stabilize her heart. She's still tachy and hypotensive.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Brain, heart, and rapidly progressing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content> Endocarditis — slow-moving infection in her heart throws clots to her brain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content> I'm not talking to you. How could you turn me in?</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="34"><utterance uid="34-1"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>I don't like you, House.  I hate you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> Even I.V. Antibiotics will take time to work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-3"><speaker>Court Officer</speaker><content>A gentle reminder — the use of cell phones is prohibited.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Give her the first dose directly into the lungs in the O.R.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-5"><speaker>Court Officer</speaker><content>Before the less gentle arrest for contempt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Put her in an isolation room with U.V. light. And get yourselves tested. You've all been exposed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-7"><speaker>Court Officer</speaker><content>Docket number 4378.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-8"><speaker>Public Defender</speaker><content>You are?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I am Mr. Alvarez's doctor. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-10"><speaker>Public Defender</speaker><content>Your honor, DNA evidence proving the matriarchal lineage of Juan Alvarez. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="35"><utterance uid="35-1"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>My mother's DNA was still on that cross?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It could be.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-3"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>You faked it?  It wasn't just me. You lied to them too!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm better at it than you are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-5"><speaker>Alvie</speaker><content>I'm gonna repaint your whole apartment now, make the drapes match the carpet now!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="36"><utterance uid="36-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Lungs sound wet. O-2 sats are dropping.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>May need to tube her. Grab some I.V. furosemide.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Wait, wait.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>She's crashing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We need to get her on a vent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>There's something on her ankle. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Tattoo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>"Eddie would go." It's a surfing phrase. Must be from her earlier life.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="37"><utterance uid="37-1"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>So you were right… in the end. It was her past. Did she get her memory back?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="38"><utterance uid="38-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Not yet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-2"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Will she?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No way to know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-4"><speaker>Sidney</speaker><content>I think roses are my favorite. But I guess I told you that at some point.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-5"><speaker>Jay</speaker><content>I don't remember.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-6"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>He's treating her as though they just met. He's courting her. Whose idea was that?  He was doing the opposite of everything he should. Suddenly he's changed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Taub thought it might—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-8"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content> That was your idea. And you asked me what I thought was going on between them. It's their relationship that's on your mind. That's why you've been thinking about this case — relationships. Lost one with Wilson, gained one with Alvie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Not exactly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Alvie?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-11"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content> You gonna tell me what the note said?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Alvie was very grateful that I'd gotten him out of trouble. It allowed him to go stay with his cousin in Phoenix without worrying about immigration looking for him there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-13"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>You didn't think he was gonna stay forever.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-15"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>What happened next?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Nothing happened next.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="39"><utterance uid="39-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That's all I got.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-2"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content> Relationships.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Bergman.  What do you want me to say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-4"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>I don't know. You're the one who set the theme — something about relationships made you go out and provoke a fight. Wilson and Sam have a relationship. You're not thrilled about it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>They're happy. Why should I screw that up? Everyone's happy. Everyone's moving in together — Wilson and Sam, Cuddy and Lucas. Even Alvie's—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-6"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Cuddy and Lucas are moving in together? You didn't mention that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>They talked about moving in together before. It's not big news.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-8"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Cuddy…  Cuddy. “Approach to the Acute Abdomen”…  Written by Ernest T. Cuddy, M.D. Any relation to your Cuddy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Her great-grandfather. I've had it for years… Always meant to give it to her for a special occasion.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-10"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>Like her… housewarming?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's just a gift.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-12"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>A woman you care about is taking one step further away from you and closer to someone else? I–I think I can safely say yes, it's significant if you don't mention it. You were willing to punish the husband of your patient because you identified with him. He was also losing someone he loved.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm not gonna go out and get hammered because a woman I'm not even with is moving in with someone. That'd be pathetic. To hell with this. When I first came to you, I told you that I wanted to be happy, and I followed your advice. And instead, I'm just miserable. How is this working for me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-14"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>It takes time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>For a year, I've done everything you've asked, and everybody else is happy. I run on my treadmill. You just sit there and watch. You're a faith healer. You take advantage of people who want to believe. But there's nothing in your bag of tricks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-16"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>House…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="39-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Whatever the answer is, you don't have it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>