<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>
<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>Jennifer Williams?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Woman </speaker><content>And you are?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>Cyrus. Cyrus Harry? You used to call me Cy if it's — if it's really you.  I–I'm trying to find the Jennifer Williams I knew 23 years ago. We spent a long weekend at the Jersey Shore? She was visiting a friend… </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Phil </speaker><content>That lasted longer than usual.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>That's it for Lansdale. Pack it up. Let's move on to Philly.  Seriously, you gonna complain? How many limo drivers are making six figures?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Phil </speaker><content>Cy, you're my little cousin, and I love you, and you've been more than generous. I'm upset because you are wasting your time over some faded memory when there is a world of pleasure out there. The kind of cash you got buys a lot of it.  Come on… be like that. I've just been driving around all day. I'm a little cranky.  Hey!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>My leg won't move. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Phil </speaker><content>Are you gonna stare, or are you gonna call 911?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Partial paralysis. Head CT and LP showed nothing. Spinal MRIs and EMG were clean. Brain symptom, yet nothing seems to be wrong with his brain. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Refrigerator mechanic, no family, in and out of work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>He just won $42 million in the state lottery. I think I read about this lucky bastard in the paper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>House </speaker><content>You sure you don't mean the lucky bastard whose grandkids snorted his winnings till he drank himself to death with drain cleaner? Or the lucky bastard who was found naked and penniless in a strip club parking lot with his winning number tattooed on both testicles?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>Neuro-otological pathology could have caused loss of balance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>Sure, some people will screw up anything, but some won't. That kind of cash, he has a chance to turn a miserable life around.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Miserable stays miserable. Happy doesn't buy lottery tickets in the first place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>Our level of happiness is set. It's in our DNA. No cash payout's gonna change that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>House </speaker><content>It's like there's two of me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>The guy repairs appliances. He's probably got toxic brain damage from years of working with toxic chemicals.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>Or his sudden disease came from his sudden millions. He's buying something, collecting something, ceramics, precious metals, which gave him atherosclerosis of his carotid arteries. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>My mother's lawyer called. She's threatening to sue the hospital over our mistreatment of her. Says it slowed her recovery.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>House </speaker><content>You know,I was just thinking how much I want a relationship with no sex, but where I still have to deal with your mother. Go to the patient's old workshop. Look for causes of toxic brain damage. Go take a new history, and see if there's any lifestyle changes that would explain atherosclerosis.  Go.  Medicinal. I'm expecting a shooting pain in my ass.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>My mom and I got into a fight. Because of our replacement hip replacement, she can barely get around her own house. I told her she has to live with me while she recovers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Oh, I'm starting to get the connection. Yeah, she has a house, my name is House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>You're the doctor that treated her, that illegally switched her meds after she fired you, that went behind the back of her actual doctor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Those beads from Thailand.  If we're listing all the things that you pressured me into.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>: The point is you're the one who's on the line here, whose name is on her hospital records.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Whose name is on her name?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>Fine. We're both on the line, but she won't discuss this with me alone. She and her lawyer want to meet with both of us for settlement talks. I need you in that meeting acting nice and respectful while I defuse this stunt.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>Picked up any new hobbies?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>How's a hobby gonna paralyze my left leg?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>If you work on vintage cars or you've taken up painting, the fumes can…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>No cars, no paints.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>Popular wallet. Three years ago before I had a dime, I had my appendix out. Phil was there. No one else even called.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>What about drugs?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>No drugs. Look, I've seen all the documentaries, I've read all the articles. I'm not gonna be a tabloid cliche. I know what I'm gonna do with my money.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Phil </speaker><content>Find and build a life with the one woman I ever cared for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>The point is nothing's changed. I live the same life. I eat the same food.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Phil </speaker><content>Same crappy canned food.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>How many of your meals do you eat from a can?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>Most of 'em. I'm used to it. I order 'em by the case online. Is that bad?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>You're worried about the trickle down effect of Cuddy versus House versus Cuddy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>You're reading subtext into my silence?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>House gets to you more than anyone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>House thinks I'm a robot. You think I'm a wuss?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>No, no, no, no. I think you're repressed. Well, it's out of your control. Tough childhood, strained relations with your family. Can't be easy trying to succeed in a white man's world.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>First of all, white man, I've done at least as well as you have. Second, I didn't think you take House's view that life sucks and we're stuck.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>I think you're stuck. Last month or so I've turned my life around. I'm happier than ever.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Sleeping with ten women instead of four?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Try none.  He was cutting metal… inhaled the dust?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Unless he was snorting lines of the stuff. None?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Was having tons of sex, and I was bored, hating myself. Was never gonna be ready when something real came along.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>So you're becoming some kind of super monk, and I can't change at all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>I challenge you to go one differential without House or anyone else getting under your skin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Since I say nothing gets to me and you won't take me at my word, how am I supposed to prove you wrong?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>I guess you can't. I hope that doesn't eat at you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Off-brand solvent. From China.  Made of God knows what.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>Patient eats cheap canned goods by the caseload. Could be metal poisoning?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>He also worked with cut-rate chemicals. Could be inhalation of a toxic volatile substrate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>Treatment for both is chelation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Great work. Alkalinize his urine and force diuresis for heavy metal poisoning. If that doesn't work, put him on dialysis for toxic inhalation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>I just said treatment for both is chelation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>House </speaker><content>And I said force diuresis and try dialysis. You need a transcript?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>You want to put him on dialysis, risk infection and hemodynamic swings when we can just chelate?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Whoa, whoa. Settle down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>House </speaker><content>If we chelate, we're not gonna know what disease he had, which means we're not gonna know if the problem was in his lousy old job or his still-lousy new life. Which for the purposes of a metaphorical argument is very important.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>Where's the dialysis machine?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>Who cares? Since I ordered chelation. We'll flip a coin, tell House it was one disease or the other. Worst case, he finds out and he's impressed we defied him.  I'm sorry. I asked you to remove the dialysis equipment, not the chelation equipment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Nurse </speaker><content>And Dr. Cuddy asked me to remove all equipment. She de-authorized all treatment.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>She won't let us make a move until you agree to a sit-down with the godmother and her consigliere.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Bitch to king four.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>Checkmate. Patient can't use his leg. You have to concede.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Or I could just knock all the pieces onto the floor.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>You're discharging me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>We really… don't have a good lie here, so…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>You got caught in some politics between our boss and his boss, but you'll be out of here 20 minutes tops.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>I'm not better, but you're kicking me out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>Which is why it'll only be 20 minutes. See, the Dean of Medicine</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Phil </speaker><content>So you're saying that she cares more about his treatment than the doctor who's actually treating him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Jennifer </speaker><content>Cyrus.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>Jennifer?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Jennifer </speaker><content>It's good to see you. I read about you in the paper, so I hopped the first train from Virginia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Phil </speaker><content>So you read that he struck it rich?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Jennifer </speaker><content>He's right. It–it must look weird. It kind of is weird. Well, we're a long way from the third street jetty. I just wanted to see you again and say hi, so… Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>Hi. I was starting to think I'd never find my…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Jennifer </speaker><content>Baby Bear. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>Oh, my God. I'm–I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry. I–I don't even feel nauseous. I don't know why—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>Your hand is shaking.  Okay. You're having a focal seizure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>Phil </speaker><content>What does that mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>It means you're not getting discharged.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>We were right that it's a brain issue, but wrong about toxic inhalation and metal poisoning. Everyone else is waiting—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>House </speaker><content>That was totally courageous of Khloe to Tweet about her weight gain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>House, I've got a patient with a seizure disorder who can't walk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>House </speaker><content>What are you doing? We got a patient with a walking disorder who can't seize. No, wait. I'm close, though, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>I wasn't finished. Of course I'll let you treat your patient if you meet me halfway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>No clinic hours for the next quarter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Yeah, three parking spots, next to each other, so I can park diagonally, and three pairs of your underwear. I'm thinking of taking up sailing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>Forget it. Treat your patient, don't treat your patient. Come to the meeting, don't come to the meeting. I'm done playing your game. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>House </speaker><content>You realize the game is automatically over when the loser loses, right?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Neurological Lyme disease explains the seizures and the paralysis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>House </speaker><content>But not the fact that Chase seems to be treating you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>He claims he can swear off sex indefinitely. Also claims that I am a boiling cauldron of repressed rage. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>You make a good point about the antibody titers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>House </speaker><content>He's a rock. How's your brother — homeless guy? Haven't heard from him in months!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>I don't know. Wish I did. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>House </speaker><content>He'd be a miserable wretch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>Actually, the prognosis is—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Oh, I'm sorry. No, I just meant his life is gonna unravel. In fairness, that applies to any diagnosis. Why do we do this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>It's not postural hypotension. He's not orthostatic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>His life may unravel, it may not. He's not chasing after material things.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Too bad. He might actually get those.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>He's looking for love. Just tracked down an old girlfriend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>And she'll never live up to the memory, and the thrill of finding her will wear off, and he won't even be able to dream about being happy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Interesting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>The patient may have found some long-ago nookie, but it doesn't mean he hasn't had some in the meantime. Herpes encephalitis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-17"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Explains the neurological symptoms. EEG to confirm, I.V. acyclovir to treat. How's Foreman's BP holding?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-18"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Same.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-19"><speaker>House </speaker><content>That's strange, since I unplugged the lead 30 seconds ago. Admirable effort. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-20"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Down on the patient's romance because your own lifespan is shorter than dinner and a movie?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-21"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>You're the one who said miserable stays miserable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-22"><speaker>House </speaker><content>You keep saying it. Several times a day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-23"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>I love being back, having every theory you and I share used as proof of my own personal damage.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>I'm afraid we'll need you to step out when the EEG begins. The waiting area's just down the hall.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Jennifer </speaker><content>I got to catch an early train in the morning anyway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>No, don't.  I'll put you up in a nice hotel, or rent you a furnished place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Jennifer </speaker><content>I came for the night 'cause I wanted to see how you were. Maybe get back in your life a bit, but if I take your money…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Jennifer </speaker><content>I guess I could keep my motel room another night or two. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Need a consult. Did an EEG on my patient. Turns out the reason that prior doctors thought it wasn't a neuro problem is because it's not a neuro problem. The EEG did show signs of metabolic distress.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>Well, scan his abdomen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Yeah, let's assume we'd already figured that out on our own, and found a mass on the pancreas. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>Mass looks solid. I'd say it's cancer. Paraneoplastic syndrome would explain the neurological symptoms. You need to get a piece of it. Schedule a CT-guided biopsy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Yeah, let's assume we'd already figured that out on our own.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>Then what's this consult?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Why haven't you been yelling at me about the Cuddy twins?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>Because you're doing the right thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Are we talking about the same issue? Is there something I don't know about that I'm responding to appropriately?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>Cuddy wants you in the middle of this. So does Arlene. Because they don't want to face their own problem. Somehow, in your knee-jerk, juvenile way, you tripped and fell into an actual adult response to this.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Lawyer </speaker><content>Where is Dr. House?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>I didn't want him here.  This isn't about her treatment at Princeton-Plainsboro. It's about the fight we had last week. I'd like a moment with my mother to try and work this out on our own.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Lawyer </speaker><content>I'm afraid my client doesn't want to—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>It's mother's day Sunday. We can't have five minutes alone to fix this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>Arlene </speaker><content>Relax. You can still bill me for the time standing in the hallway. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>I know you're mad at me, but you can barely make it up those stairs. How many nights have you spent on your couch?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>Arlene </speaker><content>This has nothing to do with our fight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>We're talking about my home, not a prison camp.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>Arlene </speaker><content>What did I just say? I think it was something about this not being personal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>You can spend time with Rachel. I can watch over you. Win, win.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>Arlene </speaker><content>Maybe I've got a medical thing. Maybe I just think I'm talking, but no one can hear me, not just my uncaring daughter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-12"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>What do you want?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-13"><speaker>Arlene </speaker><content>20 grand. I'll hire help and forget this nightmare you put me thr — make it 30. I'll put in a stair lift.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-14"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>If my board even hears about these threats, let alone a settlement, they'll investigate what happened while you were here as a patient. House and I could both lose our license. I've been assuming this is personal because I don't want to assume that was what my mother wants. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-15"><speaker>Arlene </speaker><content>House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-16"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Ex-not-mom-in-law.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-17"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>You said you weren't coming.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-18"><speaker>House </speaker><content>After you said pretty please with sugar on top? Problem is we only give store credit, so I say we put your old, cracked poisonous hip back in. Here and now. I saved your life. Happy to un-save it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-19"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>He is being an ass. If I could join you in suing him—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-20"><speaker>House </speaker><content>She's like this in bed too. Always scheming to get the lawyers out of the room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-21"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Was I supposed to be the good cop?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>I had to rig the monitor.  I had a lot of salt with breakfast. You think I'm repressed too?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>I think you're in danger of being dissolved by your own stomach acids.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Well, what about Chase? Believe all that nonsense about him being celibate?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>Don't know, but I'm rooting for him. Read the studies. The fewer partners you have, the happier you are with your ultimate partner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Hmm. Then you're gonna be miserable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>Those studies, it's important that they have a control group. There's the tumor on his pancreas.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>There's one on his kidney and one in his colon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>One looks avascular, one looks vascular. The third looks calcified.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>He has three completely different cancers at once.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>On average, not so lucky after all.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>You had to go all Wile E. Coyote on me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>House </speaker><content>You told me that Arlene wanted me in the middle of it. I had to show her that no good would come of that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>Seriously? That's your rationalization?  How about you didn't like that Cuddy tricked you? Even though you wanted the same thing as her. You didn't like that she got the best of you. You've got more anger toward her than you realize.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>House </speaker><content>I'm happier without her. I'm not stupidly expecting her to make me happy. I'm happier with my unhappiness. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>Do you listen to what you're saying? Because I have to. I'm holding a summit meeting to force you and Cuddy onto the same page before a lawsuit gets filed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>Three completely unrelated cancers at once.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>Multi-cancer syndrome — Von Hippel Lindau?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Wouldn't have touched his colon.  I hereby certify that Dr. Foreman has not tampered with this blood pressure mechanism in any way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>And after I prove I'm 100% stress free, do I get to strap you into a chastity belt?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-10"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>What if the patient's missing a tumor-suppressor gene?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-11"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>How would we even find it? We need to blast him with chemo now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-12"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>We can't give the patient chemo. His platelet count's through the floor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-13"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Even worse, it'd contain his cancers. If we want to know what they have in common, we got to see where they spread next.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-14"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>You want to wait six months while the cancer spreads and his seizures and paralysis get worse?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-15"><speaker>House </speaker><content> : Well, now, that's crazy talk. But if we pump the patient full of vascular endothelial growth factor…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-16"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Foreman doesn't like that idea. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-17"><speaker>House </speaker><content>We can't figure out what three small ones have in common, maybe can figure out what eight big ones have in common?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-18"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>Makes no difference to us, but you may want to make out a will.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-19"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Go get lotto boy's consent, and turn his cancers up to 11. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-20"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>You, what, found my old yearbook, and got a picture of my high school boyfriend?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-21"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Actually, that would have been a lot simpler. No, I took this ten minutes ago.  Your high school boyfriend who dumped you, leaving you unable to believe that anyone can rekindle an old flame.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-22"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>He dumped me after I hooked up with his sister.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-23"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Would you mind letting him down gently? I might have made promises you can't keep.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>We're giving you more cancer. The risks of that are kind of obvious.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>We'll scan you, run your blood at frequent intervals. We believe this is our best chance at finding the underlying genetic flaw. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>Will you marry me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>Jennifer </speaker><content>Don't be stupid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>If this cancer overwhelms me, at least I'll die happy here and now, instead of hoping for a future I may never have. I love you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>Jennifer </speaker><content>No, you don't. You don't know. You can't know. We both need more time. And I believe we're gonna have it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>Do you notice she's wearing different clothes every day?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>As opposed to the same, Starfleet-issued tunic?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>She said she came for one night. Why'd she pack for more?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>So she stuffed an extra sweatshirt in her bag, or she bought something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>Used? She's here because an old beau struck gold.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>She turned down a proposal. How long a game you think she's playing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>I think if she said yes after 14 hours, even he'd be suspicious.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>You're lucky you're hot and smart, because — well, you're just lucky you're hot and smart.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Not if you can make that work. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>How is that supposed to relax you? It's not for me. It's for Chase.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>House </speaker><content>I'm saving myself too. Maybe you should get a couple.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>You're riding me. Why not ride him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Because I can get a rise out of your BP. His pee-pee on the other hand… Forget yoga. Embrace Zen. You're a repressed idiot. He's a horny idiot. Neither one of you can do anything about it. Pretty sure that's Zen.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Thought we were meeting in Cuddy's office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>And I put one of the radio frequency tagged sponges from the O.R. In your portable television.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>However much it hurt, I did have a right to break up with you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>House </speaker><content>You just want everything to have a hidden personal agenda.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>You need to get over it instead of torpedoing our jobs out of spite.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Couldn't just be that you're a pain professionally.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>Stop! You're both at fault here. You for trying to manipulate House when you used to know better, and you for… being you, which is an especially bad idea under the circumstances.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>House </speaker><content>I had good reasons.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-9"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>You had lame rationalizations.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-10"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>If I hadn't played him, he'd have found out about the meeting and crashed it anyway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-11"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Would have been a lot more efficient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-12"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>Enough! Okay, here's what's gonna happen. Tomorrow I drive both of you to Arlene's. You're gonna write her a personal check for $30,000, and tell her she can stay in her own home with your blessing. You're gonna do this because you actually give a crap about your job and this hospital and your mother, and possibly even House.  And you're gonna say, I'm sorry," and not utter one syllable more.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-13"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Because I'm an idiot?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-14"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>No, because if you don't, I'm gonna tell the pharmacy to stop issuing Vicodin prescriptions in my name.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-15"><speaker>House </speaker><content>I'm not paying for gas.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>Anything look different?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>Not yet. Where's Jennifer?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>She's embezzling money from my Swiss bank account. That's what you think, isn't it? I'm being taken for a ride?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>I think she wouldn't be here if you were still fixing refrigerators. One random set of numbers doesn't change human nature.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>Those sets of numbers are what kept me going. Clutching those tickets, thinking about the life I could have, finding Jennifer again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>So you figure if one long-shot dream came true the other one will as well?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>You think you're protecting me. I think you're sad. Can't stand to see somebody happy.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>Mom, here's a check. It's a settlement for all you've been through. Of course you can stay in your home. It was wrong of me to suggest otherwise. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>House </speaker><content>I'm sorry. That we saved your life.  In the way that we did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>B-plus. I hope this resolves everything. I can tell you that both your daughter and Dr. House—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>Arlene </speaker><content>This is 30 grand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>Which is what you asked for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>Arlene </speaker><content>This covers pain and suffering. What about the probate lawyer?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>Do you two…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>Arlene </speaker><content>I have to change my will, leave everything to Julia so this one doesn't try more funny business to get control of my home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>I'm sure we can toss in another 2,500.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>Well, I guess I'll have to kill you tonight then. Mom, I'm not interested in—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-11"><speaker>Arlene </speaker><content>You already think you own my body. Why not my home too?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-12"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>Everybody stay calm, and—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-13"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>You have to lash out at everyone who tries to help you? Live in your own kitchen sink for all I care.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-14"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Harsh. I didn't think you had a case before, but that is no way to talk to a patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-15"><speaker>Arlene </speaker><content>You are right. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Chase has had his eyes on this one for months.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>Meaning he has eyes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>I paid her 100 bucks. When he hits on her — might be tonight, might be next week — she's gonna slap him and storm off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>So your plan is to prove you're both full of crap all in one move?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>First he'll compliment her hair. That's how he breaks the ice. Next comes some kind of joke or story. He's sharpening his harpoon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>Are my moves this predictable?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>She's grabbing his arm. He's going in for the kill. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content> : Don't let it get to you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>Poured a lot of gas on the fire. Ultrasound will give us a good look at the damage. Little more gel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>I never made a will. I want to provide for you, if I don't—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>Jennifer </speaker><content>Stop it, will you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>Like you to hold your breath for a sec.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>Jennifer </speaker><content>Your money, there's charities, causes. Your family. You got to ask yourself what's mattered to you most year in and year out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>That can't be right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>Is it bad news?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>No. We've been pumping you with growth factor, but you don't have any new cancers. The tumors you had all shrank.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Three tumors disappearing means we were probably wrong about him missing a tumor-suppressor gene.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>How many mulligans are you gonna ask for?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>This test is what raised my blood pressure. I'm used to it now.  Go. If it's autoimmune and he created antibodies that ended up fighting his own tumors…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Growth factor would have made the underlying autoimmune condition better.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>Maybe it was never cancer in the first place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>Amyloidosis? His EKG voltage has been on the low end of normal. What if the tumors were actually protein deposits?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>House </speaker><content>G.I. biopsy to confirm, chemo to treat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>She's making that diagnosis based off of low-normal EKG. Low-normal is still normal.  That thing cannot be right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Low-normal is still low, and that thing does not have money riding on you being wrong, like the rest of us do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-10"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Chase fixed this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-11"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>Oh, I think you're confusing Chase and Foreman. I used to do that all the time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-12"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>I know it's rigged. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-13"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>Because you're Mr. Cool? Nothing could possibly faze—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-14"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Well, we'll do it your way — go shout at the patient till he gets better. G.I. biopsy to confirm, chemo to treat. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-15"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>Here's the dirty little secret. I just think we are who we are. And I think lotteries are stupid.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>I heard Cuddy quadrupled your clinic hours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Yeah, but you know what? I'm flying through patients.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>Arlene wants another meeting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>House </speaker><content>I know. Told my seconds to tell her seconds that she gets no second chance. Well, technically, it's a third chance, but I don't have thirds.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>Cuddy told her the same thing, more or less.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>House </speaker><content>So you got us on the same page after all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>I've been thinking about your irrationality, and I've come up with a rational explanation for it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-8"><speaker>House </speaker><content>That's quite a challenge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-9"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>You don't want to let go of Cuddy, so you're clinging to the negative interaction, because some small part of you thinks the bad stuff beats nothing at all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-10"><speaker>House </speaker><content>You're almost making this work. All you got to do now is change reality. Perhaps if I was the one suing me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-11"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>You didn't start it, but you had the chance to end it, and you didn't. You love her, House, and it's human to hang on, but you're blowing up not just your job but any chance of any kind of relationship with her again.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>Hi. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>Phil </speaker><content>What's that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>It's a check. For $10 million dollars.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>Phil </speaker><content>Uh, I don't know what to say, I mean… You already been so generous.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>By hiring you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>Phil </speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>For a whopping six figures? My own blood? Best friend I ever had?  Year in, year out. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>You're wearing contacts under your glasses?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>They're tinted. Do you change your eye color?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-10"><speaker>Jennifer </speaker><content>Sometimes I like to mix it up. I don't understand. What are you…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-11"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>Wait, you–you don't have brown eyes? Where'd the name Baby Bear come from?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-12"><speaker>Phil </speaker><content>It's not like that. I swear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-13"><speaker>Phil </speaker><content>Come on, man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-14"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>Get out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-15"><speaker>Phil </speaker><content>I'm sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-16"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>He's crashing. Everything's shutting down. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>Patient had a cardiac arrest, and his lungs and liver failed before we even started the chemo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Brain symptoms that aren't brain symptoms, tumors that come and go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>It's not amyloidosis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>House </speaker><content>You're forgetting alopecia. Oh, I'm sorry. I thought you were just listing the things it's not, alphabetically.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>His long-lost love is a fraud. Thirteen figured that out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Good for her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>Decades of menial work, three cancers couldn't make him die miserable. She just did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-8"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>The truth made him miserable.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>Keep the clinic shut down. But wherever it is, it's isolated to the administrative floor. I'm not gonna evacuate the whole… </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>Arlene </speaker><content>Only way to get the two of you in the same place at the same time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>Reopen everything. Readmit everyone. Now. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>Arlene </speaker><content>I want you both to know I'm filing the suit today, delivering the paperwork to your counsel's office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>You have to be destructive. You have to tear things apart. God forbid you should say what's really on that twisted mind of yours?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>Arlene </speaker><content>And you're the great peacemaker? Single mom, can't keep a man long enough to cook a meal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>You'd be dead if it weren't for our mistreatment. And somehow you'd still find something to whine about.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>Arlene </speaker><content>We'll let the court decide who's whining since you're so sure—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-9"><speaker>House </speaker><content>We're not getting back together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-10"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>What are you talking about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-11"><speaker>House </speaker><content>It's the only explanation. Why she keeps making threats without ever filing her stupid, yet completely valid lawsuit. Why she ripped up her will, why she kicked half the hospital out on the street. She wants us united against her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-12"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>This is her drawing blood over the latest of a long line of imaginary slights. She doesn't care if anyone else is happy for a single—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-13"><speaker>Cuddy </speaker><content>I asked you to move in. That meant we weren't gonna reconcile. I'm sorry, mom.  Some things take more than a common enemy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-14"><speaker>Arlene </speaker><content>Then you're an idiot with impossible standards. (Cuddy turns to House, who is not there any more.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Common enemy. One way to trigger brain symptoms when there's nothing wrong with your brain have something else turn your brain into a common enemy. You have a teratoma, a usually harmless congenital growth which can be filled with almost any kind of tissue. And, unusually, not at all harmless. If I'm right, yours is filled with primitive cells, some of which developed into brain cells. These foreign cells leaked into your bloodstream. Now, the body is a little xenophobic. It creates antibodies. The problem is, there's not much difference between brain cells in your abdomen and brain cells in your brain. To make matters worse, primitive cells can become almost anything. Grow like weeds. Which means they can turn into tumors, destroy whole organ systems.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>Taub </speaker><content>But the cancer?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Was cancer. Just growing so fast it collapsed under its own weight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>Am I gonna live?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Cut out the teratoma, what's left of your cancer, you should be fine. Think of it as your second luckiest day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>Cyrus </speaker><content>It's hard to feel lucky. The woman I love was a fraud.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-7"><speaker>House </speaker><content>No, actually a fraud was a fraud. You fell for her just the same. You may stay miserable, but your long-lost love is not gonna be the reason why.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>It's the real Jennifer. Or at least the only one to show up who actually has the birthmark. He's renting her an apartment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>House </speaker><content>It'll end horribly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>Not for him. She may take all his money, and he may be a naive idiot, but… he'll always be hopeful, so he'll always be happy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>House </speaker><content>You lost your mother. You euthanized your brother. You got the life expectancy of a pretty good sitcom. If you can convince yourself that you'd be miserable no matter what even without all that stuff, then maybe you don't have to hate the universe for dumping a giant turd on you. Fatalism is your survival mechanism.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>Thirteen </speaker><content>And you? Dumped by everyone you've ever loved. Rehab was a bust. Your leg feels like somebody took a giant bite out of it. We are who we are. Lotteries are stupid.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>