<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>
<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Male announcer</speaker><content>This election day, the fate of our borders is in your hands. John Moreno wants to invite illegal immigrants into our country. He wants to give them our jobs. He wants to give them our healthcare. John Moreno wants to give them the American dream, and he wants you to pay for it. [People yelling) John Moreno. Whose side is he really on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Anderson</speaker><content>Whose side is he really on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Anderson</speaker><content>So do I.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>Shh… Come on, Hal. Your position on work visas is irrelevant. He's talking about a path to citizenship. I'm telling you, this ad wins you the election.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Anderson</speaker><content>By insulting one of my core constituencies. Come on, in '04 I had 45% of the Latino vote.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>And this year you're running against a guy named Moreno.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Anderson</speaker><content>This isn't one of your races in South Carolina or Oklahoma, Joe. This is New Jersey… People vote for me because I'm a moderate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>Well, that's great. You can be the most moderate ex-senator in the country. Hal, the election is seven days away, and even our own internals show you down six points.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Anderson</speaker><content>We've always been the underdog. And we've always found a way to win.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>I know. Because you have always let me do what's needed to be done. Now, I can have this on the air tomorrow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Anderson</speaker><content>No, no.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Anderson</speaker><content>No, absolutely not. This could totally galvanize the left.  You all right, Joe?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Anderson</speaker><content>What the hell? That's not a rash.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>Maybe I should call a doctor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Anderson</speaker><content>You better call an ambulance.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>What's that smell? Onions? Peppers? Oh, I know… It's a sausagefest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Sausagefest implies multiples. Now, if you're talking about yardage, I'd have to agree.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>I'm talking about your department. You still haven't replaced Thirteen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's coming along.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>You've had plenty of time to find someone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I've found plenty of someones. Just haven't kept them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>It's time to end the cycle.  Meet your new team member. Her name is Martha M. Masters.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>She's a third-year med student. She graduated high school when she was 15. She filled out the time before med school getting PhDs in both applied math and art history.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>She'll be incredibly useful if my next patient is an Escher drawing. Those things are seriously screwed up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>This isn't a suggestion.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Just because my sausage has been filling your bun, it doesn't mean you get to decide what flavor chips I nosh on during the day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Nope, I get to do that because I'm your boss. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Patient is Joe Dugan, 42, political consultant. Presents with palpable purpura, and ALT and AST are through the roof.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Otherwise known as rash and liver damage. Fascinating.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Senator Anderson sent this case to us, and personally requested we take a look. That's reason enough for me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Black guy campaigning for the opposition? Does Obama know about this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I tried calling him on the brother hotline. He didn't pick up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Martha M. Masters? I'm Dr. House. This is the rest of the team. Boring, Bimbo, and Bite-size. Martha enjoys quadratic equations, Italian frescoes, and her turn-ons include learning to be a doctor. Take a seat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>She's a med student?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Cuddy thinks she's some kind of genius. Say something brilliant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>Oh, I… I don't…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Capital of Azerbaijan?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>Baku.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Year Beethoven died?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>1827.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>20th decimal of Euler's number?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>Six.  It's my favorite constant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>She's like the Internet with breasts. Oh, no, wait… the Internet has breasts. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Our patient's liver damage explains the rash and cryoglobulins we found in his blood, but we can't explain the liver damage. Shows no other signs of drug or alcohol abuse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Now all we've gotta do is figure out which one is bimbo and which one is bite-size. Also, which monster truck won the 2004 thunder nationals?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Hep C makes sense.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-20"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Test came back negative. Same for Hep A and B.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The answer we were looking for is Virginia Giant. Feel free to chime in on either conversation. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-22"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Hate to steal the spotlight from small wonder over here, but what about toxic exposure?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-23"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Tetrachloroethylene. Could even be pennyroyal or sassafras oil.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-24"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Go to his house, get me some chemicals.  You wanna stay on this team, have an opinion. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>Oh, cool! Tudor revival architecture. Steeply pitched, asymmetrical roof over the entrance. But it doesn't have the half timbering over the facade.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Doesn't say anything about medicine, can't shut up about architecture. Great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>I know. I don't know what happened. Being around House… he's such a legend, he's so intimidating. I'm not like that around ordinary people. Uh, not that you guys are ordinary.  It's just that he's so brilliant and you work under him, so you're not as imposing. Um… I'm gonna be quiet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Good idea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>Dugan didn't give you a key?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>If patients know we're coming, they can hide something relevant to their illness intentionally or unintentionally. Their knowledge changes things.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Are you a vampire? It's okay. We're inviting you in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>But our patient didn't. I can't do this, I'm sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Well, she's gonna be a big help.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Yeah, what a rube being uncomfortable breaking into a stranger's house.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Part of our job description, not the most morally ambiguous part.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Give her a chance. She's fresh, enthusiastic, has no bad habits we need to reteach.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Is this attitude about her not having an M.D. after her name? Because I wonder if it has more to do with her being a brainiac.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>That's not it at all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I'm not thrilled someone else might be the smartest person on the team now. I can only imagine how you feel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Oh, yeah? You find this? </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>A jug of unpasteurized cider. It could be tainted with E coli, and that's what's causing the liver to shut down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>E coli is found in animals. So unless he's drinking pork cider…  Pork cider!  I need the number of the patent office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>There are indirect ways of attracting E coli.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Masters refused to go on the search with us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Interesting. Which raises the question,  what is your problem with her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>He is intimidated by her intelligence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Why would that bother Taub? He's been working with people smarter than him for a long time. I think perky new girl makes him feel old.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>She's basically the same age as Thirteen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, but she's a student. Makes you contemplate your med school days. Back when you had hair, muscle tone, and no need for a regular prostate exam.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Makes sense. Just like E coli. Orchards make cider out of apples they can't sell otherwise, like if they've fallen onto the ground. Like, into some cow feces.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Which would mean our esteemed patient is literally full of B.S. Cool. Go get the ingenue, start the patient on aztreonam and plasmapheresis.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>The cell sorter separates the plasma from the remaining cellular components, thereby removing…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Why would we do that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>Because the reason not to tell him was that he might hide something. And now that rationale is moot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>How can we ask our patients to trust us if we're not honest with them?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>How can we ask the patient to trust us after we tell him he can't trust us? Fine. Tell him. Clear your conscience, because that's what's important.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>You should probably slow down until you're out of the hospital.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>Aren't you curious how we came up with this diagnosis?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>You're doctors. Isn't that your job?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>But how we knew you were drinking apple cider?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>Well, you had to have found that at my house, so I guess you guys broke in there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>Medicine's like politics. At the end of the day, all that matters is results.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>That's not true.  Respect matters. Honesty and integrity matter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>Have you ever thought about running for public office? Because I would love to have someone like you as an opponent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>Oh, right, sorry.  You ever wonder why American voter turnout rates are among the lowest in the developed world?  Mr. Dugan?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Mr. Dugan? What's wrong? Can you hear me?  He's paralyzed.  Call Foreman and Chase, get them down here.  Mr. Dugan!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We think it's a transient ischemic attack. The clot must have broken up before we could find it. He was temporarily paralyzed, but he's regaining mobility and speech.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So, what causes rash, liver failure, clots, and the uncontrollable urge to rat out your coworkers? Oh, no, wait…  That last one was you, not the patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>I wasn't trying to rat. I was clearly trying to honor my ethical obligation. Portal vein thrombosis could be caused by Wilson's disease?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Hooray!  You popped your cherry, diagnostically speaking. Unfortunately, the first time always sucks. Pitch doesn't make any sense. Dugan's cornea was normal. You're obviously brilliant. So why would you hide your mind?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>I was brainstorming.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm not talking about your stupid ideas about the patient. I mean your stupid ideas about morality.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>My stupid ideas are what most doctors consider the rules for professional conduct.  What about a neuroendocrine tumor?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Not without diminished mental capacity, loss of judgment. Disseminated intravascular coagulation, however, fits.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Rules are just helpful guidelines for stupid people who can't make up their own mind. You obviously don't fit into that category, so why put yourself there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Masters is right about a neuroendocrine tumor. Because yes, Dugan has had a loss of judgment. He made this totally inflammatory anti-immigration campaign commercial for Anderson. It just got leaked online.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You're arguing Dugan's politics are a sign that he's mentally compromised?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>No, his tactics. He's most likely the one who leaked it and all the commentators are saying Anderson will catch a major backlash.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And honesty's a great idea until your patient asks if her distended abdomen makes her looks fat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>House, I hate to interrupt your ethics debate, but we have two solid ideas on the table.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>CT from his neck to his abdomen for neuroendocrine tumors. Run a D-dimer and fibrinogen for D.I.C.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Masters. If lying to a patient saved their life, would you do it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That's a lie. If your grandma gave you a really crappy tea cozy for Christmas, would you tell her you liked it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>Yes, but that's different.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-20"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So, you lie when it doesn't matter but you won't when it does. How'd you get so screwed up? </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>How mad would you be if I fired Masters?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Very. Unless you had cause. Real cause. Cause that a human being would consider cause.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Never mind, then. She's got principles. She's like the love child of Einstein and Mary Poppins. Didn't even get Einstein's hair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>It's worth having someone on the team who doesn't see the world entirely as shades of gray.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It is gray!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>To you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>She has a fresh perspective. Unless that threatens you. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It does not…  You thought I'd get defensive, keep her out of pride.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>No, he isn't.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>Because you told him not to?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Butting heads with House is par for the course. House has strong beliefs, and he respects other people with strong beliefs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>It's not my beliefs that are the problem. It's my personality. I'm not good at working with other people.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>You've been in there for less than a day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>I wasn't looking for encouragement. It's a fact. Growing up, my whole life, really, I-I spent a lot of time by myself. And no one in high school wants to hang out with a kid that's three years younger than them. And studying Anosov diffeomorphisms, determining whether an unattributed landscape is a blakelock or a ryder or… I'm actually boring you right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>And yet you chose medicine. Which is a team activity. It's pretty gutsy, stepping so far outside your comfort zone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>I'm not trying to prove anything. I just wanted to be a doctor. It was stupid. Nobody can do everything. I was vain to think I could be the exception.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>We gotta give Masters some pointers, help her figure out how to deal with House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Why would I do that? The entertainment factor is off the charts. It's like watching a bunny hop into a buzz saw. Repeatedly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>And if we don't help her, she's out of here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>No, something else is stopping House from firing her. I'm guessing it's his desire to keep having sex with Cuddy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>This tumor you're looking for… you're not gonna find it. My judgment is completely sound.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>So when you leaked that ad, you were trying to torpedo the Senator's campaign?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>All right, one, I told you before, I didn't leak that spot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Uh-huh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>And two… Whoever did leak that ad had nothing wrong with their mind either. It's gonna save Anderson.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>That commercial… Everyone sees through it. You're just trying to play to people's fears.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>You say fears. I say rational, protective instincts. And judging by your accent, immigration probably isn't an issue you can be real impartial about.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I waited five years to get my green card. If there's anyone who would resent someone trying to skip the queue, it'd be me. Just because Moreno favors amnesty…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>He doesn't. You know that picture of him with the Mexican flags that seems to be from a pro-amnesty rally? That's from an amnesty international speech protesting the imprisonment of priests in Oaxaca. Yes, you did just prove that that ad is even more disgusting than you thought. You also proved that ad is effective. You still think my judgment is off?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Not anymore. There's no sign of a tumor. That leaves D.I.C. I'll go check how Taub is doing with the blood work.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I guess when you get on in years, it takes a little longer to run a few simple blood tests.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>This whole "Taub's an old man" thing kinda rings hollow, considering I'm in better shape than you are. Pass the dye.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You're in rounder shape than me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You do realize you're two and a half feet tall, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>And white. And Jewish. It'd be very embarrassing. I get why you wanna say no.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Tonight after work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Crap.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Anderson</speaker><content>Did you hear Moreno's latest stump speech? He's gonna clean up Washington.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Anderson</speaker><content>This morning's tracking has me within two points.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Your blood test for D.I.C. came back completely normal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>That's good news, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>That means the two things we thought it could be, it's not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>We checked your home for toxins and didn't find any. But it's possible you might've been exposed on the campaign. Have you visited any industrial or agricultural facilities?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>Anderson</speaker><content>There was a tomato farm in Lumberton.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>They take you into the fields?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>No one wants a photo op with me. I never leave the bus.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Were the windows open? Certain pesticides…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Foreman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-12"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>What? What is it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-13"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>It's not just your liver we have to worry about. Looks like your kidneys are having problems, too.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So this guy spends his entire life campaigning against bleeding hearts. And it turns out he has one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>Bloody urine actually is a renal problem, not a cardiac one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, if I say something inaccurate, assume it's for comic effect. Then laugh,</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>200,000. It's not T.T.P.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>What about henoch-schoenlein purpura?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>H.S.P. Doesn't cause clots.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>H.S.P. Doesn't usually cause clots, but it can. And the vasculitis would explain the kidney problem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>She can't diagnose a joke, but she's making progress on the patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>We treat with chemotherapy or steroids.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>We treat with chemotherapy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-11"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>I said chemo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Then you said, "or."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-13"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Once again, the bunny meets the blade.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The road to dead patients is paved with "or"s. Chemo is the more effective treatment, which means it'll confirm our diagnosis more quickly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-15"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>I agree, but there is another option.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>There are lots of other options. There's bloodletting, crystals, prayer…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-17"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>Another medically accepted option.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Which is both less effective and less scary. So the patient might just choose it. Unless, of course, we don't mention it to him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-19"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>We can't withhold information. If we explain both the benefits and the risks of each treatment I'm sure Dugan will choose chemo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-20"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, as long as you're sure.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>The better option is chemotherapy. It's faster and more likely to completely cure you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>I'll take the steroids.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh, my goodness!  If only someone could've predicted that you'd make that incredibly stupid decision. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>Our poll numbers have stalled. That's five days till the election.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>Anderson</speaker><content>Doctor, can you talk some sense into him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Would that I could, but ethics dictate that it's his decision. So all I can do now is return to my office knowing, even as my patient endangers himself, my integrity remains unblemished.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>Please. Take some time to think about this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>I don't need any time. I want to start on the steroids.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Game to 11 by ones.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Uh, hold on.  Wanna shoot for outs?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You can have it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You gonna guard me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Can't hit two in a row.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You can have that shot all day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Three, nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>One, three.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Ten, seven.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Seriously? You're gonna beat me with that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-11"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-12"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Now all we have to do is figure out why Masters is making you feel insecure.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>I was just down by Dugan's room. They were ready to give him the wrong medicine. I tried to change the order, but I'm not a doctor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Good. The wrong medicine is the right medicine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>But he wanted steroids, not chemo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He wants to live.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>I'm gonna tell him what's going on. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, you're not.  I don't mind your morality in theory. But in practice, you're risking my patient's life. So you're fired.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>You think that's gonna stop me from telling him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If you do, I'll get you thrown out of medical school.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I know. But unlike you, I'm willing to lie.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Firing her was a mistake. We need someone like her on the team, keeping us all in check.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're incapable of noticing when I do something inappropriate?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>We're like the frogs who've been in the pot for a while. We're used to the heat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Things have been just fine without Pippi Longdivision.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Your opponent's out of the race. You can drop the smear campaign.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Masters was right. He didn't want the chemo. He didn't need the chemo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Masters was wrong. He doesn't have H.S.P. And Masters is gone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Could be an infection.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We had him on aztreonam for the E coli. He didn't respond.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Schistosomiasis wouldn't respond to aztreonam.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That's a great idea if he was running a political campaign in Africa. The guy hasn't been out of the country in years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-12"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Who needs to travel when you've got a giant fish tank loaded with tropical fish, tropical snails carrying tropical bacteria like schistosomiasis?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, break into his home, get me some escargots. Unless you wanna ask the patient's permission as a tribute to the departed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-14"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Need a minute.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>You said you were gonna give her a chance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I did! She used that opportunity to endanger our patient's life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>By insisting he receives the treatment that he asked for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That's what I just said!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Your team is there to challenge you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>He's right, I'll just…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>She's a potential star, and I want her in my hospital.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No problem. Just find her a different department. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I think I've figured it out. Why Taub didn't like Masters.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Now you're getting involved in this, too?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>My previous source of entertainment just got fired.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Exactly. She's gone. It's over.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>She's totally moral and uptight, which made Taub feel badly about his cheating.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Can we get a move on? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You didn't like her even before you knew about her morals. It's from the minute he saw her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>So… It's something about how she looked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>All right. No snails. Let's get out of here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Hello?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>It's Foreman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What'd you find?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Nothing helpful, but…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>There's gotta be something. Dugan's going completely downhill. Now fluid's collecting in his chest. Where the hell are you guys?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>In jail. You gonna come bail us out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Uh… kinda busy. </content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>There you are.  I was starting to think that my holier-than-thou-dar was malfunctioning. Our patient's liver, kidneys, and lungs are failing. I need you to help me figure out why. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>As I recall, you have three actual doctors you haven't fired today.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>They're in jail.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>What? Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Prostitution. So you're rehired.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, I don't need to hear your ideas. Just return the volley.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>Primary sclerosing cholangitis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Nope. His vitamin A level is normal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>Gall bladder problems can affect the liver.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Cholecystitis?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Did you just shush me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-12"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>Shh! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-13"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>I think he's lying. Dugan said…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The technical term is speaking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-15"><speaker>Anderson</speaker><content>Dugan violated my trust. And therefore, I have no other recourse than to fire him from my campaign. Thank you, and there will be no further questions. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He screwed you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>That was a hell of a move. Use the ad to shore up the base, fire the extremist to hold the center.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, I mean he actually screwed you. Taking weekend trips down to Bunbury. He's got a red blotch on his hand. That's palmar erythema. That, and the fact that he's got a permanent sheen of nixonian flop sweat. He's got hepatitis C, which explains all your symptoms.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>That's great, but the Senator and I have not had sex.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, then the two of you shot up together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>How many high-functioning heroin users do you know?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Actually, quite a few.  Look, I know you've got hep C. So either you shared a bed together, you shared a needle, or you shared a straw. I'm talking about coke, not coke.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>You can get hep C from doing cocaine? Look, I will deny it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Don't care.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-10"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>They tested me for hep C when I came in here. I don't have it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-11"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>What is that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>This is interferon. It delays the onset of rigor mortis. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>When did your lawyer say he was coming to get us?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>He said, and I'm quoting here, "soon."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I know. The reason you hated Masters from the moment you saw her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Come on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>That was not the first time you saw her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>That is brilliant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>It's really not. Is that guy seriously using the toilet? Oh, my God, he's sitting down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Don't try to change the subject. Did you sleep with her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You realize we're not gonna drop this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I didn't sleep with her. I interviewed her for Hopkins med school.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-11"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>So you're holding a grudge, because she chose a different school?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-12"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>We talked for an hour. She didn't remember me. She remembers the 20th digit of some math constant, but she doesn't remember a guy she had a one-on-one meeting with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-13"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Well, I barely remember you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-14"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Mystery solved. Now we can all go back to our lives.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Great news. I've decided to rehire you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>Find another sounding board.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Dugan's got hep C.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>I'm not doing this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He's not responding to interferon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>You must think I have absolutely no self-esteem. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Ethics and self-esteem? You really are a pain in the ass. What treats hep C besides interferon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-8"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>Now you want me to talk?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Come on, stop pretending you're not gonna do this. As much as you hate me, you hate failing more.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-11"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>I didn't fail. You fired me. Repeatedly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>But if you walk away now, after I just rehired you, that's quitting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-13"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>A German research study showed that 15% of patients with hep C were cured after contracting hep A. Of course, other studies have shown that up to 85% of doubly-infected patients die very quickly. So, in theory, if we can find something that mimics hep A…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>There's one thing that mimics hep A… Hep A. Good work.  You're fired.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-15"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>No!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Hep A could cure him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Better chance it'll kill him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Tell the lab to release a hep A culture to me. We'll see who's right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>It's not an approved treatment and exposes us to liability. There's no way I can let you do this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>That's an extremely cowardly position.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Listen to the genius.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>You're the one that insisted he run this by me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>It's proper protocol for an unconventional treatment. But we shouldn't compromise patient care just to avoid lawsuits.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>What about the fact that we don't have any proof he actually has hep C?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-10"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>If you really think that this is the only way to cure him, I will risk the lawsuit. But I need to know that he actually has the disease. Get me proof.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I've given you…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-12"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Proof! Get me proof he has hep C, and then you can give him hep A.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I can't.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-14"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>You'll figure something out. The two of you have combined I.Q. North of 300.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That's also true of five morons. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>So what do we do now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, considering the fact that I'm about to do something unethical…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>Oh, right, yeah… I'm fired.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Missed you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>We need a false positive hep C test.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>And why would we want to do that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The world changes when you're on the inside. You just gotta roll with it once you get out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You think he contracted hep C from the Senator, right? Test Anderson. If it's positive, that's evidence Dugan has it, too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Evidence, not proof.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Are we presenting this to a jury of our peers? That should be enough for Cuddy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Should be, but it won't be.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-12"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>The test for hep C is 99.9% accurate. That means one in every thousand test is a false positive. We do enough, maybe we get lucky.  I smell like jail.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>False false positive. That's the best we can do? Okay, go do it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I think you probably already know the answer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>But it doesn't make any sense.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You don't understand why a woman might be upset because her boyfriend lied to her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I wouldn't be lying as her boyfriend. I'd be lying as her employee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>That's not how relationships work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>My patient is gonna die.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Does the lie guarantee he'll live?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You got two choices: To be honest and face the medical consequences, or lie and face the personal consequences.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>Anderson</speaker><content>Now that you're my doctor, you, uh… You can't tell anybody, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Who'd leak a story about a sitting senator who got hep C from doing cocaine? You didn't fill out any paperwork. I'm gonna run this test under an assumed name. Trust me… No one will ever know you were here. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Blood test confirming hep C. He got sicker, his viral load came up, finally showed up on the test.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Thank you. There was a time when you would have completely ignored my request. That means a lot that you respect me enough to do this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I've come a long way, baby.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm on it. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>How'd you like to come work for me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>It's like I'm on a Mobius strip.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>We've had this conversation. You want this job.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Prove yourself to me, no more games. At least, the current game ends. Others may start. You have my deeply-flawed word.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>What do I have to do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Get Dugan to let us give him hep A. And while you're figuring out the best way to coax a patient into a treatment that has an 85% mortality rate, here's some advice: Don't.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-7"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>I'm not gonna lie to him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You have a math degree. So let's see if you can follow along here. You lie to him, he definitely consents, he might live. You tell him the truth like last time, he might not consent, he definitely dies. Remind me what's so wrong about lying?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>We're going to inject you with hepatitis A.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>That doesn't sound like medicine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-3"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>I know it seems counter-intuitive, but in some people, the virus can enhance immune function and clear out the hepatitis C. Some.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-4"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>How many we talking about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-5"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>A fair amount.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-6"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>Give me a percentage. What are the odds of this thing working?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-7"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>There is an 85% chance that this will kill you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-8"><speaker>Dugan</speaker><content>So, you wanna give me something that works 15% better than arsenic?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-9"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>Well, technically, it works infinitely better because arsenic has a 0% chance. This is your only shot. Both Dr. House and I believe that. He faked a blood test in order to get you approved for this treatment. And then he tried to bribe me into lying to you about the risks. If either of those incidents came to light, he would be suspended and probably lose his license.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh, I'm sure some other people would suffer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-11"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>He's risking his career to give you this chance. He wouldn't do that if there was any other choice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-12"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>I did it. And I didn't have to lie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And you feel good about that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-14"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So I'm hiring an idiot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-16"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>You can pretend you wanted me to lie, but you didn't. You want the people on your team to challenge you otherwise you'd just be a bully instead of a great doctor. You hired me because I don't compromise my principals.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Or I want a front row seat when you wake up and realize how useless your principals are. I don't want you to just lie to a patient. I want you to want to lie to a patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-18"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>It's not gonna happen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>See you tomorrow.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I heard Dugan is already responding to treatment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>Yeah, his alt level is already beginning to normalize.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I wanted to apologize for the way…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-4"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>Uh, wait… You interviewed me, right? For Hopkins?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-5"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>I wanted to say something the first day. I felt really awkward about the whole thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Don't worry about it.  Is this grandma's tea cozy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-7"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Nothing. I'll see you upstairs.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="34"><utterance uid="34-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If I knew hiring her meant dealing with medical school paperwork, I might've reconsidered. You really got nothing better to do than watch me sign this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-2"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>And miss the ultimate admission that I was right about Masters all along?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>She had me when she called you a coward. You gonna hang out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-4"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>I have to work late. Gloating requires a lot of paperwork.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="35"><utterance uid="35-1"><speaker>Nurse</speaker><content>Do you know where the Senator's records are?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-2"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>House was treating Anderson's campaign manager, not the Senator himself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-3"><speaker>Nurse</speaker><content>Oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-4"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>Why did you think he was the patient?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-5"><speaker>Nurse</speaker><content>House saw him in the clinic. I guess it wasn't medical.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-6"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>When?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-7"><speaker>Nurse</speaker><content>Friday. Around 3.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-8"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>House's team ran a hep C test on Joe Dugan on Friday. Can you look up the time?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-9"><speaker>Nurse</speaker><content>Chase, Taub, and Foreman were running tests all night. All negative. Positive test at… 3:17 P.M. House ran it himself. Is everything okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-10"><speaker>Cuddy</speaker><content>I don't think so.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>