<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>
<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Lady</speaker><content>If you don't know how to use a computer, we will teach you here. Most jobs require at least basic word processing skills. We try to get you up to 50 words per minute. We also have a course in how to talk to someone in an interview. Stuff like what employers are looking for, how to turn negatives into positives. We can also provide clothes for the interview if you need them. People donate shoes and suits all the time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>Wh-what if I had a history with, uh… with drugs?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Lady</speaker><content>That is nothing to be ashamed of. Many of our clients have struggled with addiction, and, if you want to get clean, we'll help you do that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>And what if I have a kid?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Lady</speaker><content>No one to help you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>You know, if I need someone to watch her while I'm in class or, uh, on an interview. Could you help with that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Lady</speaker><content>We do not provide child care. Actually, it's something that comes up often. I would love to be able to do it. I just don't have the resources. But it's definitely on the wish list.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>Okay… Okay, uh, thank you. I'll be back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Lady</speaker><content>Oh, I have to take this. Yes, please come back, we'll get you started. It was nice to meet you, Benjamin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Lady</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Lady</speaker><content>Hey, Oscar. Agh! Oh, that is too bad. Did they tell you why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Lady</speaker><content>Yeah… Mm-hmm. Well, you know what? Sometimes, you just don't get the job, but…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Lady</speaker><content>Oscar, I gotta call you back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Lady</speaker><content>Oh… uh, uh…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Lady</speaker><content>Benjamin! Benjamin, wait!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Lady</speaker><content>Oh, my God. Uh…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Lady</speaker><content>Somebody call an ambulance!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Why am I watching you cut your hair?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If I do it at home, I'm the one who has to clean it up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-20"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I was referring less to where it’s happening and more to why.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content>New life, new look.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-22"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Does that mean you like your new life?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-23"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If you're asking if your job is safe, that depends on what you have to say about the file you're holding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-24"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>It doesn't seem like much of a case. Although, I'm sure I'm wrong…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-25"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You are. Tell me why.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-26"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Guy collapsed after being on his feet for hours on a hot day without breakfast, so… that's really weird.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-27"><speaker>House</speaker><content>E.R. found nothing wrong, then I decided I should test his wallet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-28"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>He's rich? That's why we're taking the case?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-29"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, we're taking the case because no one knows what's wrong with him. And he's rich.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-30"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Dr. Adams.  Give her the file.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-31"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>This is my only copy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-32"><speaker>House</speaker><content>My M.O. depends upon the use of a team. Definitionally, that involves… more than one person. So I really have no choice. Give her the file.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-33"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>You can't afford a team.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-34"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Adams is free. And I'm referring both to her availability and her price tag . New girl, meet newer girl, and vice versa.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-35"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>You said we were meeting for coffee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-36"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, when someone asks if you want coffee, they obviously don't just mean coffee. Wait… did you think I was referring to sex?  Would you shut the blinds on your way out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-37"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I thought you were referring to talking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-38"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Talking about medicine. Specifically, as it refers to the guy whose name is on the file she still hasn't handed you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-39"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I'm not working, House. I'm in the process of looking for a paying job.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-40"><speaker>House</speaker><content>In the meantime, there's no way a do-gooder like you has been volunteering all over town — ladling kittens, spaying soup…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-41"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>There is a free clinic in Trenton.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-42"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, think of this as today's free clinic. Only with fewer bums with herpes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-43"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I don't think we actually have much of a case. I think it's just dehydration.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-44"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What happened the last time another doctor told you I was wrong about a case?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-45"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I lost my job.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-46"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You saved a life.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>Is an ultrasound really necessary? I'm feeling much better now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Oh, a sudden collapse at your age can indicate a deterioration of the heart muscle. Pretty serious condition.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>It can also just be dehydration.  Next time, you could probably drop the undercover act.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>I walk in a suit, and they're gonna put their best foot forward. Also, I don't own a suit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content> You give away millions and you don't own a suit?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>I gave those away too. One day, I was writing a check to my landscaper, and it suddenly hit me — $6,000 to take out plants and put in different plants. So I can look at them. Shouldn't I use that money to do something important?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>And by money, you mean all your money.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>I started with 10 million, and I couldn't think of a reason not to give 20. Or 40. I figure I could live off $25,000 a year. One-room apartment. Bus pass, thrift stores. Bare necessities. I still have my software company. And when I make more, I'll give that way too.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>He's nuts.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>He's generous.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>There's a neurological issue. He's getting rid of everything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>His echocardiogram is negative for cardiomyopathy. Head CT showed no signs of stroke or hemorrhage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>He has one pair of pants.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Most people with his kind of money are commissioning oil paintings of their Yorkshire terrier. Benjamin is sacrificing his own comfort to help others.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That's because helping others is his Yorkie oil painting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>That's good. Not sick.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>That's naive and sick. You really want to improve things? You do it through policy. This guy empties his pockets, what really changes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That's right, all those babies with AIDS, they're just using us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>My parents had $800 between them when they got here. They scraped and borrowed so we could go to good schools, and I worked my ass off. No one gave me a handout. It makes me work harder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Rebuttal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>What's your evil plan?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I object to your cynicism.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>It's been earned.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That's what I object to. The new Dean of Medicine has an ethical obligation to come in with a completely open mind about all employees, thus letting me blithely run roughshod for at least four weeks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>My theory is that you're running a battery of tests to convince him that you saved his life, then con him into funding you to hire back your team.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content> What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Your old team?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-20"><speaker>House</speaker><content> What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-21"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>This is your new reality. You've got your office. You've got neighbors. You've got one employee, one volunteer. Until she finds actual, paid work, or gets sick of you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-22"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I talked to Chase and Taub. They're willing to come back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-23"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>What about Thirteen?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-24"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Not a good choice. She's not long term because she has no long term.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-25"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Not taking your calls?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-26"><speaker>House</speaker><content>She will.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-27"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Discharge the patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-28"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Unexplained loss of consciousness could be cardiomyopathy, global anoxia, subarachnoid hemorrhage—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-29"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Dehydration. He was given fluids, and he got better. And I'm sure your tests have come up negative, or you would have shut me up already. Which means he goes home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-30"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>There is a symptom… Extreme altruism.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-31"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You've got two choices, House. You can recognize that your patient is just a very nice, healthy guy, and send him home, or you can consider altruism a symptom. In which case, you cannot take his money. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-32"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Send him home. And check with admitting for the net worth of all new patients.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content> I'm not coming back, House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Technically, you're back right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>I need you to stop calling me. First 17 messages were cute, but—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm putting the band back together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Interesting that you never showed up at my place, what with your love of annoying me and your inability to take no for an answer. I'm guessing ankle monitor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Guilty as charged. Literally.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>I'm not a doctor anymore, House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The job went away, but not the profession. You look healthy, so… that's not it. You met a boy. Or a girl. Fall in love, wanna be happy. You decided to… enjoy what time you have left. You're going to Thailand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Girl. And Mykonos.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Turns out I like boring.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, you wanna like boring. But if you actually liked boring, you would have figured that out in fifth grade, when you were bored.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Please stop calling me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content> No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You showed up to tell me that you don't want to hear from me. That's a mixed signal. I will choose to listen to your actions rather than your words. They're more honest.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>I'm a little confused.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>The test is designed to determine if you're—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>No, I mean you’re running a test and discharging me. Was I dehydrated or not?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I think so. But, out of an abundance of caution, my colleague has taken it upon herself to do one more test.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>All right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>You scare me a little.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content> Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I've been considering applying to Doctors Without Borders. Going overseas a while and that seems like a huge sacrifice. But… you—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>You don't scare her. You make her feel guilty.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>Oh, you… you like your life the way it is. Most people give the minimum they have to give so they can enjoy what they have left. I guess my minimum is just… higher than most.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Complete recruitment and interference pattern. His leg muscles are fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>I feel, uh, funny.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Where?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>My chest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>You're tachycardic. Your heart's beating too fast.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Unbelievable.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Patient got tachycardic to 185. We pushed 18 milligrams adenosine. There's definitely something wrong with him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Which is awesome. Now there's something to cure, which means there's something to be disproportionately financially grateful for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Morning. Got you a coffee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Thanks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Arrhythmia could easily have caused the collapse that landed Father Teresa in here in the first place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Oh, that's fine. Keep it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>We looked at his heart yesterday, didn't see any structural abnormalities. I'm thinking occult long QT syndrome?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>What about Whipple's?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If it was Whipple's, there'd be some kind of neurological involvement.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>You don't think defying human nature is neurological?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Racing heart: Medical condition. Bleeding heart: Stupid condition.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Are you saying that because you believe it, or because it's in your financial best interest to think his generosity isn't just temporary?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm told that some people are just nice. I'm trying to embrace that wisdom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Benjamin's been taking allergy medication the last few weeks. Long QT syndrome can be medication-induced.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Flush him with saline, get rid of the antihistamines, then do an EKG. No, wait. I'll do the flushing.  Take the damn $2.00. She hasn't even sipped the coffee. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I just got so angry. You know? So I made a terrible mistake. Now I'm trying to start my life over. To help people the way I always wanted. But my department got defunded, and… it's my fault. Just can't stand to think of all those patients going untreated because I don't have the resources to do my best work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>How about I help you out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>How do you mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>I'll give a million dollars as an endowment to the hospital, earmarked for diagnostics.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Wow. I am an opportunistic ex-con who just gave you a two-minute sob story as step three in my master plan, and you've offered me a million dollars. Which is step 17.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>Is that bad?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Ethics are not my strong suit.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Hypothetical — if I'm offered oral sex from a sexaholic, do I have to decline? Don't answer yet. Saying no will cause both of us pain. Saying yes will cause both of us pleasure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You can't take sex from a sexaholic. You can't give booze to an alcoholic, and you can't take this guy's money.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Could be wrong about the symptom. I'm wrong all the time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Taking money from a sick person is ethically suspect at best.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What is this, Canada? All we do is take money from sick people.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>We work for it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm working!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>How much?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>20 dollars.  Well, what if it was? It's the same principle. 20 dollars, a million… What's the difference?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Actually, the difference is pretty much a million dollars.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He came up with the figure, not me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Crap. Got a patient with end stage renal disease. Her heart can't support dialysis. She needs a transplant, but…  you tuned out as soon as it stopped being about you, didn't you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I gotta go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's all moot. Patient probably has long QT. Probably just a really, really decent person. They exist, right?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>Is long QT bad?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>It's a tough thing to control. Is there someone you want me to call?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>There's someone I would like to call. She's the same person who won't take my calls. My wife. When I started giving away the money, I-I hoped she'd want to do it with me. She didn't. I miss them. I have two little boys. Having a family doesn't exempt me from social responsibility.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>But family comes first.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>It should. I know that sounds weird, but… someone who's related to you, does that empirically makes them more special? More deserving than anyone else?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Yes, it gives you a responsibility.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>My boys have a roof over their heads. They're not starving. I pay court-ordered child support, and, frankly, it's, uh… more than they need. I love them more than anything, I just… I can't justify buying video games and private schools when other people's children are starving. I hope, one day, they'll understand that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Your hands are trembling.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>Is it the electrodes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Are you in pain?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>No. What's happening?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I'm not sure, but it's not what we thought it was.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So… arrhythmia, fainting, muscle tremors. Plus, unfortunately, mental changes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content> I still don't think it's neurological. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>God bless you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>He lost his wife and kids because he couldn't stop giving money away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>He lost his wife because she couldn't accept not being filthy rich.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content> She's not drinking the coffee either.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Drink it, don't drink it. The point is, I gave it to you, so we're even.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Even? It was a gift. An insignificant token. There was nothing owed. That was the whole point.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>She's the crazy one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>So a guy gives everything away to strangers: Sane. Girl who doesn't want anything from a stranger: crazy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>You're not a stranger. And your perverse view of the world is making you force a neurological component onto an obviously cardiological—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Your parents didn't love you enough. So you need to prove your superiority. Or they love you too much, so you need to prove your humility. Or it's just rich guilt. I'm betting on the last one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>There's a whole list of drugs that could have caused his symptoms.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I doubt the guy would spend money on drugs when there are orphans out there without cable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-18"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Anyway, he'd be getting better right now, not worse. Could be polyarteritis nodosa.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-19"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>That comes with a rash. Echovirus.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-20"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Virus, virus, virus, virus…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-21"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Fits his physical symptoms. And could, but doesn't necessarily cause personality changes.  Works for everyone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-22"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Start him on antivirals. And, Adams… when you treat, and he gets better, and doesn't give Bob Cratchit Christmas day off, you owe me a coffee. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content> Click the third tab from the left and find the box that says "previous entries." You get a drop-down menu sorted by patient name and department.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Thank you. Appreciate your help.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>You're gonna read too much into this, aren't you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, not at all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>We're gonna fundamentally disagree about what it means to read too much into this. Aren't we?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yes, absolutely.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Look, I thought about what you said, and I realized you were right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Great. See you tomorrow morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>No, you won't.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Afternoon? I can't think of another interpretation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Shut up. Look, I'm not sure what you were trying to achieve. I'm never quite sure. But you were actually a friend to me when I needed it. I don't wanna come back to work for you. But I was wrong to try to push you out of my life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Everything has gone blue. That's not supposed to happen, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Stay there. I'm comin'.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No… you don't have to do that. Although, if you did come, maybe you could swing by the Hunan Palace and get some lo mein and a Szechuan beef.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>That is six miles out of my way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh, okay, then. Guess I'll get something from the hospital cafeteria, which is where I get all my meals since I can't go anywhere.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-17"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content> Fine. I'll get the food.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're a peach.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I started the last round of pleconaril.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Can you do me a favor?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>A favor?  You want me to return these? Give them to someone? Wear them while you masturbate?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content> I… want you to have them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>That's not a favor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>It was a two-for-one sale. I couldn't resist. I need to justify buying them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>They're $120. My car is in the shop. I'm short on cash this month. I can't pay you back. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>The first pair were $120. These…  were free.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>You do know I punched the last person that pissed me off?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Was it Santa? </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>What's your patient's status?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Better. We're discharging him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> Good. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Hey, hey, hey. Why do you care? Specifically. Although I'm curious about a general answer too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Your guy just signed up to donate a kidney to my patient with renal failure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Did he meet your patient with renal failure?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>No, he heard the nurses talking about her, that she was short on time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I was wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Don't say that. House, she really needs this kidney.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He's not better. His mental status is declining.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Or he's doing an amazing thing for another human being.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I thought it was an ethical no-brainer that we can't take stuff from sick people.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-13"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I changed my mind.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He's still sick.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>His symptoms have gone away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Not all of them. Offering an organ to a stranger is a symptom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>A couple dozen people a year make undirected kidney donations.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, how many of them are also in the process of pauperizing themselves?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>If the guy threw himself on a grenade, he'd be a hero. If it saves a life, who cares?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You do! Yesterday, when you made the exact opposite argument. If there's even a chance I'm right, it'd be dangerous to give his kidney to someone else.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>More dangerous than complete renal failure? My patient needs this. Now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah. If only we could kill 60,000 more people a year, all would be golden.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>I'll give you your money.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>See? Crazy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-12"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Being a live donor has risks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-13"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>I looked it up. The risk is 1 in 4,000 I could die during surgery, which means, if I don't donate, I'm valuing my life at 4,000 times someone else's. It's not like I want to be cut open and have a part of me taken out. But I've got two, and this woman has none. She'll die without it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-14"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Perfectly logical.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>People with mental deficiency can be logical. Just like sane people can be illogical.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-16"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>This kidney thing is the only evidence you have that he's sick. I'm gonna let him be a donor. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-17"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>Dr. House, it's not a symptom. Come back after you're convinced that I'm healthy, and I will give you your money.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, you won't. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>We have time for one more test before we move him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-20"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>What test?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Whatever test will prove there was an echovirus-irus-irus, and he's not cured, obviously.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-22"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I've been saying all along this could be Whipple's. Causes arrhythmia, tremor, and mental changes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-23"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Bad idea. There's no joint pain. Where's Adams?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-24"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>We thought the case was over. She has a job interview.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-25"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Why is she here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-26"><speaker>House</speaker><content>'Cause I called her. Bigger question is why that worked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-27"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>I'm here because I have time and you have a crisis and I—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-28"><speaker>House</speaker><content>We're too busy for rationalizations. Patient made a big downgrade in his personal life. He's probably not eating all that healthy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-29"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Magnesium deficiency?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-30"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Wait until they take him back to his room — draw blood, do an expanded electrolyte profile.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-31"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>No, he hasn't had anxiety or any trouble sleeping. I think it's Whipple's disease.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-32"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Bad idea. He doesn't have joint pain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-33"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Joint pain is common, but not definitive. Whipple's explains all of his symptoms, including the personality change. And it would respond to antibiotics, which is why he started to feel better. Which doesn't mean he's not still sick.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-34"><speaker>House</speaker><content> You were right. Counts for nothing if you can't defend it. Book a procedure room. Do an upper endoscopy and run a PCR test for Whipple's.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-35"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Guilt. You feel guilty about leaving.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-36"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Yes, I think that little of you and that much of me. You're nothing without me. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-37"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Not leaving me. Leaving humanity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-38"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>I'm going with my girlfriend. The woman I love.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-39"><speaker>House</speaker><content>To have fun.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-40"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>You're trying to make me feel guilty because you're saving lives here. And I think that's great. I'm proud to have been a part of it, but… now… I just wanna be happy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-41"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh… no one's unhappy in Greece.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>Woman</speaker><content>It just appeared in the last few weeks. He's having trouble holding a pencil in school.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Does it itch? Do anything different lately? You get a new baseball glove, a new kitten?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>Woman</speaker><content>Well, the neighbors put in a pool, so he's been spending a lot of time over there. But, well, if it was something in the water, it would be everywhere, wouldn't it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It is in the water.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>Woman</speaker><content>He's allergic to chlorine?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No…  He's allergic to summer lilac.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>Woman</speaker><content>That's my lotion. And it's not in the pool.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, it's on the palms of his hands. In the pool is the neighbor's daughter. Or the neighbor's hot wife. Here's some lube.  Sorry. Too late for your eyesight.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Endoscopy didn't reveal any lesions in the small intestine. I'm running PCR test now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Found it in my office. Appears to be a gift. That can't be good. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Damn it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You got her the job interview.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>And that was supposed to be the end of it. I… don't take charity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Good for you! You loon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I don't like owing people things.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So either you're so insecure that you feel like you need to always have the upper hand, or you're so arrogant that the notion of a favor is insulting to you. Or it's your family, some kind of immigrant pride thing. I'm betting on the last one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I just don't like it. It makes me feel… icky.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That's the reason? Ickiness? You never even tried to analyze this? It's even crazier than the gift thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-11"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>House…  there's no sign of tropheryma DNA. It's not Whipple's.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well… we did what we could.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You sure you wanna do this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>Surgeon</speaker><content>Go a little bit more along here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Dr. Simpson. Heart rate's 140, pressure's dropping. Get him adenosine, stat.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Arrhythmia's back. He's on Heparin and stable for now, but this could put him at risk for stroke or embolism.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Maybe he got bit by a spider. The symptoms can take up to three days to manifest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>He'd have localized pain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>LCDD?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Almost always hits the kidneys.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Ah, Dr. Foreman. Perhaps you can help us. I can't decide whether to take out an "I told you so" ad in the New England Journal or stay classy and just spray-paint it on your car.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You're off the case.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That seems like an overreaction.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You dosed him. Couldn't stand to lose him as a patient, so you faked his symptom to prove you right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>That's idiotic.  Sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Don't apologize. I don't know if you're power crazed or paranoid, but I know she's right. Two lives are in the balance here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-12"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>House, I worked for you for seven years. I know how you operate. So when I see symptoms magically show up right when you need them—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And I was your boss for seven years. And I know what a suspicious, micromanaging hard-ass you are. Why would I do this now? Knowing you can send me right back to jail?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-14"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>What'd you give him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Nothing! You can't prove otherwise. So why don't you do the smart thing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-16"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You're off the case. You no longer have access to this patient. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-17"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>You can't let him do this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content> He's the boss. And he's right.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I assume you dosed the patient because you're really certain he has a neurological condition?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I assume you're interpreting my actions in the best possible light 'cause you didn't get the job?  What's with you and Park?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I expect my people to lie better than that. Either you're getting her gifts because you want her to like you, in which case I don't like you, or you're getting her gifts to screw with her. In which case, I will be teaching you my secret homey handshake.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I just… I thought it was interesting she couldn't accept that coffee. I wanted to see how deep it went.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>But now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Oh, now I just want to win.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content> What was in the box?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-9"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Gift certificate. The Spa.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Nah, that's not gonna do it. You're up against a lifetime of training. If you wanna win, you gotta do something she can't possibly reciprocate. You gotta push her neuroses to the point where even she thinks that she's crazy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>One more favor. Then I promise, I'll leave you alone forever. Or I'm lying. Either way, it's more interesting than whatever you're doing now.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Can I help you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>Woman</speaker><content>I'm his wife. We're separated. I heard he was sick. I just… wanted to see him. He's giving a kidney to someone he's never met?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>He wants to, yeah. I know he's talked about you. He's been alone all this time. I'm sure it would mean a lot to him to see you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>Woman</speaker><content>I wanted to spend my life with him, but… I need to feel like he loves me more than other people. Like he loves our kids more. Maybe that's selfish… I should go. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>Was that my wife?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>I don't know. You the guy, the kidney donor?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>There was a problem, but… I'm gonna try again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Um… to give it to the same lady?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>She needs it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Okay. Never mind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>Wait. What do you — what do you want?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-12"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Uh, it's nothing. It's just… I have polycystic kidney disease. And I need a transplant, and they say I don't have much time, so when I heard that you were willing, I just… But I'm glad it's going to someone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-13"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content> I'll give it to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-14"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>But you already promised it to someone else.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-15"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>I have another one. Saving one life is good. Saving two is better.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-16"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>You give away two kidneys, and you die.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-17"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>I could live on dialysis for years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-18"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Yes, and — and then you die.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-19"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>And then I could donate my other organs. Heart, lungs. I could save four or five more lives.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-20"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Foreman's gonna need a diagnostician. This guy is crazy.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Arrhythmia, muscle tremors, and, yes, mental changes. If his heart doesn't rupture, he's liable to rip it out and give it away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You know, the "down" vibe in here is totally ruining my Charlie's Angels fantasy.   And that haircut isn't helping, either.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>It seems like Graves disease or some other thyroid issue.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Is she on the team now? Like, forever?… His thyroid levels were within normal range when he was admitted.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Could be Coxsackie B virus.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Or pericarditis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>What about porphyria? It's a little weird without the rash, but it fits all of his other symptoms.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>And if it is acute intermittent porphyria, that would explain why his symptoms keep recurring.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's unlikely… but it's possible. What else?  I said what else?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh, for…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>There. That's better. Now, what else?  Well, if there's nothing better than possible, then possible gets upgraded to probable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-12"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I'll start him on hematin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-13"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>No, I'll go. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So what's the answer? Are you now on the team?  Like, forever?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-15"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>I don't know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>'Cause I was thinking of ordering T-shirts.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So… guilt?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-18"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Yes, you were right. You're always right. I just… I have the skills to help people. Is it okay for me to walk away from that because I… want to just have fun?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Obviously not.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>How's your patient?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>She died a few hours ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>No department. No money. And somehow, you managed to con her into hanging around.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I have a gift. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It was a con.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>The patient was faking?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, I was. I brought him in here under false pretenses. Just to get his money. I ordered a bunch of random tests to keep him here. One of them was a head CT, which uses… iodine contrast.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You think he's allergic to Iodine?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, again. Just don't interrupt me. Thirteen was right. This is a thyroid issue. He has Plummer's disease.  He has a nodule in his thyroid. It produces excess hormone. Not enough to test abnormal, just more than his brain is used to. Just enough to make him irrationally generous, make him vulnerable to overheating.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Then you pumped his body full of Iodine and kicked him into thyrotoxicosis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I said don't interrupt. But, yes, you're right. Take out the nodule, he'll be fine.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Two days, one surgery. I now accept that you’re all better. Where's my money?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>You made me sick.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You were already sick. I just made you much, much worse. Seriously… the money. You're not giving it to me, are you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>When you're facing death… some things come into focus. My wife…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You love your family. You want them back. Your altruism was always a symptom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>No, it wasn't. I'm still gonna—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Keep less? How much less? Just enough to spoil your kids?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>But they need it more than people with TB or children in Indonesia with no eyes? Diagnosticians with hearts of gold?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-10"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>I don't wanna give you money because you're an ass.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I was an ass last week.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-12"><speaker>Benjamin</speaker><content>I love my family. I want to be with them. That doesn't make me a bad person.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No. It makes you a healthy person. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>My mechanic called. He said the work's been paid for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>You mentioned your car was in the shop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>That's $4,500.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Smile and say thank you. Or I get you G.P.S.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>You win.  Thank you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Your car is getting fixed. You're right. She went for it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Good work. Need a lift tomorrow? 'Cause your car is still in the shop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I don't take charity. I'm just glad it's over.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Nothing is ever over. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Thirteen. Wait a minute.  You're fired.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Now what? House, I'm starving.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm not joking. You're fired. Don't come in tomorrow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>House…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I can work with people who've got nowhere else to go. People who got something to prove. People who just get off on weird cases. What I can't work with is someone who's here so she doesn't have to feel bad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>You're trying to save me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yes… I think that little of you and that much of me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content>Okay… Bye, House. </content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>