<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>
<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Note</speaker><content>Throughout this episode, House is wearing his  shirts tucked into his pants, and a bracelet on his right wrist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Guard</speaker><content>Get up, House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Must be some mistake. I specifically requested my wakeup startle three hours from now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Guard</speaker><content>Some VIP visitor. Dean of Medicine from your old hospital.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I've had dreams about this. I'm going to assume this is another one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Guard</speaker><content>Get up. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I can refuse to see any visitor I want. Tell the Dean that I don't want to see her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Guard</speaker><content>He said you'd say that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content> He?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What's the hiring policy over there? All ass based?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I can get you out of here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Not unless that file has a file in it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Judge's order for your immediate release.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I had eight months added to my sentence two months ago. The math is pretty basic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>We have a crisis. Which, is good news for you. You're out tonight on conditional parole. The condition being that you're employed by me, at PPTH.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, thanks. You think it's a good idea for me to go right back to my old life? For either of us?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Your patient, is two lungs, in a box.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-18"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>And it only has 12 hours left. No pulse, no body. No ability to answer questions. It's your perfect patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I did pay for the room for the whole week, but…</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Donor's an 18-year-old college kid back from Hofstra. Goes to a homecoming party with his buddies, hops on his motorcycle, ends up an organ donor. Asystole in the E.R. No pulse. No blood circulating. His heart, liver, kidneys were all toast. Surgeons had the recipient on the table when they realized the lungs had increased airway resistance. The team closed her up, put the lungs in suspended animation. Buys 24 hours to fix it, 12 of which have passed. We still have no clue what's wrong.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Nice painting. Blues and greens. Calming, but with a hint of nurturing. Totally offsets the stench of suffering and death. Where's my patient? We need to not talk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>ICU isolation room. The transplant team will meet you there with updates from the past two hours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Great.  Take this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>How about you drop it in your office?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I completely understand and, almost respect your desire to appear to be Dean of Medicine, given that your title is Dean of Medicine. On the other hand… Seriously?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Get this straight. You break the law, you go back to jail. Scam extra Vicodin, back to jail. Flout my authority, make the hospital look bad, back to jail. I own you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yes, massa.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>See, that, would be an example.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>When did Cuddy leave?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>She gave her notice the day after your incident. Took a job—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Don't need the details.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Ortho needed more space. You're this way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Where's my stuff?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>No idea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What about my team?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Pathetic. The first thing you said to me was you don't want your old environment. The fourth thing you said was, "where's my old environment?" It's been a year, Taub, Chase, Thirteen all moved on. The world does that sometimes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, it doesn't.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Here's your new office. And there's your new team.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-19"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Hi.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm not interested in another department's sloppy seconds.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I'm not sloppy seconds.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>3:00 a.m. If Foreman had called you in from home, you wouldn't have</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Yes, I was on call for neurology.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, if that were true, you'd be working right now and unavailable to help. Which means that you're hanging out in the hospital pretending to work. Which means you're not just a reject, you're a cowardly reject who was trying to hide her rejectedness from someone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I am not a reject.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Then go back to neurology.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I can't. I punched my attending.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Prison! Sorry, I thought I heard everyone else think that. I was in prison, you see. It was a long time ago, but still, you're curious. Never was raped, not raped-raped. Well, raped-raped, but not raped-raped-raped. Well, now that we've got that completely behind us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Is there cake? Any alveolar exudate?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well it's not ARDS. It's the autumn. Its tick borne disease season. Ehrlichiosis causing bronchialitis. You'll appreciate that I left the "idiots" subtextual.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Blood smear was clear, and we "idiots" treated with broad spectrum antibiotics.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Cocaine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Dead men don't pee. Tox screen tests for metabolites in the urine. Coke never got past the lungs. Also explains the motorcycle crash. Idiots.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Great idea. Unless you're wrong. And by you, I mean me. Then this treatment will burn holes in the lungs. I'd call you idiots again, but at this point I'm starting to doubt whether you understand what I mean by the word.  Kato, get Black Beauty and meet me out front.  We're gonna find the dead kid's stash.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Since an 18-year-old with organ donor on his license is not a cancer patient, I'm figuring the recipient is a lifetime member of the Wilson cares too much club.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Excellent deduction.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're the reason I'm out of the big house. Doesn't quite make up for never visiting—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Springing you was Foreman's idea. I wasn't convinced until Simpson failed three times.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-20"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It amounts to the same thing. You wanted me back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-21"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>See, I knew you'd over-interpret it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-22"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Strong, emotional reaction. I guess that's what a lifetime membership gets you. How’s your wrist?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-23"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Healed, thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-24"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I was wrong. I went to prison. I paid the price. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-25"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> You're a changed man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-26"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I said I was wrong. I didn't say I changed. I haven't. Neither have you—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-27"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Analyze it however you like. We’re not friends anymore. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>What can I do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Vanessa</speaker><content>My chest. Angina's back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Upping the nitro should knock it back down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Theresa</speaker><content>Sis and I were talking, trying to figure out how many hospital sleepovers we've had.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Vanessa</speaker><content>It definitely started with the great mastectomy of 2001. God, I miss my boobs. They were spectacular.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Theresa</speaker><content>Is there a chance of locating another donor?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>It's unlikely. Especially since, with the extent of the emphysema, she needs a double lung.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> How are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Vanessa</speaker><content>Better already. It's a good thing that worked. I was gonna make you bring me a bottle. Oh, lighten up, Sis. You know, the least you could do is laugh at a dying lady's jokes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Theresa</speaker><content>Your drinking wasn't funny then, and it's not funny now. Because, you're not dying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>The hospital brought in a consultant to work on the lungs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Theresa</speaker><content>Do you know him? Is he — is he good?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>He is an excellent doctor.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>We probably shouldn't be turning up unannounced like this. Their son just died.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Bright side — they're probably up weeping. Hey, we both assaulted our bosses. It's like we're twins.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I’d really rather not….</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Okay, I'll go first. My boss dumped me. And yours what? Called you his China doll? Joked about what a crappy deal you got for Manhattan? Assumed you have a huge penis? I have no idea what flavor you are, so I thought I’d just cover the spread.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>My mom's Filipino, Dad's Korean, and my boss grabbed my behind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Behind what? Oh, yeah, your — grabbed your tushy. So now you're pretending to be on call so that your overly protective boyfriend won't find out that you got groped.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I don't have a boyfriend. It's my parents. If they found out what I've done, they'd be mortified.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Your parents know your call schedule?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I live with them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Right. No issues there.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Druggies are not known for their honesty. Trust me on this one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Mr. Weathers, I am sure you're right, but we need to be thorough. Did your son ever smoke marijuana?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Sorry. But we're on a clock.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content> I think he's about to throw us out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Nope. His son is dead. The only way that has any meaning is if we fix the lungs and transplant them. It doesn’t matter how much we piss him off as long as we find something. So go back there, piss him off and find something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Do you know any of the kids at the party with your son?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Park</speaker><content> I understand that we're in a hurry but maybe he should.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Your son isn't wearing glasses in any of these pictures.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Because he was having headaches?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Answer the question before answering the door.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You’re right. He was not doing cocaine. He had a brain tumor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Don't bother. It's for me.  Turns out they monitor these monitors.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content> Thank you, officer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I thought the bracelet was decorative. My aunt had one just like it. Wait a minute.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You're allowed to be at the hospital. You're allowed to go home. That was made clear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Dead kid's house was on the way to my apartment.  Assuming I got lost, twice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Those consultants in my office are only costing the hospital 100 bucks every minute I keep them waiting. Why didn't you just tell me what you were doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I knew you were very busy, being vaguely important.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I might have cleared it with the cops.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, it's the word "might" that bumps me, but I’ll run it by you next time. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Getting you out of jail was not a popular decision with the board. I need you to solve this, and I need you to do it without making me look like I can't control you. For both our sakes. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Disciplinary hearing should be fun, and the subsequent lingering black mark on your record.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I’m not worried.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>We have to wheel this out to the MRI. We should probably leave the body in the bag.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content> There's a mass in the arm. Analyzing part of this tumor is gonna be quicker than a scan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So, where’s the next job? You worry about what people think of you, and parental secrets. The only way that you don't worry about this hearing is if you don't think there's gonna be one. The only way that happens is you leave Princeton Plainsboro.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I had a video interview with Chicago yesterday. It went well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>My money's on rhabdomyosarcoma.  Chicago has a great program, and you're a dumbass.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Running away from home is a time-honored tradition, but you're not doing it to flee your parents. You're doing it to protect them.  That's an insult to everything teen prostitutes have worked for. Time to grow up and come clean.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>You're right. I should just drive my car into their living room and tell them</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Theresa</speaker><content>Didn't it turn out that he'd stolen the hot dog cart?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Vanessa</speaker><content>No, borrowed. Bobby was very insistent on that point.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Seems like someone's feeling better.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Vanessa</speaker><content>No more chest pain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I haven't heard the name Bobby in a long time. How's he doing these days?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Vanessa</speaker><content>I don't know. We're not in touch. And don't even pretend like you're not relieved. You never liked him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Bobby is an incredibly fun, great guy. Just not a great influence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Theresa</speaker><content>I would have gone with "colossal drunk."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I was gonna leave that implied, but, yes, colossal drunk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Vanessa</speaker><content>What? It's good for a couple to share a hobby.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> Your catheter bag is empty, despite taking in 200 ccs of fluids. I'm gonna have to dial back the nitro.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Theresa</speaker><content>Won't her chest pain come back?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>We don't have any choice. The nitro is dropping the blood flow to your kidneys. They're shutting down.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>This is so our song.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>My patient is running out of time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Not worried. My team is confirming the diagnosis as we speak.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> I want to be understanding. It's your first day back—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>See? I smell empathy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You should remember all the good times. Like when I gave you that necklace that you just dumped n the ocean. What were you thinking?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> House, I haven't forgotten our friendship. For every good memory, there's a slew of bad ones.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Come in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Come in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Paraneoplastic syndrome's out. The lung donor didn't have cancer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Tell that to the tumor that I found in his arm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>That mass wasn't a tumor. It was coagulated plasma. E.R. pumped him full of it. I.V. leaked into his arm. I even did a complete MRI. No cancer anywhere. We've got nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Just 'cause it wasn't a tumor doesn't mean it didn't mess with the lungs. They're reacting to something in the plasma.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>But every unit of plasma can have up to 25 contributing donors. We need to track down all of them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Still.  It's not as bad as a thousand people going down in a gigantic boat, right? My heart will go on. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>No. You can't leave the hospital.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>25 donors contributed to the plasma that the lung donor got. My team cannot track down and interview them all in six hours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I vouch for you to the cops, you take some parole-violating detour celebrating your freedom, justified, of course, by some absurd theory connecting it to the case.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You asked me to ask you. Was that just so you'd enjoy saying no?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I don't trust you, House. I can't.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Actually you have to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Not absolutely. Not outside the walls of this hospital.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Fine, then give me a team I don't have to put in quotation marks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Use the people already on the case.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Give me Chase, Taub, Thirteen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>We don't have the money to pay them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh, yeah.  It went to interior designers, I understand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You only have Park because she's on neurology's tab. You are making minimum wage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I am?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Get out of my office, please. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What do you got?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Number three went to a baseball game the day before he donated.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Boredom is not transmissible.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>He ate a bag of peanuts, and peanut proteins would be. If our donor had an allergy, it could explain the lungs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Nice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Don't start that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Start what? I'm enjoying our conversation. The repartee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>There was no repartee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That was repartee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-12"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'm not doing this for you. I'm doing it to help my patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's just good to hear your voice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-14"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> Goodbye.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That's my whiteboard. I need it. And he really doesn't care how the cast comes off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-16"><speaker>Betty</speaker><content> Dr. Foreman warned us that you'd try something. Told me to call him if you did. I'd like to do that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'll take this outside.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-19"><speaker>Park</speaker><content> Donor six traveled to Thailand around Khorat. Region was endemic with dengue fever.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-20"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Good.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Alcohol.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He’d have to be pretty drunk for it to affect a pool of plasma.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>These guys have got that covered. Acute etoh ingestion could have— hey, paint around them, they’re not hurting anyone]</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Who's painting?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>The crew's just starting. Paint fumes didn't cause contamination. But, maybe the old paint did. They scraped off the underpass, probably because it contains… lead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Lead.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Chest pain back?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>Vanessa</speaker><content>It’s worse this time. Is there any way to take the edge off?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>We're still working on the lungs. We should know soon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>Vanessa</speaker><content>Soon is good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> How's the chelation going?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Reverend Moon started it about 20 minutes ago. You missed lunch tracking down the plasma donors. Got you a Reuben from the cafeteria.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Thanks.  Lead exposure's a nice diagnosis. I hope it pays off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It will.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I appreciate your confidence, but she's not really—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh, no, she could die. But technically it will still pay off. Even if your patient dies, someone will get the lungs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-11"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You really haven't changed. But I've given up red meat.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>What round of chelation is this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Fourth. Are you checking up on me, or on House?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>On this case. Unique situation. Oxygenating?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>98%. Airway resistance down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Great. Is House okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I have no idea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Dad, what are you doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>What text?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I'm consulting on this case. Unique situation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-10"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Lungs are crashing. I have to go. Bye.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-11"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Increasing to 100% FiO2.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-12"><speaker>Park</speaker><content> Saline flow is down to 10 ccs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-13"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Blockage? Clot in the line?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-14"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Chelation is making it worse. It means we were wrong about lead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-15"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Hold the analysis and help me save this thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-16"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Saline's flushing it forward but getting no return. One-way valve. Vasospasm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-17"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>If you're right, calcium channel blocker should relax the artery.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-18"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>The lungs have no nervous system. Will that still work?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-19"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content> We'll know soon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-20"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Saline flow is rising. Vasospasm’s relaxing. Left lung is pinking up. Good job.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-21"><speaker>Park</speaker><content> Right middle lobe isn't.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-22"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-23"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>We killed part of the lung.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Page Dr. Pinto stat to the cath lab.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>We're going to the cath lab? Are you thinking that maybe—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What? Who? One dead lobe means four alive ones. It means enough to transplant with a side order of dead tissue that we can test.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>It makes sense. Unlike you stealing my phone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You have unlimited texting. Until your parents know, you will never see that punch for what it really was. Your February 4th. Sri Lankan Independence Day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I told you I'm Korean and Filipino.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And I told you I wasn't listening. By my actions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Violence isn't an appropriate way to handle conflict. It was a moment of weakness.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You barked at me, picked a fight with a painting crew. Maybe it's time to recognize it's not a character flaw. Maybe it's your character.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Pinto!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Embrace your inner bitch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So why did chelation make the lungs worse?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>We got about five minutes till Pinto gets back. Give me a hand with this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-14"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-15"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I tracked down another bag of plasma from the batch they used on the donor. Negative for all our other exposures.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Sarcoidosis could be inflamed by the treatment.  I am a cripple, in need of assistance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-17"><speaker>Park</speaker><content> Um, transplant team ran an A.C.E. Negative.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's mine. And it's your job.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-19"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>My job is to assist you in curing the lungs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-20"><speaker>House</speaker><content>This chair will help me do that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-21"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>What if the scrapings from the bridge contained other heavy metals like barilium or asbestos?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-22"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Chelation for lead wouldn't have made them worse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-23"><speaker>House</speaker><content>But… maybe the problem isn't a heavy metal from outside. It's inside. But it's not leaving the body like it's supposed to. It's stuck. Iron. The donor had hemosiderosis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-24"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>His body wasn't disposing of iron. Massive amounts choke up the lungs. Then our chelation would wreak havoc because it picks up too much stuff.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-25"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Go stain the dead lung tissue for iron.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-26"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm sorry, young lady, I simply will not help you steal this chair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-27"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Pinto.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-28"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Hi.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>Theresa</speaker><content>She can barely catch her breath.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>Vanessa</speaker><content>Lungs ready yet?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>We're testing for iron overload.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>Theresa</speaker><content>I thought it was lead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>This is not an exact process.  Your small airways are collapsing. You're not getting enough oxygen. I'd like to try forcing an oxygen-rich slurry into your lungs. It should open up the airways and buy you some time until the lungs are ready.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>Vanessa</speaker><content>Fluid? In my lungs? Sounds like drow…drowning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>It is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>Vanessa</speaker><content>Gonna hurt, isn't it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Yes, a fair amount.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>Vanessa</speaker><content>No. I'm done.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> House, the nurses saw you come in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Enter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>It's a bathroom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Ah, explains the hole in this chair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>God, I missed doors. And air freshener.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Now go away. I'm waiting for some test results.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>My patient signed a DNR. She's giving up. Looks like someone else will be getting the lungs. Making this yet another interaction with you in which I get nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's not my fault you can't handle your patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>She said she's done. I spent half an hour trying to change her mind, but she'd made her decision. I accepted that. It's called respect.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And what's after respect? You find another angle. You hold her hand, get the sister to beg,  stick your fingers in your ears, pretend you can't hear. You do whatever it takes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-11"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Oh, whatever it takes. Thanks, House. I hadn't thought of that.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>What are you testing for?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Hemosiderosis. I'm staining for excess iron.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Promising. When your dad showed up unexpectedly, House have a hand in that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I'm guessing he does things like that a lot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>His version of a compliment.  I spoke to the head of neurology in Chicago. I gave you a good recommendation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Did you mention what happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Lawyers say I'm not allowed to. It works out well for everyone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>Park</speaker><content> Why exactly is that good for you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Excuse me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I'm a talented physician, top 2% of my class. I'm an asset to this hospital, an asset you're about to lose to Chicago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You applied for the job. You asked me to call and recommend you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-12"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Andrews is the one that should leave. He's the supervisor. He touched me first.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-13"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I can't discuss any of that, not before the hearing. But if you're having doubts about Chicago, I can call them back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-14"><speaker>Park</speaker><content> No. Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-15"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Dr. Foreman? Would you look at this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-16"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Iron?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-17"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>No. White blood cells.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-18"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content> Classic presentation of infection.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-19"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>How the hell did we miss that?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Biopsy revealed, white blood cell inflitrates.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Infection was right, after all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Fresh fruit in prison is usually chicken.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Why aren't you more alarmed? We're running out of time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Aahh, she's dying!  Were you able to figure out what was wrong while I was screaming?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Infection was the first thing that the transplant team treated for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Which would have worked if the bacteria had been out in the open. If they're hiding inside the lung cells… I'm thinking brucella. And to wipe that out, you need special ops.  An intact immune system.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>Park</speaker><content> But that's what white blood cells are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>They're part of the immune defense force, like the infantry. But those lungs need the Air Force and the Marines, antibodies raining down from above. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Antibiotics and IVIG.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-11"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Did you use metaphors for your old team? Or do you just think I'm particularly stupid?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, they were stupid too.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>Theresa</speaker><content> What are you doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>Bobby</speaker><content>I'm here for Vanessa.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>Theresa</speaker><content>Now is not the time, Bobby.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>Bobby</speaker><content>She asked me to come. Right, Doc?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> Actually, it was my idea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>Theresa</speaker><content>What? What were you thinking? She doesn't want to see him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>When Vanessa was ready to quit chemo, Bobby's the one who got her to do one more round.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>Theresa</speaker><content>Yeah, and then he got her drunk.  At least tell me you haven't been drinking today.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>Bobby</speaker><content>I should go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>Vanessa</speaker><content> Hail, hail, the gang's all here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>Bobby</speaker><content> Hey beautiful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-12"><speaker>Vanessa</speaker><content>Hi.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Case is under control. It's me time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Vanessa's gonna do the lung slurry.  You were right to push me. I needed that. Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So we're good?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>It was good advice. Just, came here to say thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I like you.  I have fun with you.  And, if you can honestly say that you don't like me, you don't have fun with me, I can accept that. But, just do whatever you have to do to get over this. You can punch me in the face, kick me in the nuts. Either/or. Both seems excessive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>The thing is, House… I don't like you. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>When did the discoloration start?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>A few minutes after I started the IVIG.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Means we're wrong about infection.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Wrong about autoimmune, not cancer, heavy metals, genetic issues… Increase peep.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I need… I need ideas.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>IgA nephropathy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That's already ruled out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content> No--o.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Maybe we're just out of time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>We're out of time when we're out of time. When they die or she dies. Keep them stable as long as you can. I need to think. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>One, two… three…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>Everyone</speaker><content>Make a wish. Make a wish.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The lungs are a smoker.  You of all people should know better.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>But the kid never smoked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He played poker. Who plays poker without cigars? Even if he didn't light up himself… It was a rainy night. The windows were closed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>All parents think their kids are special. And these ones were right. At least his white blood cells were special. They had an on switch for reacting to smoke, but no off. When he inhaled small amounts of smoke, he had small problems. No one even noticed. Big amounts of smoke, that's enough to trash a lung. As soon as he breathed in all that cigar smoke, he was a dead man. The motorcycle accident was an unnecessary dramatic flourish.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Eosiniphilic pneumonitis. But, the steroids would have treated for that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I was right. Not about anything medical, but my metaphors were perfect. We need to hit it harder. We need to carpet bomb, blitzkrieg. We need the nuclear option.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>At some point you're going to say we need to radiate, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>See, the metaphors work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>But that'll destroy the good lung too. Better to go with a strong cocktail of immunosuppressants.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Won't be fast enough. Wilson needs these lungs.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>It's working.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content> He did it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I'm not going to Chicago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>If you stay, we have to have a hearing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Dad… Do you have a minute?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>Surgeon</speaker><content>Thoracic cavity clear. Ready for the donor lungs.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>Theresa</speaker><content>Thank God you called him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>Theresa</speaker><content>I wonder what happens now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>She can handle it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content> House!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Got something for you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I found your stuff in storage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>This is all you get. Ortho still has the outer office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, that sucks. Where are Chase, Taub, and Thirteen gonna sit?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You're welcome, House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oof!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> Ah!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Dinner later? I’ll pick something up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content> I heard about a good new vegetarian place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Screw that. I want a steak.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'll meet you at your place at 8:00. </content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>