<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>
<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Airport loudspeaker</speaker><content> Attention, passengers…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Joni</speaker><content> You have to lift up the sign so he can see it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Joni</speaker><content>Evan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>Hey, buddy. Aren't you excited to see your Uncle Brant?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Evan</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>No? I think you are. I think something else is making you upset. You know I'm leaving soon, and it's okay to be upset about that, but, hey, do you remember what I told you when we were watching wrestling on Saturday night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Evan</speaker><content>Yeah. That you and Uncle Brant are like the Reaper Brothers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>That's right. And Uncle Brant has been in the ring a whole year. Now it's time for daddy to tag in. But while I'm away, I need you in your Uncle's corner, making sure he keeps you and your mom safe. Can you help me with that?  Good. Now let's get ready with that sign.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Airport loudspeaker</speaker><content> Attention, ladies and gentlemen, we are now boarding at Gate 47.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content> Now. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>Brant, what happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>MP</speaker><content>Captain please step aside.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>Sir, this is my brother. What's going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>MP</speaker><content>Pfc Macklin has been charged with treason.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>Oh, so there's got to be some mistake.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>I'm sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>Brant! Brant! Brant!</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Army apparently thought they were clearing an insurgent hideout. After this was leaked on Saturday, the A.P. investigated.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>34 civilian casualties. Six kids.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>There will be MPs stationed at every entrance to the second floor, as well as outside his patient room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No. Don't do that. Every time there's people in uniform in the cafeteria, they get served first.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Make sure your IDs are clearly visible. I'll speak with the cafeteria staff about showing more disrespect. 20 year-old male, generalized tonic-clonic seizures. Army Docs scanned for structural abnormalities. EEG was normal. So was—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Do you need me to sign for this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Let me know if you need anything. Like a transfer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Typhus?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Patient has no hair. Probably means no lice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Leishmaniasis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>No fever. Why couldn't they take care of him at a military hospital?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I think because they wanted to annoy you. Any other conscientious objectors?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>So, I'm the only one who has a problem when someone whose duty's to protect our country blowing—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Blowing the whistle is honorable precisely because it's not dutiful. Sorry, you said blowing. Maybe you were going somewhere else with that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>He's a coward.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>He risked his freedom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>He anonymously downloaded a computer file from a secure page and uploaded it to an unsecure page. Not exactly storming Omaha Beach. The EEG was normal because he was faking it to avoid going to prison.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Let's treat him with not medicine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content> Give those back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Why? You got 28. You can share.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Something's going on with House. He just seemed off. Didn't even notice that I walked out of the room with this. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You began to suspect he was off when he didn't notice the mug you stole to see if he was off? What else didn't he notice that you don't want us to notice?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content> Those are the same clothes you wore yesterday.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>And you got very defensive when House took your birth control.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Who was he? Or better yet… she?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Do I need to explain the physiology behind birth control? Attention deficit in a man who has no attention deficits has to be symptomatic of something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You're right. I'm thinking either massive brain tumor, or his soap got canceled and he's distracted.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Could be dietary. Refsum.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Or maybe he thinks you just have more than one non-descript white blouse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Or serotonin syndrome. I'm not saying he's definitely sick. I'm just saying we should look into it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>No, we shouldn't. If you believe House is sick, it's only because that's what he wants you to believe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Park</speaker><content> Let's go.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content> We think the long flight home allowed clots to form in your leg.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Take this pill.  If you feel any numbness in your leg after a few minutes, it means we're right and you should get comfortable, because you're gonna be here for a while.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content> While we wait, can you tell me why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>It was the right thing to do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>There are reports that insurgents are using your video to recruit new members.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>Making the voting public aware of what's really happening on the ground will help bring our troops home faster.  My brother's grunt means he disagrees.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>I think you're being naive. And I know you took an oath. If you want to influence policy, run for office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>Dad raised us to believe that exposing the truth is honorable. Hayes likes to follow the rules.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>Yeah, because that's what Dad taught us was honorable. You were ten when he died. You couldn't possibly have any idea—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>if Dad always believed in blindly following the rules, how do you explain Tora Bora?  My dad was commanding a Special Forces unit. He lost communication with his men. They were assumed dead. He was ordered to abandon them and focus on the primary mission. He disobeyed that order, went and found his men still alive, and fighting. He saved their lives.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Did he die in service? If it was something genetic, it could help us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>It won't help. It was a one-car accident.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>That's the army's official story. My brother's naïve on this and… I can't feel my leg.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I'll get the discharge papers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>I have a blood clot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>No, you don't. We gave you a placebo to see if you'd fake another symptom to delay going to prison.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>Wait a second. He's not faking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Because that's not the way your Dad raised him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-20"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>My stomach hurts too. What's going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-21"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>He's not faking.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Just because he's got abdominal bruising doesn't mean he wasn't faking the numbness.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>He's not contesting the treason charges. If his code of honor is that strong, he's not gonna bother faking symptoms.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Pleading guilty is not honorable. It's just stupid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>A distal esophageal rupture can lead to compartment syndrome in his thigh — explains both symptoms.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>No pain when he swallows.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What is honor? Dying for your country? Getting straight As? Killing your daughter because she had the audacity to get raped?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Ruptured triple-A.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Doesn't explain the seizures.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Pancreatitis. Gallstones obstructing his pancreatic duct.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content> People define honor as whatever makes them feel honorable. It's a circle going nowhere. Which I guess is what circles do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>We'll ultrasound his belly and look for the obstruction.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content> I need your signature on this order. The Army's leaning on Foreman to make sure this is done by the book.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Didn't need an order for his last treatment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>This last treatment wasn't a treatment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Forge it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I will. From now on. But I need the original so I know what to forge.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Gloria</speaker><content>We were having coffee when the dizziness started.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Business meeting?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Mel</speaker><content>Date. Our first. We met at the 98 Cent store.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Gloria</speaker><content>We were reaching for the same tube of cheese.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Huh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I'm sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I need to talk to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Just about done.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Good news, based on her thrifty shopping habits and taste for artificial dairy she's clearly not a gold digger. Bad news, based on his rhinotillexomania, he is. Compulsive addiction to nose-picking. A small cut on the inside of the left nostril led to an infection in the cavernous sinus.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Gloria</speaker><content>It was very nice meeting you, Mel. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Mel</speaker><content>It's not true. Gloria, wait, I can change.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content> My PPTH contract. House signed it six months ago. He signed this today. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>His hands are unsteady. Given his Vicodin abuse, I think he has hepatic encephalopathy. He's been forgetful, inattentive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Dominika's been trying out new knish recipes. One of them didn't agree with him. A little sleep deprivation could account for his forgetfulness and inattention. He loads up on caffeine. That explains a jittery hand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Maybe. But if I'm right, his liver's in decline. It's curable, but if he doesn't get treatment, it could actually be fatal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>This happens all the time. One of the symptoms of working for House — you start seeing zebras everywhere. There's nothing wrong with him.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Shh. I'm with a patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Sleep study.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> You drugged him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content> I didn't say the study was voluntary.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> I think you're sick.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What, 'cause I'm sleeping in the clinic like I always do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Slow reaction time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Because I just woke up from sleeping in the clinic like I always do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You're forgetful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Sorry. What did you say?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You forgot that we were supposed to have lunch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I didn't forget. I was sleeping, in the clinic—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'd like to run some tests.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>For what? Where's this coming from?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Hepatic encephalopathy. I've watched you destroy your body with Vicodin for years. I'm surprised your liver's lasted this long. I'll do the examination myself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>While having you juggle my jewels sounds interesting, there's no such thing as friends with benefits. It always gets weird.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Your friends out there are getting a little handsy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>Get enough death threats, eventually they start taking them seriously.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>A convoy was hit outside of Kunar Province. Eight American soldiers were killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>Army spokesperson's claiming that it's revenge for the attack that I made public. Better me take the blame than them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>You don't think you're to blame at all?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>And you do. Like everyone else. A strike like that would take more than three days to plan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>So the next one might be your fault?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Lateral view looks good. If you have such a negative opinion of the army, why did you enlist?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>I needed to find out what really happened to my dad. There were two redacted pages in his service record. Going into intelligence was the quickest way to up my security clearance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Then why would you leak that video?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>Part of my job was to grab a cup of tea with the locals. The face time is supposed to make them more likely to trust us with sensitive information, but they became my friends. If there was another attack, civilian casualties, and I had done nothing…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Your spleen, it's enlarged. We should do a biopsy and look for any—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content> He's got urinary bleeding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Park</speaker><content> Not just urinary.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Call the blood bank.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>What's happening to him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>His spleen must be sequestering platelets.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>He's bleeding too fast to wait for a platelet infusion.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We need to squeeze his spleen to release the ones he's got. Tell the O.R. we're on our way.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Pressure's dropping.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Almost there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>BP's 70 over 40, and he's hypovolemic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Pressure's rising.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>And he's starting to clot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Good news is we can control the bleeding. Bad news is… Bleeding's not the problem. Unless spleens are supposed to be lumpy.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>He's clotting, but CT confirms splenic nodules.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>No, I don't.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're forfeiting? 'Cause if you can't play the game and work…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Extramedullary hematopoiesis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>No history of anemia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>She's right. You're an idiot. Try again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Where I come from, this is called cheating.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Where's that? Stickford-upon-anus?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>TB.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>PPD's negative. Could be bru—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Don't interrupt Dr. Taub.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Brucellosis.  You just took out a family of four.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>They were clearly armed insurgents, and anyone who claims or proves otherwise is a traitor. No rash or back pain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>You defend the patient for being a whistleblower, then attack him for being an honorable whistleblower. Now you defend him for being a maligned, honorable whistleblower?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Adjectives matter. Hate nurses, love naughty nurses. Taub, pitch again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I've pitched like five—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's your turn.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-18"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Lymphoma.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-19"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>If cancer caused his seizures, we would have seen cerebral masses on his head CT.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-20"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> Yes!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Taub, pitch again. Now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-22"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> The nodules in his spleen were granulomas. He's got sarcoidosis!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-23"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Someone tell him he's wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-24"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Sorry, House. Sarcoid does explain the seizures.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-25"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>And the bruises.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-26"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> Say bye-bye, House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-27"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> Yes! Yes!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-28"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Sarcoidosis it is. Treat with steroids. Then come right back here, 'cause I'm not gonna rest until I've made orphans of all your virtual children.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>House never loses.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Seriously? Me beating House is medically significant?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>It could be. Reduced fine motor control. Add that to inattention and liver flap. It does make sense.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>We have to talk to Foreman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>No, we don't. First of all, because I can beat him in that game. And, second, even if you are right, there's no reason to believe that House's medical judgment is impaired.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>So we should wait until he kills someone for confirmation?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You really think it's a coincidence that we're treating a whistleblower and now talking about blowing the whistle on House? You're right. Playing dumb, messy signature, losing a video game — it's way too complicated to fake.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>No. I won't take it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Without this injection, you could have a fatal arrhythmia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>Tell Major Mathewson that I'm not taking any more treatment until they give me a live television interview.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>You can't really think they'll agree to that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>People need to know the tape's not the reason for that attack. They need to know why I did this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>The people who think you're a traitor will still think you're a traitor, and the people who think you're a hero will still think you're a hero.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>The truth makes a difference.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>If Dad were here, he'd be begging for you not to do this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>If Dad were here, he'd be proud of me.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>The conspiracy theorists are gonna go nuts if the patient dies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I told him that, and he told me that option is still less damaging than giving the kid a national platform.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>So what do we do now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You explain to your brother that he overplayed his hand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>That won't make any difference. The idiot thinks he's doing the right thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>What if we convinced a court that his refusal is part of an underlying psychiatric disorder? They assign a conservator. We do what we want.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Fraud. Great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Narcissistic personality disorder. Both the leaking of the tape and the refusal of treatment indicate that he has no fear of consequences.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>So instead of defrauding the court, you'll waste their time? No way a judge classifies a personality disorder as a mental illness.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>If a decorated military officer, who happened to be the patient's brother, corroborates, they might.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>So you want me to sign a piece of paper that says my brother is crazy for doing what he thinks is right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-12"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I want you to save his life. His heart could go at any time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-13"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>He's a fool, but he's not crazy.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>The patient was refusing treatment because of honor, and his brother is refusing to be his conservator because of honor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh, good. Taub's cured the patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I had to go to the bathroom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Bathroom's that way. You just ran in from that way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>That one's been out of order for two days. I had to go up to the third floor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I'm not lying. It's out of order.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I believe you. I'm gonna fix it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We could treat if he doesn't know he's being treated. Lace his sponge bath?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>It would take too long to reach his bloodstream.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>What if we aerosolize steroids and blast the room?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Speaking of which…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It'd be too hard to get the prednisone concentrations right. No one fixes anything unless they have a compelling reason.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If we're gonna treat, we have to give him a compelling reason, something that he wants more than an interview.  Fire in the hole!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>A signed order from Major Mathewson. They've agreed to declassify the redacted pages from your father's service record. In two days, you'll have all your answers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>But the only way you'll live long enough to get the truth is by accepting treatment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>I don't trust the Army to follow through on this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>But you trust me. I'll make sure those pages get here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content> Okay. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Selfishness is apparently honorable now. He wanted to create change. Instead, he's just satisfying his own curiosity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>He's getting the truth. Most he could hope for. I need to take a dump. Specifically, House's dump.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>You set this up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>All it took was showing up two minutes late and a $2.00 sign.  Bile deposits are irregular. House's liver is failing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Cognitive impairment will get progressively worse.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>What's going on?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>My foot. It's killing me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>It's completely cyanotic. This isn't sarcoidosis.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Cholesterol embolization.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Are you even gonna acknowledge what we just told you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That you pilfered my poo-poo? Yeah, I was thinking, it would be less awkward for all of us if we could just pretend that never happened.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>It's not an embolization. No instrumentation inside the arteries.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Thank you for getting us back—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>And if we start you on treatment now, get you off Vicodin—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What's the opposite of "thank you"? I'm pretty sure it ends in "you". I know my body. I'm fine. Methemoglobinemia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Army tests for GPD deficiency.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>If you're not sick, then our test, accurate 99.5% of the time, yielded a false positive, three separate times. The odds of that are in 1 in 8 million.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The test is accurate. The diagnosis isn't. Sample was obviously contaminated with other foods interacting with my liver enzymes. Now could we talk about the sick patient?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-11"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>His clot dissolved. That could have caused the vasospasm. D.I.C. could have been caused by Bernard Soulier syndrome. And, you're sick, and, you have to do something about it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-12"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>If we had a patient file with the same symptoms you're exhibiting…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And the symptoms I'm not exhibiting? Jaundice, ascites, fetor hepaticus.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-14"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>We can't tell if your breath stinks because you've been popping mints like they're Vicodin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-15"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You'd still diagnose hepatic encephalopathy. I know that because four doctors you trained have unanimously diagnosed you with hepatic encephalopathy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Park's right. Treat the patient with Heparin.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>We'll have a stronger argument if we go to Foreman as a united front.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We'll have a stronger argument if we have an argument. If House is sick, it's his business, not Foreman's.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Foreman's business is to make sure his doctors are able to do their jobs, that lives aren't put at risk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Telling Foreman will put lives at risk. We tell Foreman, House either agrees to treatment or get suspended, which means House gets suspended. And considering House at 90% is better than any other doctor at this hospital at 100%, that means our patients get a lower standard of care.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>House could be at 90%, he could be at 60%, we don't know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>And until we do, there's no reason to do anything more than what we've done.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Blurry vision… headache, a bit of nausea, and dizziness. I am com-pletely baffled.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>College Kid</speaker><content>I only had eight beers. Sophomore class pong tournament's in a week. I'm working on my tolerance.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Hop on one foot and sing the iCarly theme song. Like you don't know it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Damn it, man. Can't you see I'm doctoring?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If you want to talk to me, you can buy me a sandwich in an hour.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Or I could just hover here until you're done.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Heard enough. Just never could figure out the "breathe air" part. Next year, stick to whiskey. Or at least stay away from week-old green beers. A lot less likely to contain tartrazine-laced green food dyes for which you apparently have an intolerance. Once you break the seal, it'll be out of your system in 48 hours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What are my choices here? If I tell you I'm fine, you won't believe me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I've scheduled a liver function test.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If I ignore you, then you'll just ignore my ignoring. Which is rude, frankly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-11"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Depending on the results, we'll customize a treatment plan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If I tell you I think I'm sick and I need your help and we need to set up a time to talk about it, you'll just assume I'm lying. Again, rude. Also hurtful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-13"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Why is it that you can find the smallest thing wrong with anyone else, but when it comes to you…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I really don't have a choice here, do I?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-15"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>No, you don't.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content> I'm on the list.  But he's not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-17"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You can't ignore me forever.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, if you're right, that's not gonna be all that long.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Do it slow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-20"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>Who are you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, considering the only people allowed in this room are your doctors and your family… I'm your long-lost cousin Ralph. So glad to finally meet you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-22"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>Are you gonna check on me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-23"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's gonna be at least two hours until we can tell if the Heparin's working.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-24"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>Then what are you doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-25"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You know, my father taught me that it's dishonorable to interrupt someone when they're reading.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-26"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>Honor's not a punch line. Get out of my room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-27"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So was it worth it?  Best case, you spend the rest of your life in Leavenworth. Worst case, you spend the rest of your life here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-28"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>Justice for 34 deaths outweighs anything the Army can do to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-29"><speaker>House</speaker><content>They got justice? Do they know that? What if only ten people had died? Four?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-30"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>Even one civilian death…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-31"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What if they just maimed a few guys? Would that have been worth it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-32"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>My job was to log that tape, get all the details in the official record. After the tenth time of watching it, I stopped trying to convince myself that the shovel could have been mistaken for a gun. 'Cause all I could see were the victims' faces. All I was doing was trying to read that kid's lips to make out his last words. I couldn't sleep. Couldn't eat. Think I like the cue ball look? My hair turned gray in three days. My body was telling me I had to do whatever I could to make sure that something like this never happened again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-33"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Your hair turned gray in three days.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Loss of hair color indicates an autoimmune condition, likely Grave's disease. Hyperthyroidism leads to a hypercoagulable state, which causes thrombosis. Start him on antithyroids.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>You want to reject our current diagnosis because he had a few gray hairs, panicked, and shaved his head?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I want to reject our current diagnosis because I think we're wrong. And treating for wrong diagnoses can result in side effects like death.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Even if he did full go gray, stress seems way more likely than Grave's.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I haven't read any journal articles proving that veterans have a higher incidence of depigmentation. Of course, that could be the hepatic encephalopathy talking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Our treatment for Bernard Soulier hasn't had time—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So you all just want to ignore the new symptom?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>It's not Grave's because it's not a symptom at all. And the antithyroids you want could reduce his blood pressure and his ability to breathe. Which can result in side effects, like death.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Small soda. Grave's it is. Start him on antithyroids.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I know we disagree with House all the time, but, before, I could say, "okay, he's a genius." Now… maybe he's just really smart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We're not gonna give him the antithyroids.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Feeling okay? Any better?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>Pretty good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>He did just ask me for a blanket.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>You're cold?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>A little.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>For how long?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>It's really nothing. Maybe an hour or two.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>He's at 104.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>It's not Bernard Soulier.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Bold move. You've gone from speculating I'm sick, to acting like I'm dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>We acted like we don't trust your judgment, because we don't trust your judgment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Why don't you start by not trusting your own.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>We did more blood work, it's not Graves either.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content> Talk to you for a minute?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Anything you have to say to me, you can say to them. It's only fair. Cause</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Until you receive a clean bill of health, I'll be authorizing all treatment orders.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, I would say that that was an incredibly stupid mistake but apparently I'd have to clear that opinion through Foreman first.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>White count is high. So all the infections we ruled out when he came in are back on the table.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-10"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Legionnaire's.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-11"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Unlikely without pneumonia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Taub. Loyalty issues in his personal life. Makes sense that they'd cross over into his professional one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-13"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I was hoping we can get a diagnosis before the witch hunt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The patient's infection is an inherently less interesting puzzle than the stab wound to my back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-15"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Fine. I told Foreman. Can we move on now? What about dengue?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-16"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Patient isn't in enough pain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No. I don't mean about dengue. I have no idea. Taub's only confessing because he wants us to focus on the patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-18"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I told Foreman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-19"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-20"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The next person to confess is fired. Or Spartacus.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-21"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>For clarification, no one's getting fired. Who else has a pitch?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-22"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And then… there's Park. The only one who didn't confess. The same cowardice that makes someone unable to move out of mommy and daddy's home might also make someone a tattletale.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-23"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>You threatened to fire the next person who—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-24"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And it's malaria.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-25"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>No, it's not. The Army issues anti-malaria medication.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-26"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And has done for ten years. That's the equivalent of 5000 generations of the Afghan mosquito, anopheles gambiae. That's plenty long enough to develop a resistance. Anopheles, by the way, is Greek for "useless."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-27"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Cover for intra-abdominal sepsis and treat with antimalarials.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-28"><speaker>House</speaker><content> And was I also right that it was a stupid idea?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>We believe you have malaria. These pills—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>I don't want any medication. My dad's file should have been here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>Brant, I told you, I looked into it. There's just a delay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>I believe that's what the Army's saying. I don't believe it's true. If they're not going to keep their end of the bargain, neither am I.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>So we got groped for nothing. If he doesn't want to stay alive—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>Hold on. Is it too late to become his conservator? I know what I said before. Right now I don't care.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Of course not. We'll get the paperwork drawn up.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>He changed his mind? Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> His brother's dying. He needs a more substantial reason?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>His brother was dying the last time we asked him to be the conservator. So instead of pushing the issue with the Army to get the file, he just decided to give up on his code?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Apparently.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>So where do I sign?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>We don't need you to. The Army gave the file to you yesterday. Major Mathewson had another copy sent over to us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>Ah. You know, there's a reason I didn't want that file released.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I know. I read it. I'm gonna treat my patient now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>I was right. Wasn't I?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>How did he die? What did they cover up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>They didn't cover up anything. I did. Dad died in that car accident because he was drunk. Killed a pedestrian too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>What are you— what—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-9"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>He drank, Brant, a lot. You were too young to see it. I, uh, I had some of dad's buddies… take care of his files. It was the only time I ever broke the rules. I'm sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Can I begin treatment?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Fever hasn't broken. White count is still up. Renal function is declining.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>So he has all the signs of malaria, except the antimalarials aren't curing him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Gonorrhea? If it got into his heart…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We did an echo. His valves look good. What about—  you bastard. You were faking.  Yesterday, House stole candy by putting it into a cup. The cup was too small, so his solution was to remove some of the candy. But the obviously logical thing was to just get a bigger cup, which he did today, because he's no longer faking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>He couldn't have faked it. We tested your—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I took St. John's Wort to alter the way my liver metabolized acetaminophen. Then some n-acetylcysteine just to finish it off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You tortured them to torture me just to see who you could trust?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I did it to save lives. God, I wish I could rationalize that one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>And now you're going to brilliantly deduce which one of us is the rat?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What makes you think I haven't already?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>To be continued. I need to brilliantly cure a patient.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No hair usually means no lice. What we didn't account for was that it wasn't your hair. Tea was not the only thing that your Afghani neighbors shared with you. I'm sure they were generous enough to let you sit on their furniture, which was infested with rat lice. You have typhus. Caused the vasculitis and explains all your other symptoms. But here's where it gets interesting. One of those symptoms, a lawyer might argue, was leaking the tape. There are psychiatric issues associated with typhus. If you change your mind, plead not guilty, you've got a case.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>I'd be undermining everything I've been trying to do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>Hayes</speaker><content>You did what you thought you had to do. Going to jail proves nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>Brant</speaker><content>It proves I still have my honor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're not doing this for honor. You're doing this to please your father. And the pathetic thing is that the man you're trying to please never existed.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Traitor. You've been avoiding me for two days. 'Cause, when I stranded you behind the barricades, you went straight to Foreman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I've been avoiding you because you're an ass.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I've been an ass my whole life, I can't get rid of you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You can get rid of me now. Just turn and limp away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Huh. Your whiny righteousness has the stench of sincerity. Fine. I have to punish my whole team so that one of them will step forward.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Makes sense.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Damn. Now I'm gonna have to punish my whole team so that one of them will step forward.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You just said that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, but I meant it this time. First time I was just testing you. Either you were gonna genuinely confess or falsely confess or actually…</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>His name's li'l Chase. He's a rat. You're a rat. Get it? Taub confessed to telling Foreman to protect the patient. Adams confessed to protect Taub. But your confession was just piling on. There's no rational reason for you to have done it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>And my punishment will be nothing. You wanted me to tell Foreman. Your ability to solve puzzles is the only thing that matters to you. And you're smart enough to know even you'll lose your edge at some point. You want to make sure someone's there when you do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If that were true, why are li'l Chase's li'l cousins scurrying through your apartment's floorboards right now?</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>