<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>
<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Barton</speaker><content>Nice tie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Ainsley</speaker><content>Are you at least gonna call the cops this time?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Ainsley</speaker><content>Come on, Dad. Let Rodrigo do this. Your arthritis is obviously—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Barton</speaker><content>I can pick up my own lawn. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Ainsley</speaker><content>You know, if you wanted, you could put an end to all this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Barton </speaker><content>Oh, of course. There are other ways to save the company. I'm only moving it to China because I'm craving egg foo yung.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Ainsley</speaker><content>You know, I just got off the phone with some investors.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Barton</speaker><content>Yes, and they want a controlling interest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Ainsley</speaker><content>We get to stay here with the people who've been so loyal to this company. Everyone keeps their jobs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Barton</speaker><content>It's been a family business for 120 years. There's no way that I'm letting…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Ainsley</speaker><content>What's wrong?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Ainsley</speaker><content>Dad?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Ainsley</speaker><content>Dad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Barton</speaker><content>I need you to drive me to a doctor.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>This would totally suck.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Patient's visited China a lot recently. What about the JBE virus?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Why don't you check his vaccination record before you make another stupid… O.M.F.G. 50% off cupcakes. How sick is the patient? 'Cause this expires today.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Central serous retinopathy.  It's linked to type "A" personalities.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Funduscopic exam was normal. If you don't let me read my email, then I won't be able to read the email to the entire staff. From your ex-boss.  Thank you.  "Last month, I had an incident involving another P.P.T.H. employee. Though I can't speak to the details of the case while my disciplinary hearing is pending, I want you to know that I have completed voluntary sexual harassment training. And on a personal note, if my actions caused anyone distress, I sincerely apologize." You are so fired.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>What? He apologized.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What? Because he said he apologized? He's saying he's sorry that someone, namely you, overreacted — namely, by punching him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>He grabbed my behind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Word is it was a celebratory slap after you completed your first-ever AVM embolization.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>He grabbed it, he apologized for grabbing it, and now he's taking classes because he grabbed it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The classes make him sympathetic. Which, in turn, makes his unrepentant attacker… Evil. Which, in turn, in turn, makes you so fired.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>100 bucks says I won't get fired.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh, you don't wanna bet me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh, my.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're fired.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I… The bet is—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>But I thought—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>After… Then I… Oh—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If only—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>The bet's that I'll get fired after my hearing!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'll take that action too, but you're already a C-note in the hole.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-22"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're late.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-23"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Considering I don't work here, arguably, I'm early.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-24"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Pearl earrings? Knee-length dress. That's not a very shameful walk of shame.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-25"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I was at a job interview.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-26"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I hope it went terribly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-27"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Thad Barton? We only help rich white guys?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-28"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I am an equal opportunity exploiter. I only help those who can help myself.  I have a department to re-fund.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-29"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Atropine poisoning. He's moving his company to China, and his employees are hanging him in effigy. Could have moved on to the real thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-30"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Pupils are normal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-31"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Thyrotoxicosis?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-32"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Not… a terrible idea. I'm gonna go give him P.T.U. and T.L.C. I have no idea what that second one stands for.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Barton</speaker><content>Things don't seem small anymore, they— I woke up from a nap and, uh, everything went from really small to really huge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, then, these giant balls of medicine are not gonna work anymore. The change actually makes things simpler. Your occipital lobe is acting up, giving you a migraine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Barton</speaker><content>I don't have a headache.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Not all migraines present that way. It's called Alice in Wonderland syndrome.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Ainsley</speaker><content>Seriously?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I never joke. Good news is, it's treatable with medication. Bad news is… it can make you very, very late for very important dates. I sometimes joke.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Barton</speaker><content>Thank you, Doctor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Well, if you really want to thank me, my department's not really a department. 'Cause my boss says he doesn't have the money. Which provides a nice contrast… with you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Ainsley</speaker><content>trying to find money in our budget so we don't have to move our operations overseas.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I get it. Answer's no. Shouldn't have said anything. I'm just glad that the symptoms showed up before you left for China.  'Cause I'm not sure the doctors over there would be so optimistic, considering…  How they look down on mental illness.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Barton </speaker><content>You speak Mandarin?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Ainsley</speaker><content>What are you guys talking about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh, just how different the two cultures are. For example, our opinions on mental illness. Here, it's considered a normal and treatable condition.  There, it’s taboo enough to destroy a high profile business deal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Ainsley</speaker><content>Is everything okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Barton</speaker><content>Everything's fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>House </speaker><content>I’d never breach confidentiality, but… I could have you checked into a facility that exclusively treats mental disorders. How does that sound?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>Ainsley</speaker><content>Whatever's gonna get him better.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>Barton</speaker><content>Let's try the medication first.  How much do you want? </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're hired! Oh, you guys are gonna love Doctors Chase and Taub.  Keep your Nazi sentiments quiet around the little one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>You got the money? How?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Patient's a smart businessman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>He's destroying thousands of jobs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Jobs are not being destroyed. They're being relocated. The fact that you see that as inherently bad means you're an irrational patriot. To put it another way, a patriot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Patriotism is natural. We've always relied on our tribes to keep us safe. It's helpful for society if its members have positive feelings about that society.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Iranian women. Drag Queens in Uganda. Patriotism is nothing but loyalty to real estate, real estate that's been conquered 800 times by 800 different regimes with 800 different cultures. But each time, it's just the best.  I claim this burger in the name of Queen Isabella of Spain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I'll go check on the patient.  I have Hepatitis C.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Park </speaker><content>She got it from me.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Ainsley</speaker><content>Hey, how's my dad doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Ah, great. His vision's back to normal, and if he remains asymptomatic through the night, we'll be able to release him in the morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>No offense, but, uh, I think it's terrible your dad's closing down all your American operations.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Ainsley</speaker><content>I don't think he's moving the company out of greed. He's moving it out of grief. My mom, she died four months ago. Non-Hodgkin's lymphoma, and… It's been hard for him — living in their house, driving down the same streets. I mean, he's constantly reminded of her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Ainsley</speaker><content>Dad?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I need an intubation kit in here!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Ainsley</speaker><content>What's going on?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Angiography showed a hemorrhagic site in the left lower lobe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I think it could be hyperviscosity syndrome. Are you sure Foreman's okay with this thing in his office?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He's never gonna know. He's actually in here right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Blood count and protein count are normal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I think it could be hyperviscosity syndrome. Sorry, but after Park sent out here hospital-wide non-apology apology this morning, I assume that plagiarism is the new black.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>If it makes Andrews look sympathetic…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Copying him makes you look pathetic. And I will pay you not to go to anger management classes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>What about another clotting problem? Factor 5 Leiden deficiency.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's possible. Adams is the one who needs to deal with her anger.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Myelodysplastic syndrome.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I heard about your conversation with the patient's daughter. You were hostile.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Well, their company's making a decision I strongly disagree with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yet you were never anything but courteous to the racists and rapists in prison. Those guys made decisions you supported?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Myelodysplastic syndrome.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm guessing it has something to do with the funeral you attended yesterday morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I was at a job interview.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You got to work at 9:15. Closest hospital with an opening in your specialty is 45 minutes away. It's not possible. My condolences.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-18"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I wasn't at a funeral.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That just leaves… everywhere but a job interview.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-20"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Who goes there? Reveal yourself!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-21"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Now. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-22"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, we would. But Orthopedics is still squatting in two thirds of my office, which is weird, 'cause you got a large check last night. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-23"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>From a corporation that's going through a very public belt-tightening. Means this donation was given under duress. Patient didn't tell me the whole story, but he did say he'd be thrilled if we didn't cash this.  Got a policy review meeting in here in five minutes. Good-bye.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-24"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>What are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-25"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Holding your ass. You really didn't know?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-26"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>House…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-27"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Just trying to help you out here. I figure for sure he'd punch me in the face, thus proving it's a natural response. My God, you have super-human discipline. And glutes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-28"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Get your hands off me. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-29"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-30"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-31"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Why… did you do that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-32"><speaker>House</speaker><content>We have a bet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-33"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>But he's the chair of the disciplinary committee. Forget about the bet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-34"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You two really need to do your homework with me. Treat the patient with activated protein c.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-35"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>If he has myelodysplastic syndrome, he'll bleed out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-36"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>And if he has Factor 5 Leiden deficiency, he'll throw another clot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-37"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Exactly. It's a conclusive test. There's no actual risk.  As long as you're both paying attention, and are both good enough to work here. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Barton</speaker><content>I hear one of you thinks I'm a real bastard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I guess that would be me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Barton</speaker><content>Your boss uses blackmail, and you question my professional ethics?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Will you be instituting worker safety regulations in your new factories?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Barton</speaker><content>Oh, absolutely.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>What about juice boxes in the break room for the children you'll be hiring?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Barton</speaker><content>Charges of child exploitation against American companies have been blown</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>My ten-year-old cousin lives near Cebu City. Works at an American factory.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I am so sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>It's the best thing for him. It sucks, but the Filipino factories suck worse, and the schools would suck if they existed. So this is the family's best hope.  Are you okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Barton</speaker><content>Is this supposed to itch like this?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Itching. Interesting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Not interesting. Already went away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Doubly interesting. Means we have to explain the arrival and the departure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Ortho doctor</speaker><content>That's real mature, House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>House </speaker><content>What do you mean? This is outlandishly childish. I custom-built this puppy. It's got 106 leds, each one sending light to your eyes, slightly different wavelength.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Ortho doctor</speaker><content>Turn that off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Different wavelengths are stimulating your autonomic nervous system. That's what's making you feel like you're on a boat in choppy waters.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh ho ho! Cool.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Ortho doc</speaker><content>You think I'm not — you think I'm not gonna go to Foreman with this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Oh, you will. And… I'll deny it, and he'll believe you. But then these two believe that the policy of protecting American jobs starts at home. So they'll never testify against me. And you won't be able to prove anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Now, if I punched him in the face, that he could prove.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I remember you saying something about how loyalty to real estate was stupid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>This is about reclaiming stolen property! Loyalty to real estate is stupid, because loyalty is stupid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>First patriotism, now loyalty. You hate ice cream too?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>French vanilla, yeah. To willfully identify yourself as something else is a perversion of self-expression.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I had a thought. Other than the fact that loyalty is the basis of all meaningful relationships. The daughter said that her mother died of non-Hodgkin's lymphoma. What if she was misdiagnosed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Dutch chocolate's not bad. Gotta give 'em that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-18"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Her lymphoma could have been caused by a virus, HTLV-1, which our patient contracted through having sex with his wife.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>In other words, loyalty gave him cancer. I like it. Start him on radiation. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Asian man</speaker><content>Chang and Eng Bunker. It's the most famous conjoined twins in history. 2011 is the bicentennial of their birth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The best Halloween costumes are always the ones that need an explanation.  What took you so long? I already lost one of them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>You need help with the lacerations?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, I think I got palliative. Why don't you take preventative?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Prevent what? He got in a fight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Which he started. Which means he's both irascible and stupid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Asian man</speaker><content>I told the drunk, racist frat guy the proper term is "conjoined twin," not "Siamese."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I can't comment on the drunk or the frat. But Chang and Eng were both, in fact, born in Siam. And they were, in fact, twins. If your name was Richard, it would be okay for me to call you a Dick. But maybe some of the tripe you learn in anger management class might help keep this guy out of here the next time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Sometimes, it's incredibly satisfying to wind up and punch someone who really deserves it. But when you think about the consequences—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Okay, let's go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I thought you wanted me to help him with his anger.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, I got everything I need.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Park </speaker><content>Sometimes…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Sometimes…  It's incredibly satisfying to wind up and punch someone who deserves it. Wonder what the committee's gonna make of that.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Barton</speaker><content>This is a waste of time. There's no way that Robin gave me an STD.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I know this is hard, and I'm sorry about your wife. If you'd like to talk to someone, we do have grief counselors at the hospital.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Barton</speaker><content>You sound like my daughter. I miss my wife, but it's not driving my decision-making.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>You were CEO since 1988. You decided to move your company right after your wife died. It stands to reason that your emotions factored in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Barton</speaker><content>My wife… is the only thing that keeps me here. I visit her grave once a week.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>So your daughter was wrong. You just… really need a lot of money.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Barton</speaker><content>You ever hear of Kongo Gumi? Construction company in Japan founded in the year 578. Family-owned and operated. Building Buddhist temples for 50 generations. Wen—went bankrupt five years ago. You have any idea how that last CEO must have felt? Sorry, I… have to move.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Your heart rate is speeding up. Do you feel any tightness in your chest?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Barton</speaker><content>Yes, I figured it was from the radiation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I think you're having a heart attack. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Come in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Dr. Wilson… I need your advice. Um… I bet House $100 that I wouldn't get fired after my disciplinary hearing.  Ever since then, he's been acting like he's actually trying to get me fired.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>That's because he is actually trying to get you fired.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Does he hate me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Not sure that's relevant to the equation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>So it's really over $100?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Not sure the amount is relevant. He's fighting for his honor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>He'll ruin my career.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Not sure that's-</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>What if I bet him $200 I will get fired.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>He sees competing debts with the same person as a disgrace to the game. He'll be even more motivated to beat you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>If you were me, what would you do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You have to give him something he values more than honor. And you should update your resume.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>EKG and troponins were equivocal. It's not even clear if our patient just had a heart attack or what it was.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Let's look at segmental wall motion abnormalities. Get him an echo to confirm. I need $200,000.  His company's lost one third of its value since he was admitted.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>And you want to do some insider trading? I take it felonies aren't a violation of your parole?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's not insider trading. Just betting on myself to solve the case. Once we cure him, share price goes up, I pay you back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, you don't say "no." You… make a counter offer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I'm not loaning my boss money.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Fine. I'll make you a counter. $100,000. $20,000. I'll buy options instead of shares. More risk, but more upside. But that's as low as I'm gonna go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I could do $5,000.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Really? No backsies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>If… you double your clinic hours. Six a week. I've seen how you disrespect those patients.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So you want twice as many of them disrespected?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Spend more hours with them, you'll treat them more humanely.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And this time, a land war in Russia will be a good idea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Deal?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Here's what I'm thinking. You went to a parole hearing, where one of your old patients was denied. Hence the attire, hence the tardiness. And, most important, hence the anger. You think you can restore the cosmic balance by doing extra good here. More annoyingly, by having me do it.  And deal!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Of course, you know… this means war.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-18"><speaker>Ortho doctor</speaker><content>Oh, I know. I mean, you'll escalate, and then I'll retaliate, and the cycle will continue until we've both gone too far, at which point, I'll… maybe get suspended and… you'll go back to prison.  Happy pranking.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Patient had V-tach in the echo lab, so we capped him, but… coronary arteries were clean.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>If the plumbing's fine, check the electrical. EP study.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Nice idea. Even has a metaphor in it. Not worth more than my honor. But delightful, all the same.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I'm not going to lose. My college roommate is the editor of the Yale Law Review. She's writing my opening statement.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You will be eloquent in your loss. This case boils down to he said, she said. He said, "I've been working at this hospital for 15 years and I'm taking self-improvement classes." She said, "I've been a fellow for two months, and I'm kind of weird."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>No, he said, "I'm a drunk idiot who thinks he can grab girls' behinds without ramifications."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Wait, he was drunk? In the hospital?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I already told Foreman he'd been drinking that night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Andrews was taking sexual harassment classes, not AA. That means he didn't get in trouble for drinking. Which means that Foreman signed off on it, which means that he set all the wheels in motion. Forget that. Wild speculation. Go do the EP study.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>You already knew Andrews was drinking that night, didn't you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I think you should cancel my hearing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I hope this isn't going where I assume it's going.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>You're the one who brought Andrews in. You set the wheels in motion.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>We had a patient who was going to die without an AVM embolization. Andrews… was the only neurologist I could reach. He told me had a few glasses of wine, and that he shouldn't do it, but he also said that you were good. You were ready to do one, as long as you were supervised. So we agreed that he would come in, but wouldn't touch the patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I can understand the rationalization. We'll see if the Board agrees when I tell them the whole story at my hearing</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>I already did. I had a closed session hearing last week. The Board decided to dock me two weeks pay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Been working for House for two weeks. It's already too long.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>No sign of any electrical abnormalities in the right atrium.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I'm so dead. I-I think House set me up. Have you sent the committee a character reference for me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I thought you don't like favors.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I don't like gifts. It wouldn't be a gift. I would just be you telling the truth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I hardly know you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>O2 sat is 89. Did we perforate? Is he tamponading?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Heart rate's only 90. Neck veins are flat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Then why isn't he saturated?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Seems healthy to me. Let's release him. My option to sell Barton Foods at $34 is about to expire. So they thought the patient would be better by now. Instead, I am going to lose $20,000.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>20?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Your five plus the five I stole from Wilson. Plus the ten I got on margin. You're gonna have to talk to my bankruptcy attorney.  Unless… There is a way that you can get your money back.  Give me the full $200,000.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>And extrapolating, tomorrow you'll owe just shy of $1 million.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's your own fault. You forced me to go with the options here. Your damn anger issues are screwing with my finances. Regular stock this time, nice and safe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I'm not angry. I don't know if you're trying to make me angry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You refuse to bet on yourself. That means low self-esteem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>So if I give you $200,000, I'll feel smart and pretty.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Low self-esteem can be brought on by exposure to one's relatives. Nice clothes and anger… Classic symptoms. Family gathering. You were late the other day 'cause you were having breakfast with Grammy Adams or Cousin Itt. And she was nagging you about finding a husband.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Ah, ah, ah, ah!  No spoilers. They ruin everything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-11"><speaker>Park </speaker><content>Pulmonology was that way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Our patient's lung problem is not a lung problem. It's a brain problem. We're consulting with Neurology.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-13"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>That's my old boss. You don't actually think this is neurological.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I don't know what it is. Maybe I should just accept the patient's death, if getting help can lead to awkwardness.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Dr. Andrews. My associates. Doctors Adams and Park. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-16"><speaker>Andrews</speaker><content>Ah. Nice to meet you, Dr. Adams. Hello, Dr. Park.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-17"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Micropsia, bleeding, tachycardia, and difficulty breathing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-18"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Cute butt, huh?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-19"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Can we go now?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-20"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You really wanna turn your back on this guy? Sorry. Carry on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-21"><speaker>Andrews</speaker><content>Uh… well… It sounds like there could be spinal cord involvement. Have you considered normal pressure hydrocephalus?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-22"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Okay, normal pressure hydrocephalus going once. Normal pressure hydrocephalus going twice…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-23"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>It's not his spinal cord, it's the wiring between his heart and his brain. Autonomic dysregulation syndrome. You do a tilt table test, see how his heart rate responds. That'll confirm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-24"><speaker>Andrews</speaker><content>Well, if he has normal pressure hydrocephalus, a tilt table test could put him in a coma.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-25"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Then it's a good thing he has A.D.S.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-26"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Do you really believe in this diagnosis? Because if this is just a pissing contest, you are at a severe anatomical disadvantage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-27"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>It's autonomic dysregulation syndrome.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-28"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No… it's normal pressure hydrocephalus. Do a spinal fluid test to confirm.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>We're doing the tilt table.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>That makes sense. You'd rather have House fire you than Foreman?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>This bet's got to be a test. See if I can handle working with him. I need to prove I have the confidence to disobey him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Do you have any medical justification for your diagnosis?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>The symptoms fit, and Andrews is a hack. Do you think I'm right? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>No… you need to go prepare for your hearing.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>15 more minutes, Mr. Barton.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>A skin resurfacing laser is missing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>And why are you asking me about it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Because you work for House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>What would House want with a skin resurfacing laser?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I have no idea. Have you seen it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>Barton</speaker><content>My feet feel hot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>That's completely normal. No, but House has been talking about how badly he wants to remove those prison tats.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>It's a very expensive machine, and I'd like it back. Please tell me if you hear anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>How expensive?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-11"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>$200,000. He took it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-12"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I have no idea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-13"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Park's hearing's about to start.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-14"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>You're covering for him. I did the same thing many times. My advice to you — figure out what line you aren't willing to cross for him. Because, eventually, he'll ask you to cross it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-15"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>How are your feet?  Mr. Barton? Can you hear me, Mr. Barton?  Oh, no.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>We have convened the disciplinary committee to decide the appropriate action that should be taken against Dr. Chi Park as a result of her actions on October 7th of this year. Dr. Park, do you have an opening statement.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Dr. Foreman, members of the committee, thank you for giving me this opportunity to speak to you today, I…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>She's not yours to fire.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You guys better fire her for insubordination, 'cause she went rogue, and my patient is now in a coma.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I'm the one who did the test.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>No, it was my idea!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Seriously, House?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>At least I'm smart enough to know what I don't know. She went out of her way to defy me! She needs— Damn it, you should just fire her!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>My apologies.  My apologies, Dr. Park. Dr. House's comments will, of course, have no bearing on this hearing. Please continue.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I can't believe you did that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Right back at ya. Our patient's dying. We need theories.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>It's gotta be normal pressure hydrocephalus. Andrews predicted the coma.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, but even a broken doctor's right twice a day. Patient wasn't wet, wobbly, or wacky. Coma had to be a lucky guess.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>If you didn't think he was right, then why did you want us to collect his spinal fluid?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I didn't. I wanted you to do a tilt table test.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>You have a wonderful way of communicating.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I knew Park wanted to do a tilt table. She listens to me, I waste an hour. If she defies me… Then I get the test I want and my 100 bucks.  Up high.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're angry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Yes! Now I'm angry. Let's run the test for normal pressure hydrocephalus.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No. What else would explain our symptoms and make our patient go into a coma during that test? How 'bout hepatic encephalopathy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-12"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>No, we already tested his liver enzymes. They're normal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Or his liver's so far gone it can't even produce enzymes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-14"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>That's desperate. Fits the symptoms. And Andrews is a hack. Go biopsy to confirm. Unless you want your own hearing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-15"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>You'd have to hire me first.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>So you do realize that it is unacceptable to hit someone in the workplace?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>Ainsley</speaker><content>Is this theory more promising than the others?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>We'll know in a few hours. How are you holding up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>Ainsley</speaker><content>Other than the fact that my dad's in a coma… Terrible. Tomorrow morning, I am supposed to sign a piece of paper that will… move the company and cost thousands of employees their jobs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I thought you'd rather see the company go under in New Jersey than thrive in China.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>Ainsley</speaker><content>It's what my dad wants. And it's still his company. I'm really just keeping the seat warm. But unless he wakes up before tomorrow, it's gonna be my signature on that piece of paper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>You don't have to sign it. I'll let you know when we have the results.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Biopsy was clean. It's not his liver. I also ran the spinal fluid test, and you were right that Andrews was wrong. His ICP was not normal. It was elevated. What about HTLV?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>We ruled that out three days ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Because of his heart problems, but—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Once something gets taken off the board, I'm the only one who's allowed to put it back on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>Park </speaker><content>You owe me 106,804 Yuan. Or $100 U.S.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>God, but you're petty. Okay, so… two options. Either we figure out what's wrong with this guy, or we figure out how to make this company profitable in New Jersey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Eastern equine encephalitis?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Brain scans indicate it could be Loa loa disease.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Ah, shut it off!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Apparently we're allowed to do this now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-11"><speaker>Ortho doctor</speaker><content>Get out of here, House!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>This diagnosis was brought to you by the letter "Y."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>Ainsley</speaker><content>Dad… God, you're okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>Barton</speaker><content>I'm thirsty.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That's a side effect of not dying. Turns out your blood was getting thick and syrupy. Complexes of large, y-shaped antibodies were clogging up your blood vessels, causing your organs to shut down one by one. Now, usually with hyperviscosity syndrome, it's caused by an elevated blood count or protein count. Yours eluded us 'cause it was caused by antibodies from your rheumatoid arthritis. Now that they're being filtered out, the blood would be… a little less duck sauce and a little more soy sauce.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>Barton</speaker><content>So I'm gonna be completely cured.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's not all about you. Your stock price will be completely cured. Once you sign this.  It's a press release. It says that you're healthy, you're going back to work, and you're signing the lease that officially moves the company to China.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>Ainsley</speaker><content>He just woke up. Dad, you don't have to deal with this right now. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Ah, mm, yeah, actually… he does. 'Cause the market opens at 9:00 a.m. And this means a lot to me. You may remember me from the time I saved your life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>Ainsley</speaker><content>If you move it, it'll be without me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-10"><speaker>Barton</speaker><content>I know you object. I know you disagree with—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-11"><speaker>Ainsley</speaker><content>Dad… I can't do it. If this is really about family, you will not do this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Morning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Got lucky this time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-14"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>No, you didn't. I made this bet so you'd stop actively trying to fire Park so you'd be neutral. You went out of your way to help her. She obviously earned your respect, passed whatever test you—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I sabotaged her hearing. You do read the school paper, don't you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-16"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>If you had sabotaged her hearing, she would have gotten more than a slap on the wrist. What you actually did was make her emotional and make the board members see her as a victim.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>'Cause the panel feels badly for incompetent doctors who nearly kill people.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-18"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You know that everyone on that panel hates you. You know the minute you recommend firing anyone, they start discussing how big a bonus to give them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That's just hurtful. The fact is, winning $100 from you gives me more pleasure than winning $100 from her. Here's your five grand. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-20"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>What five grand?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Just take it. Trust me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-22"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Found her sleeping in the park. Said she ran away because her daddy didn't love her. And that is exactly what happened… as far as you can prove.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-23"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Congratulations. You're not going to jail… today. But you do know I just can't let this slide. You need to keep up your rep.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-24"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Fine. Clinic hours. I'll double them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-25"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Okay. 12 hours a week.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-26"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No… Three times two equals six.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-27"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>And 3 times 2 times 2 is 12. I know about your deal with Adams.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-28"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Call Chase and Taub. Get 'em in here. The boys are back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-29"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>This check is for significantly more than what I told you it would take to fund the department.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-30"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I know.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>You paged me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Congratulations.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You caught your boyfriend cheating that morning. You had a big fight. That's why you were late. You re-pitched an S.T.D. You haven't gotten two consecutive minutes without using the word "loyalty," which explains the anger and the low self-esteem, and the desire to feel pretty… after having been rejected explains the clothes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>It wasn't my boyfriend. It was my husband. I was at my lawyer's office signing the divorce papers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Wow. I missed the fact that you were married.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>We've been separated for almost a year.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So… old news? No anger left?  It's all bought and paid for.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>