<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>
<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Voice of a woman</speaker><content>Keep breathing. Nice and slow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Molly</speaker><content>Now, the first couple of shots will show you if the sights are off or the barrel's bent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>Yes!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Molly</speaker><content>Yeah! You did it! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>I didn't.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Carny</speaker><content>You just won your girlfriend a teddy bear. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>And then Thursday night, this physicist is giving a lecture in Brooklyn. It's about time travel and the grandfather paradox. I don't know if you're busy…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Molly</speaker><content>I'm really happy that we've been hanging out so much.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>Yeah, I-I like you too. Heh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Molly</speaker><content>Can you put down the bear?  Henry…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>What?  I can't.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Molly</speaker><content>I know. You have a girlfriend. It's just… she never seems… to want to do anything with you. Are you crying?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>No, I have allergies. I must just be, like, tearing up. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-15"><speaker>Molly</speaker><content>Henry, I think that's blood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-16"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>What? I-it… </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-17"><speaker>Molly</speaker><content>Oh!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>35-year-old male cries blood, and he's not vampire Bill. Go!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Should we ask?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Nope! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What, her? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, my favorite companion is retiring from "companning." So I'm interviewing replacements. Thank you… Butterscotch. Is that a family name? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>How long are you gonna be using the office for sex games? Just so I can plan my day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Sex and work? I'm not a savage.  I asked for a cappuccino.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Butterscotch</speaker><content>That's what this is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, cappuccinos got a nice, stiff foam on it. This is wetter than… oh… almost slipped there. Well, thank you, Ms. Scotch, but poor foaming's a deal breaker. Could you ask the next candidate to come in? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Initial exam showed no sign of trauma or subconjunctival hemorrhage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Lymphocytosis? ALC's in normal range, but it's in the high end of normal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Take a seat, Fawn. And tell me, what's your favorite Woody Allen movie? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Fawn</speaker><content>Annie Hall.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You're interviewing hookers but not gonna talk to them about sex?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Sex is a given. They're hookers.  Defend your choice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Fawn</speaker><content>It's the most popular.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Lymphocytosis works. Maybe we should take another look at the blood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Could also be cavernous sinus thrombosis. Clot builds up pressure at the base of the brain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Rerun the patient's blood panel and get a CT venogram of his head. Let's see which one of you is right.  How are you with small appliance repair?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Molly</speaker><content>Uh, this cavernous sinus thing, is it dangerous?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>If Henry's got it, we can treat it with a combo of drugs and surgery. Success rate is over 70%.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Molly</speaker><content>Amy's his girlfriend. I'm the neighbor. I did leave a message at their number.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Do you wanna try her cell? Be here for a few more hours at least.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>Oh, she doesn't have one. She worries about radiation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Molly</speaker><content>I could stop by on my way home. She knows who I am, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>You don't need to, but thanks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Molly</speaker><content>Good luck. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Have you ever paid for sex?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Every guy who's ever seen a Merchant Ivory movie has paid for sex.  No. It just… seems too demeaning to women.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Given the things you've done to women, that seems arbitrary.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Young man</speaker><content>You're Chi Park, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Who's asking?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Young man</speaker><content>Uh, you called about my guitar flyer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>You're Micah. This guy's selling a 1974 Gibson SG standard in tobacco for $1,250.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Micah</speaker><content>Yeah, actually, I came in to tell you I already sold it. Sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Oh, um… thanks anyway. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Maybe we should check for diabetes. Could weaken conjunctival vessels. And shut up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>If I'm wrong then why is he coming back?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Micah</speaker><content>My band is rehearsing tomorrow night. You should come by and jam with us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Micah</speaker><content>Great. Call me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I'll break your face.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>This is the talent portion of the interview.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Okay. You like cards. But you can juggle. I fail to see how this would be of benefit to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What if I'm busy?  Have you got anything else?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>CT showed no clots or malformations. Park and Taub ruled out lymphocytosis and diabetes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, since you have nothing of relevance to report, I assume that you're here to toss your panties in the ring.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Patient's got a mysterious girlfriend he really wants to see. She's unreachable by phone, and the neighbor's never even seen her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Debbie</speaker><content>He's gay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I think he's a junkie. The girlfriend is a fix. The guy's inhaling glue.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Can you repair a blender?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Can you bite me? Go search the patient's home. Well, thank you, ladies. I've seen a lot of very talented candidates. Got a tough decision the next few days.  This is the part I hate. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Well… this is not exactly a crack den.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Doesn't exactly look like a woman lives here, either.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>"To Amy. I love you."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Okay. She exists. Doesn't mean he's not a drug addict.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>It's good you're playing it cool with House. Once he gets a rise out of someone…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Yeah, I'm not crazy about the whole hooker thing, but I get it. Other than the fact that it's exploitative and dangerous for women, you get what you need without any of the emotional baggage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You're not seeing anyone I take it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I've been volunteering at the Trenton Free Clinic. Keeps me busy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You volunteer every night and every weekend? No time to grab dinner?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>What's more important — making small talk over ravioli or helping people who are less fortunate?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>With that rationale, none of us should ever eat again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Let's just say I'm not hungry right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Oh, God…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I don't think she's breathing. Do you think she OD'd?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-15"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>That or he killed her. Pulse?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-16"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-17"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I'll call the coroner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-18"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I don't think that's gonna be necessary.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>This one works in financial district. She can get tips, give you leg up in market. What is "fudgey Gonzalez"?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Uh, imagine a "vanilla Gonzalez," but from the other side.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm about to make a decision, but there's still time for you to sneak under the wire.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>My favorite Woody Allen movie is Melinda and Melinda.  Our patient is not a junkie, but he does have a girlfriend. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>I call her my "girlfriend" because people understand that. If I explained it, they'd just think I was a weirdo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We're not here to judge anyone's fetish.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>I'm not a pervert. It's not like I'm more attracted to dolls than humans.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>So you don't have sex with her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>It's not just about that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Does the doll talk to you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>I know she's not a real person. In a lot of ways, she's better than a person. I can tell her things, and she won't argue with me or make fun of me. I come home every night, and I know she'll be there waiting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>So is your toaster.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>No one in the world has an emotional attachment to a toaster. But a lot of people are willing to spend $7,000 on women like Amy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Have you ever tried an actual—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>Yeah, I'm 35. I've been in relationships. Just none of them fulfilled me. And one day, I saw this website, and… maybe the perfect woman's out there somewhere, but it's not worth going through what it would take to find her. Amy makes me happy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You're swelling.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>It's sort of hot in here.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Bleeding plus two new symptoms. Fever and neurological.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I'm not sure about that last one. I think he's just… weird. He wasn't hallucinating. He didn't have a thought disorder.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>And you don't think it's "disordered" to talk to—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>It's not all that different from talking to your cat or a Teddy bear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>You don't have sex with your cat or Teddy bear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If you did, you'd probably talk to them more. Guy loves an imaginary being who's never going to respond to him. He's no crazier than millions of churchgoers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>You think anything off about any patient is a symptom. This guy buys flowers. Real flowers for a piece of plastic in a dress.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>He's just running away. He hangs out with a doll, he never needs to fear rejection.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>It's sad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You do understand the irony here? Every person in this room has a sex doll. At least the patient has the stones to be honest about it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Ooh, a metaphor. What you didn't foresee is that is that I actually do have a sex doll.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Your doll is your kids. Yours is your parents, yours is your charity. All excuses for not being in a relationship.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>He's not wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I have meaningless sex with random strangers. Thanks for the insight, but I stopped that months ago. I actually had a relationship.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>My dating is getting in the way of my dating?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You don't go looking for the right person. You just shack up with whoever's in the room, and then you get surprised and/or divorced when it doesn't work out. I'm surprised you haven't asked Adams out yet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You'll bail.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>He's right. The obvious solution is for me to hand my kids over to your parents.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Can we stop trying to argue the premise and move onto figuring out why it is that you're all social morons?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-20"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You do understand the irony here. You mocking us for avoiding relationships, but you can't handle losing your "doll." You’re spending all this time and energy interviewing for a new one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're right. That is stupid. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-22"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>What about the patient?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-23"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Dude's banging a sex doll. A festering cesspool of bodily fluids and associated bacteria. Swab her out and find out which one. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I need you. Please don't quit. You're the only hooker I know who can tune a piano. If it's about the money, then I can up you to three nights a week.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Emily</speaker><content>I'm getting married, House. His name's Harris.  He's a certified accountant, he loves schlocky horror movies, and he just moved in. We're very happy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Emily</speaker><content>He knows. We've talked about it, and he accepts me for who I am.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No. He… If he accepted who you were, he would not be making you give up your career. Women need their own identities, their own livelihoods. Otherwise, why was I smoking all those Virginia Slims?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Emily</speaker><content>I know this is weird for you, but you need to figure out a way to be okay with it. I'll miss you, too.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I feel like the stirrups are overkill.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I've never done a pelvic on a doll before. I'm unfamiliar with the protocol.  I'm pretty skeeved out right now. I'm not gonna lie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>What House said back there—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I don't just date whoever shows up. I mean, I did meet women in the hospital, but they weren't just flings.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Basically, you're explaining why you're not going to ask me out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>That's not what I was — did you want me to ask you out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Yeah. I told Park to tell Taub to tell House to pass you that note.  It's completely clean in there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>He said he just bathed her.  Adams… there's a swelling beneath the skin… 3-inch mass.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>It feels like a tumor.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>CT showed an air-filled mass in the doll's abdomen. It's probably just a chemical reaction. Henry left her too close to a heating pipe or something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>This guy brushes her hair every morning, brings home movies for them to watch together. You think he tosses her in a broom closet at the end of each day?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>More likely than it getting stomach cancer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>How about clostridium? Bacteria got trapped in the airtight cavity, produced gas…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>It doesn't explain the neurological issue.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We can explain that the same way we explain the tooth fairy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh, I get to play Solomon. Cut the doll open.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We can't just destroy the patient's property. That thing cost 7 grand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Exactly. Ask him for consent. If he says yes, then we get to go hunting bacteria. If he says no, there's no need because he's crazy, and we need a different theory. See ya. Gotta go build a temple.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>You sure? It won't be able to heal when we're done.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>But you think she could tell you what's wrong with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Should we take her to the procedure room?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>It's not a “her,” which means we can do this anywhere. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Adams… you can know something's not real and still love it. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I think the procedure room might be better for this.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You are a horrible person.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>All I need is to break up one marriage. You've broken up three of your own. You're like the Stephen Hawking of killing relationships. Actually, no, Stephen Hawking is the Stephen Hawking of—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Okay. I have work to do. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Your computer is off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Sorry, I can't hear you over my "stereo."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Why do you assume that marriage is better than hooking? We don't know anything about the guy. He could be a serial killer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Even if that were true, it would still be a toss-up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You're a coward.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Absolutely, if what he's afraid of is other damsels. Your last relationship failed so miserably, you ended up in jail. Now you're clinging to this hooker when there are about 3 billion other women out there who aren't call girls, some of whom are attractive and intelligent, one of whom is living in your apartment and is married to you!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>You shouldn't sleep with Chase.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Thank God. You got here just in time. What do you have against him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Nothing, but House has a way of getting into people's heads.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Just like last week when he was prying into your relationship with Chase? It was silly then, and it's silly now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Why was it silly then? I'm not 5'9" with curves and flowing hair, so it's impossible for me to get it on with a good-looking guy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Wow. Do you resent me? You're the quirky, hardworking sophomore and I'm the evil cheerleader who steals boys? If you're not getting any, it's not my fault.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Should we get the one with the panda on it or the bird?  Good choice. Pandas eat only bamboo, they know nothing about cereal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>Woman</speaker><content>Your little girl is adorable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Thanks. She keeps me very busy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>Woman</speaker><content>You and her mom must be very proud.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Her mother… died in childbirth. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>We're growing cultures now, but she looked clean, and there was no telltale smell. I'm guessing the lump was just an air bubble that got trapped in the mold.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>You bandaged her up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I threw in some stitches, too. Just wanted to make her look her best. Do you want me to put her in her chair?  Henry?  Call a code!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You looking at the apartment with those or the transit of Mercury?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>If night comes, you'll be thanking me.  They're seeking heat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He's an accountant. How late do you think he's going to party?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>I bought jar to pee in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>We heard crackles in Henry's lungs. We diuresed him, but he still needs oxygen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Echo shows normal heart function. Could be high output failure from anemia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Hematocrit was rock normal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-9"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>Say "mushroom," charge $2. Say "truffle," charge $5. Is that the man who wants to marry hooker? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Probably. But he's not the one we're after. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-11"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Should we ask?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-12"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Nope.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh! How rude of me not to situate you. I'm doing Emily a favor. We're going to track her fiancé until Dominika can seduce and expose him as the lying cheater I need him to be.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-14"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I'm guessing she didn't ask for this favor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh, you know, the noblest gifts are the ones we give anonymously.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-16"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Crackles are nonspecific. Hypoxia plus bleeding could indicate D.I.C. or some other—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No neurological symptoms? I knew your bleeding heart would bring you around. Too bad it's also taking you off the market. And by market, I mean Chase. Come on, buck up, Chase. There's always Park. Unless… How did band practice go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-18"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Does she look like she's lying?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-20"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Kind of.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-21"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Popo needed a ride to the doctor, and my mom couldn't, so—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-22"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're terrified of dating because… a previous relationship ended because your latent rage made you vicious in arguments. Or—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-23"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Or reincarnation. In a past life, she was Anne Boleyn.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-24"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Interesting. Taub feels confident enough to turn the spotlight on himself. It's almost as if he wants me to ask… what's her name?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-25"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Wendy Jacobson. 33, Brown grad, family therapist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-26"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Nice choice. Since you got two families to "therapize."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-27"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>First date we didn't discuss everything important—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-28"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So it was just a one-night stand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-29"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You're wrong. I actually like her. I'm going to see her again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-30"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Mazel tov. Great relationships often start with snap decisions aimed at proving me wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-31"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Air bubble in the doll could mean the silicone is degrading. If he hailed some particles…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-32"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Silicone deposition. That could work. Start him on plasmapheresis. Now, turning to Adams, my theory is tripartite—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-33"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Want to hear my thesis? It's kind of interesting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-34"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>No man comes out. But old naked lady in 3-C is eating whole block of cheese.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>Will this hurt?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>No, you might feel a little cold, though.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>Ah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>No, no, it's-it's good that she's here. Molly, I'd like you to meet Amy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>I'm serious. I know it seems a little strange, but she means a lot to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>But you just got here. Sit down.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>Molly</speaker><content>Yeah, but I-I said that I only had a second. Enjoy the handouts. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Listen, um, I have to admit something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>Wendy</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Her mom isn't dead. We're separated.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>Wendy</speaker><content>Uh-huh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>Wendy</speaker><content>Was that a different baby?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>Wendy</speaker><content>That was a different baby.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Like this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>You're talking?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>It's not all I can do. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>Amy, there are doctors…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Shh…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>I don't know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>Amy</speaker><content>Just put your hands on me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Pushing lorazepam. If it wasn't neurological before, it sure is now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Right upper quadrant's distended. He's hallucinating because his liver's failing.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Elevated transaminases confirm liver failure. We'll have to put him on the transplant list in a couple days.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>It's clearly not the silicone. Could be vasculitis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Serologies were negative.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, if you want Adams to hear, you might want to not stand so conspicuously far away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I'm making coffee. And sometimes, I date co-workers. Like everyone else on the planet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Hepatic fibrosis. If it damaged his platelets, it'd explain the bleeding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Unexpected. I actually thought you might agree with my theory. Because that would mean nothing's your fault. You fell into relationships based on proximity. Of course they failed.  But I guess I was wrong. You picked perfect women. You just screwed it up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>How about all five of us live together and the $7,000 sex doll? It'll solve all our hang-ups.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>$7,000?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Adams suggests that we all sleep together, and your issue is high prices?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-11"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Pretty sure she was joking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yes, I'm 99% sure that you're right, but I would never forgive myself—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-13"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Those dolls are only $5,000. He must have had it customized somehow.  Oh, like, you didn't check the website?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I guess we don't need to ask how your dating life is going.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-15"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I was curious.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-16"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Hepatic fibrosis wouldn't cause difficulty breathing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-17"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>It would if liver failure opened pulmonary av shunts.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Fibrosis fits. Start the patient on steroids and find out how he pimped his ride.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-19"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-20"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Because I don't know the answer. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-21"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Hey. Foosball?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-22"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Can't. Marriage to destroy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-23"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Okay… </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-24"><speaker>House</speaker><content>"Okay" as in passive-aggressive reverse psychology? Or as in depressed resignation</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-25"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>"Okay" as in I changed my mind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-26"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Expand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-27"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Oh, it's morally reprehensible and bound to fail, but in a weird way, it's a step forward. This thing with Emily.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-28"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Contract.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-29"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>It's real without being real. It's a long-term relationship that can't actually hurt you. It's, um… a stepping stone. It means you want more.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-30"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So, passive-aggressive reverse psychology. Got it. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Try not to come on too strong, okay? Just get to know him a little. Ease into it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>Domonika</speaker><content>Why would I ease?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>True. You could just walk up and stick your hand down his pants, but I heard there's a middle step.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>Men want to have sex.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>Harris</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>I'm Jennifer, new to marketing department. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>Harris</speaker><content>Harris. Accounts receivable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>Oh, interesting. Do you want to get out of here and have sex?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>Harris</speaker><content>Uh, sure.  You know, I got 45 minutes left on my lunch break.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>Mm-hmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-12"><speaker>Harris</speaker><content>Where you wanna go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-13"><speaker>Harris</speaker><content>Cheating? What are you talking about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Why, I hope you're speaking out of some deep kind of moral relativism because—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-15"><speaker>Harris</speaker><content>Who are you people?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're not Emily's fiancée.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-17"><speaker>Harris</speaker><content>Emily's my sister.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>We called the company that made Amy. They said they modeled her after some photos you sent them.  Who is she?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>We met last Christmas. She's a yoga instructor. Totally different from me. She-she loved Chopin, hated Indian food. She changed entire my life for 17 weeks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>My husband cheated on me… with a girl he met on the plane coming back from our honeymoon. It's not easy to get past things like that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>She wasn't unfaithful. She didn't betray me. She just… she just wasn't in love with me. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I know Amy's not going to break your heart. But she's also not going to change your life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>Sorry. What's happening to me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Is your neck stiff?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I think you have meningitis.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>Emily</speaker><content>I'm not leaving the business. I'm just leaving you. I didn't want you to feel bad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So let me get this straight. I'm being dumped by a hooker… who's worried about my feelings?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>Emily</speaker><content>You're married.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Half your clients are married. And you're a hooker.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>Emily</speaker><content>My other guys sneak around, but you'll take me into the bedroom while your wife's in the next room. That's just… mean.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh, my God. The marriage, it's a sham. The only really thing about it is the green card she's going to get at the end of it. So, if you want to get the meter running…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>Emily</speaker><content>It's still mean.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's not a marriage. It's a felony.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>Emily</speaker><content>I've seen how she looks at you when you're together. Trust me. She likes you. And I've seen how you look at her. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Fever's up 105. He's not responding to meds. At this rate, he'll be dead by the time we get the cultures back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Spinal fluid was full of white cells. Meningitis could be carcinomatous.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Cytology showed nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>An amoebic infection would cause fever and meningitis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>But not liver failure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>It could if he had a clot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>How could amoebas get past his cribriform plate? He went swimming in a frozen lake in New Jersey?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Adams said his ex-girlfriend was a yoga instructor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-9"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Maybe he sprained his chakras.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-10"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Yoga nuts are way more likely to be into alternative medicine. He has this little weird teapot in his house.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-11"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Um, little. Weird. Teapot-ish.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Like that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-13"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-14"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>You think he drinks some sort of toxic herbal tea?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yes… if by "tea," you mean salted tap water. And by "drink," you mean poured up his nose. His girlfriend didn't just leave him with a broken heart. She left him with a neti pot. It's an Indian method of… clearing the sinuses during allergy season. Also known as now.  The distilled water can act as a snot flushing system. With tap water, it can act as an amoeba delivery system to the fluids around the brain. Start him on metronidazole. If he's lucky, he'll get to see his plastic children walk down the aisle. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>My neck feels much better.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Your fever's gone, and your liver function's almost back to normal. You should be able to go home soon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>I'm going to have some hospital bills to pay. I don't suppose used sex dolls go for anything online.  Dr. Adams? Can I get your email?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>What for?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>I just thought maybe we could see each other again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>No, I know. It's a professionalism thing, but you won't be my doctor when I get out of here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>It's not that. It's—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>What is it? You said I should change my life. You were talking about yourself, too. I know you were.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Henry, I-I think you should ask Molly out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-10"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>I should have known this would happen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-11"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>You're a good guy, Henry. You deserve more than a doll. Promise me you'll keep trying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-12"><speaker>Henry</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Date tonight? So she can't deal. There's someone out there who can. You just got to find her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I'd love to prove House wrong, but… I ruined my marriage, broke two people's hearts, had two kids who are always going to wonder why I didn't love their mommy enough. It's better if I just… focus on what I do have.  Give that band guy a call.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I'm not that good at guitar. Or flirting or small talk. I'm not as pretty as Adams, I have stuffy clothes, and I hate my hair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Adams works 80 hours a week fixing bunions on hobos because she can't face getting to know someone new. Trust me. You find a boyfriend, she'll be the jealous one. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>See you tomorrow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Do you…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Want to get a drink?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Oh, I… It's just, um… I think it's time for a change.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Yeah. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>No, mom. I'm still at work. I'll be home in a couple hours. Love you too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>Micah</speaker><content>Ready?  One, two, three, four.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>♪♫ They say we're young and we don't know, we won't find out until we grow</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>Micah</speaker><content>♪♫ Well, I don't know if all that's true 'cause you got me and baby I got you</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>I fix blender.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So I see.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-7"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>I had fun seducing hooker's fake fiancée. Sorry it didn't work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, I thought I'd take a break from the whole hooker thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-9"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>I think maybe you need milk shake. Is pistachio.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm… gonna go to bed. See you tomorrow.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>