<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>
<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Penza</speaker><content>Clear!  Charging! Clear!  Okay, I'm calling it. Time of death… 8:32.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Treiber</speaker><content>Hello…  Diana. Shall we?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Treiber</speaker><content>LV tear is within a zone of fresh tissue necrosis, implicating a recent myocardial infarction as the instigating event.  Unfortunately, the medical records show that Dr. Penza never suspected heart disease, instead giving steroids for an erroneous diagnosis of asthma, thereby causing the fatal tear.  I suggest these findings warrant further investigation into Dr. Penza's standard of care for this patient, making this my… third such recommendation regarding Dr. Penza this year. Concluding autopsy with examination of the brain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Treiber</speaker><content>I'm cold.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Yes, it's mine. And yes, I know that I can't drive stick. And no, I don't care that I parked in a handicapped spot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>"Staring death in the face has changed my life." What a cliché.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>The cliché is to lead a more meaningful life. I've taken a holy vow to lead a less meaningful one. I've spent my life caring, giving, and searching for the profound. Now it's time for selfishness, indifference, and embracing the shallow. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Your scan's in three days. Tell me this isn't just you killing time until you find out if your cancer's gonna kill it for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I just paid $75,000 for a ridiculously impractical car, the depth of shallowness. And tomorrow, I'm driving it to Cleveland to meet my boyhood crush.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The years have not been kind to David Cassidy. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Julie Christie. Dr. Zhivago, Shampoo. I was precocious. She's opening some kind of charity animal clinic or something. I'm neglecting my patients to fulfill a silly fantasy. Textbook selfishness and indifference.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Or you've made sure that your patients are well-covered, the car is a rental, and while waiting to get Julie Christie's autograph, you'll adopt a puppy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I don't even care whether you believe me or not.  Indifference.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>He tried to cut open his own skull. Head CT and tox screen were clean.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Interesting. Cotard delusion. Also known as "walking corpse syndrome." Disconnect in the amygdala convinces you that you're secretly dead. Case solved.  Rendering it… What's the past tense of "interesting?"</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>No prior history of mental illness, and before you say it was caused by antivirals, I've already ruled that out. Plus, Cotard's doesn't explain the paresthesia in his hand. Also… Treiber won't let any other doctor near him. He trusts your work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>How's Wilson doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Wilson's scan is at the end of the week. If his kick-ass chemo shrunk the tumor to an operable size, he'll live. If it didn't, he'll die.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>That must be very hard. Is there anything we can do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Other than the prayer circle, what is there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Patient's AST is high. Psychosis could be brought on by liver failure. Maybe Hep C?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I don't hate him. He hates me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>He hates all doctors, and it's mutual.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>He only hates the ones that screw up. And you. And they only hate Treiber because he finds their mistakes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Mistakes are a wee bit easier to find on a dead patient, a distinction he fails to recognize. He's a rat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Who makes the hospital a safer place by keeping doctors accountable and focused. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>What if he got something from a cadaver?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>He handles a lot of 'em. You suggesting we DDX them all?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-16"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>No, just his last one.  She had bad knees. She used dimethyl sulfoxide for joint pain. Current from the defibrillator could've converted it to dimethyl sulfate. When Treiber cut into her, her blood released toxic fumes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-17"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Everyone in the basement would be sick.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-18"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>His lungs are fine. Blood clots make more sense. One in his hand explains the paresthesia, one in his carotid explains the psychotic episode.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Treiber</speaker><content>I know House doesn't like seeing his patients, but doesn't a fellow doctor rate an exception?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Psychosis appears to be intermittent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Treiber</speaker><content>Just snapped out of it long enough to ask if House actually ordered this test.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Don't worry. We're simply carrying out his direct orders.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Treiber</speaker><content>Right. Forgot. It's what you were hired to do. Which is fine, his diagnostic error metric is .17 compared to the hospital average of .32.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>You actually think you can quantify the value of every doctor?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Treiber</speaker><content>Someone should. And since I'm the only one who sees everything—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Right, you were hired to diagnose people after they're already dead.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Every doctor, every diagnosis, every treatment, every result. It's pretty impressive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>It's pretty Orwellian. All written in his secret code.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>He has to keep it confidential.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Just like the Wannsee conference.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>The "Big Brother" metaphor wasn't pointed enough for you? You had to throw in Hitler?  A couple years ago, he noticed a link in child deaths, and it's completely changed hospital policies all over—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I get it. Treiber is nerd king. The more people we kill, the more lives he saves. Test is negative for dimethyl sulfate, her blood is not toxic. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Then we should look for toxic exposure from something else.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You really think the hospital is idiotic enough to issue toxic supplies?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Have you seen his tools?  Treiber doesn't always use hospital-issue.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Then he's the idiot?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>No, but I don't want to explain that assumption to House.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Thought we'd make it a road trip. '80s music, junk food, beer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I have a dental appointment. That I'm going to make now. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Ah. I'll let you drive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Not worth listening to you whine about your feelings and fears for three days.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>It's not gonna happen. I've taken a vow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>People don't change. You are a person, ergo, pass.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Yes, that's why I brought this.  20 CCs of propofol. You can accompany me willingly, or I will, when you least expect it, inject the contents of this vial into your bloodstream. The fall might result in a concussion, or fractures, or you might get lucky and simply wake up somewhere near Allentown with a nasty headache. The choice is yours, and in case you've forgotten, I am indifferent. We leave tomorrow morning at 8:00 a.m.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>No clots.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>No gas.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>But we found enough of this…  …to reanimate the entire morgue. He's jacked on caffeine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Stimulant psychosis. How many times do I have to solve this case?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>So all we have to do is hydrate and observe him for 24 hours.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Treiber</speaker><content>My abdomen! It's my abdomen!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>It's just the effects of withdrawal. The pain is normal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Treiber</speaker><content>No! No! This isn't right!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Abdominal pain and distention means we were wrong about stimulant psychosis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>It could be coexistent problems. He might just have an obstruction.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>You know what House says about coincidences. I didn't feel any masses when I examined him, and no bowel sounds.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Where's House?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>He hasn't come in yet, and neither has Wilson. I've already tried them three times.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Here we go again. Diabetes could cause nerve damage in his hand and guts, and—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Except his glucose levels are normal, and he probably would've mentioned he was a diabetic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>What about ulcerative colitis? Earlier attacks caused thrombosis—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>We already looked for clots, and there was no blood in his stool.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Try him again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Wherever they are, they don't want to be disturbed.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>My trip, my itinerary. We have to cover 300 miles today to be there with plenty of time to catch Julie by 4:00 tomorrow. And that thing I said about letting you drive, I lied.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm–I'm impressed. Not by that. But by your real effort to maintain the facade. It's been almost an hour, and there's been no mention of the elephant in the car.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Well, I declined the elephant option.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Uh-huh. In three days, you're gonna find out if you live or die. You don't want to talk about it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>No, but obviously you do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So, we're gonna talk about it, but because I want to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I am neither talking about it, nor talking about not talking about it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You are hard-wired to talk about it. It's how you cope, it's who you are.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Yeah, well, from now on, I'm not me. I'm… I'm… Kyle Calloway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I thought your porn name was Rusty Packard.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Kyle is roguish, carefree, and shares no qualities with James Wilson.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Can Kyle drive stick?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Treiber won't let us do anything without House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>House just took himself off the case. You said no bowel sounds when you examined him. "No" like diminished, or none at all?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>None.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You think it's an intussusception?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>If it is, it could mean cancer's behind everything. Let's get a plain film of his abdomen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Only if he knows it wasn't.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You want to lie to a guy whose favorite pastime is getting doctors fired.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We're adults with advanced medical training, not children left alone with scissors. It's one X-ray. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If we had a phone, we could've found somewhere a little less charming.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>If we had a phone, you'd be making calls, downloading porn, and playing Angry Birds. This trip is about me, and I like this place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>This is not about you not wanting me to have a phone. You're weak. You knew that you'd backslide and spend your time talking to teary ex-wives and your parents, trying to make them feel better about you being sick.  Bacon burger with fries looks awful. I'll have that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'll have the Big One.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Waitress</speaker><content>You sure? It's $79.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Unless I finish it in an hour, in which case, it's free.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'm hungry. And an iced tea, please.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>This place doesn't take credit cards.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>My meal is going to be free, and I'm going to be inducted into the wall of pain. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Belly film was normal. No sign of an intussusception or any other obstruction.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Trieber</speaker><content>House says it's there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Sometimes House is wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Treiber</speaker><content>Run my bowel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>That's serious surgery. General anesthesia, long recovery…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We can do a contrast enema if you need more proof.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Treiber</speaker><content>I have drawers filled with people who had clean scans. I know how easy it is to miss something unless you use your own hands and eyes; Run my bowel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We'll let House know how you feel.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>Treiber</speaker><content>How I feel is twisted in white-hot agony. His orders were to look for an intussusception. Until you actually do that, I refuse any other tests.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Fine. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Uh, no. Not fine. We need to talk—</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Come on, you got this! You got this! Come on! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Waitress</speaker><content>25 seconds.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You've got this. Come on, home stretch, Kyle, home stretch!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>Waitress</speaker><content>15 seconds!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Now, don't chew, just swallow. Just muscle it down!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>Waitress</speaker><content>Six, five… four…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>Waitress</speaker><content>Three, two, one…Time!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yes! Yes! Oh, you magnificent bastard! </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>Treiber</speaker><content>No hard feelings, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You'll find out when you wake up. If you really think I'm a good doctor, why do you treat me like an idiot?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>Treiber</speaker><content>It's not because you lack talent. It's 'cause you've wasted it. Did you know I applied to be a fellow with House the same year as you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>Treiber</speaker><content>Quit my other program, relocated, broke up with my girlfriend. Then your father made a call, and suddenly you had the spot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>That was almost ten years ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>Treiber</speaker><content>Do you know what I could've done after even three years with House? Gone to the CDC, W.H.O. Started a diagnostics department someplace they'd never even heard of such a thing. You've been given everything. Looks, talent, my future. Nine years later, look what you've done with it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Ah…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Must be nice to be puking for the old-fashioned reasons.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Ah. I'm glad I did it. You see those people out there cheering for me? I was a hero. For one fleeting moment, for an incredibly stupid reason, for a bunch of morons</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>How long do you think you'll work for House?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>As long as he lets me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>When House was in prison, you worked at Mercy in plastics, right? Know what I did? Surfed. For nine months.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Yes, and if I didn't have two daughters and alimony, I might have done the same.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>A fellowship's supposed to train you to stand on your own. Foreman's Dean of the hospital, Cameron's head of emergency medicine in Chicago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>And Kutner and Amber are dead, and Thirteen is having sweet, sapphic sex on some island.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Look at this. The small intestine. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Is it an intussusception?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>He hasn't checked his voicemail.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Or his email.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>It's been almost 24 hours. Shouldn't we call Foreman or the police? I think this makes him a fugitive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Intermittent porphyria.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>He's in the middle of an attack. The longer we wait to treat with hemin, the more damage it causes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>The longer we wait to tell him House isn't running the case, the more damage that causes. It's fraud.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>It's only an issue if we're wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>It's more than one X-ray. More than exploratory surgery, even. This is a drug that will damage him if you're wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Same principle. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I want a threesome.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Shouldn't we try a twosome first?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Two women.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I know they're probably overrated, and I'll probably be gravely disappointed, but I want one anyway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, you don't.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Well, Kyle wants one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Kyle's only one day old. He doesn't know what he wants. I don't want to think about consequences. I don't want to think about — I don't want to think about anything. I just want to… do. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>okay. I need you to do exactly what I tell you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>Treiber</speaker><content>Porphyria?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I know the anesthesia makes it hard to focus, but we need to start you on hemin right away.  House believes very strongly. This is the right call.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>Treiber</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>This thing is peeling.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, that is the cost of cowardice. Should've gone for the real thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I feel like I'm cheating.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>A, it is only cheating if you don't have cancer, and B, it's Wednesday afternoon. Pickings are slim, and more importantly, sober. The cancer cut is the surest way to the pity pooty party.  One down, one to go.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>She's empathetic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Gave me a cancer rate.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>No. I have never paid for sex in my life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You still haven't. It's my treat. It's either that, or you find two very open-minded women to fall in love with you in the next hour. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Bartender seems nice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Seems female.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>Waitress</speaker><content>Want something to eat?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>My friend is dying of cancer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-13"><speaker>Bartender</speaker><content>Oh, you poor thing. It took my mother two years ago. But you can't give up hope. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He's pretty much resigned. Just wants to go out with a bang. And another pun, what time do you get off? </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Pleural effusions. It's not porphyria.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We're gonna need to put in a chest tube.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>Treiber</speaker><content>I wanna talk to House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>We'll tell him exactly what's happening.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>Treiber</speaker><content>I wanna talk to him!  I want House.  Where is House? Where is he? Where's House?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We don't know.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You didn't have to sleep out here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Apparently they left a long time ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So, how was it? Was the amateur as good as the pro?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>It was confusing. Perfunctory. A bit sad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Never mind.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>And exactly what I needed.  Thank you.  You feel like buying me breakfast? One of them stole my wallet.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Porphyria was a legitimate call.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Until the pleural effusions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We've done everything House would've done if he'd been here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Fine. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I didn't say you were off the case. Sit down.  Ordered a cardiac MRI.  Enlargement of the left ventricle suggests an infiltrative disease.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>It's sarcoidosis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>We'll start him on corticosteroids and do a cardiac biopsy to confirm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I disagree. I was wrong about the porphyria, but I wasn't wrong about the nervous system. It's a prion disease. That's why his symptoms have progressed so rapidly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>It's possible he was exposed and didn't know it. Brains are often stored and not tested until weeks after autopsy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-10"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Treiber's too good to not take the right precautions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-11"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Maybe the problem is he thinks the same thing. His job's built on the premise that doctors make mistakes; That includes him. We should do a brain biopsy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-12"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>In his condition?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-13"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Then we biopsy the brains in the morgue. Find the one that exposed him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-14"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>It's a needle in a haystack.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-15"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>There's four of us. Come on, we can at least start him on amphotericin to halt the progress while you do your heart biopsy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-16"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>No, we can't. Amphotericin plus the contrast dye for the biopsy would overwhelm his kidneys. We have to choose one or the other.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-17"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Biopsy his heart.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Wallets go in the minibar freezer. If there's no minibar, the toilet tank. I've got exactly…  $20 left.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'm sorry, I wasn't familiar with hooker protocol. We can use your credit cards.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, we won't. I'm still on probation. Leaving the state without permission will really P.O. my P.O.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Doesn't matter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>We have enough gas to get to Julie. I don't care about anything else.  What this time?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Just wondering how long this can last.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You're still hoping that I'm gonna wake up and admit that Kyle Calloway is just some lame excuse to have some naughty thrills aren't you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm actually hoping you won't. I like Kyle. </content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Oh, come on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Whoo!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Whoo-hoo! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>House.  You okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Come on. We got 20 bucks to go 11 miles.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Why aren't you answering your pages?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Busy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>The biopsy showed fibrosis in his cardiac muscle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>So it's not a prion disease.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>It means Foreman was wrong too. He wants everyone to meet in his office to DDX.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>So he can tell us all it's an infection?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Interesting. Or maybe you should consider not being such a baby.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Are you trying to cure him or discredit him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Treiber can only see me as not House. Foreman too. And they're not wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-10"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>So you're not coming upstairs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-11"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>No. And when this case is over, I'm quitting.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>He's not quitting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>He already called other hospitals. Treiber did get under his skin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>He'll get over it. Fibrosis has to be a response to an infection.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Chase said you'd say that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>We'll test the biopsy samples for viruses and start him on antivirals.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You're not even gonna talk to Chase?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>He didn't leave after he got stabbed in the heart. I think we're okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Either you're right, and your friend is just really upset, or you're wrong, and he's come at this calmly and rationally, and you're about to lose a good doctor. Either way… </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>This is Oubliette, Ohio. Buses don't run here after 1968.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Ina said there's a bus every 15 minutes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Ina is living in Alzheimersville.  Been here at least half an hour.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>Ina</speaker><content>Naples, Florida. Ben and I have a beautiful three-bedroom condo. All on the one floor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You're waiting for a bus to Naples? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>Ina</speaker><content>Comes every 15 minutes. Ben'll be wondering where his dinner is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Cab.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Bus isn't coming, Ina. But this cab is going to Naples.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-9"><speaker>Ina</speaker><content>Ben'll be getting awfully hungry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>We'll tell the cabbie to call the cops. They'll come pick her up, take care of her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-12"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Then I'll stay with her until they do.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Find anything?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You've got everybody worried about your quitting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You here as my boss or my friend?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>If I was here as your boss, you'd be suspended by now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I've learned a lot here. Enough to run my own team. It's time I moved on. Unfortunately, that's how I felt last year. And the year before that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Maybe there's a reason you haven't left. You need structure. And support. Somebody else calling the shots.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You didn't come down here as my boss or my friend. You came down as House. You're trying to insult me into making a decision.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>We've both seen it work. Either you rise to the challenge and quit, or you stay. As a team member.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Dr. Treiber! Dr. Treiber.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>He stopped responding when I was changing his I.V. bag.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Peter, open your eyes.  Coma.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Treiber's comatose.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>All brains on deck.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Where should we start? We think you might be right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I'm not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>You couldn't have gone through all of these.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Don't have to.  Treiber's reports are thorough to a fault. His methods are fastidious. The answer isn't down here.  Treiber didn't miss anything. We did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>So what? Psychosis, abdominal pain, pleural effusions, enlarged heart, coma.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-8"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Autoimmune, maybe Goodpasture's.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-9"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Kidneys are fine. Vasculitis?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-10"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>No fever.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-11"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Lymphoma?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-12"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Would've seen it on the heart biopsy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-13"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Soap. It's the soap. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh, God, here it comes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>As always. All I wanted was some meaningless fun, and I couldn't even last three days.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I had the chance to fulfill a lifelong dream.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I swear, I will jump out of this moving bus if you don't shut up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>But instead, I sat with a sad, old woman for 1 1/2 hours who forgot I existed three seconds after she left. And the stupidest thing. I never even had a crush on Julie Christie.  In 12th grade I was madly in love with Melanie Robbins, who happened to look exactly like Julie Christie in Dr. Zhivago. And she really liked me. Played spades every lunch period in Mr. Charlton's classroom. But of course, there was this other guy. A great guy. Very popular. He had a car. He had a band, a mustache…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Kyle would've ditched that sad, old woman from the bus stop. Probably would've ditched me too. I can live without Kyle.  Snowball? </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>Treiber</speaker><content>Guess this isn't heaven.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We found out who screwed up. You. It was your industrial-strength antibacterial soap.  The additional triclosan does two things well: Kills MRSA and makes your thyroid look stupid. It thinks the triclosan is a real hormone and closes up shop. Excessive use over time combined with excessive use of this led to hypothyroidism. Which went undiagnosed until it presented with psychosis. When the ER put you on the sedatives, it kicked you into myxedema crisis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>Treiber</speaker><content>Don't know that I ever would've thought of that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>House told us to look for irony.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-5"><speaker>Treiber</speaker><content>Hey. This wasn't House.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="34"><utterance uid="34-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>My locker key.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I'll give you your own team.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Thanks. But it's time to step out of the shadow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>It's about time.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="35"><utterance uid="35-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Any news?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Not yet. You come here so I could talk you out of it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I came to say thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's been fun.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Fun?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Sounded pithier than… "We've shared a variety of situations."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Why did you let him go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Legal loophole. 13th Amendment. Abraham Lincoln may have looked great in that hat, but his labor policies…ß </content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>