<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>
<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Collins</speaker><content>Good afternoon, Cedarville!  It is my distinct honor to present our annual community service award to one of our most outstanding citizens. Now, many of you may recognize him as Coach Bob of our champion little league team. And some of you may know him as the treasurer of our Harvest Scholarship Fund.  But I know that all of you know him as the guy that owns the only gas station in town.  Bob Harris, get on up here with that beautiful family of yours!  Bob Harris, folks! Bob, your community activism, charity work, and character represent the finest Cedarville has to offer.  Please accept this on behalf of all of us and know that we love you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Cindy</speaker><content>Are you all right? Bob?  You're crushing me! Wake up!  I think you're having a heart attack. I'm gonna call the ambulance!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content> No. Just drive me to the hospital.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>As the new dean of medicine, I'd like to personally welcome all of our new employees and ask, why the hell do you want to come back?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Tired of surfing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>He hasn't changed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>And neither has the job, right? We still get to do crazy crap?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Save people's lives instead of just their noses?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>About that… about the crazy stuff?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Here we go. He's gone from ally to enemy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>He has no choice. He's the boss now. He has to be professional. He has to base his decisions on what's best for the entire hospital. We can't take it personally.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Couldn't have said it better myself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You did. I'm just reading the notes on your desk.  He also wants us to spy for him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Not spy. I'm trying to keep House out of prison. To do that, I need to know what he's doing and planning.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Chase and Taub</speaker><content> Spy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Come on, guys. I am your boss. You do have to treat me appropriately. But it doesn't have to be awkward and weird. Outside of work, I still consider us all friends.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I'm glad you feel that way, because I do have a favor to ask. I told House I couldn't come back until next week. He said he understood completely and that I was fired. So…  Since I have my kids for the next two days, I need a babysitter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-15"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>No!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Male patient went into v-fib but shows no signs of heart disease</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What was he doing when his heart decided to do the mambo?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>He said he was at work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're late.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>According to my calendar, I'm a week early.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Beard's a nice touch. Lets everyone know that you're not a teenage girl.  Oh, now, you two make a cute couple.  And you two…  It's not important.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Dr. Park.  You're a lot taller than I thought you'd be.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>And I look forward to working with you as well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He's lying, not just Taub… the patient. These abrasions on his knees… they're minty fresh… about ten hours old.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>He got them playing flag football.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He said he got them playing flag football. I'm sure that's true if "flag" is a euphemism for "penis" and "football" is a euphemism for "entering a vagina."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Why lie about it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Everybody lies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Speaking of which, how are your two baby girls?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Wow, twins… congratulations.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Awkward!  He knocked up two different women at the same time… At least he thinks he did. You have them DNA tested yet?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Why would I? They look just like me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>But they will grow. Find out what else he's lying about. Do an exercise test… see if you can get him to go back into v-fib again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>But we could end up causing another cardiac arrest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-20"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Hopefully. Then we'll know what set it off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-21"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>He means it's better to do it here where we can revive him than have it happen somewhere else.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-22"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The prodigal son has returned.  Now, if you'll excuse me, I have to go slaughter a fatted calf for lunch.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>I told you, I was sitting at my desk when the attack happened.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>These rug burns are from last night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>We think you were having sex, but memory loss could also be a symptom. Maybe we should ask your wife.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>Don't. I-I did something stupid last night, but it was a one-time thing. You have no idea how bad I feel about it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Your guilt is between you and your wife. We just need to know what happened.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>I was having sex at a motel when I started to feel light-headed. Next thing I knew, I was laying on my back. I could barely breathe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Denise</speaker><content> Is everything all right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We'd like to perform an exercise test, re-create the stress that may have caused his symptoms.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Denise</speaker><content>He was sitting at his desk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>It's his heart we're worried about. The test will monitor its rhythm so we can check for any abnormalities.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content> I spent a month in solitary. You don't think I can keep this up all day?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I have a headache. Could you just lower your voice?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Chase and Taub are back!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You want me to pick up an ice-cream cake?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I also think that Taub has brought his little Taubettes into work with him today.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Why would he do that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Because I didn't give him time to do anything else. Then I started wondering, who'd be sappy enough to watch them for him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>They're not here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What? I just came for a chat with a friend. What's that I smell, friend?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I understand your confusion. I was eating a baby for lunch, and…  I have a massive migraine. Will you please just go away?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You should probably lie down and rest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Yeah. I was trying to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Oh! There is one more thing.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>He's in too good of a shape. We need to get him to the point he was at last night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Well, don't look at me. But if you want to…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Cute.  I didn't mean physical stress.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Don't you guys think this is irresponsible? It's like you getting two women pregnant at the same time. I just mean the part about the odds of it happening. They had to be incredibly high. And if we induce v-fib, odds say that we'll be able to revive him. But there's always a chance we can't.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>It's extreme and reckless. That's House. You get used to it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Or I fire you. Look what I found…  Kiddie-winkies! I wonder who they belong to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> Give me my kids.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No. I genuinely wonder who they belong to. I need a DNA sample. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I'm not letting you DNA test my kids.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Already did. This swab's for you.  Fine. If you don't mind paying a fortune in child support for some other guy's kids, no skin cells off my cheek.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>His heart rate's finally elevating.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Denise</speaker><content> Dr. Chase said you had something to tell me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We were talking about how you got the abrasions on your knees… the flag football game.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>Oh, um… Yeah, honey, I'm gonna need you to let the guys know I'm not gonna be able to play on Saturday. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Denise</speaker><content>The whole town knows that you're in the hospital. I wouldn't worry about it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>That's not what you wanted to tell her. You said the game wasn't typical. Something happened that you were upset about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>I don't understand. What are you t…  I don't f… I don't feel very w…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>Denise</speaker><content>What's happening?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>It's not his heart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-20"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I know. He's having a seizure.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>There wasn't any abnormal electrical activity in his E.K.G. when his seizure occurred. It wasn't caused by a v-fib.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content> We still can't rule it out. His E.K.G. from the E.R. documented…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Myocarditis… viral infection weakening the wall muscles. We need to biopsy his heart to confirm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Myocarditis wouldn't cause a seizure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Could be genetic… Brugada Syndrome.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh, my God. Two prodigal sons. Come on. Let's hug it out. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You really like the idea, or you just want to grab some hair for a DNA test?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's a stupid idea. We would have seen evidence of Brugada in the E.K.G.  You know, this is… this is just messing with my feng shui here. What about over there? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>A pheochromocytoma.  Excess adrenaline can cause heart problems and… seizures.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Boring!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I'm sorry. I thought I was here to treat the patients, not entertain you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Would it hurt to do both?  Oh, this is much better! I said it was boring. I didn't say it was wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>So I'm right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Nope. You're wrong. Photic epilepsy… it's equally boring, but it has the advantage of possibly being right. Give him an E.E.G. to confirm.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>If you ever hear me mention anything about wanting kids, please feel free to punch me in the liver.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>It's like Satan's alarm clock.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content> What's House up to? He hasn't asked me for anything. He's been incredibly well-behaved. He's doing his clinic hours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>That is a sign of concern.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>And you know him as well as I do. He needs to constantly establish he's the Alpha dog.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>He's got his team back. He's got his office back. He's got everything he needs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You really believe that… He's content? I don't want to let House sabotage himself by sabotaging me, and I need your guidance and your trust to do that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> No, no, no. Cuddy had a problem with House, she came to me. Wanted to vent… me. How did that turn out? You have a problem with House, deal with it, or find someone else who can.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I'm sorry about earlier, but we needed to provoke a reaction.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>It worked. I can barely look her in the eyes anymore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I'd want my husband to tell me the truth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Sure. You'll feel better, and she'll feel what… devastated, betrayed? Heartbroken. Do you really want to do that to her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>No. But I can't live like this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>But she can. All set.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>All right, we need you to sit back and try to relax. Just look at the light.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>What exactly are they building back there?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>A dream.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>The E.E.G. didn't show any abnormal brain activity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>He doesn't have photic epilepsy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I know, because he has a pheochromocytoma.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>You said I was wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You were wrong not to rule out epilepsy first. That only takes a couple of hours. Finding a tumor that's flushing adrenaline through his system is gonna take all night. Monitor his brain activity, start a continuous urine test and blood draws every two hours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I can't! I have my kids! Wilson's leaving in, like, minutes!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Chase and Adams can do the test.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>For the massage bed. You and Park are checking the motel he was bumping uglies at for environmental factors.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>He couldn't find a babysitter. Get over it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> You're gonna get us killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content> She thinks I'm a prostitute on her turf. Showing weakness is what gets you killed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> Why would she think you're a prostitute?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content> I'm in a dump with a guy almost twice my age. What else is she gonna think?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>How old do you think I am?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>So who cheated on you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>We just met. Don't you think it's a little early to be dragging up our baggage in front of each other?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Who says I have baggage?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I know when House went to prison, you quit medicine. — You don't do that unless…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I didn't quit. I took a vacation. I knew when he got out, I'd get my job back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>House didn't even know he was coming back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I had faith.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Now, that has baggage stamped all over it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Seizure activity?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>No. One of the sensors came loose.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I'll fix it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-12"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>What is it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-13"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Not a pheochromocytoma.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Our patient now has a mass in his neck, and his body temp's been rising over the last three hours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Where is the construction crew?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, I'm not gonna make them work day and night. So I chose night. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>And his urine and blood tests didn't show any evidence of an adrenaline-secreting tumor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Meningitis. We can do a lumbar puncture to confirm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> Sorry. I had to drop my kids off at day care across town. What'd I miss?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>It's not meningitis. His neck isn't stiff, and his mental status is normal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He's only guessing. I'm talking to Taub. He can't say "my kids" until he lets me test them. Tell me about the love shack where he cheated on his bride.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Quarters came in handy. My kids loved the massage bed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Lab tests show the bed tested positive for, uh, semen, vaginal secretions, saliva, and fecal matter, both human and animal. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Probably want to boil the kids for a couple hours when you get home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-12"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>The bathroom also tested positive for five different types of pathogenic bacteria.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Fusobacterium necrophorum was one of them. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-14"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Yeah. How'd you know?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The bulge in his neck. The bacteria colonized his parapharyngeal space, moved into his jugular vein, causing a thrombus… Lemierre's Syndrome. Treat with amoxicillin and clavulanic acid. Take out the clot before it moves to his lungs and kills him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You have at least a trillion cells. You're gonna misplace one of them eventually.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>I have to tell my wife the truth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>There's plenty of time for that after the operation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>What if I die, and one day she finds out I cheated on her? I'll never be able to explain, never tell her how sorry I am.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You're increasing the odds of that every second we waste here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>No, I'm not agreeing to anything until I talk to her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>David</speaker><content>Daddy!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>Hey. Hey, guys.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>Sally</speaker><content>Ew! Your neck looks really gross.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>I missed you both so much. But I need to ask you favor. I need to talk to mommy alone for a second.  Would you mind watching them for us?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>This guy's an idiot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I think he actually has a good point. What would you think if you found out years later your beloved dead wife cheated on you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I wouldn't believe it. As long as I don't hear it directly from her, then I can hang on to hope that it's not true. But this way… she has to either dump him or forgive him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>Denise</speaker><content>Guys, get your stuff. We're leaving.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I'm so sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>Denise</speaker><content> I'll be back. I'm gonna drop our kids off at my mother's. Look, he made a mistake… a stupid, horrible mistake. But we'll get through this. All I care about right now is that my husband gets better.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Sorry about yesterday. House was like the child catcher from Chitty Chitty Bang Bang.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Why is he so obsessed with my kids being my kids?  Because he sees insecurity, and when House senses weakness, he pounces, and because his insecurity is the fact that other people can have faith and don't have the obsessive need for physical proof.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Also, he started a betting pool on which kid is yours and which isn't. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> An entire hospital betting on the legitimacy of my kids? It's great to be back among friends.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'm not the bad guy here. I'm betting on them both being yours.  I would have donated the money to charity.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Approaching the clot. Stand by for…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content> That’s not a clot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>It's his lymph nodes. The bulge wasn't caused by pus or blood. It's tissue inflammation. How can there be that much tissue…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>…lymphoma. We need to take a biopsy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Did I nick something?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I don't know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I don't see any bleeding in here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>His sclera's jaundiced. I think it's his liver. It's failing.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>We did a major operation for no reason. It's not Lemierre's Syndrome.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We would have had to biopsy his lymph nodes anyway to check for cancer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Which it's not. Biopsy was clean.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>We could be dealing with an alcoholic going through withdrawal. It explains his heart, seizures, and liver failing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>But not his swollen lymph nodes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Why are we stealing cable from here? We don't even have a TV in our office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm an ex-con, trying to adjust to a world that's passed me by. Stealing's all I know… that and the fact that I was right about what's wrong with our patient. Just wrong about what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>He means it's not Lemierre's, but it's still an infection, which is why it's spreading so rapidly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Cultures take time, and his liver doesn't have much left.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That's why we're gonna blast him with broad-spectrum antibiotics.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-11"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>The blast will fry what's left of his liver. The cure will kill him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-12"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Not if we get him a liver transplant first and then treat him with a broad spectrum.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content> And old team for the win!  Not that I'm keeping score. It's more of a grid where I assign numerical values to determine who gets raises, vacation time, and my respect.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>We he him on the donor list for a liver. But these things take time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>Denise</speaker><content>So he could die before he gets one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>It's a possibility. But we have another option. We can do a partial liver transplant from a living donor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>If you're a match, but to increase our odds, we'd like to get your friends and family tested as well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content> Is it safe?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>It's a major surgery. The donor spends a week in the hospital and up to three months convalescing at home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>I can't ask someone to do that for me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>Denise</speaker><content>There are hundreds of people who would do that for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>Because they don't know the real me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>Denise</speaker><content>You are a good man who made a mistake.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>Then I have to tell them first.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-12"><speaker>Denise</speaker><content>I have to live with this too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-13"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>I know. And I'm sorry, but… this is the only way that I can do this.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>Before I ask any of you to sacrifice three months of your life for me, I have a confession. I had an affair. I cheated on Denise. I wouldn't blame anyone if you decide…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>Denise</speaker><content>I forgive him. That should be enough for all of us.  Thank you so much for coming here…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>There's more. Larry… that new transmission I put in your truck… you didn't need it. Joe, same thing with the engine rebuild. In fact, I cheated most of you here tonight. Half the time you bring your cars into my garage, there's nothing wrong with them. I've been ripping you all off for years.  I also took $10,000 from the harvest scholarship fund, and I lost it gambling.  I'm sorry. I'm not the man you thought I was.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content> That went over well.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Out of the two donors who didn't walk out, both were negative for a potential match. Telling the truth may have just killed this guy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I told him to tell his wife he cheated, not confess every sin he's ever committed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>If everyone did that, we'd never find a donor for anyone again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Everybody doesn't lie, cheat, or steal from their friends.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Yeah, they do. Maybe not as much as this guy, but if people told nothing but the truth, the world would probably burn down overnight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Some people think it's burning now. Maybe if everybody didn't lie…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Aw, that is cute.  I'm talking about your breasts.  They always get perky when you're being painfully earnest. Truth. It's uncomfortable, isn't it? More truth… I only noticed because Chase was staring at them.  He'd never admit it, because he doesn't want to offend you. Same reason he'd never tell you that he's thought about having sex with you. Although, to be fair, every man you've ever met has thought about having sex with you. They'll lie, because if you knew… you probably wouldn't want to have sex with them. And that's just some of the lies from the last minute. And here's a bigger one… you already know this, but you pretend you don't because it makes you feel civilized. Most people find it easier to ignore the truth. Ask Taub. Our patient can't wait for a transplant that's never gonna come. We need to get reckless and extreme. C.T. his liver, find the damaged area, and cut it out. Hopefully, what's left will be enough so we can start treatment with broad-spectrum antibiotics.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I'm sorry the first time I had both of you together I had to work. But daddy's boss is what we call a jackass. Good. Stay right there.  I'm also sorry… for what I'm about to do… because… because nothing will ever change how I feel about you guys.  But…  but daddy is weak and needs to know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Okay. Just gonna put this right here… okay?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>It's 3:30 in the morning. Why are you still here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>House is here and apparently prepping for an operation that will probably kill a patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I wouldn't be doing this if I thought there was another way.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>There is. He needs a transplant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You have one lying around? 'Cause he'll be dead if he doesn't get one in the next few hours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>That falls under natural causes. If you kill him, we're looking at…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Dead is dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Not as far as our lawyers are concerned. I'm not being a dick. This is a real issue, and I have to worry about the big picture now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I don't. I'll be doing what you would have done a year ago. I'll be in surgery.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-10"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Chase… you need to check this out. This is a C.T. scan of his liver from ten hours ago… this is from now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-11"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>It's healing itself.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>When I left the room, he was telling her about the strippers from his bachelor party.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Liver function has improved 30%… buys us a few extra days before he'll need a transplant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Interesting question is, why is it regenerating?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And scene. Now we're back to boring reality reality. His liver was in shock before. He's been having an allergic reaction since he got here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Could explain why his symptoms appeared so rapidly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>And maybe starting to go away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>We need to run a scratch test to find out what set it off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Or who. This all started when he cheated on his wife.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>He's allergic to a person?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Or something she's wearing… makeup, perfume, birth control method, her "Hello Kitty" doll. Two of you go find her and find out what. Two of you start treatment with corticosteroids and epinephrine while you run the scratch test.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>Cindy</speaker><content>You think I did this to him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Or something you wear, own, use, or gave him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>Cindy</speaker><content>I gave him a condom. He didn't have one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>What kind?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>Cindy</speaker><content>I don't know what kind. I got it from the health fair I was working at.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You're in the medical profession?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>Cindy</speaker><content>I'm Miss Cedarville. The health fair is one of my responsibilities.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Is another one hooking up with 38-year-old married men?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I guess I'm supposed to be the good cop. I know this is tough. But anything you can remember might help save his life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-10"><speaker>Cindy</speaker><content>He was giving me a ride home, and… he always seemed so nice. And then we ended up at the motel. And now everybody's talking about it. And if they find out it was me, I'm gonna lose my title and probably my job. And no one in town is ever gonna speak to me again. I made a mistake, and now it's gonna end up ruining my life.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>Denise never wants to see me again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>What did you think was gonna happen?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>I was sick of living a lie. Everybody loved me. Everybody looked up to me. But… I didn't deserve it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Everybody makes mistakes. They just don't usually broadcast all of them at the same time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>Well, if I'm gonna die, I might as well do it with a clean soul.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>And if you live? You didn't just burn bridges. You torched, nuked, and salted the earth with them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>Everybody has to pay for their sins.  Oh, it feels like you stuck me with a hot poker.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>An allergic reaction.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>It's the swab for wheat-based allergies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-10"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>I've been eating wheat my entire life. I'm not allergic to wheat.  Now it feels like my whole body's on fire.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>This doesn't make any sense. He broke out with a rash right after I tested with the wheat-allergy swab, but none of his blood samples show he's allergic to it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Then he's not allergic to it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Could the corticosteroids have somehow caused it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I didn't hook them up yet. After he broke out, I wanted to confirm it was gluten before we dosed him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Could be a latex allergy. Started with a condom, and we kept it going with our gloves and equipment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>He doesn't test positive for that either.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>None of his samples test positive for anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Then he's allergic to something not on the tests. I'll keep looking here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We'll start the steroids and see if it clears up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-10"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You have one patient and three DNA results?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-11"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>How else do I compare them to other genetic disorders? What's up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-12"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Chase basically called me a sellout.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-13"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Just because you hung up your lab coat for more money and a bigger office?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-14"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I hung it up because someone had to run this place after Cuddy left.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-15"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>There are a lot of good administrators out there, not many good doctors.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-16"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>More to it than you think. For example, you're looking at monkey DNA.  My analysis… House took your results after he manipulated you into providing them.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>He's shedding his skin like a snake.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>If it was an allergic reaction, the corticosteroids and epinephrine would have made him better, not worse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Is everyone trying to think of an answer? Or is everyone afraid to say</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I take it you're in the latter category.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Stevens-Johnson syndrome… it fits all of his symptoms and explains why he got worse after the steroids. Most medication exacerbates the condition.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>There's no treatment for it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content> It fits. Case closed. Why don't you go home and get some sleep?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content> I feel like I'm in hell.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We can't give you too much pain medication, or we'll make your condition worse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>I got one final confession to make.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>What's left… you cheated on your taxes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>I'm a murderer.  I killed my business partner. I shot him in the head. I made it look like suicide. And he was just the first.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You killed more?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-7"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>Uh-huh. Three… or four.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Try not to kill anyone else until I get back.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>It's neurological. There's an aneurysm in the anterior communicating artery of his brain… the area moderating impulse control and compulsion. As it grew larger, so did the confessions. Watch.  Bob, one of my shoes is missing from my locker.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>I'm so sorry. I… I needed the cash, and, um, the locker was open.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I never heard of a neurological problem that causes someone's skin to fall off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Because there isn't one. The aneurysm is just another symptom. It's not the cause. You add them all together, we get…  We get Kaw… Kawas… Kawas…  It's Kawasaki's Disease. It's autoimmune.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Yes, we knew what "kawah" meant. We just figured since it basically presents only in Asian children…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Which you might have, by the way. Which is basically why we missed it. Rug burns… certain carpet-cleaning chemicals have been linked to it. Start treatment with intravenous immunoglobulin. Monitor the aneurysm. If it doesn't resolve itself we'll have to repair it.  The rest of you… aren't surfing enough.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Monkey DNA… nice touch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Really? You don't think I should have gone with rat? I've been second-guessing myself all day.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Where are the DNA results? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>First admit that I was right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You manipulated me into doing it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, I'll admit to that. Now you admit that it was incredibly easy, because you can't cheat an honest man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I love them. I don't care if one of them isn't biologically mine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What about both? Could be. Haven't read these. Now say I was right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-9"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>No. I'll admit I was weak for a moment, but I'm not doing this. I don't care.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You do, and I'll prove it. I will shred this. I will call off my pool, return the money, and we'll forget all about it. Or we'll go to the light box in the lab and know the truth once and for all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-11"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Stop. Let me see them.  Just wanted to make sure all three were inside.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>Denise</speaker><content>The mayor checked. There wasn't any money missing from the scholarship fund. Dr. Chase told me… about your disease, how it made you confess to crimes you hadn't committed.  The affair with that girl… is that real?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>Bob</speaker><content>Honey, I… would never… have never cheated on you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>Denise</speaker><content> I knew you could never do that to me. I don't know how… but I knew.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="34"><utterance uid="34-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Glad to see taking a year off didn't dull your skill set.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I got lucky.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>About the other night… I have enough problems with this job. Second-guessing my best doctors shouldn't be one of them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Why are you up here? You have your own bathroom and office now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Shower. I haven't left the hospital in four days.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>House won't go home. And there's no way I'm leaving him here unsupervised.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>House is screwing with you… by not screwing with you. He's watching TV and drinking martinis all night. Meanwhile, he's keeping you here searching for a plan that doesn't even exist. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>How the hell did I not see that? I'm glad you're back. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-10"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content> Me too.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="35"><utterance uid="35-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Either a hot tub or a sauna.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>A hot tub would be cool.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>New team, old team… I present… Phase one of Operation Outer Office 2.0.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Nothing's changed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh, everything has changed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>