<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>
<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Ben</speaker><content>Okay, boys and girls. Guess what kind of animal Wacky Benny's making now? Give you a big hint. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Red Headed Boy</speaker><content>Is it a dead animal?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Red Headed Boy</speaker><content>You're a sucky clown.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Ben</speaker><content> And you're a super-duper audience.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Ben</speaker><content> Hey, that is not okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Ben</speaker><content>Tell him to keep his hand off me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Ben</speaker><content>I can't move my arm or leg.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>So how does a completely healthy teenager have a mini-stroke?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Head CT and cerebral angiogram are normal. Clotting parameters are normal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're forgetting the wrinkly clump in the middle of his shirt. Thought we'd diagnose the middle-aged clown first.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> It's probably from my seat belt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Wrinkle pattern's too varied. It looks like someone shoved you or grabbed you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> Probably from the diaper bag. If the patient's using drugs, cocaine could have caused an arterial spasm in his brain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The tox screen was clean. I'm gonna say it was the ex-girlfriend you cheated on, not the ex-wife you cheated with. If the latter was prone to violence, you'd have been scattered in various dumpsters years ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> Seriously? No one else wants to talk about the patient? New office furniture. Meaty topic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>What's the action on the ex-wife?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> It was Rachel's boyfriend Phil. His company's moving him back to Portland. He wants me to change my visitation order so he can ask Rachel and my daughter to move out west with him. Things got a little heated.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>The patient was punched in the groin. Could have triggered a massive sympathetic discharge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Carotid duplex is normal. Who's better qualified to be the daddy? The guy who spilled a little DNA in her gene pool or the guy who's gonna be there day and night to pass on important values like, not shtupping mommy after the divorce?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I am her daddy. She's staying here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>House has a point. A couple nights a week with each kid may make you feel better. Doesn't replace two 'round-the-clock parents.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>'Round-the-clock or not, parenting's an impossible job. No way not to mess it up. Why shouldn't Taub be the one to do it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Thank you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Makes sense. Park's tiger mom and dad were so insufferable, she has to measure their affection in hours. Chase's careerist dad and alcoholic mom were so indifferent, he has to believe it's a wash.  Your turn. What did your screwed-up parents do to screw up your view of parenting?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>They were good parents.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That's an oxymoron. Chase is right. All parents screw up all children. He's also dreamy, but it's not relevant now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>So all parents screw up all children, but it makes some huge difference if I keep my daughter here or let her move?  Endocarditis. Flipped a piece of vegetation into his brain, which could have broken up before the angiogram.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Transesophageal echo to confirm. Screwed up is your best case. Bouncing between a philandering workaholic dad and an embittered, sexually betrayed mom, it's gonna lead to screwed-up squared.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Janey</speaker><content>Is endocarditis treatable?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Very. The echo will show us any growths on his heart valve. Most likely meds will be enough. He won't even need surgery.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Janey</speaker><content>He's just taken up performing and it's very stressful for him. Could that have caused this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Ben</speaker><content>It's not stressful. I have fun.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Stress wouldn't be relevant, but anything that increases his adrenalin could have made it worse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Janey</speaker><content>Maybe we find you a new hobby, one you're a little better at.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Ben</speaker><content>I'm gonna get better at it, and it's not a hobby. I-I think I want to get a job working as a circus clown, making people laugh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Janey</speaker><content>Ben, I-I don't think that's a good idea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Ben</speaker><content>It was good enough for my dad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content> You're a, uh…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-11"><speaker>Janey</speaker><content>No, his biological father.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-12"><speaker>Ron</speaker><content>Could his dad's melanoma be a factor here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-13"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>That wouldn't be related.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-14"><speaker>Janey</speaker><content>Ben, you barely knew him. You're such a smart kid. You could aim a lot higher than face paint and seltzer bottles.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Clinic Patient Monroe</speaker><content>I need treatment for my type 2 diabetes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>There is absolutely no part of that sentence that is true.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Monroe</speaker><content>I've been experiencing weight gain, fatigue, and sluggishness.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Weight loss is a symptom of diabetes. Fatigue is a symptom of thinking you have disease you don't actually have, and sluggishness is a synonym of fatigue.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Monroe</speaker><content>I need Insulin. I know it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Much as I'd like to kill you by dangerously lowering your blood sugar, murder violates my parole.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Monroe</speaker><content> That bloodwork is week's old. Test me again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I am the test. The test is negative. The test also thinks you're a giant pain in the ass. That last insult was your cue to leave.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Monroe</speaker><content> Test me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Fine. Wait right here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Monroe</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Sleep study. Please make sure he's not disturbed for the next eight hours.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>We need to talk about Saturday night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, no, no, no, no. Historians will talk of Saturday night, not us. The legendary night, on which we watch Santos shatter Rubio's jaw and you epically pay me $50.00.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I have a chance to really watch it. A patient of mine has a pair of tickets he can't use, and obviously you're under house and office arrest. I just wanted to make sure you were cool if I go to Atlantic City without you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Uh, no, thanks. I'm afraid I'm gonna have to decline your invitation to not spend Saturday night with you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>These are ringside seats.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Cameras are ringside too. If you want, I could sweat and spit and bleed on you from time to time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'd take you if I could.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-20"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, I'd take me if either of us could. See what a tough spot I'm in?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-21"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'm going to that fight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-22"><speaker>House</speaker><content>All right, I'll take the other ticket. Let me worry about logistics.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Patient's heart valves are normal. It's not endocarditis. But he has a thickened pericardium, which makes no sense.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He has a heart problem but not one that could have caused his T.I.A.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Syphilitic vasculitis would explain the T.I.A., and the pericardial inflammation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Syph test was negative. Plus, the kid's never been sexually active.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, I got that from the line in his chart that says "birthday clown."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>His late father was a circus clown.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Histoplasmosis?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He's not immuno-compromised.  And I assume you added that irrelevant tidbit because you're moved by the son's idiotic tribute and think it justifies keeping your daughter in New Jersey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>What if he has a heightened immune system?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I mentioned it because…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Take your time. We'll continue with the medicine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Sjogren's could have given him chronic pericarditis and cerebral arteritis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Sjogren's it is. IV immunosuppressants to treat.  Anything?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>This will calm your immune system. Should be out of here within the week.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Ben</speaker><content>My mom will be happy to hear that. I've got an internship that starts in three weeks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I take it it's not at a place with a big top.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Ben</speaker><content>It's at my stepdad's law office. I know I'm not any good at being a clown yet, but when I do get a laugh and see those kids' eyes light up, that's how my dad made me feel when I was a kid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You need to hang on to that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Ben</speaker><content>Heh. My mom says he was a loving father but, always broke and, always on the road. It's a stupid way to make a living.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You're 16. Plenty of time to make money. Wanting to build a connection with your dad and pass on some of the joy that he gave you, that's not stupid at all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Ooh. I got it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Ben</speaker><content> Is, uh, is this because of the medication? Is it normal?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>It's not normal, and it's not Sjogren's.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>T.I.A., thickened pericardium, and now he's bleeding from his nose and mouth.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>What are you doing with her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>"Her"? Surely this bundle of fun has an actual name.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>It's Sophie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Both your kids are named…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>She's Sophie. The other one's Sophia. It different enough.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>They actually have two completely different derivations.  No, they don't.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I wasn't in a strong negotiating position.  Why is she here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Ruby dropped her off. Seemed pretty upset. Apparently someone forgot that it was daddy's night. She wasn't even gonna leave her until I said that I was letting you off early.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Damn it. I just started back on the team. My schedule's a mess.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>If your own kids are a scheduling item, maybe you should let one of them move.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Patient has low platelets. Makes me think D.I.C.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>She doesn't seem to like that idea. You're right.  He has no schistocytes in his smear. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>He also has a low red count. What if it's a retroperitoneal bleed?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>No Grey-Turner's sign.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content> She wasn't fussing like that when I was holding her. Maybe she likes the sound of my voice, which is weird because I have no genetic connection to her.  Could it be, she doesn't know the difference?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>So many children of your own. No wonder you have such insight into my relationship with my babies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Good point. How could I comprehend that you're too despised to keep them from having the same name, too overwhelmed to remember your own calendar, and too vain to admit that at this stage, you don't matter to either baby.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Low white count suggests infection.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-20"><speaker>House</speaker><content>What if you're all right? Low platelets plus low red count plus low white count equals…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-21"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Aplastic anemia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-22"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Kid needs a bone marrow transplant. Everyone except Adams, transfuse his platelets till you find a match.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-23"><speaker>House</speaker><content> You started college a semester late because you left high school a semester late because  you had five incompletes in your junior year.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-24"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>And you're offering one bad semester as proof that my parents screwed me up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-25"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Did okay before that. Straight As after that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-26"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I went through a rebellious phase.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-27"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Don't tell me. Mom and dad were at each other's throats and the academic crisis was a cry for help.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-28"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Sorry to mess with your worldview, but I'm not messed up, so my parents couldn't have messed me up.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Mom's HLA is only a 3/6 match.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Maternal grandmother's worse than that.  Where did you unload the baby?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Maternity ward.  Shut up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>You realize you're making House's argument for him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>The part where he said any parent who uses day care should ship their child across the country?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>No, the part where he said that baby doesn't need you. You've only got her a couple days a week and most of that's spent with a rotating cast of nurses.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>That's how daddy likes to spend his time too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Shut up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>First cousin's also a whiff.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>So much for genetics mattering. I'll try the marrow registry.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Dr. Park is searching the registry. Transfusing his platelets will keep him healthy while we wait.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Are you sure there's no one on the father's side of the family? If one of them's a match, that'd speed things up a lot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Janey</speaker><content>His parents died young. He was an only child. There's no living relatives that I know of.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Something will turn up soon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Ron</speaker><content>How soon is soon? Will he miss a lot of school?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Ben</speaker><content>I'm actually thinking of just getting my GED.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Janey</speaker><content>How do you expect to get into a good college?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Ben</speaker><content>I'm gonna take classes on magic and juggling and try to make a go of this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Ron</speaker><content>Ben, you keep your grades up, you can do anything in the world.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Ben</speaker><content>Like what? Work in some boring office? I mean, do you think my father would have done that for ten minutes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Janey</speaker><content>You don't remember your father. You don't know…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Ben</speaker><content> I want to build a connection with him, pass on some of the… the joy that he gave me.  My, uh, my back hurts. Uh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>His BP is dropping.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Man on Phone</speaker><content>We think we've dealt wit all the liability issues.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content> I'm in a meeting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Sorry. Since you paged me, I didn't want to keep you waiting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Yeah, I paged you, which means you're next.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That's cool. I'll wait.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content> That's a good start. Let's go through it point by point. First up…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content> I'll call you back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content> Just got this. The American Association of Rheumatology wants you to speak, 9:00, Saturday, in Atlantic City. Dr. Neusinger canceled on them at the last minute.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I hate conferences.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-10"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>This is a big one, and it's the premium slot. I'd like you to do it. I'll clear it with your parole officer. What do I need to do for you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Halve the clinic hours that you recently doubled and double the hooker budget that you recently halved. I think you refer to it as petty cash.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-12"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Fine. Just one thing. I'm gonna ask them to put you on in the morning. We're doing them a favor. Why should you have to spend the night?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You said that 9:00 was the premium slot. I mean, I want to feel like I've earned my hookers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-14"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>The place will be a madhouse, especially since it's two miles from the Rubio fight at the exact same time. Nice try. You called up, pretended to be Neusinger, cancelled, and suggested yourself as a replacement. You go to that fight, you go to prison.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>But that'd be redundant, when I have an angry black guy waiting for me to drop the soap right here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-16"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Better go do some of those clinic hours I recently doubled.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Monroe</speaker><content>Test my urine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Looks like I was wrong about my diagnosis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Monroe</speaker><content>Yeah. I have diabetes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, but you're not a hypochondriac or you would have imagined some new disease after I shot down the first one. So whose urine is that? Diabetic girlfriend without health insurance?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Monroe</speaker><content>It's not a scam. I'm sick. Now I have swollen ankles.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The medical term is cankles.  Is there some black market in insulin that I don't know about?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Monroe</speaker><content>It's in my genes. My old man got diabetes at 50. My older brother, got it at 50. I just turned 50.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, it's a great argument if diabetes was a gold watch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Monroe</speaker><content>I got sciatica, like my dad. Class-four hemorrhoids, like him. I need to get a jump on this thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We had to stop the transfusion. Patient's having an allergic reaction to donor platelets.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>No one in mom's family's a match, and as far as she knows, dad has no living relatives. It's been years since he died.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content> If the kid's dad died young of melanoma, how come the overprotective mom never took him to a dermatologist?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>Monroe</speaker><content>Are you gonna test my urine or what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Not diabetes.  Use cross-matched platelets. Try to find the patient some blood that's closer to his own. And get the real story on clown senior's death. Mom's hiding something. It's a good bet that it's medically relevant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Apple juice. Easiest way to fake a spike in blood sugar.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>His family history of melanoma may have affected his cellular outlook.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>If we had more data on the exact type of melanoma his father had…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Otherwise, we might not be able to find a marrow match.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Janey</speaker><content>He never had melanoma.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>How did he die?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Janey</speaker><content>He didn't. He lives in Pennsauken, under a different name, Mitchell Gordon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Ron</speaker><content>How could you keep this from me? From Ben?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>Janey</speaker><content>He really needs to know his dad just breezed in and out of his life, drunk and incoherent? It's better to think the man's dead but decent.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You realize I have to invite someone else to the Rubio fight?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Nope. No realization whatsoever.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You have a LoJack on your leg.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I was happy watching the fight on pay-per-view. You're the one who insisted we go to Atlantic City.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Your biological father was a decent, God-fearing minister. The guy who raised you was a cold-hearted jerk. I'm trying to figure out why you're so convinced Adams has parentally inflicted damage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're trying to deflect.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Now you are. You have to believe that every parent screws up every child or you were screwed out of a decent childhood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>My decent daddy of the cloth was also being indecent with my married mom. He probably would have taken other kids to the playground.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's not my fault. Bad parenting. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Mitchell Gordon?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>Mitchell</speaker><content>I've already got a religion. Go away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>We're doctors. Your son Ben is in the hospital, at Princeton-Plainsboro. He's very sick.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>Mitchell</speaker><content>Yeah, well, I don't have a son. Not anymore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>We know there are some issues there, but your bone marrow could cure him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>There's a hospital two miles from here. It's a simple test.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>Mitchell</speaker><content>You said he was at Princeton-Plainsboro?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>His mother feels it's better to do the test at a different hospital.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>Mitchell</speaker><content>Well, I guess I don't have a son anymore.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>House isn't gonna give up. Just tell him about your parents or make up a lie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I don't want to lie. I don't want to validate his ridiculous theory.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>It's not ridiculous. Even the best-intentioned parents end up damaging their kids.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>You're a smart, successful doctor. How much damage could you have?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You know how I got interested in medicine? When my mother drank, she couldn't handle me, so she locked me in my father's study. Only so many hours you can cry and bang on the door before you give up, find something to read. We all have family dysfunction. That's why we're successful. To fill that hole.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>My parents have a lot of money, but they didn't make it legally.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>White-collar crime?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>It started with card games. High-stakes poker. Then my dad got into narcotics, at first just selling but then, using too, or he never would have gotten into the slave trade. Children mostly. Easier to pack in small crates. Plus the shipping's a lot cheaper.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Won't even trust a co-worker. What did your parents do to you?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> You have to go see him yourself. He wouldn't even come to the door a second time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>Janey</speaker><content>Okay. I'll drive over there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>It's a pleural effusion.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>He had a bleeding problem earlier. Must be bleeding into his lungs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Except there's no blood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>Janey</speaker><content>What does it mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>It means you don't have to make that drive. The problem isn't his marrow. It's his liver.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Liver failure. Explains everything. The question is, what explains the liver failure?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>It's not an infection. We tried antibiotics, but he's not responding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>More curiously, what explains the mom lying about dad pushing up squirting daisies?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content> This is how you plan to get to the boxing game?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Why are you looking at her?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>'Cause I'm stunned, and I have to look at something. Match, bout, fight, contest, day, Helena. Almost anything works after "boxing," except the word "game."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Your bigger problem is the people who design those things aren't idiots.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>Workman on the floor</speaker><content>Huh huh.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Can you believe she used to work in the can? Nothing is tamper-proof.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>It's a synthetic problem. His liver's not synthesizing proteins, so fluid is leaking out of his blood vessels. And mom's a selfish jerk. She traded up, married a lawyer, wants to forget the lowly circus clown.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're defending the father because you feel like a jerk for baking buns in two different ovens. You want to believe the mythical biological connection excuses being a man slut. Ow!  I don't know why I'm starting to doubt your expertise. You do have a classified ad and a piece of metal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-12"><speaker>Workman</speaker><content>It's temperature that sets it off, not force. The rivets go pop, I slide in the heating pad. Easy peasy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-13"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>More likely the patient has a hyperammonemic problem. His liver's not cleaning out his blood. The buildup of toxins is causing everything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-14"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I'm defending the dad because he got screwed. After he lost his son, he lost his job. Been in and out of rehab, gave up clowning. Yes, as a parent, I empathize. I say we tell the kid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-15"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>He's a minor, the mom's his guardian, and it's not even medically relevant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-16"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>She robbed them of 12 years together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Or she ripped off the band-aid too late. That memory that she let son of Bozo establish is making him chase his father's moronic profession when he could be living the high life in Portland. And I mean that metaphorically, of course.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content> This is where you dazzle me with your contingency plan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I see why employers are reluctant to hire ex-cons.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-20"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Well, what about the patient? Is the problem hyperammonemic or synthetic?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-21"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Can't treat for both. One requires hemodialysis, the other a liver transplant, and we couldn't even get the kid a marrow match.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-22"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Get the mom's consent to pump him full of protein. If it's a synthetic problem, more fluid will leak into his chest and his heart will fail. If it's hyperammonemic, toxins will overwhelm his body and he'll go into a coma.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-23"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Do you only like tests that involve the risk of death?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-24"><speaker>House</speaker><content>There are some slower, less conclusive tests, but why take that risk? </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>Man holding receiver</speaker><content>In here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Oh, my God. The water. This is completely my fault. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>There are very serious risks, but if we don't figure out what he has, we can't treat him at all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I may be a little out of bounds here, but in case there are complications, it might be a good time to come clean to your son, let his father visit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>Janey</speaker><content>A little out of bounds?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I don't know the history, but everyone makes mistakes. Your son worships him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>Ron</speaker><content>Doctor's right about that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>Janey</speaker><content>Oh, yeah? And when did he learn that? When he encouraged Ben to drop out of school?  Mitchell is not Ben's father any more than a sperm donor would have been.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Unless you're a locksmith or an electrician with political contacts. I'm busy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>My condolences on your forthcoming divorce.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Since I have no intention of testing him, treating him, or cooking for him… </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The advantage of fake prescriptions is, you don't have to be a real doctor to write one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Imaginary medicine is not my specialty. I do have an imaginary colleague who's just sent me an imaginary page.  Imagine how sorry I am. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Still mad about what happened in the lab?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I'm not mad. I'm being professional.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You claim you're not screwed up. You may even believe it. But House doesn't and I don't, so you can wait till he camps out on your parents' lawn or you can admit you don't live on some higher plane and thank me later.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>Ben</speaker><content>My, uh, my eye feels weird. What's happening to me?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You look tired.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>Ruby</speaker><content>I hate it when people say that. I know, I look bad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I thought you were gonna go to bed early last night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>Ruby</speaker><content>Like an idiot, I went out with my girlfriends to pretend I have a life,  when all I did was flirt with guys who'd have no interest in a mom, miss the baby I couldn't wait to get rid of, and then get yelled at by my mom for staying out too late.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You need your own place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>Ruby</speaker><content>Yes. I moved back home because it was too drafty at the Four Seasons.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>So go back to work at the hospital.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>Ruby</speaker><content>Day care costs more than what I earned as a nurse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Have you considered sub-standard day care? Why don't you stay here tonight?  No. I mean, in the guest room. I'll watch the baby again, and you can get a real night's sleep.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>Ruby</speaker><content>You'd do that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Win-win. Mommy gets a rest,  Daddy gets more time with his little angel. There’re some sweats in the closet in the back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-12"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Lucky girl. Gets another sleepover with da-da. It makes a difference. Doesn't it?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Didn't answer your page last night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Sorry. Battery died.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We got the patient's eye back in place with steroid injections, but a bulging eyeball means it's not a liver problem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And mom's determination to keep dad away, even as her kid gets sicker and sicker, means she's got more to hide.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>It's not diagnostically relevant. Let's let it drop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You just lost my vote. You flip-flopped on parental rights.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I've been trying to persuade the mother, but it's her son, so it's her call.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, that very evolved of you. Don't usually see Darwinian changes over breakfast. You made nice-nice with Phil. You decided that he'd make a decent father for thing 2 after all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I had Sophie again last night and Ruby slept in my guest room, which has nothing to do with Phil, who will never be a father to my children.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-10"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Angioneurotic edema can cause rapid swelling.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Hey, we're having a conversation here. No abdominal pain.  So that must have been nice, having Ruby and the baby under one roof.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-12"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Yes, it was nice having my daughter in my home. That's why I would like her sister to live near my home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-13"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Anasarca?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-14"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Swelling would have followed gravity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Isn't that getting this whole parenting thing ass backwards? Aren't you supposed to figure out what you can sacrifice to maximize their niceness?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-16"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>And do you think I should sacrifice myself from their lives?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Just one life, until the other one's mommy meets someone nicer than you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-18"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Swelling that fast and localized has to come from the lymph nodes. Burkitt's lymphoma.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Swelling. Cankles.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-20"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>That's not a symptom of Burkitt's. Are you saying it's…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's Burkitt's. Prep him for chemo.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I think you should give House permission to go to Atlantic City. We'll stop by the rheumatology conference. Everyone's covered.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>The guy has earned the right to go to one boxing match. He's done everything you've asked… Funded and staffed his own department. Hasn't even broken as much as a traffic law.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You're right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>So, you'll let him go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>No. I get why he wants to go to that fight. I'd love to go myself, which is kind of why I have to stop him. My job is to be the jerk. House has to believe that I have authority over him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>He can't function under someone's thumb.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I know, which means you can't go either.  Your job is to be his friend, to stay here and sit with him and watch the fight on pay-per-view while bitching about me. If we both do our jobs, we might actually get him through his parole.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> You're right.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Sorry to show up like this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I was expecting a battery of lawyers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>No lawyers. Phil had something that he would like to say, so I thought that he should say it in person.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>Phil</speaker><content>It was wrong of me to confront you about taking Rachel to Portland.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> You don't want to move to Portland?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Of course I do, but this is about your daughter too and I'm not gonna do something like this without your support.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>So you guys are trying to manipulate me by playing good cop/good cop?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-8"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Is that how little you think of me? It's clear you're back working for House. I will see you this weekend when you pick up Sophie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-9"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Sophia.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-10"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>We actually started calling her Sophie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-11"><speaker>Phil</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-12"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Great. It's cute.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Cankles.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>Monroe</speaker><content>I'm faint. I've been gaining more weight. I think I need a bigger dose.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If you double his placebo, he might drown.  Also, you forgot to mention that your heart rate is slow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>Monroe</speaker><content>My… my heart rate is not…  52?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The technical term is slow. Those awful anti-diabetic meals you eat, do they contain bok choy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Bok choy has glucosinolates, which inhibit thyroid function and account for all your symptoms.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>Monroe</speaker><content>So this isn't diabetes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You have a bad case of irony. The food that you're eating to stop making you sick is making you sick.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>Monroe</speaker><content>Hey, maybe I don't have my father's crummy genes after all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>On the other hand, maybe you're fat enough to get diabetes even without ‘em. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>Ben</speaker><content>I can't believe I have cancer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>We caught it early. You should be okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>Ben</speaker><content>I could die. I never went anywhere, did anything. If my father had lived, everything would have been different.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Your mom and stepdad love you. They've given you a great home. That counts for a lot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>He's crashing. Everything's shutting down.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Renal failure, lung failure, heart failure, all before we started chemo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Burkitt's lymphoma is fast-moving, but not this fast.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No rush. ICU stands for take your time, in Latin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Multiple aneurysms?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That would mean that every symptom after his T.I.A. was a coincidence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Cholesterol emboli?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Bingo. Fits perfectly. Check the file, confirm that we did major abdominal surgery on him and then completely forgot about it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-9"><speaker>Mitchell</speaker><content>Hello?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-10"><speaker>Janey</speaker><content> What the hell are you doing here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-11"><speaker>Mitchell</speaker><content>I was told that this might be my last chance to see my son.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-12"><speaker>Janey</speaker><content> You had no right! This is none of your business!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-13"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I didn't.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-14"><speaker>Ron</speaker><content>I called him.  This man's Ben's hero. Let them spend five minutes together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-15"><speaker>Janey</speaker><content> No!  Get out of here!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Wait.  You sexually molested your son. Your walk, tabes dorsalis. You have late-stage syphilis, which you gave to our patient, presumably 12 years ago, which also explains why mom is not big on family reunions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-17"><speaker>Mitchell</speaker><content>I shouldn't be here. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-18"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>We tested him for syphilis. He was negative.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>After 12 years, the active infection would have died down. Everywhere except the arteries in his brain, where it could hide out from our tests.  But when that six-year-old heckler punched him in his juggling pins, it kicked up the dormant bacteria in his pelvis. The immunosuppressant’s we gave him sent it into overdrive. The antibiotics we gave him actually started destroying the syphilis. But like pouring water on a fire, that led to a trail of toxic smoke and ash, which made his immune system overcompensate. Severe Jarisch-Herxheimer reaction.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-20"><speaker>Ron</speaker><content> Is this true?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yes, Jarisch-Herxheimer is real. It sounds silly, but… Oh, you mean the… the… right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-22"><speaker>Janey</speaker><content> I found stains on his clothes. He didn't understand and he didn't seem traumatized. I kept trying to talk to him, but before long, he'd forgotten, and he seemed… and he seemed happy and he seemed normal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-23"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So you made daddy go away and you made sure junior had no reason to go looking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-24"><speaker>Janey</speaker><content>I was just trying to protect him, like I should have done from the start.  Sorry. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-25"><speaker>House</speaker><content>IV penicillin and anti-TNF antibodies, he'll be fine. Apart from the whole daddy-rape thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-26"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>We're not done.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-27"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, we are not. Notify the dad's sexual partners. Notify his employer, his landlord. Notify the police.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-28"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I meant the kid. We're not gonna tell him he was molested?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-29"><speaker>House</speaker><content>To make him miserable or to forfeit your license?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-30"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>To tell him the truth. He's a virgin. How do we explain the STD? It's a medical diagnosis. Screw the parents. The kid's our patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-31"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I guess Taub's got a tough choice to make when the kid wakes up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-32"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Why is it my choice?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-33"><speaker>House</speaker><content>'Cause you're a dad. How could the rest of us possibly understand?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>Ben</speaker><content>What was… what was wrong with me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>It's called syphilis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>Ben</speaker><content>Uh, you… you can get that without having sex? </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I didn't tell him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Your heart said he needed to know. Your brain knew he's better off without it. Following your heart is easy. Following your brain is tough. Especially after years of following that much smaller third organ. That's why all parents screw up all children.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Evening.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Clever tactic, pretending you're not interested anymore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>How could that possibly work as a tactic? The fact is, once I saw those incompletes, I knew your parents screwed you up. The details are just gravy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>You're wrong. The only evidence you have is proof of something else. I ran away from home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Because you had lousy parents.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Because I didn't. All my friends' parents were divorced or having affairs or barely knew their kids' birthdays.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You envied their dysfunction.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I-I thought it made them deeper somehow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-9"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>It was stupid. I hitchhiked to Manhattan, moved in with an older guy. In two months, I came running home. It took my parents years to get over it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That's when you started to excel. You were making it up to them. Your parents screwed you up by not screwing you up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-11"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>How does briefly wishing I was screwed up make me screwed up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's normal to be screwed up. It's really screwed up to romanticize it. I guess that's why you wanted to work with prisoners.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-13"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>It's why I wanted to work with you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It was a tactic. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>Chris.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Yeah. I need to talk to you and Phil.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-3"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content> Is everything okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Yeah.  I can't let you move.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-5"><speaker>Rachel</speaker><content>You drove all the way out here just to tell us what you already told us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I'm sorry. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>House, open up. I don't want to miss the opening bell.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>House?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>Television Announcer</speaker><content>Telecast, we expect an electric atmosphere in the arena and a sellout crowd of about 10,000, for Rubio versus Santos, two great fighters with illustrious careers who might have been expected to meet a long time ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-4"><speaker>Television Announcer</speaker><content>As for Santos, his handlers tell us that he's done more roadwork than at any time in his career, hoping to prove tonight that he can box for 12 full rounds.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-5"><speaker>Television Announcer</speaker><content>Significant because Santos hasn't heard the final bell in more than six years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-6"><speaker>Television Announcer</speaker><content>He comes in with straight knockout wins and we saw how a power puncher with a left hook was able to cut Rubio over the right eye in the tenth round of that last fight.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>