<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>
<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>We're in the car, honey. We're going to the hospital for tests.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>We're in the hospital. We're going to the Doctor's office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Andres </speaker><content>Uh, you use it to get food from inside.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Andres </speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Andres </speaker><content>Uh, no, it's, um… it's, um… You're trying to make me look stupid.  You can go to hell! Why don't you kill yourself?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>Andres.  It's okay. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>Here I am. Here, come on.  You just need to answer a few more questions. Then we're going home. We'll have lunch, okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Andres </speaker><content>Okay.  I'm sorry. I have Alzheimer's.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>The mood swings come on quickly, but, um… It's under control.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>Andres…  Oh, my God! Andres…</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Early onset familial Alzheimer's. Brazilian descent. Blood chemistry showed high ammonia. Vomiting stopped after the E.R. put him on antiemetics.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Park </speaker><content>Any recent health issues?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Just a sore throat a few weeks ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>How advanced is he? Could be hyperalimentation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Advanced enough, but no IV feedings. The wife shut down a floral company to stay home and feed him every meal he's had in the last four years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Do we owe this case to your guilt at having ignored your own forgetful mommy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>My guilt over my mom is why I put up with my dad. You're taking this case because we're running a phase-two trial on an Alzheimer's drug.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>House </speaker><content>You couldn't round up enough doddering old Guinea pigs. You need us to fix this little piggy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>I'd like to sit in. Especially since you're short a team member.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>House </speaker><content>You mean Taub?  Got him in here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>He asked for a personal day. His daughter's sick.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Isn't that the point of having a spare? I denied his request.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>After I'd already approved it, which you knew because I sent you a memo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Dr. Adams… taped under your chair is an index card. Would you read it, please?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Adams </speaker><content>"Wednesday, 2:43 p.m., a black Pawn will believe he's the black King and attempt to capture the… white head of diagnostics."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Park </speaker><content>It's 10:15 on Friday.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Damn it. Look, the point is I saw this coming. Dr. Foreman and I did not always see eye-to-eye. But he never had the power to overrule me. Now that he has the power, he won't be able to resist the temptation to use it. With great power comes great micromanaging. And great vests.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>I know you're the better diagnostician. I'm not gonna interfere. I'm only here to help.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>Park </speaker><content>Could be transient nitrogen load from a G.I. bleed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-20"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Not if the vomiting's persistent.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-21"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Which we won't know, because the E.R. put him on antiemetics. Take him off. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-22"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Wait. He's puking his guts out. We'd risk aspiration.  I'm just disagreeing, not overruling.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-23"><speaker>House </speaker><content>So glad you're on board. Take him off antiemetics, do an upper endoscopy to check for bleeds.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>It could be a bladder infection. We'll run a pregnancy test.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Kayla </speaker><content>Oh, I'm not pregnant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>Any type of birth control can fail.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Kayla </speaker><content>Not mine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>Oh, I'm sorry. You said you were married.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Kayla </speaker><content>Yeah, happily.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>That's okay. Sex can wane in any marriage over time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Kayla </speaker><content>No, neither of us. Celibacy is a choice. This is our orientation. We're asexual.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>You're making a mistake. If I had the power to veto him, given all the crap I've put up with over the years, don't know if I could use it objectively.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>I do, I can, I have.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Might be easier if you'd stay out of the room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>I thought it'd be different. This week. Supposed to talk to his P.O. about getting his ankle monitor off early.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>You're saying he should defer to you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>No, I'm just saying what he's doing doesn't seem rational, which makes me think it's rational in a way I'm not privy to. He always has a plan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>And he's always self-destructive. He may just be shooting himself in the ankle.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>I know it feels strange. Dr. Chase is just looking in your throat. We're in the hospital. You're fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>He coached youth soccer. Took a team that was 0-6 all the way to the state finals at Long Branch. Hey, thanks for doing this in here. Switching rooms can be very disorienting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Park </speaker><content>You take very good care of him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>I love him. Sickness and health, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Upper esophagus is clear. Moving on to the G.E. junction.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Joseph </speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Park </speaker><content>I'm sorry. Family members only during procedures.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Joseph </speaker><content>Uh, I'll— I'll be outside.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>Oh, no. Please, um, it's okay. Joseph helps me with my husband sometimes. He's a good friend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Park </speaker><content>Which means not family.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>Okay. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Park </speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Surprised you didn't go into the diplomatic corps.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>Park </speaker><content>Oh, you think they're… </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>No, if they're having sex, it's probably with their genitals.  Mallory-Weiss tear. Vomiting must have torn the lining.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>You know that close to 1% of the population identifies as asexual?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>House </speaker><content>We really gotta get you laid. If I have to plough that furrow myself, so be it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>I have a patient who's asexual.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Is she a giant pool of algae?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>It's a valid sexual orientation. According to this article, at least.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Yeah, I think I read that too. Is that fugliness weekly?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>She's perfectly fine-looking. Happily married for ten years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>House </speaker><content>To a guy who loves penis enough for the both of them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>He's asexual too. Ran a complete physical on her. Nothing wrong except a common bladder infection.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-10"><speaker>House </speaker><content>100 bucks says I can find a medical reason why she doesn't want to have sex.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-11"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>You're out of your mind if you think I'm letting you anywhere near my patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-12"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Fine. I won't go near her. Just give me her file and any blood samples you have left over.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-13"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>No contact, whatsoever. You talk to her, the bet is void.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-14"><speaker>House </speaker><content>No contact. Plays to my strengths anyway.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Right now's not a good time, House.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Not for the Dean of Medicine. But it's a perfect time if you're a member of my team. Which one are you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>What did the endoscopy show?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>No signs of ulcers or blockages.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>But you found a tear just below the esophagus. Explains the bleeding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Park </speaker><content>Doesn't explain why he vomited so hard he ripped his insides.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Adams </speaker><content>His liver enzymes are slightly elevated. Gallstones could've—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>House </speaker><content>no complaints of pain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Steatohepatitis would make his AST and ATL levels rise.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Are you calling his liver fat? Start the patient on statins, and do a biopsy to confirm. And knock him out. I've heard he's a wiggler.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>There's no need to put him under. We can confirm fatty liver with an ultrasound.  Just making an observation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Well done. Now, as a member of my team, you can make the equally-useful observations that the sky is blue, I'm wearing pants, and I'm ignoring your first observation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Of course.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Wait.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>House </speaker><content>And there it is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-16"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>You're trying to screw with my confidence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-17"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Well, if I wanted to do that, I'd tell you how much the nurses hate you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-18"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>You're trying to get me to define myself as a subordinate to keep me from ever intervening, even if it's fully in the scope of my duties. Like now. This isn't about diagnostics, it's about what's safe for the patient. Do the ultrasound.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-19"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Ultrasound it is. And the nurses love you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>You don't think I knew House was gonna tell you to ignore me and not do the ultrasound?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>This is an ultrasound machine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Which you're gonna use to do an ultrasound-guided biopsy. Probably got a kit stashed here…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>Adams </speaker><content>"Cuddy dark will waste his afternoon chasing conspiracy theories."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>You're letting him get inside your head. He could do a lot of damage in there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>Dr. Chase. He started vomiting again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>This is why we stopped the antiemetics. We needed to see if it was still a symptom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>Okay. Here, you want this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>It's okay, Andres. You're in the hospital. Here. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>10 milligrams of Diazepam!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Already on it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm all right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Foreman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Blood in his urine.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Adams </speaker><content>Resume the antiemetics and increase the sedation. He really went after her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Park </speaker><content>Maybe he found out about her "good friend."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>It was just paranoid rage, typical of Alzheimer's. We don't even know if they were sleeping together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Park </speaker><content>A few hours ago you were sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>House </speaker><content>And that's significant why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Park </speaker><content>Sorry. Only the bleeding's medically relevant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>House </speaker><content>No, I wasn't being rhetorical. If they are sleeping together, why do we disapprove?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Adams </speaker><content>You're pro-infidelity?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>House </speaker><content>She's not married. If marriage is feeding and cleaning someone, limiting conversations, to repeating a few simple commands, then I was married to my pet rat. And a lot of people owe me wedding gifts.  And we're walking, we're walking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Adams </speaker><content>I don't care how sick your spouse gets, you don't jump ship.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Alzheimer's is different. She can't share her problems with him, or plan for the future. The man she married no longer exists.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Adams </speaker><content>Yes, he does. He's in there. This is why you get married.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Said the divorced woman to the divorced man.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Adams </speaker><content>I didn't jump ship. My husband sank it when he cheated on me. Commitment's not conditional.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>She is there for him in the only way that matters now. She gave up her life to take care of him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Which proves she's an idiot. If she had any sense, she'd have stuck him in a facility and jumped on that strange— Dr. Foreman! We were just looking for you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>I was right about the antiemetics. If you kept him on them like I said, he wouldn't have gotten agitated and punched his wife.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Yes, we're back to my supposed diabolical plan to shake your confidence. Let's see if this helps.  If you're speaking as a team member, then I'd say you're a moron. Because taking him off the antiemetics gave us crucial diagnostic information. If you're speaking as Dean of Medicine, then I'd say you're a moron. 'Cause your micromanaging kept us from doing a biopsy. If we had, the patient would have been anesthetized hours ago, thus unable to go all Chris Brown on her ass.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-19"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Unless one of your index cards actually predicted the guy was gonna punch his wife, everything you're saying is post hoc rationalization.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-20"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Dr. Park, would you please reach under that chair? [House sits down on his chair. Park is sitting on the other side of his desk. She reaches under the chair House pointed at and finds an index card.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-21"><speaker>Park </speaker><content>"The patient will punch his wife." </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-22"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>You clearly wrote that after the fact.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-23"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Dr. Adams, would you please reach into my pants? </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-24"><speaker>House </speaker><content>"Dr. Blackenshmurtz will accuse me of writing about the punch after the fact." Now, look. Here's a photograph of me holding a newspaper.  Dated last Tuesday. Now, how could I have gotten my hands on that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-25"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>You done? Rhabdomyolysis fits the vomiting, pigmenturia, and renal failure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-26"><speaker>Adams </speaker><content>No muscle symptoms, and urine had no myoglobin. TTP fits, though.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-27"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Start him on plasmapheresis. Unless… unless I need to say, "mother, may I?" And mother is an abbreviation. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Fresh plasma will replace the damaged red blood cells that are clogging his kidneys.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Joseph </speaker><content>That sounds hopeful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>I've never been hit in the eye before. I feel kinda badass.  I think maybe you should go. I'm fine. Okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Joseph </speaker><content>I’ll see you tomorrow. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>Okay.  We're not having an affair.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>It's none of my business.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>I mean, not— not really. 'Cause nothing's happened. We've talked about it a lot, and… it's just really hard doing this by myself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>When's the last time you had a full night's sleep?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-9"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>You're not going to get any rest here. People who are sick are not the only ones who need to be taken care of. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Park </speaker><content>Why doesn't Chase have to be here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>House </speaker><content>You think he knows anything about women who don't want to have sex?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Adams </speaker><content>Hormone levels are normal. This woman seems perfectly healthy. What does it matter if she says she's asexual?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>House </speaker><content>It's the fundamental drive of our species. Sex is healthy. Orgasms oxygenate the brain, lighting up over 30 different areas and making us forget how boring Susie Cooper is. That last one may not be universal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Park </speaker><content>How about damage to her spinal cord blocking the signals from her genitals?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Adams </speaker><content>Sex drive is in the brain. I suppose it could be psychological intimacy issues caused by childhood abuse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>House </speaker><content>She's been sharing a toilet with the same guy for the last ten years.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Adams </speaker><content>It's not the same. Sex releases oxytocin. It's the neurochemical basis for bonding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>House </speaker><content>And that's why men always marry their right hands.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Adams </speaker><content>It's different for girls.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Park </speaker><content>No it's not. I've tapped over 30 guys and never wanted to see most of them again.  I live next to a Jewish frat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-12"><speaker>House </speaker><content>We are veering wildly off track. Please continue.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-13"><speaker>Adams </speaker><content>This woman's life is probably better off without sex. Eliminates most of her insecurity, she's immune to most advertising and can have honest relationships with men.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-14"><speaker>Adams </speaker><content>We've run every test and ruled out all the options. You're gonna have to accept she just doesn't want sex.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-15"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Lots of people don't have sex. The only people who don't want it are either sick, dead, or lying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-16"><speaker>Adams </speaker><content>So maybe she's lying. You think she's had a boyfriend on the side?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-17"><speaker>House </speaker><content>For ten years? Sticking around the whole time? Doesn't make sense.  What does… </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-18"><speaker>Park </speaker><content>Everybody lies. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>Followed your advice and took the night off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Seems to have done you some good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>Mm-hmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>Where's my husband?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>He's not in the hospital.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>So he just walked out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>All of the shift nurses had their hands full with a double code.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Perfectly reasonable explanation. Same thing happened to me. Couldn't find my keys for days.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>The police have been notified. I have staff searching.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>I'm sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>He has Alzheimer's! It's freezing outside, and he's sick! I mean, you don't even know what it is yet, do you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>The plasmapheresis hasn't had time to work, but TTP is our most likely—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>Okay, I'm just— I have to go look for him. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>Joseph </speaker><content>Hey, don't be an ass. Can't you see she's upset?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>House </speaker><content>No, she's guilty. 'Cause instead of being at her husband's side, she was under you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-16"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>Okay, that's— y—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-17"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Yeah, yeah, yeah… He already said I was an ass. Personally, I applaud your decision to step down off your cross and get on with your life, but your misplaced guilt is shutting down your brain. We need you to sit, focus, and answer our questions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-18"><speaker>House </speaker><content>So, at 6:00 a.m., the patient wakes up, and the first thing he sees…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-19"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>In moments of confusion, Alzheimer's patients regress to old routines.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-20"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So what would your husband do on a Saturday morning?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-21"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>Nothing. Be at home.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-22"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>What about a year ago? Or five years? Ten?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-23"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>I don't know, um, he… he trained for a marathon once. Soccer practice. We took a cooking class.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-24"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>That soccer trophy you were telling me about.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-25"><speaker>House </speaker><content>It's gone. Where was practice?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-26"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>It was close to here. On Chesterfield.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Okay, he comes, he thinks he's waiting for practice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Adams </speaker><content>He'd want to get out of the wind. What's somewhere he could see the kids arrive?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>On three.  One, two, three.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Not dead until he's warm and dead.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Get him to the ICU. Start him on extracorporeal circulation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>Adams </speaker><content>That'll raise his temperature too quickly, it'll cause acidosis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>House </speaker><content>We can deal with his metabolism crashing, we can't reverse brain damage if we go too slowly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Either way, we don't get his temperature above 95, it's not going to matter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>Adams </speaker><content>Multiple warm lavage is safer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Do what House says.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>He has no heartbeat, and he's not breathing. How can he not be dead?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>The body slows down when it cools, but it doesn't fully stop. We're warming his blood outside of his body, then putting it back. It'll raise his temperature enough that his heart should naturally start. Then we can shock it back into rhythm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>And if it doesn't start?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Then there's nothing we can do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>Adams </speaker><content>You think it's possible he knew what he was doing? Like some part of him gets what he's putting his wife through, so he tried to—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Kill himself? It's what I'd do if I were him. At least I wish I would.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>If you really l love them back, then… yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>That's really dark.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>It's not naive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-10"><speaker>Adams </speaker><content>I just believe people are capable of more than you do, apparently.  We've got brain activity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-11"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Temp's at 93. His heart should start soon. My dad left me alone to care for my alcoholic mom and raise my baby sister. I was just a teenager. I spent half my time changing diapers and the other half cleaning up my mom's vomit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-12"><speaker>Adams </speaker><content>But it must've been important that you stayed for both of them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-13"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Mom died after a few years. It was ugly and painful, and she went with me hating her. My sister ended up drinking half of her life away and hating me because I couldn't help. After mom, I had nothing left. So do I wish mom had used a gun instead of a bottle? Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-14"><speaker>Adams </speaker><content>I— I didn't know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-15"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>That's why I told you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-16"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Ventricular fibrillation. 300 milligrams amiodarone.  Careful. Once we establish rhythm, any accidental movement could crash him back into V-fib.  Clear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-17"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>We still have a long way to go. Cold can be protective to the brain, but there is a possibility of damage. We also need to confirm and treat whatever's making him sick.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>House </speaker><content>I just gotta do a standard battery of tests. Blood, urine, EEG…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Excuse me. I have to deal with someone who's having a panic attack.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>I specifically said the bet was off if you contacted the patient.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Exactly. Never said anything about the patient's husband.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>The deal was a medical reason why she doesn't have sex.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>House </speaker><content>I admit I was stuck, until I realized the medical issue was not hers but his. She's lying to compensate. It's a tale as old as time. Boy meets girl, girl falls for boy, boy says, "I'm asexual." Girl says, "yeah, me too."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>Your twisted logic can't hide the fact that tricking a patient into being tested is completely unethical.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Come on. Don't you think she deserves to know why her husband won't bend her over the kitchen counter? You love all that caring crap.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>You're not doing this out of the kindness of your heart. You're not even doing this out of medical curiosity.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-10"><speaker>House </speaker><content>I thought I made it clear I'm doing it for the cash.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-11"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>Two people are happy, and your natural impulse is to destroy it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-12"><speaker>House </speaker><content>How do you know she's happy? Did she tell you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-13"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>No, chirping birds flew out of her butt carrying a banner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-14"><speaker>House </speaker><content>All right, I admit that my natural impulse is to doubt peoples' claims to happiness, but yours is to be a sucker for them. You tell me which one's worse. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>Park </speaker><content>He just opened his eyes a little while ago. His heartbeat's doing well, and his body temperature is stabilized.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>There he is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>Park </speaker><content>Is that Portuguese?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>Yeah. Honey, I don't understand.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>Andres </speaker><content>Me sinto quente.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>Park </speaker><content>What's he saying?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>I don't know. I tried to learn when we got married, but I just — it's okay. It's okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>Park </speaker><content>His body temperature is rising. It's above normal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-9"><speaker>Park </speaker><content>I don't know.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Vomiting, liver, kidneys, and now fever.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>House </speaker><content>I don't want to tell you how to do your job, Dr. Foreman, since telling people how to do their job is your job, but when your less-than-competent administration of this hospital affects what's written on my whiteboard…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Get to the point.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>House </speaker><content>The word "fever." Could come from the patient's illness, or it could come from the fact that you allowed him to saunter out of your hospital and take a nap in the snow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Couldn't have caught a virus while he was outside. Fever came on too fast.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>The hypothermia could've caused cell necrosis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>House </speaker><content>TTP was the diagnosis when he walked out. Fever's a little high, but it still fits. We should continue plasmapheresis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>We're missing symptoms. We should add language loss and aggression.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Should we also add forgetfulness? He's got Alzheimer's.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>We've just been assuming.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-11"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Because the patient's wife said he exhibited both for a year.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-12"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>He's never hit her before or lost all his English. We have to consider any change since he's been admitted as relevant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-13"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Have to? Do I need to pull out another card?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-14"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Disseminated viral infection with encephalitis. Patient complained of a sore throat a few weeks ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-15"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Start him on Interferon.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Encephalitis makes his brain swell, which causes symptoms that are hard to distinguish from his Alzheimer's. With the Interferon his English should come back, and the aggression should subside.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>But you're not sure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Unfortunately, no.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>And you're not sure if he has brain damage from being frozen. So best-case scenario, I've just had a glimpse into his future?  I can't take care of him anymore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>Adams </speaker><content>Chances are his mental state will improve. You could get more time with him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>We married six months after I met him. A year after that, he started forgetting things. I've known my husband longer with his Alzheimer's than without. I've watched more of him disappear than I ever got to know. I just can't do this anymore.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>House </speaker><content>You lose. Blood work shows high levels of prolactin.  Add that to some peripheral red-green confusion, puts my money — excuse me, your money — soon to be my money, on a tumor near his pituitary. Probably started growing in his early teens.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>Lowering his libido and causing erectile dysfunction.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>House </speaker><content>A year on dopamine agonists, and he'll be a sex-crazed creep just like the rest of us, completely fascinated by Susie Cooper. I'd prefer to be paid in a single $100 bill. Always wanted to use one to light a cigar.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>Hooray for us. We disproved his asexuality. We also probably ruined his life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>House </speaker><content>He'll thank us. Then he'll doze off, and then in a couple hours, he'll thank us again. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>It could destroy his identity. It's like a gay person being told they're really straight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>House </speaker><content>So don't tell him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>Yeah, why bother telling a guy he has a tumor growing in his head? He'll notice it eventually, when it starts leaking out his ears.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>House </speaker><content>It's a slow-growing tumor. He'll probably die of boredom long before that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>House </speaker><content>You knew the second you told me about this case that I'd get involved. You wanted me to meddle. Because no matter how much you wanted to believe in this chaste romance, you didn't buy it either.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Where's that petition House's P.O. sent over about getting his ankle monitor off?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>Regina </speaker><content>On your desk.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>You played me. This whole thing was about your ankle monitor. You weren't trying to undermine my confidence; you were trying to inflate it. You manufactured conflict with me so eventually you could let me win.  You knew it was encephalitis, but you waited for me to say it because then with my ego boosted, you thought I'd be in the mood to take off your monitor because I'd think I could control you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>House </speaker><content>You're right. Take off my monitor. See, the beauty of the plan is that if it works, you think you can control me. If it fails, then you will actually have proven that you can control me. It's pretty genius.  These are your training wheels. If you think you're up to this job, it's time to lose them.  Second half of my plan might need work. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>V-fib. Two rounds of 360 without establishing a rhythm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>Adams </speaker><content>Wait, Dr. Foreman! </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>House </speaker><content>He's back.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>House </speaker><content>I sure hope this Alzheimer's drug trial is worth a lot to this hospital, 'cause we're wasting a crap-load of time and manpower just to let this guy watch his mind shrivel and keep his wife miserable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Heart attack while he was on Interferon rules out encephalitis, but I still think I'm right about the neural symptoms. It's probably aseptic meningitis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Would have seen meningial signs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Given his abnormal mental status, not necessarily.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Dr. Foreman, would you please reach under your chair?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>There's just wet gum under here. Where's the card?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>House </speaker><content>What card?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>I'm happy to leave if you have a better theory than aseptic meningitis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Toxins. This guy went on walkabout. Chances are he's done it before.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-10"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Wife keeps the doors on the house locked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-11"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Plenty of nasty stuff to get into during the middle of the night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-12"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>We asked about toxins on the history. The wife said she was sure to clear the house for her husband's safety.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-13"><speaker>House </speaker><content>I'm sure she succeeded. She's a PhD in toxicology, right? She's an ex-florist. Search the home for toxic plants, methyl bromide, any medications. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-14"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Stop. You're not infallible. You were wrong about encephalitis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-15"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Just before you were.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-16"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Run CSF tests. Find out what's causing the meningitis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-17"><speaker>House </speaker><content>You said you weren't gonna overrule me diagnostically.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-18"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>And you said I wouldn't be able to help it. Apparently, you were right about that one. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-19"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Fine. I'll look for toxins myself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-20"><speaker>Adams </speaker><content>You can't go to their house without Foreman's permission.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-21"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Don't need it. I'll talk to the toxicology PhD upstairs. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>House </speaker><content>What about gifts from South America? Anyone send any fruits or vegetables?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>I don't think so, no.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>House </speaker><content>I'm gonna need your boyfriend to collect samples of plants in and around your house. Toxins are the most…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>House </speaker><content>He's— he's repeating, "blue shack." You know what that is? Is it somewhere where pesticides may be kept?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>It's where we had our first date.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Do you have a cleaning lady who might bring her own supplies?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>What's he saying?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-8"><speaker>House </speaker><content>If it's not relevant to the case, I don't care. And neither should you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-9"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>Please. This might be the last time I ever know what he's thinking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-10"><speaker>Andres </speaker><content>La esta ela.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-11"><speaker>House and Natalie </speaker><content>There she is. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-12"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>He's still in there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-13"><speaker>Andres </speaker><content>Quem e ela?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-14"><speaker>House </speaker><content>He asked who you were.  Don't get your hopes up. Have your boyfriend give me those samples.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>Man </speaker><content>How'd you even know to look for a tumor?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>Well, Dr. House noticed hormone levels in your blood, and consulted me as an oncologist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>Kayla </speaker><content>Who cares how they found it, okay? They found it. Are there any side effects to the treatment?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>Some nausea, dizziness, and as the tumor shrinks, there will be behavioral changes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>Man </speaker><content>Like what?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>Well… the tumor interferes with certain natural systems. Um…  It lowers libido and causes erectile dysfunction.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>Man </speaker><content>Eh… Y-you mean the treatment will, um… m-make me want to have sex? Wh-what if I don't want the treatment?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>I would strongly advise…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>Kayla </speaker><content>You have a brain tumor, okay? You have to have the treatment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-10"><speaker>Man </speaker><content>Okay, look, I know who I am, okay? And I'm not one of them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-11"><speaker>Kayla </speaker><content>Hey, look, we'll adjust. Okay? We can go through this together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-12"><speaker>Man </speaker><content>You mean have sex? I can't make you do that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-13"><speaker>Kayla </speaker><content>Maybe it won't be so bad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-14"><speaker>Man </speaker><content>It'll be terrible.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-15"><speaker>Kayla </speaker><content>It's actually pretty fun. From what I remember.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-16"><speaker>Man </speaker><content>But you said that…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-17"><speaker>Kayla</speaker><content>I know. I know. I wanted to spend my life with you. And I knew that meant making certain sacrifices. But a girl has needs.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>With respect, Mr. Laffont, that's only because we temporarily shut down our Diagnostics Department. It's up and running again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>No, no, I just… Those flowers are from last week. They should be dead by now.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>It's Reye's syndrome. Patient had a sore throat a few weeks ago before he was admitted.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Reye's in adults is a reach.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Not if he took aspirin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Aspirin in adults is a reach. Especially in a house with locked medicine cabinets.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Wasn't in the medicine cabinet. Wife used to run a floral company. Still does a few orders from home. She uses crushed aspirin in the water to make the flowers last longer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>House </speaker><content>So the husband has a sore throat, takes an aspirin without her knowing, realizes he's got a sore throat, takes an aspirin, realizes he's got a sore throat… Stop me whenever you like. Have Chase start him on steroids.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-7"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Already did.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-8"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Then why're you telling me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-9"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>'Cause I wanted you to hear it from me. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>Here I am.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>Andres </speaker><content>Your eye. What happened?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>Natalie </speaker><content>It's nothing I can't handle.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>MRI confirmed macroprolactinoma. He's doing the treatment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>House </speaker><content>And the wife?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Come on. You saved a man's life. Course-corrected two peoples' wildly screwed-up world views. It's not bad for a day's work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>I think they were happy. Even if it was based on lies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>We can't smoke in here. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-6"><speaker>House </speaker><content>We also can't summon people into the clinic based on a lie motivated by a petty bet. And yet it happens. It's an imperfect world.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-7"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Well?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-8"><speaker>Wilson </speaker><content>Disgustingly satisfying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-9"><speaker>Uniformed man </speaker><content>Is one of you Dr. House?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-10"><speaker>Uniformed man </speaker><content>I got an order here to deactivate and remove his ankle monitor.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Hi, sis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>I know. I thought of you on mom's birthday.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>Yeah, yeah. Fine. I just…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>Chase </speaker><content>wanted to see how you were.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>Foreman </speaker><content>Now get out. I have work to do.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>House </speaker><content>Whoops.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>