<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>
<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>Don't bother. He's dead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're dead too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content> The fire isn't.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>You might want to get up and start heading for the exit signs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>For all I know, I already am up. More interesting question is why would I hallucinate an ex-employee who I last saw with a self-inflicted gunshot wound, as opposed to someone more… busty?  Care to explain why you're here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>The dead guy. Who is he? How'd you meet him?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Oliver</speaker><content>I was in a car accident last month.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I won a swimming trophy in high school. Your turn.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Oliver</speaker><content>I-I ran out of pain medication. I got an orbital fracture. It's just taking ages to heal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Take off your shirt. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Oliver</speaker><content>My eye's up here. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Orbital fracture means your face went into the windshield, which means your chest went into the steering wheel. Painkillers can suppress heart rate, so unless you want me to kill you, take off your shirt, let me do a heart exam.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I also wanted to see the ring of burns around your collarbone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Oliver</speaker><content>How'd you know?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The codeine allergy you told the nurse about. That's shorthand for "give me the strong stuff," which matches your seen-better-days-because-my-life-fell-apart suit. The two old burns on your fingers mean you tend to nod off with a cigarette in your hand. No reason you shouldn't do that with one in your mouth. May all your doctors be stupid.  Hold on a second. That bruising around your belly button.  Well, you might get some fun drugs out of this after all.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Cullen's sign. But the ultrasound showed air as well as blood. Now, I know what you're thinking. Hemorrhagic pancreatitis. But I also know what I'm thinking. Doesn't explain the pneuomoperitoneum.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>You took a new case?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>You ran tests yourself?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I saw the chance to help someone in need, and I instinctively — Oh, no, wait, that was someone else's instinct.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Wilson is dying. Your parole officer is probably on his way here right now. How are you possibly in a good mood?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Did you never see Dead Poets Society? Carpe diem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Air in his abdomen could mean blah, blah, blah. Blah?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>But blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Blah. Blah, blah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Nobody cares about the medicine. It was a perforated ulcer. Laparotomy to find the hole in his tummy and close it up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>You didn't answer the team's question.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Which is weird, because normally, when I talk to my own employees, I'm under oath and hooked up to a lie detector.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>You were looking at six months of prison instead of five months of Wilson. Why happy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Obviously I had a plan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>Obviously, obviously you had a plan. The more interesting question is why you didn't tell the team. I think it's because part of you knew from the start that the plan wouldn't work.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I need a meeting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I'm busy. Call my office.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Yes… because wobbly tables don't just unwobble themselves.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I need a meeting.  Thanks for fitting me in. My team has eight urgent, life-or-death cases that they've been waiting for me to accept or reject.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>When is that not true?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, right now, for one. But tell my parole board that I'm taking all eight… that no one else can crack them; that you need me here for the next five months or eight people will die.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You're asking me to perjure myself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's a tiny, white lie. No offense. Especially since, from what I hear, nothing black is tiny. Except your penis, I guess.  You really think I wanted to cave in that ceiling? It was a prank that went wrong. Dock my pay, sue me—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Felony vandalism should have added another year or two to your sentence. It's a miracle the parole board agreed to six months.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content> I will go to jail, eventually. I will pay the price. I just rather that Wilson didn't. Come on, be a friend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content> Okay. But whatever cases you have, you have to take them all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>"Be a friend"?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>How many fingers am I holding up?  Of course you know it's three, because you know everything I know. Everything my smack-addled brain can remember, including that I actually said, "be a friend."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>My point wasn't that you said it. My point was, once again, why? I think it's because part of you knew you were gonna need a friend. Part of you knew the plan, even when it was working, wouldn't work. And right now, I'm curious about why you're sitting on the ground instead of heading for the door.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>Guess we’ve figured out why you're seeing me; your suicidal friend.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>He'll call you twice a day. Then his wife will call you twice a day to make sure she understands what he told her you told him, which she won't because he didn't.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Frankel</speaker><content>Maybe you want to give this one to Connors.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Where's House?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Don't know, don't care. Working.  Excuse me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>No one has seen or heard from him since two nights ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'm sure he's enjoying himself. Last time he went to prison, he maxed out his credit cards.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Last time he went to prison, he thought he had you waiting for him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You think he could've done something stupid?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I think stupid is our best-case scenario.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>Why do you want to kill yourself?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, here's a reason. I can't even get stoned without some annoying jerk deciding I need to be deeply analyzed. Isn't this just an incredibly simple calculation? I'm going to jail, losing my job, losing my best friend. Do I need more?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>You think that's the sum total of who you are? A doctor? A friend to Wilson?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm also a tremendous baritone. Now go away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Kutner</speaker><content>Even with your subconscious, you're evasive.  Death's not interesting. You exist for what's interesting. Puzzles, ideas, analysis. Death is the opposite of a cool puzzle. It's eternal nothingness. But you don't find life interesting anymore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>Amber</speaker><content>Stop being an idiot.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Can I have Kutner back, please?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Amber</speaker><content>How much pathetic wallowing do I have to sit through?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>How are things in hell? Is the humidity the big issue?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Amber</speaker><content>What happened next with the guy's medical case?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>Amber</speaker><content>Exactly. Why am I, meaning you, still obsessing about this case? Obviously we think it's relevant to why we're still sitting on the floor of a burning building.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>There was a code.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Gotta be a clot in his lungs. We need to get him to an O.R.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>No time. His O-2 stats are falling. We have to suck it out here. Bedside embolectomy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Float a catheter through his heart and his oxygenation will get even worse. He'll die before we can finish the procedure.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>House, we need a call here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>What are you doing? What did you give him?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Five… four… three… two…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Oliver</speaker><content> Ahhh! Arg!! Ahhh!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Naloxone. We should've got suspicious when his visiting cousin signed in as "Mr. Tar H. Horse." Heroin caused the respiratory distress. The naloxone turned off the receptors, caused your distress.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Oliver</speaker><content> I'm not gonna stop doing drugs! It's reality that sucks!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're saying I'm lying… to my subconscious?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Amber</speaker><content>People do it all the time. And like it or not, you are a person.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He said every one of those things.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Amber</speaker><content>But not then and not like that. This guy was going nuts from the naloxone. He couldn't be rational if you wanted him to be, which you did. Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I compressed the story a little—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>Amber</speaker><content>Context matters. You never talk to patients for non-diagnostic reasons, but this guy…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Feeling better?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-17"><speaker>Oliver</speaker><content>I'm not gonna stop doing drugs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You were a stockbroker. Son of a stockbroker. Married, children.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-19"><speaker>Oliver</speaker><content>I was miserable.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-20"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, you say you were miserable because you need to rationalize screwing it up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-21"><speaker>Oliver</speaker><content>Except I didn't. I mean, I-I did. But I'm not miserable. Not anymore.  I had a ski injury and painkillers weren't enough, and a friend of mine gave me some heroin. The second it entered my veins, it was like… God had taken over my body. It was like there was no more pain or unhappiness in my life or anybody else's.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-22"><speaker>House</speaker><content>But then you lost everything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-23"><speaker>Oliver</speaker><content>Everything wasn't enough. Because it's reality that sucks.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Amber</speaker><content>Are you arguing that he's a good role model?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He's happy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Amber</speaker><content>He's dead. You heard what you wanted to hear. The more interesting question — always — is why you wanted to hear it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You're stealing this guy's oxygen?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>There's oxygen everywhere.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You passed on all your cases, reassigned them to other doctors.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>They weren't interesting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>They were my reason for getting your sentence delayed!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, well, I guess you'll have to tell the parole board something else. Maybe that I was in the O.R. the entire day the ceiling collapsed, so I couldn't have caused the plumbing problem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You set me up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Not really. You were going to basically perjure yourself so that I could delay jail time. Doesn't it make more sense to actually perjure yourself so that I can actually avoid jail time?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Why are you doing this? Why are you risking destroying yourself?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>There's no risk. I know you. You'll do the honest thing. You'll lie.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-11"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>No.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He's happy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Amber</speaker><content>He's dead.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Amber</speaker><content>You weren't worried.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Of course I was worried. My plan fell through.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Amber</speaker><content>The plan didn't matter. Your plan to replace that plan didn't matter. Wilson didn't matter. Jail didn't matter. The only thing that mattered, the only thing that ever mattered, was the puzzle.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I noticed a slight twitch in his thenar eminence, which meant…  You're dying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>Oliver</speaker><content>Because my thumb's a little shaky?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Plus the thinning in the muscle, plus that speech you gave at Yankee Stadium saying you were the luckiest man on the face of the earth. Add them up, it means ALS.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>Oliver</speaker><content>Lou Gehrig's disease? You're trapped in your body; you can't move or speak while you just die?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If it makes you feel any better, at this rate, it'll be fast.  You're not symmetrical.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>Amber</speaker><content>Wait. Now you're standing at the door. What happened in the meantime?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And lo, there was a miraculous wonder — I walked across the room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>Amber</speaker><content>No, you just skipped over a chunk of conversation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He swore that he would live a better and more selfless life in his remaining time, blah, blah, blah. After two blahs, I'd heard enough. I moved to the door.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>Amber</speaker><content>No, you're avoiding it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Do you smell smoke?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-12"><speaker>Amber</speaker><content> Fair enough.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content> You're not symmetrical. The veins on your right side are distended.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-14"><speaker>Oliver</speaker><content>What does that mean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content> There's a bulge in your superclavicular notch. There's something in there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-16"><speaker>Oliver</speaker><content>What?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, I'm not that good a doctor.  Good news: your case is fascinating. And good news for you: you're gonna live.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content> You've inhaled a small branch, probably while you were realizing that it's all worth it, while you were passed out on a park bench. Anyone else would have coughed it up, but 'cause you're a junkie, your cough reflex is suppressed.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>Oliver</speaker><content> And it grew?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Not unless you also inhaled a chunk of the sun and a drip-irrigation system, you idiot. It set off an auto-immune reaction, which — I can't help saying this — was the root of all your problems. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>Amber</speaker><content>You're smiling.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I was, and now I'm not. Because a moment's fun a few days ago does not trump a friend dying.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>Amber</speaker><content> Yeah, it does, you idiot. 'Cause after he's dead, you cry for a while, and then you go back to doing what you love.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Every patient that I've had, 70 years from now, they'll all be as dead as Wilson. Everybody dies. It's meaningless.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>Amber</speaker><content> When you solve a puzzle, the world makes sense, and everything feels right. And you'll always have another one, because people always get sick. It's shallow and it's insignificant, but if you don't give a damn if idiots live, why would you possibly give a damn about shallowness? It makes you happy. And why would you need more than that? Go home.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Foreman!  House would never leave food out here rotting for days.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>His suitcases are in his closet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>If we had handled this differently—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>We did the right thing.  Hello? I'll let his accountant know.  House no-showed on a hooker two nights ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> Outgoing calls. Hooker… me, I didn't pick up. Chinese place…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Wait, wait, wait. Who's that? He called four times.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I don't know.</content></utterance>
</scene>


<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>Male Patient</speaker><content>It's a total disaster. Do you have any idea how hard it is to schedule a cable appointment with the hours that I work?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>House has been missing for two days. We know he talked to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Anything you can tell us about his mental state, or where he was headed — anything at all—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content> Would be a breach of confidentiality and a violation of the law.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Not if he's a danger to himself or someone else.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>Male Patient</speaker><content>Is this coming out of our 50 minutes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Is this your douche bag group?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content> Excuse me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>What makes you think he's a danger to himself?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>He hasn't been home, but he didn't take anything with him, not even his cell.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-11"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You're not saying anything, which means he didn't specifically mention suicide, but you came out here to talk to us, so he must have said something that worries you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-12"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content> There are other ways of reaching oblivion.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-13"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Vicodin?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-14"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>He always has his Vicodin. There's no reason to call a shri— His last patient was a heroin addict.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-15"><speaker>Nolan</speaker><content>So I guess we're all done here. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-16"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>The guy's address has gotta be in the file.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>What about God? You were leaving, and then you stopped. Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Your theory is I'm not leaving, because I believe in God? What, he's calling me home?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>Maybe falling through that floor was a sign. Maybe that the universe hates you. Something. You really don't believe? Really? Not in some deep crack of some remote recess of some dark corner of your mind?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No. Except that some deep crack of some remote recess of some dark corner is here telling me—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>That's enough. In a burning building, facing imminent death, that's more than enough.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Pascal's wager is facile.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>Saying it's facile is facile. Why is it wrong?  Don't be logical, be desperate. You gotta have something to hold on to.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You can't live your life based on something you don't believe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-9"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>But you can end your life based on something you don't believe? What about love? I lived with you for years. I know you believe in love.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Foreman wouldn't help me, which means I need you to take the fall.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You do remember I'm dying, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Which is you will never spend a day in jail. Fresh-faced, cancer-ridden. It's tough to do both, but you pull it off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Your fingerprints are all over those hockey tickets.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I never admitted to flushing anything. My prints make sense if I gave those tickets to you as an incentive to stay alive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>And I was so angry that you didn't respect my dying wishes, I took thousands of dollars of season tickets and flushed them down toilets?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>All you have to do is create reasonable doubt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Great, what if I do more than that? What if I end up in jail? Or spending my final months in endless hearings?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That is a risk you are willing to take.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I have a reputation. I have a legacy that could—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Wilson… I don't want to lose this time with you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-12"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Thanks. I knew I could count on you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-14"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Wait! Wait.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content> You want the fries back?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-16"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'm not gonna take the fall.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Don't do this to me, Wilson. This is our only option.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-18"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Exactly, because you overplayed your hand with Foreman, because you knew you had me as a backstop. Even with me dying, you-you just assumed I'd be here to bail you out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Since you're here, and you are bailing me out, it seems like a pretty safe assumption.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-20"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Hey! I won't be here soon. If I do this, I'm teaching you that your bad behavior will always be rewarded. You need to learn—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content>How to act when you're gone? 'Cause if that's the lesson, we got a really great opportunity coming up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-22"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You'll just try to find someone else, and it won't work, and it shouldn't work!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-23"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So that's the great wisdom you're imparting? That I'll always be alone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-24"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>There's only one person you can count on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-25"><speaker>House</speaker><content> I thought there were two.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-26"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> I need to do this… for you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>Wilson's right. He's always right. He's always been your good side.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I always wondered why I photographed so poorly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>And because he's always played that role, you've never had to develop a conscience of your own.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>People don't change. Consciences don't spontaneously develop.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>You're wrong, Greg. Which is… why you'll be better off without him. You've been looking to him to find what you have gotta find within yourself.  Something you can find.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>Hold your child.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>This is a reason to die. This is what my life could've been, not what it can be.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>If it could've been, you're capable of it now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're married. Cuddy's gone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>We aren't the only two people who could love you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Why settle so easily?  These are just idiotic fantasies…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-12"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>Greg, don't.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>… at odds with every logical bone in my body.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-14"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>Get up.  You do not have to die in here!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Is this hell? An eternity of people trying to convince me to live?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content> Who says I'm here to convince you to live?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're the last one I thought would hate me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>I don't hate you. I love you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And yet you think I deserve to die.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>But not as a punishment. As a reward. I think… you've suffered enough. You've given enough. I think you deserve a chance to just… give up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Like Wilson did?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content> Like Wilson did. You accepted his choice — that ending the pain was better than the pain. Why can't you give yourself that gift?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>This is the address House's patient gave?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Everybody lies.  You smell smoke?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>Just let go. Just go to sleep.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I had a chance to avoid this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>You had many chances, and you blew them all up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, this was different.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>They're all different, but the reasons are all the same. You're arrogant. You're self-destructive. You only care about yourself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That moment with the patient… the chunk of the conversation I skipped over… I told him he was dying.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If it makes you feel any better, at this rate, it'll be fast.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>Oliver</speaker><content> Let me take the fall. For you, for that prank.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content> You don't owe me anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>Oliver</speaker><content>You tried to save me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I failed. Motives don't matter. Only actions.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>Oliver</speaker><content>Trying is an action. Why are you trying to talk me out of this? You just fake the records. You say I came into the clinic last week. I'll tell the cops you treated me like crap, so I stole your tickets and flushed 'em.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Thank you.  And you're doing this because you're dying?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>Oliver</speaker><content>I'm doing this because I have nothing left to lose.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content> So when you were living, you did nothing for anyone and you didn't care. Now that you're dying, you're willing to help a virtual stranger. Which means you're a better person dying than you ever were living, and the world is a better place because I didn't save you. Which makes me wonder why I'm about to tell you… you're not symmetrical.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-10"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>What's your point? That you cared about him more than you cared about yourself? You cared about the puzzle more than you cared about yourself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If I kept it to myself, then it would just be a puzzle, but I opened my mouth because I thought it was more.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-12"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>You know it's the same, or you wouldn't be bickering with me while the flames lick at your feet. You're afraid of this decision, and you are trying to argue until fate takes it out of your hands. You're taking the cowardly way out. And worse… you're too cowardly to even admit you're taking the cowardly way out.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're right. But I can change.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>He could've gotten out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>People are found sometimes, even in… collapsed—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I think they're pulling a body out.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Coroner confirms it's him. Dental records match. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>House hired me when no one else would.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>He got me fired.  He gave me the guts to get fired.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>Masters</speaker><content>He gave me the courage to quit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>Blythe</speaker><content>Gregory was — he was a good son. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>Stacy</speaker><content>He was a trying boyfriend, but I… never stopped loving him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-6"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>He was my husband for real.  I couldn't help but love him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-7"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>He was my boss. And… my employee. And both times… I learned from him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>He made me a better parent, whether he meant to or not.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-9"><speaker>Thirteen</speaker><content> He was willing to kill me. And I'll always be grateful.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-10"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>He wasn't always easy to deal with.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-11"><speaker>Cameron</speaker><content>But somewhere in there… he knew how to love.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-12"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> He was my friend. The thing you have to… remember — the thing you can't forget is that Gregory House saved lives.  He was a healer. And-and in the end…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-13"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>House was an ass.  He mocked anyone —patients, co-workers, his dwindling friends — anyone who didn't measure up to his insane ideals of integrity. He claimed to be on some heroic quest for truth, but the truth is, he was a bitter jerk who liked making people miserable. And he proved that by dying selfishly, numbed by narcotics, without a thought of anyone. A betrayal of everyone who cared about him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-14"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Phone. A million times he needed me, and the one time that I needed him— Oh, come on. This is a funeral. Just get it.  Well, this is embarrassing. Could've sworn I turned this off.  This isn't my phone.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Hi.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>How?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I got out of the back of the building.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>The body—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Just switched the dental records.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You're destroying your entire life. You can't go back from this. You'll go to jail for years. You can never be a doctor again.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'm dead, Wilson. How do you want to spend your last five months?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>When the cancer starts getting really bad…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Cancer's boring.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>