<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>
<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>Let's get back to Phil and Diane.  Phil's been having a hard time finding work, and Diane wants him to talk to her about his fear, his disappointment. And Phil wants Diane to trust him that they'll get through this, ideally, without having to keep discussing…  feelings. Not your exact words, but am I wrong?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>And most guys out there are the same way, but ladies, if you're feeling frustrated, remember… it's not our fault. We were raised to be strong, not emotional, to deny vulnerability, not embrace it. And do you know what that makes us?  Dinosaurs.  Nobody needs us to hunt wild animals for food. Nobody needs us to cut down trees to build shelter. They need us to evolve, to catch up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>Since the 1960s, women's roles have shifted radically.  And as -- uh, as their-- in--as their roles have changed, so have women, they've -- they've, uh -- well, they've become tougher, and more demanding of us. They're partners. And–and -- who can blame them? Who –- who can -- who can, uh… expecting us to -- to do this—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Marlene</speaker><content>Joe! Joe! Joe! Joe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Aide</speaker><content> We need an ambulance.</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You want?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I'm good.  Your limp's almost gone.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It pains me to interrupt the collegial banter, it pains me even more to listen to it continue. 38-year-old man. Spikes a fever and collapses during a speaking engagement. E.R. checks out blood volume, cardiac function, and autonomic reflexes, all normal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Patient makes a living telling men to behave more like women. I'm surprised you didn't throw psych symptoms into the differential. Either way, could be a cerebral AVM.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>E.R. did a head CT. No sign of AVM. Decent thought, though.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The patient's philosophy makes perfect sense. Its only flaw is that it's impossible. Evolution does not work that way. You can't talk legs onto a fish. We're gonna go extinct, and we're gonna do it drinking scotch and driving muscle cars. Am I right?  Am I—  Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Cephalic fibromuscular dysplasia?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>It doesn't explain the fever. The patient's talking about compromise. If you don't think that's possible, you don't think relationships are possible.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Anyone in this room in a position to disprove that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>This guy's just playing to his audience. Women are, by far, the biggest consumers of the self-help industry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>He could have a pulmonary embolism. Clot in his lung increases right ventricular afterload, drops the blood flow to his brain. We should do a pulmonary angiogram.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Patient lacks major risk factors for a P.E. Doesn't rule it out, just makes it unlikely. Maybe we start with a D-dimer?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> Less invasive than the angiogram. Good idea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Fine.  Now, I am hereby searching for a number two. So I'm eating a lot of bran.  Also, I want a team leader. Someone to fill Foreman's old job.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Why?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're right. We don't need any more structure. It's not like we had a near-fatal stabbing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, if it isn't the old ball and Ukraine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-18"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Who's that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-19"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>His wife.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Dominika.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>House. You survived prison.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And you Atlantic City, where they also have gangs and pruno, but slightly less recidivism.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>I start Ukrainian food truck business. After gambling — win, lose — everybody likes a little knish.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're here, and I seem to remember throwing out a bunch of certified letters from immigration. I'm assuming there's a connection.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>Our green card interview is in four days. They come to the apartment, they ask questions about marriage, vacations, family history, what side of the bed each sleep on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>We've never taken a vacation, I don't like your family, and on top. I hear Kiev is lovely this time of year. And your mother, who may or may not be dead for all I know, misses you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>Can it be that genius doctor is afraid to take on a silly government apparatchik?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, I would say more not interested than afraid, but why quibble?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-10"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>Then I go to plan "B." Make you an offer that cannot be refused.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>How long you been doing seminars?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>The marriage counseling, just, uh, the past couple years. Before that, I did corporate coaching.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Can't imagine the same advice works for both audiences. Guess you shifted with the market?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Marlene</speaker><content>There's nothing cynical about my husband. He and I—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>No, it's okay. I get it. What guy thinks men should be more like women? A macho jerk who got a big wake-up call courtesy of three drunks who beat the crap outta me outside a sports bar in Milwaukee.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I'm guessing that explains the broken wrist in your medical history?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>Those morons did me the biggest favor of my life. I realized I'd sacrificed my health because I couldn't back down from an argument over football. Meeting Marlene was the final piece in the puzzle. She changed my career, my diet. She gave me a whole new direction in life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>We'll need to know exactly how you changed your diet, and when.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Need my apartment key back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>If you're breaking up with me, can we at least talk about it first?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Maybe if you weren't all nag and no shag.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I don't sleep with married men.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I'll get a copy made.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You're an ex-con. If you get caught perjuring yourself to Homeland Security, you'll end up back in jail.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And that would be troubling if there was the slightest chance that we'd get caught.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You barely know each other. You've got about five minutes to remake yourselves into a convincing married couple. And… why? Dominika gets a green card. What's in this for you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>This is what men do for the women they pretend to love. Also, she's paying me 30,000 bucks once we pass. Apparently knishes sell like hotcakes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> Lab results.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Afraid you're gonna have to finish your nag later.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I said I think it's stupid, right? Then I think I'm done.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-13"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>D-dimer came back normal. Rules out pulmonary embolism.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-14"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>And our patient's a true believer about the follies of masculinity. He underwent a spiritual overhaul three years ago. He also went off gluten and red meat. Unfortunately, that doesn't explain any of his symptoms.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>One of those points is not absurd.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-16"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>What's absurd about a change of heart? What this guy believes is making him a better person. He's going against his baser instincts.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>"Base" meaning foundational. Meaning things we are biologically programmed to do. Yes, perfectly natural that he stopped doing that stuff.  You know, that's the kind of lapse that could take you out of the running for team leader.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-18"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I feel surprisingly okay with that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Comes with a 50-buck-a-week raise.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-20"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I'm in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-21"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You don't want to do that. Might need your dignity later in life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-22"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You didn't. And she could be on her way to living the dream unless the rest of you nut up and give her—  This spiritual overhaul… did it come after a physical overhaul? A major injury of some kind?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-23"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Bar fight. But there's no way a broken wrist explains—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-24"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Adams, come with me.  You too. You guys… get a copy of that made. </content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Did those dudes bend your ball sack like Beckham? Three years ago. The bar fight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>This is Dr. House. He has a theory.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Oh, Dr. Adams, would you mind?  I asked you a question. I assume you know the answer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>Yeah, I took a couple serious knees to the groin.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Wha — what has gotten into me? Dr. Chase.  Just pick it up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>Do you know what's wrong with me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Nothing that The Golden Girls couldn't have handled in 23 hilarious minutes. You had a hot flash. Those guys kicked your guys hard enough to do lasting damage. You didn't even look when presented with two reasonably attractive tuchi.  Yeah, I said it!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-8"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>I was listening to my doctor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>People generally listen with their ears, leaving their eyes free to wander. I'm guessing that your testosterone level is just below "Bieber." Do a blood test to confirm, and start hormone replacement. It's no wonder that you think women are so great. You've basically been one for the last three years.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Tests confirm House is right. Low testosterone explains all your symptoms. They should go away with replacement therapy. Uh, we're gonna give you a fairly high dose. Over time, your personal physician may reduce it a little.  Just need you to turn around.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Marlene</speaker><content>Will the shots increase his libido?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>Are you worried about that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-4"><speaker>Marlene</speaker><content>No. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-5"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>Have you been unsatisfied?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-6"><speaker>Marlene</speaker><content>No. No, it's just… Well, it's usually me that initiates things. Sometimes I–I think maybe you aren't that attracted to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-7"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>Are you crazy?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>With these injections, you will see an increase in sex drive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-9"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>Okay, great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-10"><speaker>Marlene</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-11"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-12"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>All done.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-13"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>Okay.  Oh, something's wrong. I think I peed myself.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-14"><speaker>Marlene</speaker><content>Is that from the testosterone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-15"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> It couldn't be. I don't think you're going home just yet.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>It's not a plumbing problem. Means it's probably neurological.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>And?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content> And name Dominika's three brothers.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Uh… Volodymyr, Oleksiy, and…  aaugf.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-5"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Low testosterone is off the table as a symptom. Guy got his nuts cracked three years ago. Don't need to look much further than that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So his hose just happens to spring a leak at the same time he's in a hospital for a totally unrelated problem.  Fjodor.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>It's Fedir.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>If low testosterone means I can't get sick with something else, then punch me in the junk right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I would, if it weren't redundant. Is Fedir the one who married Mykola?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-10"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content> Mykola is… Dominika's uncle?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-11"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>How is it you can retain every detail of our habits and personal lives, and none of this?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>'Cause I find it hard to remember things I don't give a crap about. Ergo, Dominika has one brother, and his name is Al.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-13"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Maybe the testicular damage set the stage for something worse. Multiple Sclerosis causes incontinence, and progresses faster in men with low T.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Way to stay on point. It's that kind of leadership that's putting you at the head of the pack.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-15"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>There is no pack. She's the only applicant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, that's settled, then. Have your underlings do an LP and get a cranio-spinal MRI to check for plaques associated with M.S. I will go tell Foreman about your promotion.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="8-17"><speaker>Chase and Adams</speaker><content>Wait.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>So nobody cares about the job till I apply, and suddenly it's the last limited-edition light saber at Comic-Con.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Just seems like it should go to someone with more… seniority.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Meaning you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I said "more," not "most."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Meaning you or Taub.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>House is a dictator. Second in command is a meaningless position.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Doesn't look meaningless on my resume.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Doesn't have to be meaningless at all. The right person could turn it into something. Get the department running smoothly.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I wonder who that "right person" could be.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>House is the head of the department. It's only fair that a woman should hold the other position of authority.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Yeah, let's go affirmative action on this, because then I'll definitely win.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>This is what House wants. Wind us up and watch us fight over an empty title, which would make us extra stupid because of what we've just been through. We should let him choose whoever he wants and move on.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>So if these proteins are in my spinal fluid, that means I have M.S.?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Proteins may indicate M.S. There's no one definitive test. That's why Dr. House ordered an MRI as well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>This is anesthetic. It's a scary diagnosis. But advances are being made. Several drugs approved just this year.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>To be honest, at the moment, I'm feeling a little more worried about the testosterone injections. It's making me feel, uh, different. Just kind of amped. I went through this big life change, and it felt really… meaningful. But what if it was all just chemistry?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Loss of testosterone could have been a factor, but think of it as a catalyst. It got you to reevaluate. Now you know what's important. You can choose to hold onto that. Right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>It's certainly worth trying.  Deep breath. Stay very still.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Just tell House to drop the whole team leader thing. That's the only way it'll go away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>I don't think it's such a bad idea. A little more structure in your department couldn't hurt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Yeah. House is doing this because of his great love of structure, not because he wants us to turn on each other.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>So don't do that. It makes sense to have someone in there with a little more accountability.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>As long as it's not Adams. She sees the whole thing as an opportunity to remake the department in her image. Or Park, for obvious reasons. And Taub's got the kids. He's pretty busy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>Are you seriously angling for a job that you mocked its fate the whole time I had it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I don't want the job.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Foreman</speaker><content>You just don't want anyone else to have it. This'll be great.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Your grandmother's kind of sexy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>That is Taras Shevchenko, the greatest Ukrainian poet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Is he the guy behind "There once was a man from Kremenchuk"?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>Help me move coffee table.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Well, then where will we have coffee? And by "coffee" I mean scotch.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>Coffee and booze are artificial high for me. High is in exercise.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-7"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>Dance aerobics. Fun, and good for the butt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-8"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>Whoo!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Amy Grant?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I know. But there's a hot girl jumping up and down in my living room, so…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-11"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>Aww!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-12"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>You have a limited amount of time to learn a ton of uninteresting facts. Welcome to my wheelhouse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You brought a protractor?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-14"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>You never know when you might need to make a pie chart.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Looks like someone is currying favor for the team leader position.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-16"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Yes. We'll be using a basic alphabet technique with a mnemonic multiplier. In high school, they called me "The Bookie Monster."  Pop quiz. Where did you get the candlesticks?  On three. One, two, three.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Morocco.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-18"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>Denver.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-19"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Drink up. It's gonna be a long night.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>You really think this guy's gonna hulk out once the hormones kick in?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Some male lizards do push-ups to attract mates. When scientists gave them extra testosterone, they did push-ups until they died. Same drive you took advantage of to get Chase to carry a box of files down to your car yesterday.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Periventricular and subcortical white matter are clean. So you're saying masculinity is ingrained and irrational.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I'm saying it's pointless to try—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-5"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>By extension, you're also saying femininity is enlightened and rational. It's the way we should all be, guys just are incapable of it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content> Brain stem and cord are clean.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-7"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>Is it okay if I scratch my nose?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-8"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Go ahead.  Guess he doesn't have M.S.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-9"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>Something's wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-10"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Is it your hand?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="13-11"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>No, it's my eyes. I'm–I'm seeing double.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content> Smile. It's your honeymoon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content> So what causes double vision on top of all the other symptoms?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content> It's not a brain tumor or we would've seen it on the scans. Eye exam didn't offer anything conclusive.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Let's do some winter shots. Wardrobe change.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Thyroid eye disease in conjunction with Graves.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Thyroid level was normal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Check it out. Simpson traded this in exchange for me helping out on some of my days off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Quite the display of initiative and leadership.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>But you're way too smart to fall for a blatant bribe like that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Or a blatant flaunting of cleavage. Like those.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-11"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>What happened to not letting House get to you? You're like lemmings, marching off the cliff of competitive humiliation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-12"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>All I'm doing is my job. House has indicated that he considers me attractive. There's nothing wrong with me using my strengths to my advantage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-13"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>With an argument like that, maybe you should just drop down to your knees and — I mean, unless that's not your strength.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-14"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>Oh, big hug, big man. It's cold out here.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-15"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>At the risk of derailing this very productive photo shoot and bickering session, what about myasthenia gravis? Extra-ocular muscle weakness leads to double vision, atonic bladder leads to incontinence. Could've been triggered when his T got really low.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-16"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content> Ooh, a little one. He'd be a good pick.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Smooth. You let the rest of them compete, tear each other to pieces, then you swoop in with a save. Start the patient on IVIG and plasmapheresis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-18"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Can you handle that, please? I need a minute.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, make it quick. We're doin' Memphis.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You think you want this, but it's a bad idea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I was gonna go Dollywood, but I'm not sure I could pull off that wig.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Everybody was playing nice, and in your world, nice doesn't solve cases, but after what happened, a little bonding is a good thing.  We still have ideas, we still argue. Maybe it could work better if we appreciate each other.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>That was impressive. You said that whole thing without once moving your lips.  The ones you're not moving.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Oh. I get it. I won't play along with your stupid games, so I'm no longer a man. Clever.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Actually, you won't play along with my stupid games because you're no longer a man. Still clever, though. Studies have shown that raising kids lowers testosterone levels in men. The more involved you are, the lower it gets.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Right. Having kids has neutered me. Or maybe it's helped me finally grow up.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>How are you feeling?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>As long as I keep my eyes closed, pretty good. Really good, actually. I got energy, I feel confident, clear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Testosterone does tend to perk you up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>Marlene</speaker><content> Hey, Hon. I brought you a burger.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>Really?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>Marlene</speaker><content>You're in the hospital. Eat whatever you want.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>You're the best wife ever. And I'm not just saying that because of how great your ass looks in those jeans. I'm sorry. That was—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>Marlene</speaker><content> No, it's okay. Girl likes to know she's appreciated.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-9"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>Come here. So I think we should talk to Leading Lights about seminars and DVDs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-10"><speaker>Marlene</speaker><content>Are you sure? You were worried about the commitment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-11"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>Yeah, there's no point in being in business with them halfway. You okay with that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-12"><speaker>Marlene</speaker><content>It's good to finally have a decision.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-13"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Fedir is the brother she worries about the most. Ever since Luba passed.  Sorry. But this is the closest we could find to the cold, soulless offices of a government bureaucracy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>If you're not using your office, I will.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Does Dominika still communicate with her high school friends?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Uh, Vasyl, yes. Oksana, no. Not since she kissed Pavlo. 'Cause that bitch knew that Dominika liked him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Wrong.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>Oh, Oksana is a slut. Dead to me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>The right answer is the wrong answer. No husband would pay that much attention to his wife's friend dramas.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Haven't you been divorced three times?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>In-between those divorces, I was married, non-fraudulently, for 12 years total, which is 12 years longer than anyone in this room.  Move.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>So are you going for this team leader thing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Probably.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>You deserve it. You have way more experience than me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You're giving up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I wish. I still have a lot of med school debt, and my parents need help with their mortgage. So I could kinda use the money.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>As of an hour ago, I'm just seeing one of everything. Looks like you guys were right—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We'll be right back.  "I could use the money"? You want to game me, you gotta do better than that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Chase—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>You want to be a leader, you have to know how to manipulate. You can't just spill—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-10"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I think the whites of his eyes were yellow.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-11"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>Everything okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-12"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Jaundice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-13"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>There's something wrong with your liver.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Liver function tests confirm his enzymes are totally out of whack.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>So much for myasthenia gravis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Can we hurry this up? I have a government to defraud at noon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>If you need to leave, you should. I'm fairly confident our patient's got sarcoidosis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Wow, you said that with so much authority. Did anyone else get chills?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Just until I realized our patient has no sign of parenchymal lung abnormalities, which makes sarcoidosis a long shot. And bookkeeping isn't gonna get you any farther than boobs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Though in fairness, the boobs were really, really helping.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I still think it's myasthenia gravis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Did you miss the recap? We treated for that. The liver tanked.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>But his vision got better.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-11"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Liver problems could be a sign of celiac. He's been back on gluten since he's been in the hospital. Yesterday he had a burger.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-12"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>That would've kicked the celiac into gear, causing the liver problems.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-13"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>So your theory is that he has two unrelated diseases. And he's already got low testosterone. I seem to remember something about House hating coincidences.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's true.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-15"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I think it's Lyme disease. One single disease named "Lyme."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-16"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Without a rash.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-17"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>10% of cases present without a rash.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Lyme disease it is. Start the patient on antibiotics. Now I have to get home before my fake wife gets real annoyed.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Something bothering you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>I asked the nurse for an extra pillow. That was half an hour ago.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Sorry. Things can get pretty hectic.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>It was a pillow. I mean, how hard can a pil — Listen to me. I'm being a jerk.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Testosterone can give you a shorter temper even when you're not sick. You noticed and adjusted. That's a good thing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>Marlene</speaker><content> Hey. Just got a call from our lawyer. You changed our counter to leading lights?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>You deserve proper billing and a salary bump in the second term.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>Marlene</speaker><content>We talked about this. We decided it wasn't worth potentially blowing the deal.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content> It'll be fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>Marlene</speaker><content>I've got to get some work done.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>These are such pretty flowers you buy for me every Friday, from Japanese florist, on corner of Edison and Conway.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Just one more thing.  With this ring, I thee wedded. You left it here when you skipped town with your boyfriend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>You kept the rings.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Actually, I tried to trade them to a hooker for unspecified favors, but it turns out she doesn't accept zinc.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>Like modern fairytale.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>Weinmann</speaker><content>Dr. and Mrs. Gregory House?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>Weinmann</speaker><content>Nate Weinmann. U.S. Immigration.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Welcome to our home.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Give him time. When I was 14, there was a girl I wanted to impress, so I jumped off the roof of her house. Broke my ankle. Joe's basically going through puberty. It'll take him a while to adjust.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>Marlene</speaker><content>I-I tracked down a video from one of Joe's business coaching seminars from before I knew him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content> I'm hearing a lot about the value of compromise. We don't live on Sesame Street. We live in the real world, the business world. If you're not a winner, you're a loser. If you aren't comfortable with that, go open a pottery studio.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>Marlene</speaker><content>I never would have gone out with the guy in this video.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>Weinmann</speaker><content>Uh, do you remember the last time she visited Vasyl?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Uh, let me see, that would be… August? No. No, July. 'Cause I remember it was right after our half-anniversary, and I forgot to put a gift in her suitcase. And… I've never heard the end of that one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>House specialty. I made up this pun.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>Weinmann</speaker><content> Is it — Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>Mm-hmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Honey, why do you do this to me? You know I'm watching my weight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>Then maybe you'll stop eating cheese in front of open fridge in middle of the night.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>Weinmann</speaker><content>This is delicious.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-10"><speaker>Weinmann</speaker><content>So everything looks good in here. I'm just gonna step out and get a corroborating interview from one of the neighbors.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-11"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>Neighbors? It's-it's middle of the day. I-I-I think everybody's at work.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-12"><speaker>Weinmann</speaker><content>Yeah, then they're at work. I just got a form to check off, and you will be on your way to permanent status.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-13"><speaker>Weinmann</speaker><content>'Scuse me, sir. Do you have a minute?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>How can I help you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>Weinmann</speaker><content>Do you know Dr. and Mrs. House?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Of course, they've been my neighbors about two years, now. Lovely couple. I see them almost every night. They seem always to be together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-4"><speaker>Weinman</speaker><content>Great, well, thanks for your help.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Cheerio.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-6"><speaker>Hastings</speaker><content>Hey, what're you doing? That's my door.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> Handing out menus for a new Chinese place.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-8"><speaker>Hastings</speaker><content>You're that guy that plays noisy video games with House on Saturday nights.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>There's a simple explanation.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-10"><speaker>Weinmann</speaker><content> Be at my office tomorrow at 10.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>The patient's shown zero improvement.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Because he's only been on the antibiotics overnight.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Or because he doesn't have Lyme disease. Where are you?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>Ayres</speaker><content> House. Hang up.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I still think it's myasthenia gravis plus celiac. His change in diet has to be significant.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>We just need to do an intestinal biopsy to confirm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>With his low platelet count, a biopsy puts him at risk for an abdominal bleed, which puts him at risk of death.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>Ayres</speaker><content>Either you're done, or you're walking in there without a lawyer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I know, it sounds like a phone, but it's a timer to remind me to pee before our meeting.  Hello, old chap.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You need to save yourself. I was up last night trying to find another angle, but I can't. Tell immigration you were in love with Dominika, but your marriage fell apart, and that's why you haven't been living together.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>She'll be deported, permanently.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>House, I know you like Dominika, you have fun with her, but you got caught. There's no getting out of this. The best you could hope for is that you don't go back to jail.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Tell my team to-to skip the biopsy and give the antibiotics more time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>Ayres</speaker><content>They're ready for us.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>I drew a line in the sand, and I won. We should be celebrating.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content> Do you need a few minutes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>I’d rather keep getting better.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>Marlene</speaker><content>That's just it. You won. You made a demand that could've blown up the deal, and you never even asked me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>Deal didn't blow up. They caved.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-6"><speaker>Marlene</speaker><content>Joe, you say it in your seminars. Process matters just as much as results.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-7"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>Are you seriously busting my chops because I made one little move without you? How 'bout stepping aside and letting me be the man in this relationship for a change?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-8"><speaker>Marlene</speaker><content>I really can't talk to you right now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-9"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>I don't know why I said that. Just — I got so angry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-10"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Hopefully after this dose, you'll start to feel better, and we can get you home.  But I'd like to do one more test.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>Ayres</speaker><content>The testimony of one angry, nearsighted neighbor shouldn't outweigh all other evidence. Photos, utility bills—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>Weinmann</speaker><content>Yes, because your clients would never fake anything.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>Ayres</speaker><content>Uh, we acknowledge the neighbor thing was a mistake, but that doesn't mean that all of the other documentation should just be thrown out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>Weinman</speaker><content>Look, look, you know, I get that it's your job to try to act like there's a case here, but shut up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>Ayres</speaker><content> Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>Weinmann</speaker><content>USCIS will be denying Miss Petrova's green card application. You'll be referred to immigration court for deportation proceedings, and we're gonna inform your parole officer about evidence of fraud. So, unless anybody has anything else to add…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-7"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content> Please, I am begging, do not send him back to jail. Maybe we have not lived together all these—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-8"><speaker>Weinmann</speaker><content>Mrs. House, I have to advise you not to continue.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-9"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content>This man and I, did we marry for love? No. But this past week, we have a lot of fun. Working really hard to fool the U.S. government, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-10"><speaker>Ayres</speaker><content> Don't answer that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Way ahead of you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-12"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content> It was fake, but… it felt real. Maybe because it become real. This man — my husband — I want to stay with him, but if I cannot, please send me away, and let him be free. I love him.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-13"><speaker>Weinmann</speaker><content>I didn't buy a word you said. But a judge might.  I'm gonna let you stay. But for the next six months, I'm gonna hold onto this file, and our investigators are gonna show up unannounced at 6:00 a.m., 11:00 at night, and they better find the two of you sitting on the couch, watching NCIS, eating ice cream from the same spoon. Or both of you will be sent to places far less pleasant than New Jersey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content> What you just said in there…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-15"><speaker>Dominika</speaker><content> Don't worry. I'm much too smart to be falling in love with you. I will be needing extra shelf in bathroom.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Abdominal biopsy showed flattened villi. Looks like you were right about celiac.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You do remember Chase got stabbed doing a test House didn't order?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Good comparison, since both patients were tweaked on steroids.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You only did this to score points over Chase and Park.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-5"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>We were right. I proved it, and the patient didn't bleed out. Why are you being a jerk about this? Let's go see if House is back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Patient's having trouble breathing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-7"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>So much for celiac.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>His breathing is stabilized, but his lung function is at 60%, and his liver is tanking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>And he has major symptoms of celiac without actually having celiac.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Could be Whipple's.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Doesn't explain the incontinence. Intestinal lymphoma?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Doesn't explain the double vision.  Any time you want to jump in.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Is dance aerobics even a thing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-7"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>I hear it's good for the butt. What about a parasitic infection? Strongyloides is known to damage the small intestine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>In this country, he's about as likely to get that as win Powerball.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Someone does win Powerball. Every week. The patient went to Puerto Rico a few months ago. One of the few places in the U.S. you could pick up strongyloides.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Treatment is ivermectin. We give that to someone with liver problems, he could have seizures, or worse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Do it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="34"><utterance uid="34-1"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>I'm hearing a lot about the value of compromise. But we don't live on Sesame Street, we live in the real—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I was wondering if maybe we overlooked a symptom, or something.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Makes perfect sense. If you're the patient, and "pantywaist" is the symptom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Adams and I both thought the patient could have celiac, but only she was willing to go out on a limb and run the test. I gave up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Now you're in here watching a motivational speech. Even your attempt to get your balls back lacks balls.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-6"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>— world, the business world. If you're not a winner, you're a loser.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>His voice — it's lower than it is now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If only there was a good reason for a professional speaker to be hoarse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-9"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>Go open a pottery studio.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Good point. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's not a good point. It's a decent point. You're doing it again. You have any other videos? Other seminars?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-12"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>A couple.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-13"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>When you see a weakness, that's a time for strength.  A lot of people say, "Oh, I feel bad about it. The other guy made a mistake."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You bailed too early. Now I get all the credit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-15"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>That kind of thinking is what makes you have a bad day.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="35"><utterance uid="35-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Chronic hoarseness is a symptom of a condition called silent thyroiditis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-2"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>But I'm not hoarse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Exactly. But you were three years ago. Silent thyroiditis comes and goes. And it, in turn, is a symptom of polyglandular autoimmune syndrome type 3, which makes this a really bad idea.  PAS 3 attacks the body's own endocrine system, moving from gland to gland.  It started in the thyroid, and probably helped along by your low testosterone, moved on to the gut.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Where it caused celiac disease, or it would've if you weren't on a gluten-free diet. I was right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>This is incredibly relevant. Eventually, PAS 3 attacked your thymus gland. You developed myasthenia gravis, which landed you in here, and you started eating gluten, which only made things worse.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-6"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>So am I gonna be okay?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>We'll treat the various conditions with high-dose steroids. Assuming they respond, you should be fine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-8"><speaker>Marlene</speaker><content>And the testosterone?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Kicked in the nuts is kicked in the nuts.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="36"><utterance uid="36-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Over the past week, you've all had good moments and bad. No one candidate has prevailed. And so now, we embark upon a contest of medical strength, stamina, and skill.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Can we just get this over with?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>If the competitor representing Australia would like to take a point deduction, he should, by all means, continue yapping.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Your glee is on the verge of making this not worth it for any of us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Can I at least light the torch?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-6"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Hurry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="36-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I declare open the games of the number one, number two competition. Je declare ouvert—  All right. Ready, set, suture!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="37"><utterance uid="37-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>T time.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-2"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>What happens if I don't take it? Or at least go to a much lower dose?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Are you having side effects?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-4"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>No, I feel great. Faster, clearer. More like myself. But my marriage and my career, they're both built on me being somebody else.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Low testosterone can cause depression and problems sleeping. It's also been linked to conditions such as osteoporosis and diabetes. It'll make your life harder and more dangerous on top of all the meds you'll be taking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="37-6"><speaker>Joe</speaker><content>I'll take that risk. I'm a better man without it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="38"><utterance uid="38-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Well, this certainly has brought more structure to the department.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Really, I'm just excited for the wheelchair race. You were smart not to enter. Never in, never lose. And since you no longer have stones.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I'll split the 50 a week with you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="38-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Deal.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="39"><utterance uid="39-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Honey, I'm home!</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>