<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<script>
<scene id="1"><utterance uid="1-1"><speaker>Player</speaker><content>Over here, over here!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-2"><speaker>Player</speaker><content>Clear him, clear him!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-3"><speaker>Fan</speaker><content>Hey, what was that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-4"><speaker>Fans</speaker><content>Hatchet, Hatchet, Hatchet!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-5"><speaker>Bobby</speaker><content>Nice to meet the pride of Trois-Rivieres. I still got your Wings rookie card.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-6"><speaker>Szabo</speaker><content>So what's that worth?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-7"><speaker>Bobby</speaker><content>It's a collector's item. They don't make them like you anymore.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-8"><speaker>Szabo</speaker><content>So do you wanna go?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-9"><speaker>Bobby</speaker><content> Square up. Good luck.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-10"><speaker>Linesman</speaker><content>He didn't get a hand on you? You're going to be a force in the show.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-11"><speaker>Toros Fan</speaker><content>Whoo!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-12"><speaker>Spartans Fan</speaker><content>Boo!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-13"><speaker>Toros Fan</speaker><content>Come on, Toros!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="1-14"><speaker>Linesman</speaker><content>Get a trainer over here!</content></utterance>
</scene>

<scene id="2"><utterance uid="2-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Capacity crowd is on its feet. Five seconds on the clock. Ah. How is it possible for one man to be blessed with so much skill? Ahhh. </content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I had one just like this, except it was Bruins and the Habs. Where did you get it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Birthday present for someone in pediatric oncology. 22-year-old enforcer with hemoptysis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>He's a hockey player?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No, he's a superhero.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>He's coughing up blood because he probably broke a rib and punctured a lung while breaking someone else's rib and puncturing their lung in the name of sport.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Nice conclusion to which the E.R. already jumped 18 hours ago.  Short man equals bullied child.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I was average height as a kid and never bullied.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-9"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Until now. X-ray ruled out traumatic sequelae, overt TB, and lung cancer.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-10"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Sarcoidosis. Nodules could be too small to show up on an X-ray. Fighting's the best part of hockey. Without it, you've got the Ice Capades.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-11"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Fighting has nothing to do with hockey. It's like the cheerleaders at a basketball game.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-12"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Cheerleading's the best part of basketball. Without it you've got… basketball.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-13"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>He's a duck hunter. He could've contracted psittacosis from exposure to fowl.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-14"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>He had three teeth knocked out two weeks ago. Infection could've led to oral bleeding.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-15"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Not without continuing dental pain.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-16"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Then he took an elbow to the gut, which caused an esophageal tear.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="2-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Chase, CT the patient. Check for sarcoid.  Adams, sputum cultures and serologies for psittacosis. Taub… I'd tell you why I think your theory is not just wrong but ill-conceived, but it's more fun to prove it by having you check the stool for blood. And while we wait for the stool fairy, I'm a man down, so you want to drop your pants and hit the ice.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="3"><utterance uid="3-1"><speaker>Bobby</speaker><content>The faster you guys can do this, the better. The NHL's been sniffing around, and being in the hospital is not really helping my marketability.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>You have to be pretty good to get called up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-3"><speaker>Bobby</speaker><content>Yeah, leading the league in penalty minutes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>And visits to the E.R., not counting the ones you've caused.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-5"><speaker>Bobby</speaker><content>Not a hockey fan, I gather?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I am. That's the point. Fighting cheapens a great sport.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-7"><speaker>Bobby</speaker><content>Oh, come on, that's like saying passing cheapens football. It's part of the game. I don't cause injuries.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>They're self-inflicted?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="3-9"><speaker>Bobby</speaker><content>No, I prevent them. I take the hit so the smaller guys don't have to. I thought you'd appreciate that.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="4"><utterance uid="4-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Neighbor's baby again?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I could hear it through earplugs, two pillows, and three sleeping pills.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Hmm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> What is wrong with you?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I just said, "hmm."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You're trying to figure out some deeper significance to my having a couple of crappy nights.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Which one of us is analyzing the word "hmm" here?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> Fine. Sorry.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Apology accepted. However…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Mm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It's not the crying that's keeping you awake. The sound of a needy child is stirring your paternal juices.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-12"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>The sound of a needy child at 112 decibels has stirred my inner murderer. Don't mess with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Explain the stains on your shirt. You're lactating. The fact that you're the only fruit on your family tree is getting to you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-14"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>It's not a big deal. So I'll probably never be a dad. It's–it sucks. I'll lose a little sleep, but—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You're not supposed to feel bad when you dodge a bullet. It's like you got survivor's guilt.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-16"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>There are actually things in this world that give life even more meaning than soap operas and monster trucks. And we happen to be missing out on at least one of them.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Remember the falconer?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-18"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Beth?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You dated two falconers? Yes, Beth. The night the two of you split up, you came around to my place, wallowing in self-pity and tequila. You passed out. She called that night, asked me to give you a message. She said she was pregnant… Which, God and Planned Parenthood willing, means you are the father of an 11-year-old.  I told you the next morning… hypothetically. I asked you how you'd feel if Beth had gotten pregnant, and you said, and I quote, "It would be the worst mistake of my life."</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-20"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>And… scene. Two performances Sunday, dark Mondays?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="4-21"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Just as well.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="5"><utterance uid="5-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I want to kill my mother. My Popo's on her own, and my mother always needs me to take care of her.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Well, you could kill Popo instead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I have to take her shopping, to her friends, to Atlantic City. I love her, but every night, every weekend…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>And only if there was some solution, someplace where you could live… that's not there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>My mom would freak. It would be the ultimate sign of disrespect.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Okay. Then stay. And maybe you consider not bitching about it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-7"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Not everyone's lucky enough to have your independence.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-8"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Don't worry. When you lose your family, you'll have it too.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content> He doesn't have sarcoid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-10"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Look at that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-11"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>That's his spleen.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="5-12"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I know. But he's gotten it supersized.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="6"><utterance uid="6-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Deep vein thrombosis caused by any one of his many injuries or surgeries.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Leukemia's a better fit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>We have a guy who is punishing his body on a daily basis. Don't you think that's a more likely cause than cancer?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-4"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>No, because she doesn't have an agenda.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Well, that was incredibly unprofessional. Well, it was really Taub's fault.  If you're not prepared to slam her into the boards, she's got no reason not to go after you. Might I suggest pulling her jersey over her head first?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="6-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We should get an ultrasound for DVT and WBC for leukemia.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="7"><utterance uid="7-1"><speaker>Bobby</speaker><content>You think I could have cancer?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>More likely, it's just a DVT.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="7-3"><speaker>Bobby</speaker><content>This is my agent. I gotta get this, man. Give me some good news, Kenny. I thought you said any day. Okay. All right.  I gotta go.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="8"><utterance uid="8-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I called Beth. I have an 11-year-old son.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="9"><utterance uid="9-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Liver failure could alter hormone levels, cause abnormal breast development.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Alcoholism. We should search his home and locker room.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Note that the person who wants to search the home didn't sleep in one last night. You have the imprint of a seatbelt buckle in your cheek.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I got in a fight with my mother.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>She hit you with a seatbelt?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Could be hemochromatosis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-7"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Explains the liver and the spleen, but hemoptysis is a stretch. What about leptospirosis?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>That's a good fit, if you ignore the fact that he's a pro athlete who looks like the Incredible Hulk, which means he's gotta be on steroids, which is a better fit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>All we really know for sure is it was his evil job that caused the problems.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Yes, I don't like him. Doesn't mean my judgment's affected.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Maybe. Let's take a look at the instant replay.  This is the hit that precipitated Booby Orr's fight. Dirty or clean?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-12"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>The hit was clean.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-13"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Really? The guy released the puck at least a second before the hit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-14"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>We have a difference of opinion. That's all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="9-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Absolutely. Maybe she's as biased as you. Or maybe the entire league is.  After review, the league disciplinary commissioner ruled the hit illegal and dangerous and suspended the player for three games. Adams and Taub, run antibody titers for lepto. Chase and Park, check out the home, the locker room for booze, steroids, and Taub's objectivity.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="10"><utterance uid="10-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>At least you're free. Going to get your own place?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>If I can find a place I can afford, so… no.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>If you want, you can crash at my place in the spare bedroom.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>That might be kind of weird.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I live in an apartment, not a dungeon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-6"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>It's just two single people, opposite sex. I—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Your bedroom door has a lock on the inside.  Hey, if you prefer your car, be my guest.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="10-8"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Scrip for glanciclovir. If his neighbor has mono, could mean he has mono. If he has mono, explains his spleen and hemoptysis. And it's caused by Epstein-Barr virus, which explains his liver. And my moonroof leaks. Thank you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="11"><utterance uid="11-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Why don't we just assume that you're not the dad?  Either you're the dad, or she cheated on you with your dad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Oh! Sand art. I used to love this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He's bitter, not mentally handicapped. Who knows what Beth told him about you? At worst, you're a rapist. At best, you're a rapist.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Maybe she said I was a dead war hero.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Raised by a lunatic mother and abandoned by his father. Oh, I know! Squirrel handcuffs. You think he's gotten any of those?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>If you really wanted me to do nothing with this information, then why did you give it to me?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Because you were pining for a kid, and you deserved to know that you already had one. But your parental cravings are more theoretical than applied. You want vicarious immortality more than you want a lifelong burden.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You're assuming he's going to be a nightmare. What if he's a good kid?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He's a kid. Best you can hope for is he's a nightmare.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="11-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>House, I'm not naive. I realize that this thing could go very badly, but the point is my son wants to meet me. And I want to meet him.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="12"><utterance uid="12-1"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Popo, I presume.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Hey, uh, I let myself in. Um, this is—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-3"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We've met.  I thought the whole point of this was to get away from Popo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-4"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>My dad's getting a cyst removed, and my mother had to take him to the clinic. Don't worry. She'll be gone in an hour.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-5"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I'm not worried, because it's not my issue.  She seems awfully quiet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="12-6"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>You haven't seen her drunk.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="13"><utterance uid="13-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Bobby?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="14"><utterance uid="14-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I found him crying in the fetal position.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-2"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>It's not a new symptom. He's crying because his liver failure threw his hormones out of whack.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Aside from the crying, he's actually recovering nicely.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Aside from the guy in the book depository, the Kennedys had a lovely trip to Dallas. Repetitive blows to the head can cause chronic traumatic encephalopathy, symptoms of which are aggressive behavior and depression.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So your theory is that his aggressive behavior caused his aggressive behavior. He's not depressed. He's just bummed because he knows he's a talentless moron who's only one lost fight away from being a barista. I understand that can get to a guy after a while.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>If he quits being an enforcer, it could save his life.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You don't want to save his life.  You want to kill his career.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-8"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I moved into Chase's apartment.  He knows. He was staring at our matching cups. I told you we should split up. We're not having sex. With each other…</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yet.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-10"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-11"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content> Yes?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-12"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I just mean no one knows the future right now, so we don't really know… The only conclusive test for CTE is post-mortem.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-13"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>But an MRI of his brain could reveal white matter disintegrity, which is the effect of CTE.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Why? Are you trying to sleep with her? 'Cause the simpler technique is just to ask.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-15"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>I was doing something nice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-16"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Mm, no. Th— mm. No, that doesn't fit.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-17"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>He's only had three concussions since he was ten. It's not enough to cause CTE.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-18"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Three reported concussions. These guys are taught in high school how to dupe the tests.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-19"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Guilt?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-20"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>This is really insulting.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-21"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>It's not guilt. Park is a friend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="14-22"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So it's guilt. Chase convinced you to leave mommy, and now he feels responsible. No MRI. Do a psych eval. If he doesn't start weeping again, send him home.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="15"><utterance uid="15-1"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>Dr. Wilson?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Duncan. Uh, James.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-3"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>Uh, n-n-nice to meet you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>It's nice to meet you. Um… How are you doing?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-5"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>Good.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Good. I got you this.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-7"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>Oh. Thank you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Go ahead.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-9"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>Okay.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>It's got three games built in, but you can download more from the website.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-11"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>Yeah, I know.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-12"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You already have one.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-13"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>I can always use a backup.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-14"><speaker>Waitress</speaker><content>Hi, can I start you with something to drink?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-15"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>Just water, please.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="15-16"><speaker>Waitress</speaker><content>You got a Gamedeck? Way to go, Dad.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="16"><utterance uid="16-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>According to your psych eval, the only thing happier than you is Disneyland.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-2"><speaker>Bobby</speaker><content>I'm sorry you had to see me like that last night. I'm just upset about being in the hospital and… I'm on some weird meds, but they must be working, because I'm feeling a lot better now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Depression could be the symptom of a serious illness. CTE.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-4"><speaker>Bobby</speaker><content>Yeah, my aunt sends me every article she can find on it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>And you know it could kill you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-6"><speaker>Bobby</speaker><content>In the long run, like a lot of things.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You might be right. And an MRI could confirm that.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="16-8"><speaker>Bobby</speaker><content>I have enough evidence of head trauma in my file already, so…</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="17"><utterance uid="17-1"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>My mom said you had trouble maintaining relationships with normal people. She also said you were a nice guy. I always figured she was lying 'cause she didn't want me to hate my deadbeat dad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I didn't know—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-3"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>I-I know… now.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You're a bright kid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-5"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>Thanks to you. Thanks to my mom, I'm also a big, soft-hearted wuss.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> I think you may have gotten that from both of us.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-7"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>Uh, I gotta go, but it was really nice meeting you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>It was nice meeting you, Duncan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-9"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>Uh, you want to hang out again?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> Absolutely.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-11"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>Tonight?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-12"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Tonight? Well, I-I-there's, um…  That would be great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="17-13"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>Okay. I'll text you.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="18"><utterance uid="18-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Thank you. How did you talk him into it?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>He agreed once I promised him anonymity.  Mr. and Mrs. Doe liked the name John apparently. Unfortunately we just wasted his time and proved House right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Nothing?  What about that?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>That's an artifact.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>That's a density. I know you think I'm convincing myself, but this brain has been hammered for years, meaning evidence may be subtle, but it's there.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content> Meaning you see what you want to see.  Unless, of course, Chase is an idiot, and I do have brain damage.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Patient's stroking out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="18-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Chase? Can you get me out of— Ohh… Hello?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="19"><utterance uid="19-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The good news is, it's isolated ophthalmoplegia, which means you didn't have a stroke.  Bad news is, Taub was right. You're still sick.  I said "right," not "competent." Bursts your CTE bubble. You're going to need a whole new theory to keep Uncle Jesse and his Olsen twins on the bench.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Can we discuss my incompetence somewhere else?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="19-3"><speaker>Bobby</speaker><content>Dr. House. Could I talk to you for a minute?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="20"><utterance uid="20-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Could be neurosyphilis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>He's only 22.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>And he's been on the road since he was 14.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So he was trash even before he was trash? You curious about what he wanted?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I assume he wanted me off the case, and you told him I was hit in the head as a child, and your mother made you promise to take care of me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He was doing what he always does — sticking up for the little guy. He told me to apologize to you, or he would… excrete down my throat. I'm paraphrasing.  So if he should ask, I was a gentleman, or I will excrete down your throat.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Microscopic polyangiitis fits.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>We should start plasmapheresis immediately.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>We need to run an ANCA panel to confirm first. Putting him on plasmapheresis could make him bleed out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>MPA can progress quickly. We may not have time before it reaches his lungs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="20-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I think you're right. Thus confirming my objectivity. Start the treatment.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="21"><utterance uid="21-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Miserable yet?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>He’s polite, well-adjusted and a straight-A student.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Which means he doesn't need you. So why don't you get out while the butterfly effect is still in the cocoon stage?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'm making him dinner.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You don't make an 11-year-old dinner. You give him a jar of peanut butter.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>It'll be fine. I could give this kid a quinoa salad, and he would eat it just to be nice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>'Cause he's a gutless placater, just like his dad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>He's nice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>This is a terrible idea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Because we like each other?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yes. 'Cause of the statement "we like each other." You've known him 25 minutes. All you know about him is that he'd lie about a quinoa salad, whatever the hell that is.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="21-12"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You're jealous of an 11-year-old because you are an 11-year-old.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="22"><utterance uid="22-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>So tell me about yourself. I mean, you're smart, you're nice, but what else?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-2"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>I don't know. I'm a kid.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Right.  What are you looking for?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-4"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>Nothing.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You want… peanut butter?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-6"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>Do you have prosciutto?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You like prosciutto?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-8"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>I'm weird.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>No, no. I-I like it too. I've got some in the fridge.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-10"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>How about goat cheese?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-11"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> I love goat cheese.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="22-12"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I think that was the best pizza I ever had.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="23"><utterance uid="23-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I think that was the best pizza I ever had.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-2"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>It was the hint of Dijon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Do you have any aunts or uncles or grandparents?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-4"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>My mom got into some stupid fight with my grandfather. They all kind of cut us off.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Hmmph.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-6"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>Are you talking to your parents?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Yes, and they're going to be very surprised and excited to meet you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-8"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>That's awesome.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-9"><speaker>GPS Voice</speaker><content>You have arrived at your destination.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Well—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-11"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>Thanks for the pizza.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-12"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Sure, sure. It was, uh— I mean, it was great to spend time with you and—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="23-13"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>I love you, Dad.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="24"><utterance uid="24-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Can't be easy doing what you do. I mean, do you love it? Is it fun? I had my own plastic surgery practice making lots of money, but I wasn't happy. It wasn't what I went to med school for.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="24-2"><speaker>Bobby</speaker><content> Every winter my dad would flood the backyard and made a rink. I was Lemieux. My little brother was Gretzky. I was good. I won the NDHA scoring title three years in a row. I kept getting bigger and stronger and better… ’til I didn't. My Juniors coach told me that, if I wanted to stay on the team, then I'd have to use my size. Every game, I got less and less ice time until it was all fighting and no hockey. I, uh…  There's something going on with my arms. I can't feel them. I— Doctor, I can't feel my arms.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="25"><utterance uid="25-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Patient's arms are now paralyzed. ANCA panel was negative. It's not MPA.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-2"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Lyme disease could cause paralysis. If he was hunting, he'd be exposed to ticks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>No target rash or cardiac involvement.  Roomies with benefits keeping you up?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Cribbage. I played with Park's Popo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Is that two separate events?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Grandmother. ALS could explain the symptoms.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-7"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Sensory involvement rules out ALS.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Okay, yeah. Now this is interesting. We'll get back to the patient in a second. Your issue is the same as Wilson's, except… you're haunted by the pitter-patter of tiny skanks. You don't feel guilty about getting Park thrown out of her home. You feel guilty about all the women that you've screwed over. My mother needs 1,000 bucks for snow tires.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-9"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Park's a friend. Popo's fun.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Paralysis has gone from his face to his arms, meaning it's descending, which is the hallmark of botulism.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>So it was something he ate. How innocuous. You've overcome your bias by reversing it. The only problem is that being in love with a patient is just as judgmental as being in hate. We didn't find any contaminated—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-12"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>No contaminated food. I'm not an idiot. But what if it's not from ingesting but from injecting? He was treated for intractable muscle spasms by the team's trainers. Sometimes they use botox.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-13"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>We need to start the antitoxin—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-14"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>The antitoxin could cause anaphylaxis. We need to test first to confirm.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>As if to prove my point, last time you said there wasn't enough time to test prior to a more dangerous treatment.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-16"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>It's a different situation, different symptom, different diagnosis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="25-17"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Different emotion. Give him the antitoxin.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="26"><utterance uid="26-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Anything?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>No adverse effects.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>Chase let me move in with him to get away from my grandmother. Then he practically let my grandmother move in with the both of us. He's being way more than nice.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Then which answer is it? Chase feels guilty for pushing you to move out?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>He didn't push me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Guilt about skanks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-7"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>He loves skanks.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>It's not the other option.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-9"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>There are people that like me. People even want to sleep with me. Some of them are even good-looking.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>That good-looking?  Did you see that?  You're feeling something?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="26-11"><speaker>Bobby</speaker><content> Yeah.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="27"><utterance uid="27-1"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I could give you crap for making me wait 11 years, but instead I'm going to thank you for not making me wait another 11.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Every little girl wants a pony till they have to clean up after it.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-3"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You think I'm going to quit on this? On an 11-year-old?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>The only relationship you haven't quit on has been with me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-5"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Hmm. A needy, truculent narcissist. I think it's been perfect training for parenthood.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content> That's not even close. This is the rest of your life. You screw this up, you don't get to run away. You get to ruin both your lives. This is a bigger responsibility than any you've ever taken on and screwed up.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="27-7"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I know. That's why I'm so excited about it.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="28"><utterance uid="28-1"><speaker>Bobby</speaker><content>You're really happier doing this than looking at boobs all day?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Luckily I get patients like you every now and again who let me reexperience the joy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-3"><speaker>Bobby</speaker><content>You know, the best part of my day is when I'm sitting in that penalty box after I beat someone up. That's the only time I know I'm safe. Think Lemieux ever felt that way? I'm not going back.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>To hockey?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-5"><speaker>Bobby</speaker><content>To enforcing… whatever that costs.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="28-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Good for you.  Ooh! First goal for the pocket rocket. Bobby?  We need a team in here!</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="29"><utterance uid="29-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>He's completely paralyzed, and he tested negative for botulism.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I am now accepting long shots.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-3"><speaker>Adams</speaker><content>Polio. Some kids were never vaccinated.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Unless they played sports all their lives and had two physicals a year.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>How about MLD?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-6"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>That's a bad fit. I say that not because there's no treatment for MLD but because it's a bad fit. His cognitive abilities are unaffected.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-7"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>Prion disease could explain the waxing and waning symptoms.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-8"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>The test for Prions is a brain biopsy. Given his history, there's got to be brain swelling. We can't risk drilling into his skull.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Pretty sure we can.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-10"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>We also could keep talking until we can find an answer we all can agree on.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>All of us? Those who love him, those who hate him, those who don't give a crap about him or you—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-12"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Or I could just discuss it on my own with Foreman.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He's not your friend.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-14"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I get it. He's a patient. I'm not—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="29-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>He never had your back. He didn't insist that I apologize to you. He asked me to take you off the case.  Biopsy his brain.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="30"><utterance uid="30-1"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>Hey, Dad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-3"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>Sorry I'm late. Got in a fight with my mom. She's such a tool.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I'm sure she means well.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-5"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>She wants to open a reserve in Costa Rica for rescued birds of prey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>But how serious is she? From my recollection, she used to talk about doing a lot—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-7"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>Yeah, but she bought plane tickets for Monday.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> Well, Costa Rica is beautiful. And the schools are supposed to be great.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-9"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>Oh, I'm not going. It's her stupid dream, not mine.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Then what will you do?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-11"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>Uh… I-I thought maybe I could, uh… Maybe I could stay with you? Uh, y-your place is only 3 miles away from my school. I could bus it every day.  And I do my own laundry. I keep my room tidy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-12"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Duncan, th-this-this is very sudden.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-13"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>I know. I'm sorry.  Please don't send me to the jungle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="30-14"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>If it's okay with your mother, it's okay with me.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="31"><utterance uid="31-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Take me off the case. I've obviously completely lost my objectivity. I'm not helping, I'm not even neutral.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Agreed. So why shouldn't I take you off all my cases?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-3"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Because you were right. I hate bullies.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-4"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You work for me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-5"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You're not a bully.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-6"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Pretty sure I am, dickwad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-7"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I've known a lot of bullies — people who didn't like me because I'm short, people who didn't like me because I'm Jewish—</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-8"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Yeah, I get it. There's a long list of reasons not to like you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-9"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>You relentlessly mock, but it's not for self-aggrandizement. It's because ideas are bigger than feelings. At least that's what I choose to believe. I also thought you had the side effect of desensitizing me.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-10"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You little Hebe. Here's some ideas for you. You screwed up. You kept on screwing up. Everything you said is true, except… it doesn't mean you walk away. You just learn to trust nothing. Everything you think you feel, everything you think you know. Question every call, play through every whistle.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-11"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>I just had a light bulb. Maybe.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="31-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You can trust light bulbs.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="32"><utterance uid="32-1"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>Stop. It's not prions. Epstein-Barr gave him mono. It also gave him Miller Fisher syndrome. The plasmapheresis played through the whistle. We gave it to him for MPA, but when he got worse, we took him off. When he got better, we thought it was the antitoxin. But it was actually the plasmapheresis still working. We had the right treatment, just the wrong diagnosis.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="32-2"><speaker>House</speaker><content>It was my metaphor that solved the case. Put him back on plasmapheresis. He'll be fine. Nice save. Didn't quite make up for being a sieve the rest of the game.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="33"><utterance uid="33-1"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Ex-girlfriend's baby again?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-2"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>His mother is moving to Costa Rica. He asked if he could move in with me.  And I said yes.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-3"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, it's only six or seven years. Unless he can't get into college, in which case, it's more a matter of your life expectancy.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-4"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I said yes, knowing I'm not remotely ready for that, knowing he's not ready to be separated from his mother. This isn't the act of a mature, rational adult. I-I can't do this, House. You were right.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-5"><speaker>House</speaker><content>I have an idea… that can make this entire problem go away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-6"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Yes, I really want to hear your clever late-term abortion joke. You were right about everything. This is life. It's real. It doesn't just go away.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-7"><speaker>House</speaker><content>None of that is true.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-8"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>Hey.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-9"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Duncan.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-10"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>Actually… Wendel.  One "l." If you're going to get pissy, remember, it was House's idea.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-11"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>You're an actor?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-12"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content> Five commercials and a recurring on Days of Our Lives.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-13"><speaker>House</speaker><content>You were regretting not having kids, so I gave you one… thereby rendering you regret-free. It's a priceless gift.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-14"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>Get out.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-15"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Well, it's not priceless 'cause he charges SAG minimum.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-16"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content> Get out!</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-17"><speaker>Duncan</speaker><content>Chillax, Dad.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="33-18"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Can you do an Australian accent?</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="34"><utterance uid="34-1"><speaker>Bobby</speaker><content>I just got the call. Three-year deal. $2.1 million.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-2"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>What about the flooded backyard and pretending to be Lemieux?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-3"><speaker>Bobby</speaker><content>That's why I took it. After all I did to get here, half a dream is better than nothing. Maybe my new coach will see what my Juniors coach didn't.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="34-4"><speaker>Taub</speaker><content>That'd be nice.</content></utterance>
</scene>
<scene id="35"><utterance uid="35-1"><speaker>Park</speaker><content> I'm not sleeping with you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-2"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>That's a shame.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-3"><speaker>Park</speaker><content> This is about Popo.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-4"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content>She's not sleeping with me either, right?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-5"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>You were jealous of me. My family.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-6"><speaker>Chase</speaker><content> Maybe you've got too much, and I've got too little.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-7"><speaker>Park</speaker><content>I might sleep with you after all.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-8"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>The woman that I called — that was really Beth?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-9"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Found her on Facebook.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-10"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>How much did she charge?</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-11"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Nothing. She's still pissed at you.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-12"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Pass the bacon.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-13"><speaker>Wilson</speaker><content>I thought you liked prosciutto.</content></utterance>
<utterance uid="35-14"><speaker>House</speaker><content>Nobody likes prosciutto.</content></utterance>
</scene>
</script>